<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="CHT_ENG_20101001.0000" medium="CHT" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2010-10-01 16:02:46 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Hey Andres, are you going to be around this weekend? I'd like to stop by sometime and get my lamp and stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2010-10-01 16:05:32 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Hey.  Ill be around for the most part.  So you're talking to me again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2010-10-01 16:09:50 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well, I'd like my stuff. I'm sorry if I am confusing at all. I just don't think it's beneficial to stay close to exes. Even if I am not talking to you, it doesn't mean I don't wish you well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2010-10-01 16:14:36 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>thats fine, I just dont think its beneficial to shut someone out of your life.  I would have agreed with you in the past, but I am starting to see how friendship w/ people Ive dated is a good thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2010-10-01 16:19:36 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Yes, well I was a bit jacked up from how our relationship panned out. And I am still working through some stuff on a much deeper level. It's nothing personal towards you per say, it just opened my eyes to some things about myself and how I operate. And I wouldn't be able to make the progress I have made without distancing myself.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2010-10-01 16:20:10 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>And I also wouldn't have learned these lessons without you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2010-10-01 16:22:50 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I agree that initially you have to do that, but in the long run I think it helps to acknowledge the people that have had an impact on your life.  I have learned a lot as well, and I feel as though it would be beneficial for us to communicate about the past and perhaps provide some clarity.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2010-10-01 16:23:52 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I also understand that you are seeing someone professionally, and that you have to follow their treatment, which doesnt necessarily include me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2010-10-01 16:36:22 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I'm not. I just went a few times. All I am trying to do is put myself first and look out for my best interests. And try not to hurt others in the process. What kind of clarity do you feel talking to me will provide? What can I say or do that may help you feel better?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2010-10-01 16:40:24 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I feel fine for the most part.  Or felt fine I should say.  Ive realized that I tend to push away from people who show a fondness for me.  To be honest, I never really thought our breakup would turn out the way that it did.  You wanted us to go to a councelor, which I opposed.  What I really needed was some time to clear my head and be single.  Now I am starting to see that it had more to do with MY relationship issues that OUR relationship issues and I want to figure it out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2010-10-01 16:42:58 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Im at the point where I feel like I may not be able to do it on my own.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2010-10-01 16:45:38 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Someone recently pointed out to me that I try to hard to prove to myself that I am independent.  So when I am in a situation where I rely on someone else, I get all weird.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2010-10-01 16:51:31 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>perhaps you are feeling guilty and think that seeing me and talking about it will somehow relieve your guilt?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2010-10-01 16:52:00 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>guilty?  about what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2010-10-01 16:53:20 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well you just said that you now see that Our relationship issues were actually YOUR relationship issues. Plus when you were pushing me away, you were kind of an asshole.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2010-10-01 16:55:13 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>A very strong cynical side of me is wondering right now if you only want to work things out with me in order for you to have my income to help you out. And that's my deep seeded issue. I don't trust men's intentions with me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2010-10-01 16:55:51 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Wow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2010-10-01 17:01:10 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Sorry, you see I have some work to do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2010-10-01 17:01:37 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I thought you knew me better than that.  I suppose I can understand seeing as how I was acting before, but honestly I dont see things in terms of financial gain.  Im doing fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2010-10-01 17:03:13 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Yes, well I guess I didn't realize how much money I was spending on us before. Now that I live alone and have a fairly expensive apartment rent and car insurance, I somehow still have alot more cash than when we were together. So it's on my mind.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2010-10-01 17:05:54 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I never made it an issue of money.  thats why I didnt bother to figure it out when you moved out.  I just thought that it wasnt important to figure out if someone owed someone.  I dont like to keep score with money in a relationship because in the end its going to equal out in my opinion.  I did appreciate you helping out while I was getting back on my feet, even thought I was kinda an ass about it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2010-10-01 17:09:54 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Alright now I am just thinking about past hurts and stuff so it's not really helping me. I can think of many good reasons why our relationship didn't work and I know it takes more than a few months for a person to make significant changes on their own.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2010-10-01 17:13:00 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Im not suggesting that we just jump back into anything, Im just saying that I think we would see more progress if we had more interaction.  I know I said initially that I would not see a councelor but now I realize that was just me trying to be independent and that it was actually a very reasonable way to deal with our issues</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2010-10-01 17:18:51 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Andres, I am not interested in getting back together or working with you and a counselor anymore.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2010-10-01 17:19:51 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>We had a 2 year run and I think that was enough for us to see if things could work out or not.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2010-10-01 17:22:00 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I guess Im not being all that clear.  While I wasnt necessarily ruling it out, getting back together was not my suggestion.  I am referring to being able to recognize that we did have an understanding of each other and using that to help each other out, that is all</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2010-10-01 17:22:33 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I've got to get back to work now so I can start my weekend.  Let me know if you want to come by and get your stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2010-10-01 17:29:31 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I am not the same person I was with you. I believe in God. I have a very strong faith. I meditate. I am creating artwork like I never have before in my entire life.I have made at least 10 new friends several of which are very close to me. I am really quite happy and on a better path. I don't think you would understand me the same way. I have let go of my goal of being married and having children and I have taken ownership of my own happiness. And I surround myself with people who treat me with respect only.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2010-10-01 17:30:01 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I'll text you if I plan on picking up my stuff.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

