<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="CHT_ENG_20100729.0000" medium="CHT" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2010-07-29 14:33:04 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>hey</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2010-07-29 14:38:14 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>hey</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2010-07-29 14:38:37 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I found your passport</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2010-07-29 14:39:01 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>really? huh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2010-07-29 14:39:07 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I thought I had that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2010-07-29 14:40:09 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>hopefully you don't have any trips planned</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2010-07-29 14:40:17 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>nah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2010-07-29 14:40:39 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I have your haight ashbury tshirt and some more of your mail</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2010-07-29 14:41:11 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>ok, I just sent you some stuff in the mail yesterday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2010-07-29 14:41:29 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>ah, a package</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2010-07-29 14:42:11 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>yep, license plate, phone charger cd, some random things that were in the car</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2010-07-29 14:42:15 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>so you movin this weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2010-07-29 14:42:22 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Aug. 7</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2010-07-29 14:42:47 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>oh, I just assumed youd move in the 1st</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2010-07-29 14:43:22 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>barry moves in this w/e.  He painted your old room.  White walls, with a red accent wall and black trm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2010-07-29 14:44:05 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>how's it look?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2010-07-29 14:44:56 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>strange, but it's alright.  Im having carpet installed tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2010-07-29 14:46:57 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>you know Andres, you told me that you were treating me with indifference because you were bored and looking for something more extraordinary. That still sits pretty heavy on me. I'm trying to move forward so that I can meet someone who will treat me nicely</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2010-07-29 14:48:11 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I thought I treated you nicely for the most part</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2010-07-29 14:49:03 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>something changed, and im not really sure why</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2010-07-29 14:50:14 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I felt like things just got to predictable.  I needed something exciting in my life, not ness. in a relationship way, just something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2010-07-29 14:51:13 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well, certainly turning around and walking away from me the last time we ever saw eachther, no goodbye, no well wishes, I felt pretty much the same way that made me fed up, unimportant, uncared for. And I kida felt sorry for you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2010-07-29 14:51:22 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>after a while, a relationship looses some of it's fire.  It's inevitable and it happens regarless</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2010-07-29 14:52:23 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I'm sorry about that.  It just felt easier</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2010-07-29 14:53:13 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I got the feeling that there was more you wanted to say, but I wasn't sure I wanted to hear it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2010-07-29 14:53:57 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well it was just that I wanted to say goodbye and wish you well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2010-07-29 14:54:12 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>You can't imagine how crazy the last few weeks have been</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2010-07-29 14:54:27 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>right, and I wasn't sure I wanted to hear that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2010-07-29 14:55:39 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>It's like the ben harper song, " stones from my enemies, these wounds will mend, but I cannot survive roses from my friends."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2010-07-29 14:57:19 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well I hope you can work that out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2010-07-29 14:58:36 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I am happy right now. Life is good. But I still can't help but think that I am missing out on something that was good for me.  Something secure.  I haven't had a lot of security in my life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2010-07-29 14:59:54 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>and I don't want to let go of that.  I believed that if we were apart for a while, we would either move on or we would find ourselves together again, perhaps with a newfound appreciation for each other.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2010-07-29 15:02:00 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>but as time goes on, I feel that the opportunity has passed and I have to face a new life and it's lonely. I enjoy the freedom, but I dont like the feeling of being alone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2010-07-29 15:04:43 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Nobody does. I felt pretty lonely in our relationship. I feel much better about myself now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2010-07-29 15:06:56 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>why did you feel lonely with me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2010-07-29 15:25:58 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>because I needed more attention and affection I can think of some examples:I would get in the car after not seeing you for a while and you wouldn't say hello or kiss me or anything, I would walk in the house or you would walk in the house and rarely look at me or say hello, I would initiate affection and you would not receive it, like example I can think of that you squirmed your way out of a hug,  I would share my feelings with you and you would call me dramatic and tell me that you were fine so I should be fine, I would do nice things for you and you thought I was upto something,  you spent more time on your computer rather then on me, you only wanted to do things that interested you, and you didn't believe in thank yous</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2010-07-29 15:27:41 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I think what you are missing here is that those things had less to do with you and more to do with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2010-07-29 15:28:07 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well they affected me obviously</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2010-07-29 15:28:18 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I was an unhappy person at that point in my life and I felt like all I could see was the bad in thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2010-07-29 15:28:24 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>of course</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2010-07-29 15:29:11 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>It's funny because I actually understand how you feel better now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2010-07-29 15:30:06 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>yes, well I'm quite a catch in my opinion. I know I'm not perfect. But I think I am a pretty interesting girl with alot to offer to a relationship</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2010-07-29 15:30:29 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>*I now have a better understanding of how you felt</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2010-07-29 15:30:55 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I have always agreed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2010-07-29 15:31:05 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>:-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2010-07-29 15:31:26 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>the problem was internally with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2010-07-29 15:31:46 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I am just never satisfied</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2010-07-29 15:32:52 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>It was hard for me to see that and not take it personally. But once you started getting more angry something inside of me just said hold on a minute here, I know I don't deserve this.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2010-07-29 15:33:01 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>perhaps there is something out there that will fill that void.  I feel my life is getting better, and has been getting better all along</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2010-07-29 15:33:31 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well that's good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2010-07-29 15:33:38 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>but a few years back I was really lost and I didnt know if I would be able to overcome it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2010-07-29 15:34:20 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well, I'm pretty sure you were alot more inlove with that Kari chick, because she needed you more.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2010-07-29 15:34:27 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>then I met you and I was glad, but still struggled to get past some of those things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2010-07-29 15:35:16 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I felt guilty for not caring more about you, but I realized that it was probably just my way of staying safe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2010-07-29 15:36:13 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>the way I felt about her was different.  It was not a healthy relationship, but it was very gratifying in many ways</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2010-07-29 15:41:50 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well, what should I do about the passport and stuff? Can you send it to me? BTW the mail should be stopping soon.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2010-07-29 15:44:03 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>yeah, I guess I could ship it to you sometime.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2010-07-29 15:44:39 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>did any of the mail look time sensitive?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2010-07-29 15:45:09 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>not that I recall</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2010-07-29 15:46:36 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>ok, hey I wanted to thank you for the help with finding me a car again. I'm not sure if you know how much I appreciate it. I got it inspected this week, and it just needed 2 new tires. Dude said it was in pretty good shape. He was impressed.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2010-07-29 15:48:07 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>funny, there is something about helping that makes me feel worthwhile. Perhaps I just wasn't feeling helpful enough.  Not working, accepting help from you with the bills, etc.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2010-07-29 15:48:45 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>It's something I have been noticing lately.  I notice a lot of things lately</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2010-07-29 15:49:38 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Perhaps we could get together sometime if you are feeling up to it.  Maybe some thai.  Let me know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2010-07-29 15:53:19 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>You should probably know even though it might not be easy to hear, but I've met somebody. It's nothing major but he's a pretty nice and interesting guy. And remember how we both agreed that I need to date really nice guy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2010-07-29 15:54:54 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Im guessing that means you think us hanging out is a bad idea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" time="2010-07-29 15:56:33 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>FYI: guys are always nice in the beginning.  Remember how I was in the beginning.  I don't have a problem with you seeing anyone.  I don't expect you to just sit by and be alone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" time="2010-07-29 15:58:53 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>yep i know, but this guy is my friends brother, and I kinda trust that the nice part is for real. But anyway, nope I don't think hanging out is a great idea right now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" time="2010-07-29 16:00:51 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>since we are being honest, I am also seeing someone, and she is not really nice. I almost feel like I am dating myself, and it is very enlightening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" time="2010-07-29 16:01:41 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>hahahaha, sorry that kinda made me laugh out loud. Well, maybe at least you'll understand eachother a little better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" time="2010-07-29 16:04:04 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>it's very exciting, but not very stable.  I sometimes wish for something more comfortable, even though I know it would compromize the excitement, go figure....I guess you just always want what you don't have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" time="2010-07-29 16:08:00 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>well, perhaps you should just enjoy the excitement for now. I got's to go get some lunch.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" time="2010-07-29 16:09:08 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>thats the plan, but it's just not what I am used to so it will take time. Enjoy your nice guy.  Have fun!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" time="2010-07-29 16:09:21 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>you too.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

