<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="CHT_ENG_20101011.0000" medium="CHT" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2010-10-11 19:56:26 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I did some numbers on my end. I think with the car it about evens out. My apologies on being petty.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2010-10-11 19:56:47 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I didn't do the numbers because I felt no need to.  I said I would if it would make you feel better and I would need your input as I may have holes in my info</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2010-10-11 19:57:25 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well it looks like I paid you $3300 in rent for 5 months.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2010-10-11 19:57:42 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>And I put $857.00 into house expenses.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2010-10-11 19:57:47 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>we can make it as complex as we want, but I felt that it would be an unnecessary inconvieniece</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2010-10-11 19:58:22 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>But you paid me back $1000.00</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2010-10-11 19:58:47 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I believe we agreed on $500 a month for you to contribute to house expenses</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2010-10-11 19:59:03 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>yes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2010-10-11 19:59:08 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>which I am not concerned with</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2010-10-11 19:59:33 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>the main thing was the checks you wrote me and the expenses for renovations</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2010-10-11 19:59:55 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I put about $2900 into the car purchase not including insurance costs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2010-10-11 20:00:45 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>RIght, I put $2600.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2010-10-11 20:01:59 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I hope you can see why I cashed the check back in june.  I didnt feel like I was taking advantage.  I dont think I have ever taken advantage in my life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2010-10-11 20:02:08 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I could get super petty and calculate money I put into groceries, but that's just stupid. I know you paid for electric and whatnot.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2010-10-11 20:03:03 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>like I said, you can make it as complex as you want.  This is why I dont bother to tally it up, it just gets messy and overcomplicated</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2010-10-11 20:03:43 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>I guess the bottom line was I never felt taken care of in the relationship. So yes, it's not about the money afterall.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2010-10-11 20:03:46 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Lets not even get into the parking tickets and towing fees</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2010-10-11 20:04:56 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I never really had an opportunity to take care of you.  You took care of yourself quite nicely.  In many ways I would have preferred it if I was the one taking care of you more. It makes me feel better about myself, I suppose</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2010-10-11 20:06:57 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>That's not what I recall. I recall you holding a lot of stuff over my head when it came to you doing something special or paying for my dinner. Like our one year anniversary dinner. All I heard was complaints from you about going to dinner and paying for dinner. That's why I thought of when you sent me that text.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2010-10-11 20:08:35 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>And I recall you yelling at me when I was doing something wrong and needed your help. I don't think tha's helpful at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2010-10-11 20:08:40 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I honestly don't recall that.  I was being ridiculous about money back then, i don't know why.  I was having a hard time because work was sucking and I had alot of bills</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2010-10-11 20:09:13 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well you took it out on me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2010-10-11 20:10:13 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>Ill admit, at times I unfairly took it out on you, but thats how it works. Its unfortunate, but its just how it goes.  I realize that a lot of my frustration came from my own life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2010-10-11 20:10:58 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I only wish we could have dealt with those things as they happened instead of letting them build up.  It was not the best way to handle it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2010-10-11 20:12:39 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>One thing that I always thought was strange is that whenever we had a disagreement, I would end up making you see it my way, and you would apologize</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2010-10-11 20:13:05 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Well that's becuase I was afraid of the outcome.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2010-10-11 20:13:24 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I never understood that. I mean it felt good to have my point taken, but I didnt feel you were trying hard enough to stand your ground</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2010-10-11 20:13:32 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>what was I going to do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2010-10-11 20:14:21 UTC" participant="153906">
      <body>Perhaps listen to my feelings on things and see my perspective.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2010-10-11 20:14:48 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I know that I come off that way sometimes, but you have to remember that I am 5% serious when I am talking that way</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2010-10-11 20:15:13 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>I always listened, but I didnt always understand your perspective</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2010-10-11 20:15:48 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>bottom line, even thought it would not be easy, you cant let someone get away with it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2010-10-11 20:16:40 UTC" participant="153901">
      <body>and if you felt strongly about not being able to 'open up' or be understood, then professional help is what we needed, and I would have seen that eventually, even though I didnt at first</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

