<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150128.0015" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-28 15:17:20 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hey. Sorry to have to ask, but do you think we can go to the movies tomorrow instead of Friday? Since we had a delay on Tuesday, my original Thursday in-class exam turned into a Friday online exam that I have to take before 11:59 pm. Let me know!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-28 18:30:53 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hey! I can go whenever :) We can definitely go tomorrow. But since you have your exam on Friday, do you want to have tomorrow to study too? We can go on Saturday or anytime over the weekend if you want?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-28 18:33:36 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>If it's all the same to you, can we go tomorrow for the 6:50 show? I needed the weekend to study for microbio </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-28 18:34:52 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Awww I'm sorry :( of course! I'm excited!!! We finally get to this this elusive movie! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-28 18:36:15 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I know!!! Do you want to eat there too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-28 18:37:51 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Sure! I'm down for anywhere. Since we're going at that time, I'm sure we'll have our pick of places to eat :)))))</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-28 18:42:08 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>￼Any of those interest you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-28 18:44:27 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Ohhh I wonder what Cafe Bravo or Philly's Gourmet Cafe serves!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-28 18:44:55 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm going to try to find a menu online. Hopefully it's just not coffee and muffins hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-28 18:50:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. Me too! But thanks for going tomorrow!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-28 18:51:59 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Oh my j no problem! I'm looking forward to hanging out!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-28 18:54:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Me too!!!! So what time would you want to get together? Sorry for the 20 questions.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-28 18:58:21 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>No worries. I want to plan out the day too because I'm taking my mom to her doctor's appointment tomorrow too. I hope to get home by 5 at the latest. Do you want to eat before or after?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-28 19:01:20 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Probably before. I have to get up at 6:30 the next morning. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-28 19:03:28 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Good nuff. There doesn't seem to be restaurants so I think we'll be okay. Right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-28 19:03:45 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Okay. I'm going to try to get to South Philly by 5:30 and we'll get there by 6 and have 50 minutes to eat?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-28 19:06:26 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I think so! I don't think having enough time to get food will be a problem. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-28 19:06:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Awesome!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

