<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130603.0016" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 12:58:30 UTC">
      <body>What's going on, giacometti?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 13:13:14 UTC">
      <body>First day in a new apartment. MY STUFF IS EVERYWHERE - time to reassemble my domestic life...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 13:15:43 UTC">
      <body>Was it a far move??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 13:54:50 UTC">
      <body>No luckily just cross town. Im not complaining really, I actually like the chance to set up shop in a new way. What are you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 14:17:45 UTC">
      <body>Working at a computer lab right now, about to go run some errands before working at the bar tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 15:31:15 UTC">
      <body>Sounds nice and varied - good balance youve got there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 16:29:23 UTC">
      <body>Yeah definitely keeps me sane. I'm full time at the bar for the time being but I'm looking to split my time between the places more evenly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 16:32:21 UTC">
      <body>You can probably do it by becoming a thriftenheimer. NO MORE EATING OUT ITS NOT WORTH IT. Thats my technique when Im poor, at least.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 16:54:07 UTC">
      <body>Hahah yeah true. What do you do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 16:57:01 UTC">
      <body>Im a video editor! Im poor generally when I take more satisfying creative work (music videos and such) and comfy when I take commercial work (sleazy casi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 16:57:10 UTC">
      <body>no commercials).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 17:01:55 UTC">
      <body>Haha are you in philly? A good friend of mine does the same thing and has the same woes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 17:10:52 UTC">
      <body>I AM in philly! Im Walker. Feel free to direct your friend to my production company's site: Revisionist.Co. I always heard this line of work would be lik</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 17:11:03 UTC">
      <body>e this, but its an odd way to live at times.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130562" time="2013-06-03 17:12:17 UTC">
      <body>He works with Backseat Conceptions. Careful with names, they don't want much personal info in the database</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131200" time="2013-06-03 17:49:34 UTC">
      <body>Good point - Ive always been a little flippant about personal info / security.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
