<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140628.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-06-28 15:15:12 UTC" participant="149387">
      <body>######### How are you? I'm on my way back to Philly. Beautiful week with with my family in Asheville. I have a question for you regarding a dog sit. I'm scheduled for a Biggie Sit July 4-13 and was wondering if you were free to do three of those nights: Sun, July 6th thru Wed, July 9th. I could do the sleepover on the 4th and 5th and then continue the sit on Wed night, July 9th. Still sorting out my plans, but wanted to see if you were available. Let me know. Thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-06-28 15:19:01 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Hey, I'm glad to hear everything went well on your trip. I won't be available those nights because my girlfriend will be visiting for my birthday. Sorry I can't help out with this sit. Hope u are doing well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-06-28 15:21:31 UTC" participant="149387">
      <body>Girlfriend!?!! Oh, nice! Where's she visiting from? My plans were loose anyway for those dates, so don't worry about it. I'm sure there will be plenty more dog sits this summer.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-06-28 15:27:20 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Yeah, she lives in ####### I also just started back working at the ############### so I am busy again with that. Sorry I couldn't help out this time but thanks for keeping me in mind! Hopefully we can meet up soon and get a ######</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-06-28 15:29:38 UTC" participant="149387">
      <body>I figured she must live in ########You've been heading up there a lot lately. Good for you! Yes, regarding a drink. Soon!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-06-28 15:38:06 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Thanks, she's an old friend from penn. If ur working this weekend maybe I'll see you when I'm at the gallery</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-06-28 15:38:40 UTC" participant="149387">
      <body>Working a double tomorrow. Was supposed to work brunch today, but flight from Asheville was cancelled last night. On my way back now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-06-28 15:48:25 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Ugg... Sorry to hear that. Safe travels.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-06-28 15:48:57 UTC" participant="149387">
      <body>Thanks:-)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

