<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120914.0025" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2012-09-14 21:16:48 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>You went there twice while you you were here this time?  I live like 5 minutes away.  Ive been bouncing around a lot.  Moved here in 07 for like 3 years.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2012-09-14 21:16:49 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>  Then in va for a couple.  And been back here since november.  Done a bit of fishing on the road too.  Over the last 3 years I spent 3 months in Alaska </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2012-09-14 21:16:53 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>and 3 months in Florida  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2012-09-14 21:41:18 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>That sounds awesome! I've been in Philly since 2004, planning to move outside the city soon. So you fish for your job? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2012-09-14 21:45:32 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>s much as  3,000 in a day.  I wish I was right now but I don't have the money for my license.  Its a shame because id be making more money than what im d</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2012-09-14 21:45:33 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>oing now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2012-09-14 21:45:36 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>I try to.  Its on and off work and is a lot like gambling, Haha.  Sometimes you make a killing and others you don't even make your expenses.  I've made a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2012-09-14 21:57:03 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>That is crazy! It sounds tough but more fulfilling than some random job. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2012-09-14 22:01:21 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>Very tough work but very rewarding.  Overall its a good living with a lot of tax benefits.  I just haven't been able to get through the lows very well.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2012-09-14 22:01:22 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>Right now the mullets are running and im not making 2-500 a day because I can't afford a $2500 license.  Frustrating</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

