<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140920.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-20 01:24:33 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>Hey Gabi it's Talia, just got your email! Id love to join tmrw though usually they don't offer student tickets on the Saturday concerts. With my juilliard card I can get two tickets $15 each so I can try tmrw and see if they do.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-20 01:25:20 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>My teacher is the principal bass there so I can also try to see if he has extra, but since it's last minute I doubt it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-20 01:30:42 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Cool, that would be great! If not we should meet up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-20 01:48:04 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>Absolutely! I'll let u know about the Phil tmrw morning. If I don't text u before 2 remind me!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-20 17:48:33 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Any word on tickets?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-20 17:54:25 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>They had some last week for today but now they don't. I texted my teacher we'll see if he answers..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-20 21:02:56 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>Hey sooo he's not getting back to me which means he prob doesn't. Also my friend asked me to help her out tonight and babysit her kids. She'll prob be back around 10 but if it's too late we can hang tmrw maybe?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-20 22:06:06 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I'm not sure what my plans are but after 10 could possibly work, where will you be?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-20 22:53:52 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>72nd and broadway. I'll let u know when I get out hopefully not too late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-20 23:17:55 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Im gonna go with my friends to a movie at 945, if you get out in time you should join us.  Otherwise  would you wanna get breakfast?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-20 23:42:56 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>I doubt I'll get out on time. But yeah for tmrw.. Where in nyc are you staying?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-21 00:10:36 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Im staying near geamarcy park</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-21 00:10:53 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Gramarcy*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-21 00:23:28 UTC" participant="152579">
      <body>And when does the march starts?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

