<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140727.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-27 01:08:16 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>we're back home now. what's your day look like tomorrow? where are you staying tonight and what time do you need to get going back to philly?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-27 01:20:47 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Hey. Thinking about going back to gun powder river tomorrow. I saw so many chanterelles there today but I didn't have a bag. No schedule, just give me a call or I'll call you tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-27 01:21:04 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>what stretch of the river?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-27 01:21:25 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I'm staying a Phill's I might leave Monday morning or later tomorrow evening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-27 01:23:08 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Wildlands loop swimming hole. Belair and miller</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-27 01:25:20 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>sounds perfect. talk to you in the morning. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-27 13:45:36 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>zozo usually takes a nap somewhere in the middle of the day. wakes up around 1 or 2. want to go then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-27 13:52:18 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah that sounds great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-27 16:17:22 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>We're gonna head over there shortly. Do you wanna meet us at the swimming hole? Do you know where I'm talking about? Blue trail to yellow trail</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-27 16:21:15 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>I think so, is it where you and I went before? from the parking lot you go west, through the tunnel under belair road then along the river? I'll look at some maps, I'm sure we can find it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-27 16:25:40 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah under the tunnel then blue to yellow trail with river on your left. I text u route to make sure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-27 16:27:49 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I can also meet you closer if it's too far to carry Zoey</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-07-27 16:32:00 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>we have a backpacky carrier thing so we should be ok, especially with two of us. and with the trail marks I'm sure we can find it. she's asleep now I can let you know when we get to the parking lot. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-07-27 16:33:12 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-07-27 17:33:16 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Blue trail to yellow. Cross the creek at all the downed trees that are blocking the path</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-07-27 17:41:58 UTC" participant="149366">
      <body>sounds good. leaving the parking lot now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-07-27 17:43:46 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

