<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121009.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131015" time="2012-10-09 17:24:07 UTC">
      <body>Hey Gary, it's Santana. I had a question for you: Do you hire day laborers for the work that you been doing? I'm asking because I need a lil work done at my crib as well and it I was just seeing if anybody had any recommendations..?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136729" time="2012-10-09 17:51:01 UTC">
      <body>yea, im rollin 9 deep today. what do u need done?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131015" time="2012-10-09 18:04:00 UTC">
      <body>Nothing major. Some window work. Mainly the outside flashing cut/fitted/installed. It seals the window from the rain. I don't know how to do it myself yet. I might have some other stuff too eventually. How much is a full days work cost? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136729" time="2012-10-09 18:06:39 UTC">
      <body>i got guys everywhere from 70/day to 150. that type of job tho i would charge per job. theyll take it cheap bc it is only a couple days work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131015" time="2012-10-09 18:10:37 UTC">
      <body>Alright. Good to know. I potentially have quite a bit of work to do on my house but I was just trying to get an idea of what I would be working with cost wise. Eventually I need to redo my kitchen and also bathroom. I would be working side by side with anybody that was in there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136729" time="2012-10-09 18:13:50 UTC">
      <body>my guys are good. just let me know. if u buy materials, id work on a day rate, but if its something where u need a lot of material, they get good deals, </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136729" time="2012-10-09 18:13:51 UTC">
      <body>so i would pay they for the whole job. either way, its cheap</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131015" time="2012-10-09 18:18:14 UTC">
      <body>Good to know. Thanks.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
