<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130430.0051" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 15:55:38 UTC">
      <body>hiiiii. where are youuu </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:01:14 UTC">
      <body>I'm at Nakul's. Lauren, I think I'm starting to care about him. Hellppppp. I don't like it I don't like it I don't like it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:03:14 UTC">
      <body>Wait, what are you doing? I need to come home and take my medicine. He's going to be the death of me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 18:04:02 UTC">
      <body>i'm in lullwater taking pictures. i also realized some things about andrew. ugh. also are you planning on being home tonight after trivia? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:06:28 UTC">
      <body>We need to talkkkk. I'm freaking out and I want to hear your realizations. And idk. Nakul wants to take me to dinner and we're supposed to study, but I don't kn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:06:29 UTC">
      <body>ow when. I can probably avoid the room pretty easily.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 18:08:07 UTC">
      <body>hopefully i'll be back in time to shower and clean and we can talk then, but the quizbowl team wants to party (aka answer questions whilst intoxicated) and i volunteered our room. you're more than welcome to be there, you're actually invited, but if you were planning on schoolwork or something i didn't want to bother you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:12:26 UTC">
      <body>Oh fuck. I have to clean. I was in a panic last night and dumped all my laundry on my bed. As you witnessed. And that sounds like a lot of fun. I might join you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:12:27 UTC">
      <body> depending on how much work I get done.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 18:13:13 UTC">
      <body>yay! so if you've got dinner plans then i'm guessing you're not coming to trivia? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 18:15:32 UTC">
      <body>I don't know. I'm waiting for Nakul to get the fuck out of the shower. I swear he's a girl.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 18:15:49 UTC">
      <body>but a very cute girl! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 19:46:39 UTC">
      <body>now where are you?! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136378" time="2013-04-30 20:24:19 UTC">
      <body>I'm still with Nakul. Sorryyyy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136112" time="2013-04-30 20:52:57 UTC">
      <body>no probs! just curious! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136378" time="2013-05-01 05:27:31 UTC">
      <body>I think I'm ###########, hahahaha. I've never experienced this kind of intense lust before and it's awfulllll. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136112" time="2013-05-01 05:28:22 UTC">
      <body>hahahahahahahahahahaha. my favorite thing you've ever said. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136378" time="2013-05-01 15:57:58 UTC">
      <body>Had a panic attack because I thought that I lost my keys. Turns out they were wedged between my boobs and my computer. Hate my life.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136112" time="2013-05-01 15:58:15 UTC">
      <body>hahaha. funniest thing ever. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
