<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130613.0003" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 14:11:53 UTC">
      <body>Hello again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:17:45 UTC">
      <body>Yesssassss</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:18:02 UTC">
      <body>Haha how are you? Look at this system trying to keep us apart for hours on end</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 14:31:57 UTC">
      <body>This is the technologically current version of locking people in a room together. How is your day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:35:26 UTC">
      <body>haha I hope you don't hate it that much. Also you could not respond if you wanted. But I like the imagery</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 14:40:41 UTC">
      <body>Not as in punishment, but rather sociological experimentation. Though they say its for linguistics...anyway, it's not bad, it helps to interrupt banal computer work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:43:54 UTC">
      <body>I got "it helps interrupt anal computer work".... didn't know you were in such a specific field.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 14:46:36 UTC">
      <body>The world needs specialists. That should have been banal. Texts are like Rorschach images</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:49:43 UTC">
      <body>So you make these banal images that are essentially ink blots?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 14:50:39 UTC">
      <body>Yeah and then I sell them to ikea. It's pretty lucrative</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 14:53:41 UTC">
      <body>And then you get yo hang out with Rorschach afterwards?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 15:09:55 UTC">
      <body>I pour the first sip of my forty out for Rorschach</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 15:56:05 UTC">
      <body>But he isn't dead</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 15:59:44 UTC">
      <body>Maybe we are talking about two different Rorschachs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 16:13:11 UTC">
      <body>Have you seen the movie the watchmen? I suppose the character and the original test must be based on a real guy, who must be dead, which makes your actions totally appropriate</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 16:19:19 UTC">
      <body>The character was pulverized by dr manhattan at the end of the comic. I think at the end of the movie too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 16:22:22 UTC">
      <body>O. You are right again. Man I was not paying enough attention at the end of that movie. Maybe I should drink more fortys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 16:28:05 UTC">
      <body>I've read the graphic novel too many times, it's burned into my brain</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 16:30:48 UTC">
      <body>You are interesting mugsy. Do you read a lot of graphic novels? Do you play video games? Most importantly, do you go on reddit?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 16:36:02 UTC">
      <body>I don't read a lot of graphic novels, but I like anything by Allen Moore or Jesse Moynihan. Not really to video games, unless it's in an arcade. Reddit sometimes, but just when I am killing time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 19:47:21 UTC">
      <body>Arcades? Do they have alot of those in Philly? I feel like they aren't really a thing anymore. I did like the movie wreck it Ralph though. So you actually sell paintings to IKEA?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
