<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140901.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-01 21:46:12 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Just to verify. I am watching shadow again right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-01 22:17:55 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea. Tonight is the last night.  We'll be home tomorrow evening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-01 23:00:54 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay that's what I thought. I'm there already</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-01 23:23:06 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok cool.. thanks agAin for staying over.  Steph asked her brother first to not bother you again but he couldn't</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-01 23:51:56 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>It's okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-01 23:52:05 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Not a problem</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-02 12:14:19 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>So you know, Shadow doesn't have his collar on. He kept taking it off, so it's on the coffee table. There are curly fries in the fridge. You can eat them or trash them. I didn't wanna put them in the trash. I threw out the trash bag in the bathroom because it was full. I couldn't find a replacement bag. And you need to fill up the toilet paper dispenser. Also, my bed is still in the back room.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-02 13:00:07 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol yea shadow likes to strip naked, we only keep it on him when someone comes in just to have a handle to grab...  did you put the bathroom trash in the regular trash? Yea we are out of plastic bags lol haven't been food shopping. Toilet paper is in the upstairs hallway closet, top shelf.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-02 13:05:17 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah It's in the trash And that's almost full</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-02 13:25:15 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>That s fine, trash goes out tomorrow anyway. Normally wed night but holiday pushes it back a day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-02 17:43:36 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah I know</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

