<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140617.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-06-17 13:10:49 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Just sent you a new version, if you are close to a computer with internet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-06-17 16:11:08 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hi! I only have my phone for a few days. Don't think it does the video any justice. I am seeing my cousin tomorrow night and will ask her if I can check the video!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-06-17 16:11:18 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Thanks for letting me know!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-06-17 16:13:49 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Sure thing!  It is good to take a vacation from the digital world and totally understand if you need to go off the grid until Friday.  I have the whole day to work on Friday, so we can wait until then if need be.  My only concern is the rendering.  It takes ALL night to render that shit.  No Joke!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-06-17 16:33:43 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Tell me about it! The video took 6 hour on my slow computer to export and I had to do it twice! I am meeting with Val Friday at some point too.  Are you free in the afternoon Friday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-06-17 16:36:16 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Yeah, I think Drew wants to leave town no later than 6 PM.  It takes 3 hours to get to where we are going.  But we are staying at a hotel so it's not like we have to set up camp or something. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-06-17 16:42:03 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Okay maybe you and I can meet in the morning and I can go to the editor from there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-06-17 16:43:50 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>That works for me!  I can take the train in and be at your place or somewhere close to Penn as early as 9 am.  Just let me know what is best for you.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-06-17 16:51:54 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>That will probably be perfect. I will let you know for sure and try to give some feedback ASAP!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

