<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130226.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 02:07:01 UTC">
      <body>Mon fau! I'm free this saturday, any good? Also, do you know who is teaching tomorrow morning for morgan?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 02:08:03 UTC">
      <body>Not sure about Morgan. This weekend I will be in NYC for an acupuncture thing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 02:09:45 UTC">
      <body>Boo for us, but yay for you! Are you back by sunday evening?xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 02:10:23 UTC">
      <body>Probably not. I'm not sure about my return time yet.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 02:11:58 UTC">
      <body>Boo. Hmm. When else are you free?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 02:13:22 UTC">
      <body>Next week maybe? Monday night. Thursday maybe? I can go to Thursday morning yoga?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 02:20:15 UTC">
      <body>Monday is limbs. Boo. I might come to thurs yoga. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 02:25:24 UTC">
      <body>I know! I keep offering  Monday night bc I keep hoping it will work! The weekend after this is uncertain but maybe Thursday during the day? I'm on spring break but don't want to overpack myself! I do want to see you though!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 02:32:37 UTC">
      <body>This is so difficult! Roll on summer holidays and the end of limbs...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 03:03:51 UTC">
      <body>Ah! What is next Thursday and Friday like for you? Also maybe next Wednesday night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 03:08:34 UTC">
      <body>I can do next week wed and thurs eve after 8:45, and fri eve after 8:15. All so late....if you pass through campus in the day time on week days I can also meet for coffee near there. Xxxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 03:19:49 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah, I mean that would be when I was free  by the time I get home after class, which is usually at like 7:50, shower, and get out of the house again. Ditto for post-aerobics on thurs and post-yoga on fri. Xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 16:01:52 UTC">
      <body>Lets go to Morgan's 6pm (is that the right time) next weds (spring break so I'm free!) then hang for a bit! Does that work for you? I need you right now!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131422" time="2013-02-26 16:09:50 UTC">
      <body>Excellent!xxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-02-26 16:18:27 UTC">
      <body>Yah!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
