<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150309.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-09 17:36:00 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Any ideas for a restaurant for this weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-09 18:46:56 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I heard Barbuzzo was good, are you into that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-09 18:54:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Looks pretty good. I'll send out a group message and see what everyone else wants to do. I don't really care so I'll let everyone decide via menus. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-09 20:25:16 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Coolio. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-09 23:09:03 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hola mi amigos! So I made a reservation at white dog cafe because so far I had more votes for it and I didn't want to wait any longer. The bad thing is that the reservation is at 815. I hope that's okay. I figured if we wanted to go somewhere after, we could. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-09 23:22:18 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Me too!!! I made a reservation for 10 people. In the off chance that boyfriends can't come, I can change the number. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-09 23:32:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okie dokie!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-10 11:18:29 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hey Jen, how much does it cost to take the train to Suburban Station? Actually, how does any of it work (where can I buy tickets, what are the stops, is it easier to take the bus)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-10 11:22:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I've never taken the bus, but you can take the Paoli/thorndale line at market east station and it stops right at suburban station.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-10 11:22:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Actually...at market east, you can take any train to suburban station on tracks 3 &amp; 4.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-10 11:24:46 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm thinking of driving to Broad, parking there, going underground (can I do that?), and catching a train to Suburban. Is that an option?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-10 11:24:48 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I thought you meant suburban square at first....although I don't know where you're starting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-10 11:25:44 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm coming from my house. I just want to avoid parking and traffic in Center City. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-10 11:26:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hmmmmmm....I don't know what the transpo is like from you. My guess is that there's a broad street line (the Orange line) somewhere, but it stops at certain stops. Like near me, it's broad and Ellsworth or broad and tasker. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-10 11:26:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I would check septas website? It lists all the stops of the Orange line. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-10 11:28:31 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm nervous about this. Just want to deal with driving around the city :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-03-10 11:28:55 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*don't want</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-10 11:29:31 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I might just do that. Maybe I'm making it scarier than it actually is in my head.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-03-10 11:34:45 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I think so. Cause I was always nervous but it's not too bad. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-03-10 12:52:42 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm paranoid. Even more so especially since i heard the news story about the woman who was attacked at one of the stops. Guess I just have to be aware and know what I'm doing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-03-10 13:10:08 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Why not just drive then? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-03-10 13:23:25 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Traffic and parking.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-03-10 13:39:00 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Mmmmm. Okay then!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-03-10 15:30:08 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Adjusted to the weight, not adjusted to the spakliness! Haha. It constantly catches my eye. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-03-10 15:30:42 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'll be fine hahahah! How's your finger feeling? Has it adjusted to that extra weight??? ;)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

