<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130531.0031" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 21:58:02 UTC">
      <body>You're right, I can barely open my mouth.  This is total horseshit </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:00:52 UTC">
      <body>Haha its the worst. Are you at least able to drink your flackseed shakes?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:06:26 UTC">
      <body>Dude eating those shakes hurts sooo bad, idk why.  Too cold maybe?  Applesauce all day err day though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:17:04 UTC">
      <body>That's what I did. Applesauce and Greek yogurt. Sometimes that would hurt though cause the spoon was too big haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:26:10 UTC">
      <body>Haha you and your chobani.  So I wanna watch game of thrones but I'm scared to start it because it seems like a lot of work...  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:31:50 UTC">
      <body>I love the books. I have only watched the first season, but I did that in like two sittings. It's pretty rad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:35:32 UTC">
      <body>Oh, i thought you'd watched it for some reason.  Yeah everyone seems to love it.  I don't even know how many seasons there are ughhh tv is so hard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:37:17 UTC">
      <body>There should end up being 7, cause that's how many books are planned but only 5 books are out. They're on the 3rd season for tv</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:40:43 UTC">
      <body>Sooo much GoT.  This is probably way too mainstream for me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:42:19 UTC">
      <body>Read the books, that's still pretty underground. Especially if you get past the 3rd book</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:46:22 UTC">
      <body>Oooh you're right, do you have them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:48:58 UTC">
      <body>Yes, but my first book is a first edition. I'm that cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131945" time="2013-05-31 22:51:08 UTC">
      <body>Omg.  That's way to nice for me to borrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131960" time="2013-05-31 22:52:23 UTC">
      <body>You can probably buy them real cheap at bookmans. That's were I got that book</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
