<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130726.0011" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 12:38:34 UTC">
      <body>I guess they started a new chat... I thought it was for people around the world. Are you M or F ... I'm a 40 yr old F</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 12:48:50 UTC">
      <body>I don't think it is location specific, its just text generating. I'm female, 32. What do you have planned for the weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 12:51:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm up at my vacation place ..cleaning,decorating and spending money :) trying to get everything organized. Its like decorating a second home! Then a fire pit, drinks and rest!" How about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 13:03:18 UTC">
      <body>Did you just acquire this place? I'm heading to work in a moment, having a hard time leaving the park..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 13:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Yes I did... last week</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 14:18:06 UTC">
      <body>Congrats, that is exciting! Is it in the woods or on the water?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 18:46:15 UTC">
      <body>Woods!! Im more of a water/beach person but can only afford up in the woods but its nice and I didn't even know it but 2 of my employees live here about6 houses away so its great !!! What do you do for a living</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 21:21:00 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow, what a coincidence. It always feels good to spend some time in the trees. I'm a student, studying at Bryn Mawr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 21:22:44 UTC">
      <body>I'm a retired Sgt. I worked in the jail... I prefer the ocean but my sons love the mountains</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 23:11:29 UTC">
      <body>I'm split, I like both. How is retirement?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 23:34:33 UTC">
      <body>Its good!! A little boring at times but now that I have this place its giving me something to do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 23:46:36 UTC">
      <body>Will you be able to use it year round, or is it a seasonal home?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136540" time="2013-07-26 23:50:38 UTC">
      <body>Yr round but I think I'll use it till it snows..too cold!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130664" time="2013-07-26 23:54:00 UTC">
      <body>Right, no point going north in the winter. Did you have a fire tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136540" time="2013-07-27 10:24:44 UTC">
      <body>Yes.... it was a nice night out. What's your plans for today? We're just hanging out around here..</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
