<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150116.0027" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-16 23:17:20 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body>How is my favorite Jenna? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-16 23:22:42 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Oh my goodness Sheridan. I've had a very long day. Dads car broke down last night so we couldn't leave for nyc until this morning in a rental car. And then we dropped the little puppy off at kk's and he ran away from kelly, so we came back to look for him and couldn't find him:( now we're in Pennsylvania and still have 3 hours to go, and the sick puppy is nowhere to be found. So much stress. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-16 23:24:34 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body>Oh gosh, I really hope they find him, and I'm so sorry to hear about the car. I love you dearly and everything will be okay. You are almost back to classes and your schduele of life. Plus you have tons of awesome people hear for you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-16 23:24:36 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body>Here</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-16 23:25:18 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>❤️❤️❤️ love you so much Sheridan!!! Tell me about Minnesota! How's everything there? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-16 23:26:59 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body>Everything is alright, I've been dealing with some emotions and being scared. I'm still waiting to hear back from the u of m, and I hurt my back so ehh. But i think everything is getting better </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-16 23:35:41 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>You're so brave, dear! You've got nothing to worry about- you're strong and beautiful and can make it through anything! And a long hot shower might not fix your back, but I guarantee you'll feel better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-16 23:36:32 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-16 23:52:48 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>I love you dollface</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-16 23:54:48 UTC" participant="153850">
      <body>I love you too dollface </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

