<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130716.0014" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 12:20:36 UTC">
      <body>I will be incommunicado for 10 days. Heading to Italy with my mom. When I think about it, i've been on two international vacations since we started chatt</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 12:20:36 UTC">
      <body>ing.:-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 12:29:14 UTC">
      <body>How's life in SF?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 12:57:59 UTC">
      <body>(1/2)Hello! Life's good. I know it's summer, but it's so cold here! You should count yourself lucky. The last time I went international was a couple years</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 12:57:59 UTC">
      <body>(2/2)ago! :-) Are you gonna be vacationing in Italy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 16:19:19 UTC">
      <body>Yup! Vacation. We're booked on a tour of Venice, Florence, Rome, Pompeii, Sorento &amp; Capri</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 16:41:40 UTC">
      <body>That sounds amazing! Have fun! :D My friends and I are thinking of going to maybe Alaska or Miami for the Labor Day weekend. Haven't picked one yet.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 16:46:09 UTC">
      <body>My vote: Alaska!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 16:46:56 UTC">
      <body>I haven't been yet but I think there's more to see there. However, if u only have 4 days, then Miami seems more doable in that short time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 16:50:11 UTC">
      <body>(1/3)Exactly! I'd rather take a long-ish vacation and go see everything. There's so much to see in Alaska that 3 days won't do justice, I feel. Plus, it's a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 16:50:47 UTC">
      <body>(2/3)little heavy on the pocket as well. :P You said you've lived in FL, right? Where would you go if you had 3 days to spend there? Miami, Orlando, Naples,</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 16:50:47 UTC">
      <body>(3/3)Fort Lauderdale...?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 17:20:48 UTC">
      <body>I've never spent time in Miami. I'm not a fan of Orlando since it's so touristy. Ft Lauderdale is nice but pricey. I would say the FL Keys. Never been bu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 17:29:32 UTC">
      <body>t I'll be going in Sept and everyone always talks about how nice it is.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130970" time="2013-07-16 17:29:32 UTC">
      <body>Of places i've been to, I recommend St Petersburg, FL. It's a historical city with great atmosphere and people and lovely beaches</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130662" time="2013-07-16 19:49:40 UTC">
      <body>Thanks a lot for your input! I know nothing about FL, so this info will help me plan a bit.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
