<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120303.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 04:56:52 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Are you working? I know I'm an unwelcome distraction but Fridays are particularly tough on this end, especially once all my friends have gone their sepa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 04:57:03 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) rate ways . I'd like nothing more than to discuss with you what it means to be 20-something. Too far? Maybe. But you know better than anyone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2012-03-03 06:31:06 UTC">
      <body>Better than anyone? I just got out of work and am exhausted. Im sorry I can't discuss </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 06:44:59 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I meant to say know me better than anyone. I'm sorry Mattie, I really don't mean to ask  you to have convetsations you're not interested in. Just missin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 06:45:10 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) g your wisdom in my life, which I realize is probably  too much to ask for. Rest your body well </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2012-03-03 21:27:23 UTC">
      <body>Please don't feel like you're an inconvenience or  an annoyance. You're not. I'm still trying to make sense of this and besides I'm just totally out of my mind busy. I haven't talked to pat in a month. So please, just be generous and know that I would talk if I could</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 22:08:07 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) Thanks for saying that Mattie, and I know, I'm sorry you're so busy and I don't expect that you can talk. If you can and want to I'm very happy to, but </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 22:08:11 UTC">
      <body>(02/03) I know you've got so many things on your mind. Know that I completely understand and truly just want you to do what you need to do to be good to yoursel</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135117" time="2012-03-03 22:08:16 UTC">
      <body>(03/03) f </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
