<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130725.0015" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136133" time="2013-07-25 16:30:04 UTC">
      <body>Hello! How are you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131527" time="2013-07-25 17:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Hey there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136133" time="2013-07-25 20:33:40 UTC">
      <body>How are you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131527" time="2013-07-25 21:04:46 UTC">
      <body>Super busy, still working. U?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136133" time="2013-07-25 22:48:18 UTC">
      <body>Oh I see. How is work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131527" time="2013-07-25 22:59:58 UTC">
      <body>Big deadline on Wednesday; end of 8 month long project with TONS to do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 00:04:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh nice. Well good luck on the large amount of work!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 00:05:22 UTC">
      <body>Thanks!! I love it (still working, lol).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 00:06:00 UTC">
      <body>How are u? It's late on east coast, where r u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 00:54:57 UTC">
      <body>Ah I see. Its awesome that you love what you do. :) Don't get to hear that too often these days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 00:56:13 UTC">
      <body>I am well. Just got home from a family dinner. I'm in TN lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 00:57:07 UTC">
      <body>How is life on the east coast? I haven't visited that area before</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:07:36 UTC">
      <body>:-) took a leap of faith (and a few months of unpaid bills...along with a HUGE student loan debt) to pursue a job I love. But still new to recent shifts,so still giddy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:08:45 UTC">
      <body>Love dinners with my family (parents and siblings more so than extended family). You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:10:01 UTC">
      <body>East coast is where I've always lived, but one of my intentions by shifting to self-employment is to afford more time/$ to move/explore/travel</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:17:46 UTC">
      <body>Wow I wish I knew more people with that amount of dedication. Very inspiring! :) I'm still not sure what my dream job is. Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:29:15 UTC">
      <body>I grew up in a very large asian family so i like the atmosphere. But I also enjoy spending quality time with my parents and brother since we are busy allthe time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:29:16 UTC">
      <body>Thanks :-) Honestly, it has evolved over the years and in hindsight, I wish that I were more curious and exploratory about careers in college. I was so rigidly "married" to the career title and what was required to do it (clinical psychologist); could have saved myself time and $ if I had been more flexible. So... Enjoy the adventure of exploring what you might do for a career (so cliche, but enjoy the "journey")</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:29:16 UTC">
      <body>Ah I see. My parents seem to enjoy self employment over the years. It does have many benefits but a lot of hard work. Where do you plan to travel once you have time?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:34:04 UTC">
      <body>EVERYWHERE, lol!! From doing a cross-country camper trip with my husband and son to a three-week backpack tour of Europe (my sister, mom, and me - planning and just started making payments for trip in 2015).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:34:04 UTC">
      <body>I want to explore so many other places too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:34:29 UTC">
      <body>Have u travelled!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:37:20 UTC">
      <body>Ill do my best to keep your advise in mind during my college life:) thank you so much for your words!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:39:04 UTC">
      <body>Happy to share :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:47:37 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow that sounds like an amazing time! I've never really thought about a cross country camping trip before. Must be a unique experience. And backpacking sounds like so much fun with family.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 01:48:08 UTC">
      <body>I haven't done much traveling since I began college but I've been back and forth between Vietnam and California since I was very young. My parents required me to learn traditions and skills needed for when I am married. Other than that I didn't do much traveling so far. I'm hoping to qualify for teachingEnglish in either Korea or Japan in 2015 though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131527" time="2013-07-26 01:55:44 UTC">
      <body>Wow! What was/is that like?? I value my family's traditions strongly, but they are consistent with American traditions. What have u noticed? Do u noticea "shift/transition" from American to Vietnamese (right?) traditions? So curious, please feel free to go to bed too, lol. I could ask questions all night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="136133" time="2013-07-26 11:51:52 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry I fell asleep without saying anything. Haha. There are a lot of differences between the cultures. For example: we pay close attention to out family linage. Power within the family is usually seen there. We have to be very careful when addressing people in and out of the family. some people getvery angry if the basic traditions aren't followed correctly. It's been a bit difficult to learn everything while growing up in America but its pretty interesting to see the differences</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
