<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150228.0026" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-28 16:20:02 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Hey Brian, can I schedule a time to have you snake my soil line, and maybe the street trap? It has backed up twice in a week and several times this year. I can usually get it flowing again by shop vacking the blockage but I am sick of this literal shit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-28 16:55:28 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Yeah man, can we do Tuesday afternoon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-28 19:38:11 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Absolutely,. I teach from 3-5:30 but I can have someone here or leave a key for you. I think I lost the end of my shopvac hose in the pipe unfortunately. So first objective would be snaking that out. And then auguring it I guess. I can do cash if it'll be any cheaper. Thanks a million Brian</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-28 20:28:48 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Hide a key somewhere and let me know, cash is always cheaper, shop vac hose I'm drain sounds sketchy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-28 20:28:48 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>How the hell am I gonna get that out, are you not using any water right now to keep that hose near where it got lost</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-28 20:38:15 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> I don't know. I've been using water. I'll try to fish it out. It's the hard plastic bit on the end of the hose. It could have already been missing. But I just noticed it today right before I shopvacked. I think it was on there 5 days a week ago when I last vacked it out so I assume it's in there. Also I could only get the vac about 4' down the pipe this time so I think that's where it is. There's a chance it needs to get dug up and replaced anyway so doing the auger is the last resort before digging it all up. Sucks because it's right underneath my concrete front stairs so it's gonna be a bitch to dig up if I need to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-01 16:10:35 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-01 16:12:00 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I tried to get the plastic out with this. Pretty sure I hooked it good twice because it was really hard to get unhooked. But the thing won't budge. What's your verdict?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

