<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141219.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-19 02:47:07 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:( Kyle, my bfs parents who live in Mexico are only coming into the US for one weekend (this weekend) this year and they really want to meet me- would you mind if I either rescinded covering for you Saturday OR I take your Saturday but you take my Sunday?? I'm sorry, I forgot that this was the one weekend they will be in NY and it's apparently a big family deal bla bla </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-19 03:02:54 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>I can open Sunday. No problem, I just really don't see myself being able to function the day after the Xmas party. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-19 03:51:16 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ha I totally understand. I'm sorry to do this but I have to be in NY Friday and Saturday and I can't just switch w Sunday. I truly am just finding this out now and I won't be at the Xmas party either. I didn't forget- my bf screwed up and told me the wrong dates that his mom and grandfather and father will be in the US and I really want to meet his family obv and tomorrow and this Sat are apparently my only chance. Thanks and I owe you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-19 04:05:20 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>Do whatever you want, I guess. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-19 07:19:28 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>I'm not working Sunday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-19 13:45:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes I know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-19 14:48:29 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>Just wanted to clarify. Since, y'know, you didn't ask me to work Saturday, you just told me you weren't working it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-19 15:37:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Wait </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-19 15:37:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-19 15:38:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You asked if I wanted your Saturday shift so I said yes bc I did </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-12-19 15:41:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Then last night I suddenly get told by my bf that he told me the wrong weekend dates and his family is coming This weekend from Mexico and his dying grandpa and bla bla and his mom planned us a whole weekend and blaaaaaaaa and so suddenly I was put in a super shitty situation- so I thought I could negotiate and just see his parents Sunday but no, his grandfather is only in the country Tomorrow and whatever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-19 15:42:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I realized that I really couldn't cover for you Saturday after all bc ya I obv want the One chance to meet my bfs parents </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-19 15:43:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Like I Never cancel or call in sick or anything ever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-19 15:43:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Never have since I started working at the last drop </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-12-19 15:43:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But I'd call in sick or somethig for this bc it's super important </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-19 15:43:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So if you want to just have me tell nam I agreed on sat but now can't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-12-19 15:43:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>That's fine </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-12-19 15:44:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But basically I also threw my besties birthday under the bus too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-12-19 15:44:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And also Brittany who suddenly I bailed on for two days </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-12-19 15:45:02 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And everyone is mad at me but like I honestly am not going to miss the one chance to meet my dudes family since he just moved in w me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-12-19 15:45:12 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I don't care how we do Saturday but I won't be here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-12-19 15:47:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You don't need to work sat is my point </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-12-19 15:47:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I have worked at the last drop for a year and Never called sick </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-12-19 15:47:43 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Never asked for a cover</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-12-19 15:48:05 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>Who do you think covers you if you call in sick tomorrow?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-12-19 15:48:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I have worked at the last drop a year and never called in sick and never not shown up and never had an emergency and never canceled </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-12-19 15:49:06 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You asked me to cover and I said sure and now I'm saying an emergency came up and I can't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-12-19 15:49:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It IS my responsibility </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-12-19 15:49:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So that is fine but I cannot cover Saturday anymore </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-12-19 15:50:20 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I will tell nam I agreed to cover your sat and screwed up and can't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-12-19 15:50:29 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>That's my responsibility  and fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-12-19 15:50:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I don't need you to patronize me and teach me how to be responsible. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-12-19 15:55:44 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>Whatever. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

