<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150217.0021" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-17 01:16:48 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Ohhhh honey!!! I have already seen it like 10 times. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-17 01:17:06 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=4zBlG8Lv01k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-17 01:17:47 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Your Tom Hiddy is picking some weird roles! What's up with that?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-17 01:18:29 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Anything to see Tom hiddleston. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-17 01:20:43 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I couldn't even watch the whole thing once! I had to look away and cover my eyes at certain parts. Freaked me out!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-17 01:25:15 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I should have known! Hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-02-17 01:50:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. I can't wait to watch it!! I'm so excited!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-02-17 02:39:43 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Are you really going to watch it? Ah I didn't think it was going to be that kind of movie when I heard the title. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-02-17 03:41:38 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hell yes I'm going to watch it! Haha. 
What did you think it was about?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-02-17 05:10:18 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Like from the glimpses that I dared to look at, I reckon that the actress named Mia gets together with Tommy H's character. They move into that creepy house that belongs to him and his sister. I'm guessing people died there and it's now haunted. Oh and Charlie Hunnam like her too and wants to rescue her.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-02-17 05:10:44 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I think it's a book. I didn't read it though hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-02-17 10:50:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Really? I don't think it is. It came from the "great mind" of del toro. 
From what I gathered, you're right. I don't know much of the plot story either. All I know is that if I had a chance to live with T. Hiddles, I'd do it even if the house was haunted.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

