<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130509.0094" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-05-09 15:06:05 UTC" participant="152526">
      <body>Wow. Passive aggressive much? I didn't know he was donating equipment. His ad is in the playbill, but there is no acknowledgement for his contribution. 
There's nothing I can do about that. Of course he should get comp tickets. Talk to Phinn and Lois about and then just let me know which nights. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-05-09 15:19:23 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Yea, but hes also volunteering to do the soudboard for 3 shows so ill ignore passive agression.  Will do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-05-09 15:36:26 UTC" participant="152526">
      <body>I'm sorry. I just wish communication could be a little better so that these kind of exchanges didn't happen. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-05-09 19:39:33 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Im tempted to shave my head so i look like the giant man on stage, whadya think? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-05-09 20:52:16 UTC" participant="152526">
      <body>I'm so charmed by you sometimes. 
I'm a little creeped out by the giant man. I'm not sure what that tells you about how I would feel about you looking like him, but...I will support any decision you make!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-05-09 20:56:01 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-05-09 21:01:26 UTC" participant="152526">
      <body>Wow. I'm laughing hard. 
I needed that. I just emailed in my take home final for my German cultures class 
You're the best, Gabi. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-05-09 21:03:23 UTC" participant="152526">
      <body>Now I really want you to do some kind of strong man schtick in the show. You know, like lifting barbells or the strength competition where you hit the target with the hammer to try to ring the bell. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

