<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130614.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-06-14 21:18:56 UTC">
      <body>Hi! i miss you! also I want to vent to youuu so you can tell me how to be reasonable :P the other research assistants at work know I'm in a relationship but nothing more, and two are being gender neutral and not pressing me but one (who I am most concerned about) referenced my boyfriend three times today in front of others and I didn't correct her and hfkksbdjfkshfjvk I don't know what to do help call me sometime (not urgent I'm actually fine just rambling) &lt;3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135080" time="2013-06-15 16:09:07 UTC">
      <body>Or girl who said boyfriend can find out because she friended me on Facebook, as opposed to my saying something on Monday? Is that weird?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135269" time="2013-06-15 17:35:49 UTC">
      <body>Huh. I don't think you have to say anything in that case. Or you could wait to friend her until after you've talked to her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-06-15 17:36:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I just friended them all on fb. I'm sure Allison will bring it up and no one else will care</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135269" time="2013-06-15 17:39:09 UTC">
      <body>It will work out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135080" time="2013-06-15 17:39:54 UTC">
      <body>Yes haha it is done. How are you? Any weekend and or just hanging around?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2013-06-15 17:45:46 UTC">
      <body>Cool! :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135269" time="2013-06-15 17:45:50 UTC">
      <body>Pottery pottery. But also second annual north ga chamber music festival opens tonight! Yay! So excited. Going with sister. Schmann, beethoven, etc.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135269" time="2013-06-15 17:46:54 UTC">
      <body>What about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135080" time="2013-06-15 17:47:50 UTC">
      <body>I'm at haverford right now but when Anna gets back from lab we will head to Philly and help Lizzy move in. Not sure about tomorrow. Also sleeping in :P</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
