<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130418.0032" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 19:01:20 UTC">
      <body>Remembered the books. See ya later </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-04-18 19:13:48 UTC">
      <body>Aw so sweet. Thanks. See you later.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 22:25:50 UTC">
      <body>Hey Monica.  Slow afternoon for me today.  Would it be ok if I took off early and caught up w u another time? I will leave books here in trader joe bag for u </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-04-18 22:38:14 UTC">
      <body>Of course! I'm 6 blocks away on trolley but no need to wait.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh. Argh. I left about 10 minutes ago  I was thinking you wouldn't be there till 730-ish</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body>Is your break next week or week after?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-04-18 22:43:00 UTC">
      <body>Week after</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 22:45:20 UTC">
      <body>If you are in town we can shoot for a rendezvous Lunch drink whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-04-18 22:46:36 UTC">
      <body>Yes! That would be fun! I like drinking at lunch actually. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-04-18 22:47:04 UTC">
      <body>The idiots guide to ethics...really! I am appalled. (No surprise there.)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 23:35:38 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that book IS appalling...and in some ways the class is too.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131424" time="2013-04-18 23:36:04 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm how do I swing lunch drinking and an afternoon shift?  ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:11:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh funny! I totally wasn't thinking of that!! No to alcohol at lunch then! Do you want to pencil in lunch on Thursday the 2nd?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:13:07 UTC">
      <body>Ed might be mad. I am leaving for Maine to study with my teacher for a week and will miss 2 weeks of class! I'm going to an island in the middle of a lake to study IDs. Do you want to come? No electricity, no running water, camping. I think you would love</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:13:47 UTC">
      <body>They got a new Chinese teacher. Have you met Pierce Salguero? He studies this history of Chinese medicine at penn state Abbington. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131424" time="2013-04-19 00:21:20 UTC">
      <body>I WOULD like that island setting!!  Have gone to one of perce's lectures. The old Chinese teacher was extremely patient but don't think she liked how poorly the won communicated w her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131424" time="2013-04-19 00:23:42 UTC">
      <body>I think eds class is only 5 weeks so u should chat w him.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131424" time="2013-04-19 00:25:22 UTC">
      <body>Ok have u down for lunch on 2nd.  In west Philly. Ill let u pick place </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131424" time="2013-04-19 00:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Looking forward to it.  Good luck w finals!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:26:19 UTC">
      <body>Yes I will definitely chat with him. Missing two weeks is not ideal but I know most people will miss at least one. I will do extra work if I need to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:26:39 UTC">
      <body>I already have picked the place! Haha! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:27:44 UTC">
      <body>Have you been to Atiya Ola at 45 and Baltimore? It's mostly vegan raw and really yummy. Or Ethiopian. Or Indian are good too. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 00:28:29 UTC">
      <body>Lunch will be fun!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131424" time="2013-04-19 01:06:08 UTC">
      <body>Haven't been there - I'm open to all of them.  Yes F U N </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
