<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150323.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-23 21:56:33 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>This fence is pretty incredible! I'm seriously impressed that you just threw that up this weekend!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-23 21:56:50 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>(Just got here and all is well!!)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-23 22:06:46 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Thanks so much. They were probably crazy relieved to see you. They are so spoiled. That was a long day alone. Lol on the fence for the new wild life preserve :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-23 22:08:07 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>When you head ustairs, pls check the middle room for a puddle. I don't think he'd do it but oti has occassionally whizzed in there. We meant to put the gate there for the day but forgot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-23 22:14:07 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I didn't see anything I think he held it! Piper is being a little shy and won't come down to eat but I'll let her warm up and try to feed her dinner in a bit.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-23 22:16:36 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Awww. Pyper! If she doesn't sho interest later you can always just put the food in mc's room for tonight. Soo proud of oti :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-23 22:21:13 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Ah I will do that. Hope the drive is going well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-23 22:28:28 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Went well. Did the vassar tour already. Sitting down for some gluten free pizza in poughkeepsie now. Speaking of which. Serioulsy eat whatever you find. I know there is an avocado and tomato and lots of potatos</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-23 22:29:55 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh man sounds good! I have half my lunch still but maybe I'll make a baked potato. Thanks!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-23 22:30:13 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Enjoy pizza!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-23 22:30:31 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>There is cheddar, salsa and sour to go with :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-23 22:32:49 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>The works!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-24 00:45:41 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Sounds like a package may have gotten delivered today. We are expecting 2. The UPS guy sometimes puts stuff by the side door. Can you peek out and see if anythin is there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-24 00:48:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yep. One package so far. I'll keep an eye out for the next one.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-24 00:49:11 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Ah, great. Thx! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-24 00:49:35 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>No problem!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-24 20:42:59 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Hope all is well with you and the animals let you sleep until a reasonable hour. Mckenna is dying to know if pyper has warmed up to you yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-03-24 20:45:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>7:30! I feel like that's pretty good for Finn. Pyper is hanging out with us but won't let me pet her yet. I think by tomorrow we will be Bffs.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-24 20:53:32 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>7:30 is great. That's about as late as they ever let us sleep. Aww, pypes. She's gotta be dying for affection. She'll give in soon :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-03-24 20:55:57 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I know me too! Its really hard not to snuggle her! But she's getting there </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

