<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130419.0033" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 01:24:02 UTC">
      <body>Hey Glenn u want me to send u what I get done tonight tomorrow morning or should I just wait til I have a big chunk of it done?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 01:25:44 UTC">
      <body>If it's not a big deal, I'd be curious to see what you did. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 01:30:35 UTC">
      <body>yeah I think its better to keep updating small increments so its easier for me if u wanna change something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 01:31:08 UTC">
      <body>I haven't put it tower of Pisa yet but I must say I really love the castle</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 01:34:35 UTC">
      <body>Ok, if you're really feeling the castle, then let's go with it.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 01:36:29 UTC">
      <body>Its up to you. I couldn't really find a good Pisa tower without tourists in front of it but I only gave it a quick look. I was just trying to get the cuts for second verse today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 01:46:02 UTC">
      <body>I wasn't totally sure about the tower myself, and Jacob said he really liked all the backgrounds you chose, so I'm ok with keeping the castle. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 01:49:46 UTC">
      <body>Cool. I'll get u an update tomorrow morning. I'll most likely be up early and working on it all day. I won't be at work tomorrow. Might be able to wrap it up by end up the weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 01:51:17 UTC">
      <body>Cool, </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 13:22:32 UTC">
      <body>The video didn't process last night so I'll send you a version later today. Sorry bout that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 13:23:33 UTC">
      <body>No problem. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 14:28:25 UTC">
      <body>U guys on Facebook or anything?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 14:39:26 UTC">
      <body>Cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 14:42:47 UTC">
      <body>I'm gonna stop editing for now before I do too much before you see it. I should have a copy for u in a few hours</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132555" time="2013-04-19 21:02:53 UTC">
      <body>Just got a chance to watch it.  Let me watch it again later tonight when I see Jacob, then I'll make some notes.  It's definitely looking good.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 22:18:03 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130747" time="2013-04-19 22:18:36 UTC">
      <body>Im not really in love with the Cadillac. Going to try and find something better still</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="132555" time="2013-04-20 14:56:51 UTC">
      <body>Hey Dan, a few things on the latest edit: I like that the video is fast paced, but I think there might be a bit too much shifting from one image to another in verse 2 (1:12-1:36).  Also, can we get a bit more screen time for the renaissance era?  I defini</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130747" time="2013-04-20 15:00:19 UTC">
      <body>OK so you like less cutting in the second. Yeah I was thinking cut up the dance scene too. And yeah I haven't added the drinks yet. So the modern scenes are cut enough for you aside from adding drinks at end?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="132555" time="2013-04-20 15:05:58 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, a bit less cutting in the second.  And yeah, I think the modern stuff is good, apart from throwing in a few seconds of drinking.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130747" time="2013-04-20 15:08:43 UTC">
      <body>What about end where I have I guys put Ur instruments down and walk away after song stops...keep or cut that out?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="132555" time="2013-04-20 15:09:09 UTC">
      <body>I was trying to come up with some 50's background ideas, but I'm not having much luck with that.  If you YouTube Elvis on the Ed Sullivan show, you'll see he had music notes in the background.  We could maybe do something like that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130747" time="2013-04-20 15:09:55 UTC">
      <body>OK I didn't look at those links u sent yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="132555" time="2013-04-20 15:11:55 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure how useful they'll be.  I just thought maybe we could give the impression of one of those old tv appearances. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130747" time="2013-04-20 15:13:20 UTC">
      <body>I'll take a look</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="130747" time="2013-04-21 01:04:42 UTC">
      <body>Lemme know if you want me to cut down second verse more</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="132555" time="2013-04-21 15:16:39 UTC">
      <body>Hey Dan, I'm really liking this.  The second verse looked good to me, and so did the rest of the video.  One suggestion I have is to find some place where you can put in a very brief clip of the renaissance guys drinking.  This way, for the sake of the st</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130747" time="2013-04-21 15:19:27 UTC">
      <body>OK cool. I will fix up the timing of the cuts send u a version tonight</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
