<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120216.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135117" time="2012-02-16 21:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Have you been able to charge your phone? If so, can we please talk tonight? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2012-02-16 23:40:54 UTC">
      <body>It's charged but I need space. That song was lovely tim, but too much. I'll be in touch.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135117" time="2012-02-16 23:48:18 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I'm sorry I did that. But can we please talk? This is killing me Martha. Be in touch makes me crazy and you've given me no reason to believe it. You owe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135117" time="2012-02-16 23:48:33 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  it to me to answer questions  that you've left unanswered. I'm begging you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-02-16 23:55:53 UTC">
      <body>I can't talk tonight. You can't corner me like that and give me no option.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135117" time="2012-02-16 23:57:32 UTC">
      <body>Corner you to do what? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2012-02-16 23:59:37 UTC">
      <body>To talk. I'm not going to text you back tonight, ok? I have so much to do for school. Im sorry.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135117" time="2012-02-17 00:03:40 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Ok, i understand. I don't mean to corner you. You can always say no. It's just that you keep saying no and I need you to say yes every so often. Or say </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135117" time="2012-02-17 00:04:00 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) anything at all. Thanks for at least telling me you won't text back. I'm sorry I'm being so crazy. I'm trying hard. Good luck with school Mattie </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135117" time="2012-02-17 23:52:39 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Should I assume you're too busy to talk tonight? I'm free tonight, anytime tomorrow, any time the next day etc. I can wait but being ignored hurts a lot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135117" time="2012-02-17 23:52:50 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) . I know you don't want me to text you but I need something to let me know you're not cutting me out entirely </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 05:38:25 UTC">
      <body>Tim I'm not I'm just so fucking busy with work from the end of the school day until now when I get out. Don't push me please</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 05:43:22 UTC">
      <body>I'm really sorry Mattie. Really. I'm proud of you for doing what you're doing and admire it. Hope you get some time to relax.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:17:10 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Hey I'm really sorry about last night. If I would've known I would've let you alone. I'm trying so hard to give you the space you request, but can you p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:17:20 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) lease, as a friend, give me even a general idea of when we can speak? I have uncontrollable anxiety without that prospect. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:18:26 UTC">
      <body>Is this a casual conversation or something more weighty?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:19:28 UTC">
      <body>Why does it matter? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:20:20 UTC">
      <body>Bc I'm totally exhausted and need to know how much energy that I'll be expending so I can plan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:25:01 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Probably both. I want to hear about your life but i also have so many emotions. I don't want to pressure you and if you simply don't want to talk with m</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:25:11 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) e then I'll deal.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:26:47 UTC">
      <body>I just don't know how much help I'll be with some emotions. I don't know if I'm the person to help you and that's a super painful thought which already makes me feel unprepared and emotionally wrecked.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:29:36 UTC">
      <body>What thought? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:29:50 UTC">
      <body>That I can't help you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:36:12 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Cant or don't want to?  you're the only one who might be able to, and I know you can. I'm not expecting you to be able to fix me. But if we can't talk a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:36:22 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) bout this then how can we maintain a friendship? Is that important to you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:42:54 UTC">
      <body>It is important to me. I'll call in an hour or so</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:44:18 UTC">
      <body>I hate the idea that you'd ever feel unprepared to talk to me Mattie. It's just me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:45:03 UTC">
      <body>That last conversation wrecked me for days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="135117" time="2012-02-18 23:49:05 UTC">
      <body>Me too. Actually just a high point in an ongoing wreck. But the thought of not talking wrecks me even more. Please don't fear me. I don't want to hurt you.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131839" time="2012-02-18 23:50:48 UTC">
      <body>It does hurt me though Tim. Quite a bit. There's nothing i can do about your pain right now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131839" time="2012-02-19 00:25:47 UTC">
      <body>Do you want me to call?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131839" time="2012-02-19 00:36:46 UTC">
      <body>Don't ignore me, it'll make me worry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="135117" time="2012-02-19 00:45:28 UTC">
      <body>Believe me I know the feeling. Sorry I was having intense convo with Jon. Of course I do want you to call. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
