<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130522.0084" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:00:29 UTC">
      <body>Salam Fernaz! What's your home address? We'd like to send Sorays a small gift for her graduation!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:02:56 UTC">
      <body>It is a pleasure!! We like her</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132437" time="2013-05-22 16:03:23 UTC">
      <body>:)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:03:36 UTC">
      <body>I am sorry that swath didnt work out and happy that BMC is renewing your contract</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:04:14 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea what's going on at swath now! Khaled isn't the best communicator in the world.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132437" time="2013-05-22 16:07:26 UTC">
      <body>I am partly disappointed that I couldn't get the Swarthmore job but then as I said I know better. He could be making it up. I mean when he says that he really wanted me there. Why he would do that I don't know. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:09:58 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea. He is a hypo! I honestly can't believe anything he says. I left swath and he ever wrote a word to say thanks or just anything:) so if I were you and I was relaxed and comfy in my job at BMC, I would just stay put. Swath is only one year and the pay isn't as good as what you have now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="132437" time="2013-05-22 16:15:03 UTC">
      <body>I am very comfy in BMC and I was worried about losing my slot there since the Swarthmore job was not going to be stable. I was also worried about working with Khalid and his friend...so in many ways it is better that I stay at BMC. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:17:09 UTC">
      <body>Yes, you can apply next year from a solid position! I assume it will be for three years then.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132437" time="2013-05-22 16:18:21 UTC">
      <body>Lets see. So far so good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="137377" time="2013-05-22 16:20:06 UTC">
      <body>Great! I am happy to hear it is resolved</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
