<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121002.0021" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 17:04:00 UTC">
      <body>So my essay will most likely be about Keanu and I was reluctant to show Jordan but I did and he was like I think u shud do a different one etc but I think it's more cus Keanu was his friend and like we weren't close and like everyone else who has read it is like wow that's a great essay and I'm just like joooordaaannn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 17:53:05 UTC">
      <body>So my essay will most likely be about Keanu and I was reluctant to show Jordan but I did and he was like I think u shud do a different one etc but I think it's </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 17:53:08 UTC">
      <body>more cus Keanu was his friend and like we weren't close and like everyone else who has read it is like wow that's a great essay and I'm just like </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 17:53:12 UTC">
      <body>joooordaaannn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 17:53:14 UTC">
      <body>And I'm telling u cus we had similar Keanu situations </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-10-02 18:15:38 UTC">
      <body>I know what you mean. There was an essay here I was gonna write about Keanu. I ended up not doing it though. Can I read it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 18:31:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. I'm handing it in to ms rowley tmrw. I'll send it to u later </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136164" time="2012-10-02 18:44:05 UTC">
      <body>Kk. Rowley is pretty good with college essays</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136203" time="2012-10-02 18:54:56 UTC">
      <body>Good. Yeah so I mean idk you'll see for yourself. It was the one that I found said the most about me but I had a feeling Jordan would dislike it</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
