<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130501.0049" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 12:06:26 UTC">
      <body>Soraya chose Vassar last minute and reluctantly. Where is Lili going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 14:48:39 UTC">
      <body>Omg yesterday it was at Thomas in town today it is Maquette in Milwaukee 
Congratulations on Vassar...she should have no reluctance! She'll be brilliant!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 14:49:08 UTC">
      <body>Tears thrashing and general craziness </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 15:04:13 UTC">
      <body>She had five panic attacks in two days and at one point was honing a kitchen knife!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 15:07:04 UTC">
      <body>She is unhappy with her choice and is considering transfer...40% of the guys at vassar are gay and the rest ugly!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 15:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Wow I wonder who did the stats on that? Is that in the brochure?  If only I could have gone to an elite school like that! And that still means that 60% have potential...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 15:39:40 UTC">
      <body>She was there for two days hanging out with her friends and confirms that there is no potential. The worse part is that the student body is extremely homogenous: they are all "interesting" Suburbanites. Plus the bubble factor and no city... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 15:45:04 UTC">
      <body>That's us too . And that is lilys greatest fear .... On the other hand they are there to be challenged academically and maybe  being around familiar kids helps give them some comfort. I have no idea anymore...maybe you and mark could set up a home school for college people</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 15:52:58 UTC">
      <body>I know that she will thrive in Montreal if she were to go there. I am sad that she had to go for Vassar. Some of the reasons she declined McGill were the need to be very self reliant, huge classes, uncertainty about internship possibilities, distance from home, and perhaps to please mark...I am encouraging her to keep transfer in mind. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 18:50:44 UTC">
      <body>￼Asea and Farnaz 
It's unbelievable 
Farokh is almost done with a 1000 pc puzzle that Asea brought! You can't believe how compacted it is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 18:58:20 UTC">
      <body>Well I'm sure she will bloom where she's plan elated and there's always parties at the other ivy schools where the boyz are!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 19:08:50 UTC">
      <body>She is hoping to visit NYC a lot. She has a very good friend who is going to Barnard... Also junior year abroad, and internships in NYC in the summers... Still I feel miserable that she didn't choose McGill. I don't like the mentality of these small colleges...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 19:11:47 UTC">
      <body>There's always grad school!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 19:29:59 UTC">
      <body>Yes, we have been talking about that too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 19:31:38 UTC">
      <body>But she is so extremely undecided about career/specialty that she doesn't know if she will need to go to grad school</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="137361" time="2013-05-01 19:33:20 UTC">
      <body>She has time to figure that out and no one doesn't want someone from Vassar?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="132437" time="2013-05-01 20:27:46 UTC">
      <body>That is what she is counting on I think </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
