<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130122.0014" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:29:36 UTC">
      <body>FYI. Some of the things Patricia and that meridian book cover are pretty effective in treatment room. I always try to do the EOV points that apply to the condition.  Sp4+pc6 = gold for tons of things. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 13:52:41 UTC">
      <body>Thanks Bob. I would love to talk more about those channels and how you use them. I can tell they're special. I opened the du and dai on a friend with lower back pain and she had no back pain for a day but then it came back.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:54:45 UTC">
      <body>cool that you've been working w them.  I have lots to learn about them (im sure a pro may find my use of them pretty rudimentary) but I have immense respect for them.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 13:56:09 UTC">
      <body>Me too. Double that!  I especially love the four seas. The transporters are more esoteric to me but I love them too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:56:34 UTC">
      <body>If your friends pain is in the 6+ range out of ten she needs multiple treatments in a week.  Also supplement du w corresponding LU points and yaotongxue?  Corresponding Ear spine pts too? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:57:03 UTC">
      <body>Wish I knew more about when to use the accumulation points of the EOV </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 13:57:45 UTC">
      <body>What are the accumulation points?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:58:03 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like U are well on your way to success in clinic. Further ahead than I was in jan of second yr </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 13:58:24 UTC">
      <body>doesn't ea EOV have an accumulation pt?  Kd 8 or 9 etc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 14:13:57 UTC">
      <body>I'm a total mess! Wood is my first within and water must be my second. I feel like I know next to nothing and its all a crap shoot!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 14:38:56 UTC">
      <body>But this feeling is what drives u to be persistent and overcome obstacles.  It will make u a better practitioner.  The downside is the anxiety and self doubt that may overcome u at times. Perhaps recognizing that it can be a positive will help?  Don't for</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 14:41:04 UTC">
      <body>And don't forget that some say anywhere u put the needle will help...and others say intention is paramount...u can't help but do good if u are present for your patients </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131424" time="2013-01-22 15:10:56 UTC">
      <body>And may I add that this is what makes u unique!  Embrace it and use it to your advantage!  Resistance is futile!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 15:13:19 UTC">
      <body>You are correct in every way! Sorry I didn't text back. I'm at work and just sent something out that made a million emails to reply back to!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-01-22 22:58:51 UTC">
      <body>Thanks for your texts today. I love how you acknowledge what may seem like my pitfalls as precious strengths. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131424" time="2013-01-23 03:54:04 UTC">
      <body>Yw.  I'm sure u would do the same.  I think u need to remove that phrase from your vocabulary - "my pitfalls"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130962" time="2013-01-23 13:06:43 UTC">
      <body>Yep you're right! That's why I said what may SEEM like my pitfalls. A fancy workaround. But I was trying to acknowledge that others see aspects of me (or anyone) as purely pointless when I can see the beauty. That's definitely one of my assets. :) How's y</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131424" time="2013-01-23 13:17:52 UTC">
      <body>Very good points. I read that too fast. Nice workaround.  Look at me giving u advice when you got things pretty much together!  Gma not doing super well but Ty for asking.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130962" time="2013-01-23 14:23:20 UTC">
      <body>I still appreciate the support regardless. :) Your advice comes from an understanding of me, which is rare. I will keep you and your grandma and your family in my prayers. It's so good that you are able to be near her when she needs you. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
