<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141025.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-25 23:02:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>That sucks but I'd rather get bad news sooner then later.  Cindy is coming back again on Monday.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-25 23:02:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I want her back there a every couple days until either they bedbugs are gone or we give up &amp; switch to a new exterminator.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-25 23:53:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-26 16:33:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Our dryer is broken just FYI </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-26 16:34:04 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It dries barely and def isn't strong enough to kill bed bugs anymore </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-26 16:34:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:/ sorry to tell you bad need </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-26 16:34:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>*news </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-26 20:36:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also I was bitten 3 times last night :( bc our dryer doesn't dry all the way, and my blankets fell on floor but I couldn't high heat dry them :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-26 20:36:21 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>For now I can go across street to laundromat </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-26 20:37:18 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But just FYI I've been drying my bed linens Every single night on high heat before sleeping (along w having bed totally isolated from walls and on coasters and nothing under it etc ) and that's the only reason i hadn't been bit all along </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-26 20:37:24 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>They're def all over my room </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-10-26 20:37:29 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-10-26 20:38:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Like for the past two months, every single night, I take my entire comforter all pillows all sheets and put through dryer 40 min before going to bed </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-10-26 20:38:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The bites are like, welts </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-10-26 20:38:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm def allergic to them so I'm a good 'tester' I guess lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-10-26 20:39:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(Oh oops! I didn't see that you responded to my first alert concerning the dryer. Carry on...) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-10-26 22:00:48 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Sorry. I just spoke to the appliance guy who is great.  He is was picking up his dad at the airport.  He is going to call me back.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-10-26 22:13:20 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm a little afraid he might not want to come out b/c of the bedbugs. The plumber doesn't want to come back until they are gone.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-10-26 22:28:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I just texted everyone about the bed bugs. No one else has gotten bitten or seen a bed bug in a couple weeks.  They really do like you. Beth said that happens.   They like your blood type or something.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-10-26 22:28:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>
I'm am So So So Fucking sorry you are still getting bitten. So frustrated we can't get them out of your room.  And as I'm sure you are wondering, I'm very much considering replacing Cindy. But obv don't say anything to her or Beth. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

