<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121130.0015" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 19:48:19 UTC">
      <body>Fairleigh tells me that you're planning on taking more classes at bmc than hc next semester. don't do it! It's not worth it! What are you considering taking though?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135080" time="2012-11-30 19:50:06 UTC">
      <body>Haha but they sound so gooood!!! Women's mental health (which is clinical psych) and topics in social history: sexuality in America. It sounds awesome and there are things that sound cool here but not as cool as those...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 19:53:21 UTC">
      <body>Bmc is never worth it. I'm in a really good Spanish class and art history course but it's so annoying going there. The blue bus gets so old haha. But those two classes do seem up your alley. Bethel is teaching Women's history in the us up to 1870 or something next semester.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2012-11-30 19:55:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah Emily was trying to convince me to take it but I'm more interested in current issues and connections to the present, and it seems like ullmans class will do that more...I know the blue bus sucks but I'd also only have class three days a week :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 19:59:24 UTC">
      <body>Oh it's Ullman? I hear she's great from everyone including professors graham and saler. She's Mary Margaret's advisor too so I wouldn't be surprised if she's there. How are things in your life? Haven't seen you in ages.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135080" time="2012-11-30 20:02:18 UTC">
      <body>That's good, I've also only heard good things. :) my life is pretty good! We should get food or something and catch up :) I'm between thesis deadlines for now, it's the weekend, things are good with Anna and my suitemates and everything. :) how are things in your life?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 20:04:02 UTC">
      <body>Wow. That sounds awesome. This semester is incredibly stressful at all times for me but I also am down considerable in my work ethic. Rough life haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135080" time="2012-11-30 20:06:33 UTC">
      <body>Aww that's a bad combination. :/ yeah I hear history thesis is hard...haha :P how are things other than work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 20:08:40 UTC">
      <body>I dont really have things other than work haha. I just hang out with jacob and matt. My life is really boring at the moment. Though I convince marta to have a study beer with me way too often. Bad influence haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135080" time="2012-11-30 20:10:22 UTC">
      <body>Haha that's funny :) I'm sad you're stressed but at least there's alcohol involved!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135268" time="2012-11-30 20:11:49 UTC">
      <body>Always! That's what senior year is about: more work than ever, less work ethic, ans more alcohol haha.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
