<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141126.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-26 23:15:45 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hey!!! HB said hunter probably didn't need to make greens cause there is enough food already so we got some wine!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-26 23:16:23 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>And a pumpkin pie!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-26 23:17:20 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>You guys bring and do whatever you would like. It's always nice having new things added to the table. But I also know hb needs extra hands and she said hunter didn't feel well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-26 23:17:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>But let us know if we can pick anything else up beer, anythingn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-26 23:18:59 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>We aren't picky. Just excited to have everyone together. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-26 23:20:11 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Me too! Hunters been sick and napping so he might give up on his grand plans. Ha. Okay well call us if you need anything! Can't wait!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-26 23:21:26 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha that's fine. I understand. I've had two sick kids. I disinfected everything today. Don't stress over it. Just do me a favor and help hb as best as you can. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-26 23:21:26 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Please </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-26 23:22:42 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yeah we are packing up the dishes tonight and making the oysters in the morning. Hunter is hanging a painting on Friday. I think she was happy your mom came over to help</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-26 23:23:44 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>We only need two now. :-). Don't let her pack any extras. We just set the table. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-26 23:23:44 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yeah I think so too. It was good for her. And my mom. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-26 23:23:44 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yes. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-26 23:24:11 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Only two plates? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-11-26 23:24:20 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Okay I'll make sure.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-11-26 23:28:00 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Thank you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-11-26 23:31:59 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>No problem! Can't wait to see you guys. &lt;3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-11-26 23:42:09 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Omg is it bad I'm pintrest ING how to set a table. Haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-11-26 23:44:54 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hahaha. I love it! I think I've done the same thing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-11-26 23:45:04 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>I don't want to hear hb say it's wrong. And then I got Cesar's saying who cares it's on the table. Haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-11-27 02:54:29 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>How's hb and hunter feeling </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-11-27 02:55:10 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hunter is in bed and HB and I are being chatty! Why are you awake! Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-11-27 02:56:58 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha!  I just sat down. Tell hb...playroom cleaned, bathrooms (yes all) cleaned, floors cleaned, table set, kicthen cleaned, potatoes peeled, turkeys are in the brine.  Yep I'm tired!  Haha. Eating Oreos and drinking milk. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-11-27 02:57:04 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>All that's left is to vacuum. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-11-27 02:57:04 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha I'll go soon. It feels good to sit down. I won't lie I did take a hour break earlier, and I did an orange box for dinner. Haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-11-27 02:57:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>OMG. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-11-27 02:57:35 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>You are amazing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-11-27 02:57:47 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>She says you deserve a good night sleep!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-11-27 02:58:54 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I think you deserved an hour break jeesh!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-11-27 03:03:28 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha. I did have a cup of coffee to recharge. Good thing we are done for tonight. Cesar's dying on me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-11-27 03:05:46 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I lost Hunter an hour ago! I'm glad you guys get some down time tonight. I'm ready to hit the hay myself.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-11-27 03:10:29 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yeah we are headed up in a few. Have a great night. Enjoy hb!  Love ya. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-11-27 03:11:34 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I will its been sooo nice catching up. Have a good night.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-11-27 03:26:29 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-11-27 14:16:55 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Good morning cuz!!!  Update:  Cesar and I are on our way to see grandpa.  Mom and dad have the kids and their list of timelines. Haha mom is trying to figure out what to do and how to get the corn pudding done. Anyways I told her I was pretty sure you guys would cook the oysters at hb and bring it up.  We will be back at 12 to get the turkey on the fryer. It will take 60 minutes for it to cook. Leah, and dad and Iliana will be at the house around 1130!  Mom put her cell phone on so if you guys need her call her and call when you get there. I think that's it. I hope hunter is feeling better. Andrew has a nasty barking cough. So exciting. Good thing i disinfected yesterday and I think I'll do it again tomorrow. HHaha. Love you! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-11-27 14:19:08 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>It's gonna be a sick factory. The oysters take 1 hour and a half from what HB said. We are doing good over here though! Pretty much all ready to go Cept for oysters! Give Cesar's family my love. I'm thinking about them.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2014-11-27 14:19:44 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>  Hahaha. Sounds good. I just wanted you to know if you need to stay there to cook it to give hb some more resting time then please do. I know she's not feeling well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2014-11-27 14:21:23 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yeah she's is stress in but everything is actually really good! I'm just trying to keep her butt in that chair! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2014-11-27 14:21:52 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yes please do!  How do you like her family room?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2014-11-27 14:21:52 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>She shouldn't stress. It's all going to work out!  And it's my job to stress now. Next year I'll do the stuffing. I should of done it this year. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2014-11-27 14:24:00 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Oh I'll do it next year. In 5 years I'll do it all. Everyone can come and eat. Mia will be in school. Haha I'll have time. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2014-11-27 14:24:12 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>What!! You are doing enough!! It's all good. I love the family room! So much space!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2014-11-27 14:26:08 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha. Sounds good. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2014-11-27 14:26:22 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Okay I gotta get these oyster in the oven stat! We will see you very soon</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

