<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120123.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 04:20:12 UTC">
      <body>Where are you?!?!?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 04:20:57 UTC">
      <body>We didn't know u guys were done until just now so we r coming back to butler now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 04:21:29 UTC">
      <body>Okay Regina and I both wet to your room and were turned away by your roommate</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 04:21:57 UTC">
      <body>Turned away?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 04:22:03 UTC">
      <body>Well we r coming back now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 04:22:18 UTC">
      <body>Like she said you weren't there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 04:45:12 UTC">
      <body>Your broken elevator sucks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 04:47:05 UTC">
      <body>Hhahaha yep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:08:36 UTC">
      <body>Bad news bears I have part practice during chapel choir today. Is it still worth it to go of o can only go for 30 minutes at the end?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 19:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Why did you put part prac then? Alex doesn't decide part prac, the part does. Also, te last part prac I went to with you like everyone missed except you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:11:19 UTC">
      <body>I don't make part practice, the part leader does. And just because other ppl miss doesn't mean I can miss!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 19:12:15 UTC">
      <body>You can miss if you have a conflict. Especially one you knew about months before.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:13:42 UTC">
      <body>That's not how we do it we have to have part practice today because we ha problems in rehearsal yeterday and have to learn new split parts because of the ppl who are missing tour an their parts need to be filled</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 19:15:54 UTC">
      <body>You and I both know your arguments don't hold water. I get it that you just don't care about Chapel Choir. Just don't make excuses</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:17:09 UTC">
      <body>It's not that I don't care about chapel choir, it's that lils always comes first for me. If it's a decision between chapel choir and lils rehearsal, it's goin to be lils rehearsal. I have to be more committed to lils.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 19:21:26 UTC">
      <body>Ariana, if you cared a grain of salt about Chapel Choir, you wouldn't have this problem. You literally missed it for nothing this past Sunday. You skip it to sleep. If you told Alex she wouldn't've had rehearsal then. If you told Bailey, she wouldn't have had part prac then. If you tried being responsible you could easily be fully committed to both</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:27:07 UTC">
      <body>I'm the president and can't be fully committed to both. Lils will always come first and chapel choir is something I do because I love the music but it's not something Im going to put before studying or other things I have to get done during the day. I just prioritize it differently than you do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 19:30:50 UTC">
      <body>I don't put it before Nassoons or school, but I tell people if I have a conflict and they work around it. I study so that I don't need the extra hour and a half. This is m point Ariana I have the same conflicts but I work it out. Also, I love you an I'm not arguing for an reason except to try to change you. Just in case you were getting mad at me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 19:33:33 UTC">
      <body>I know it's just not something I'm going to try and make the group work around because it's hard enough to work around everyone else's conflicts as it is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 20:36:14 UTC">
      <body>But your conflicts are just a valid as theirs if not more</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 20:36:38 UTC">
      <body>You can't keep taking them for the team you must be selfish!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 20:41:05 UTC">
      <body>Also come for as long as you can we can walk over juntos</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 22:57:19 UTC">
      <body>No ones here don't come but wait for me to eat please</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 22:57:59 UTC">
      <body>I just walked to Whitman after rehearsal I'm in nitashas room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131821" time="2012-01-23 22:58:20 UTC">
      <body>Cool you guys coming to Wu at 6:30?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131825" time="2012-01-23 22:59:04 UTC">
      <body>No they don't want to leave Whitman but it welcome to join us in Whitman!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131825" time="2012-01-24 15:15:32 UTC">
      <body>Maura and I are about to get breakfast if u want to join!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131821" time="2012-01-24 16:41:32 UTC">
      <body>Hehe too early</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131825" time="2012-01-24 18:03:50 UTC">
      <body>We r getting a quick lunch</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131821" time="2012-01-24 21:13:41 UTC">
      <body>Right now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131825" time="2012-01-24 21:18:04 UTC">
      <body>Haha no that was sent three hours ago!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131821" time="2012-01-24 21:18:24 UTC">
      <body>Oh well sad day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131825" time="2012-01-24 21:18:44 UTC">
      <body>:(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131821" time="2012-01-24 21:19:13 UTC">
      <body>When are you having dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131825" time="2012-01-24 21:41:19 UTC">
      <body>We have rehearsal from 5 to 6 30 so right after then</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
