<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150224.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-25 00:04:27 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Don't stress </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-25 00:04:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You'll do it if it feels right </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-25 00:04:42 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You have nothing to lose though </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-25 00:05:02 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>At the very least, you are rubbing it in her face that someone else hired you lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-25 00:06:24 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Hahahaha yeah I guess I didn't see it that way. I'm just very unclear about what to put. One minute I think I'm supposed to specifically outline everything I would be doing and then the next minute I realize that being specific is premature when I don't even know everything I would be doing and that I can actually be pretty vague in my proposal </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-02-25 00:06:24 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Then of course I flip back to the first thing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-02-25 00:32:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Write both versions and send them to me and maybe I can help you pick?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-02-25 00:33:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I would be specific but preface it with "here are suggested roles I could fill" or something similar </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-02-25 00:34:13 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I think as long as you say that they are suggestions or examples, you are fine </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-02-25 00:34:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And you can be quite specific </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-02-25 00:34:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I think it is best to hand hold and be clear and specific than to err on the side of being too vague </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-02-25 00:44:48 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Okay you're right. That's good advice. I need to just start writing the stupid thing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-02-25 00:44:48 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>I'll send it to you as soon as I'm done. Hopefully Thursday morning </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-02-25 18:46:24 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Read your email -- I'm digging all of those ideas. Also, let's meet up as soon as you get the business cards -- I'm going to Baltimore on March 6th and I would be glad to leave stuff around MICA or wherever I can get to during the weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-02-25 19:11:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes absolutely. That would be perfect. Emailing business card files to fireball today so I will give them to you ASAP</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-02-25 19:12:43 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Great!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-02-25 19:41:17 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Oh also -- today I went ZAKTi, the fitness center that LP is doing the website for, and I asked Pete if he had anyone to write his website content and if he didn't, if I could do it and he said yes! So I can put in my proposal to Mechelle that the website will officially be my first assignment :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-02-25 20:04:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Wait why would that benefit her though?! Wouldn't she want to get paid for that directly? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-02-25 20:05:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>are you telling her that he agreed to hire her (and thereby you) to do the content?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-02-25 20:08:22 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Yes, the second thing. She is having a meeting with him tomorrow where they will discuss the scope of the project. I told Pete to tell her that he is interested in having the content rewritten with the new website as well as new imagery and structure (something that Mechelle had already told me needed to be changed). Then on Friday I'm gonna say that I want to be the new freelance writer and my first project should be ZAKTi. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-02-25 20:09:04 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Mechelle does not have time to write website content. But if I am there, then she can offer it as a new service to people and charge more right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-02-25 20:09:56 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>When she gets paid, she will pay me for writing the content for her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-02-25 20:11:44 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>All I asked Pete is whether he has hired someone else to write his new website content. He has not, so I said that I was going to propose to Mechelle that I should do it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-02-25 20:13:24 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>I'm not trying to screw anyone over lol, I'm just trying to find a new position doing something I'm good at and also taking work off of Mechelle's hands</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-02-25 20:19:33 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>I thought you said this was a good idea! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-02-25 20:27:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oh I mean I think asking her to hire you as a writer of content is good idea yes </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-02-25 20:28:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But asking her client without going through her might make her leery? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-02-25 20:28:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Basically, I would think that speaking to her clients at all without her as mediator would make her uneasy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-02-25 20:29:04 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You kind or went rogue to quote palin haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-02-25 20:29:45 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But you know her and her needs better than I do, I would just assume that all business owners are very very protective of their client connections </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-02-25 20:30:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And scared of the idea of their employees approaching them at all unless it is directly overseen by them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-02-25 20:30:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Not trying to make you worried! I mean, you don't work for her anymore anyway </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-02-25 20:30:46 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So who cares really in the end </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-02-25 20:30:56 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Oh god. Well I think I made it clear to him that all I wanted to know is if he already had someone hired for web content, or if Mechelle would be handling that too. Then I told him that I hadn't talked to her yet at all so he should say anything, but I want to propose that I should be her new content writer and that ZAKTi could be my first project. But I didn't want to put that in my proposal if he already had someone hired, so I just wanted to confirm that it was a possibility.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-02-25 20:30:56 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>*he shouldn't say anything </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-02-25 20:33:04 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Basically I'm trying to make a strong proposal so I asked Pete if I could put this project on my proposal </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-02-25 20:33:04 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>And he said yes, he would be open to rewriting web content. And then the conversation ended </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-02-25 20:33:04 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>I hope that was okay! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-02-25 20:35:12 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>I'm definitely not trying to take the ZAKTi account haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-02-25 20:35:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I am sure it is fine! I wasn't there </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-02-25 20:36:09 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I didn't mean to make you nervous. I am wishing you luck!' </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2015-02-25 20:36:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I ordered the cards </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-02-25 21:19:24 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Haha okay great! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

