<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20111129.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2011-11-29 02:55:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry I missed you yesterday! The last few days have got away from me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 02:57:07 UTC">
      <body>It's ok sweets, I wouldn't have been very pleasant anyways. #transitions #lifefeelsbetterinspanish harlem. How was turkey? Feel good to be home?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2011-11-29 02:59:55 UTC">
      <body>Oh were you sad to go back? New ulm is so comfortable.... I was just talking about that today. In having a hard time focusing having not been there for the holiday. My holiday was ok... I got sick! But Boston was great.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:01:39 UTC">
      <body>Actually the opposite - it's only comfortable when I had the house to myself for the whole day. It's really hard for me to find flow with family and the communi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:02:31 UTC">
      <body>Ty and then I got in a fight with my dad. So it feels better just staying here to be honest. But the IDEA of nu is comforting - just changes everytime I go </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2011-11-29 03:06:33 UTC">
      <body>Yea, it's not about flow really just it being a bubble. I know what you mean. What were you fighting with your dad about?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:10:47 UTC">
      <body>About how I'm discontent with our relationship but then it just got hurtful - It just didn't end very well and it felt really isolating. I talked to tyler and </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:11:29 UTC">
      <body>Brett about it and I'm feeling better about everything. I think at this point we're all going through that adjustment with our rents :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2011-11-29 03:14:03 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry, pat. It is that time in our life but you don't deserve to be hurt.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:16:30 UTC">
      <body>It's good to hear that because so often I feel like I have to fight to prove my own pain because they think it's incomprehensible since I had such a nice </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:17:06 UTC">
      <body>Upbringing. But what he failed to recognize is that I'm discontent with the present, not the past. Life life life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131839" time="2011-11-29 03:25:11 UTC">
      <body>Yea, feelings are valid etc :) maybe it'll sink in later. How did you leave it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135093" time="2011-11-29 03:30:04 UTC">
      <body>There wasn't really closure - I just kinda withdrew. He called today to apologize. The space and time has already did me good :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
