<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141209.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-09 03:59:14 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Hey, we need a licensed contractor to give an estimate for loan purposes in the near future and then do some work in late Jan/early Feb. Would you be do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-09 03:59:25 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>wn for that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-09 13:02:35 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> I'm not really doing construction any more. I could see if Michael will do it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-09 18:04:04 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Yeah, that could be good. We're looking at trying to stick to a pretty tight timeline; is he pretty prompt with stuff? Also, I don't have his contact info.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-09 18:05:18 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> It depends on how busy he is but winter is usually less busy. I'll contact him first</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-09 18:06:03 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>What kind of work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-09 18:11:15 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-09 18:11:58 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>He said he could do thursday or Friday or possibly this weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-09 18:12:25 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Sounds good. We have a master bedroom that still has plaster and , whereas </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-09 18:13:16 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Sorry, didn't mean to send that. More proper text coming.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-12-09 18:15:09 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>We have a master bedroom that still has plaster and several coats of wallpaper that's falling off, whereas the rest of the house has been redone with dr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-09 18:16:15 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>ywall. So we'd like to update the bedroom to match the rest of the house.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-09 18:17:21 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> Ok, I'm not sure if he's going to want to do that job or not, but he can give you a licensed estimate anyway</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-09 18:26:04 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Gotcha. We'd prob want the person doing the job to do the estimate just for continuity. If he's not interested, do you know someone who might be more in</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-12-09 18:26:14 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>to something like that? If not we can look up some people our realtor might know about.@</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-09 18:27:44 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Gonna be hard to find someone who's licensed to do a tiny demo and drywall job. He might do it. Just ask</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-12-09 18:29:06 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I would say Adam cooper but he's not licensed and has a full time job now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-12-09 18:30:02 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Or Michael may know of a drywall contractor that's licensed or be able to get subs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-12-09 18:30:25 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Yeah, needs to be licensed cuz i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-12-09 18:33:49 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>U can check Angie's list too.  Check with Michael. I shouldn't speak for him whether he wants to do it or not. I just know that I wouldn't want to do it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-12-09 22:15:21 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Sounds good. Can I get his contact info or could you give him mine?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-12-09 23:24:45 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I already sent it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-12-09 23:25:31 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-12-09 23:27:33 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Sent my info to him, or sent me his info via email?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-12-09 23:31:42 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Sorry I didn't realize that you can't forward contacts to non iPhones</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-12-09 23:33:16 UTC" participant="149363">
      <body>Yes, my phone is special. Still haven't gotten on the smartphone wave. Thx! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

