<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130528.0017" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 12:01:55 UTC">
      <body>Yo, whats goin on?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:05:14 UTC">
      <body>in right now, then pick up later for more. That ok with u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:05:14 UTC">
      <body>Hi, rhosymedre! I'm sittin' at my desk tryin' to work, and trying to get my typing right on this gadget (frustration). I figure I can chat for about 15m</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:14:51 UTC">
      <body>the time.)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:15:25 UTC">
      <body>Or bits &amp; pieces scattered thru the day Is something else that I would find OK. (I didn't start this trying for a rhyme But this just happens to me all</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 12:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Yea of course, its whatevers easiest for you im kinda busy myself. Sorry it took so long to respond by the way, i was just grabbing lunch real quick.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:25:23 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. I was on hold w an insurance Co on the phone when yr latest txt came in. (Nothing bad, just changing some info) Good thing abt text chat is that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:26:08 UTC">
      <body>it doesn't have to be instant, as long as both people agree.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 12:48:07 UTC">
      <body>Yea totally. Its pretty chill, albeit really impractical when you think about it. As much as i love texting i try to avoid it whenever possible, especia</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 12:48:56 UTC">
      <body>lly when i have something important to say</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:57:31 UTC">
      <body>e links that are better written than spoken, and better pasted than typed. And of course there's hardmail, on paper.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 12:58:09 UTC">
      <body>Makes sense to me. F2f or voice 2 voice (phone or Skype) for interaction. Email for important details I want to review &amp; check b4 sending, or things lik</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 17:14:42 UTC">
      <body>What a headache! My desk computer's external backup disk here at work has been occasionally deciding not to work. One of our Systems guys has been comin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 17:23:10 UTC">
      <body>g over and getting it running again. Now it says "Cannot repair backup disk. Back up all your files as well as you can, reformat this backup drive, and</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 17:23:10 UTC">
      <body>back them up here."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 17:23:10 UTC">
      <body>While I was writing that, he got it fixed. Now "Backing up 1,012,802 items." Jeez Louise.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 17:23:10 UTC">
      <body>So, back to the job till I llea e at 6. "Leave"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:02:47 UTC">
      <body>Sitting in a theater while my friend's band gets ready for a recording session. I felt I needed some relaxation &amp; music (my drug of choice, I call it).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:02:47 UTC">
      <body>I've got the phone silenced, so I can still text chat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:05:00 UTC">
      <body>Oh - I may have to turn it off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:08:21 UTC">
      <body>ive been having problems with and is already a month late got deleted off the server, so i had to apologise to my professor and start the project comple</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:08:21 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool, do what you gotta do. Sorry i havent been very chatty, today has been really taxing for me :/ my mum is selling the house and while moving fu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:17:04 UTC">
      <body>rniture my granddad broke my bookshelf, which is really upsetting for me because my father and i built it from scratch. Then i find out my project that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:17:04 UTC">
      <body>tely over for the nth time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:25:44 UTC">
      <body>Holy mackerel, that's a load of headaches! (Yr txts came in as a bunch of fragments &amp; I had to figure our their order - not yr fault)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:28:43 UTC">
      <body>g. Hows your friends recording session?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 20:28:43 UTC">
      <body>Its all good. Its just been a long day. Im finishing up with some stuff and then my guy and i are prolly gonna head home and play videogames or somethin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:30:06 UTC">
      <body>They're just doing sound checks.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 20:33:31 UTC">
      <body>Now they've started. WOW!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 22:29:46 UTC">
      <body>what band if you dont mind my asking?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130583" time="2013-05-28 22:49:26 UTC">
      <body>I've just been enjoying / enjoyed by a large lapful of purrrr. Σ:•X3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131016" time="2013-05-28 23:32:28 UTC">
      <body>I only got like half of that haha. My guy and i are eating icecream and playing kingdom hearts, its really chill</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130583" time="2013-05-29 00:32:32 UTC">
      <body>English, Ladino, and Arabic, their music sings the celebration, emotion, and spirituality of Jewish texts, bringing listeners along on a musical journe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130583" time="2013-05-29 00:33:19 UTC">
      <body>Jessi Roemer &amp; Sonic Theology Melaveh Malkah Concert Jessi Roemer and Sonic Theology perform fresh, original Jewish music rooted in Sephardic, Ashkena</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130583" time="2013-05-29 00:33:19 UTC">
      <body>y of the soul!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130583" time="2013-05-29 00:33:19 UTC">
      <body>zi, Middle Eastern, and North American styles. Sweet, sinuous melodies and lively drum rhythms inspire the body and move the spirit! In Hebrew, Yiddish,</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130583" time="2013-05-29 00:33:19 UTC">
      <body>And with that… Good night zzzzzz</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
