<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130406.0029" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 14:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Ready for clinic!?!  starts in a few weeks, right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:06:46 UTC">
      <body>I'm going to go with YES I Am!!! (Why not rock it/be confident?) I think soliciting patients is he scariest part. Do you have suggestions on how you did that? My issue (besides not feeling as confident about my skill set/me at this point) is that most peo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:07:36 UTC">
      <body>You're a really nice cheerleader btw. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:08:40 UTC">
      <body>koala AND the thumbs up AND the heart?!  Wow.  I'm flabbergasted </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:09:13 UTC">
      <body>You're sweet! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:14:13 UTC">
      <body>Not much advice on the solicitation for the same reasons u say.   Don't trust Eds expertise as a marketing person.  I think the clinic should have a sandwich board outside w balloons - Ed didn't think it would work but it worked really well when we had ou</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:14:38 UTC">
      <body>Not sure if that would count as a solicited patient though </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:20:12 UTC">
      <body>Ooh I like it! I'm doing clinic Saturday morning and it will be 5 of my classmates plus 3 seniors. Good idea. I made a blog/website too. Can I send it to you for feedback? I just want to get ok now with getting patients bc I plan to do private practice wh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:25:20 UTC">
      <body>great re Saturdays.  In some cases u won't even have to sell yourself. Just being in room. Smiling. Getting water when assisting is all it takes.  At end of semester u can ask if u can give them your card (write name on it w clinic shifts for fall). 
Sure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Don't forget that most authorities' just know a few hairs more than the ppl in the audience. U already have that.  Plus u have passion. It can be contagious </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:26:57 UTC">
      <body>Won should have classes where we work on elevator speech. Answer questions etc </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 15:27:19 UTC">
      <body>U will learn to wing that in clinic and fine tune your lingo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:45:51 UTC">
      <body>Yes there should be a class where we practice elevator speech. Totally!!! I've done that a few times and need to work on language for different people.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:47:22 UTC">
      <body>I'm not worried about people knowing more than me as much as I just don't know how I would make a presentation that appalled to multiple people and didn't fail? Maybe I will do something about the changing if the seasons or something related to Acu that w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:48:21 UTC">
      <body>You did a presentation on stress and Acu? Where did you do that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 15:48:44 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:06:15 UTC">
      <body>U can't outguess everyone's reasons for coming. In most cases acu they are just curious.   Do what interests u and whatever u do do it well.  Whatever u do there may be questions like does it hurt. How big are needles etc. be ready for those. 
Did stress </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:08:32 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I answered ur question well but I tried.  Don't feel u have to do everything in April and may. Perhaps getting feel for clinic is best start then expand ur marketing efforts in fall.  U also can't control that someone who likes your presenta</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:21:16 UTC">
      <body>You know I will do it well when I do it! I actually really like your reminder to not do it all in April and May. Getting settled first might be more important/make more sense. :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:21:48 UTC">
      <body>Ed is not the person to learn marketing from! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:25:02 UTC">
      <body>I totally know that u will do it well!   Let the others spaz while u settle in study. Observe, practice the talk etc. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:26:33 UTC">
      <body>Ed may teach u things in clinic but outside?  Hmmmm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:27:44 UTC">
      <body>I shouldn't say that.  U an learn from Anyone w experience even if its just to get insight as to how others think and expose yourself to that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:28:11 UTC">
      <body>"May" :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:29:31 UTC">
      <body>lol.  Ed goes in phase where he is in teacher mode and when he is in passive "tell me how that makes u feel" bs mode.  He is supportive as a supervisor and he will respect u cuz I know u will study and have rationale for your treatments </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:29:32 UTC">
      <body>Don't apologize. I'm smiling and I completely understand. Also I don't think that you are a jerk. I can't stand Eds needle class. I don't get it at all. There's no technique covered ever. No ergonomics or anything.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:31:00 UTC">
      <body>it's just a good place to practice.  Hate to say this but u have to teach yourself a lot at the won. Don't rely on them.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:31:23 UTC">
      <body>I think u will like Donna </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:31:39 UTC">
      <body>Yes I probably will like Donna. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:31:47 UTC">
      <body>Watching Ed needle ears hurts MY back </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:31:52 UTC">
      <body>I know the teach yourself us good and bad.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:32:00 UTC">
      <body>U are still a fawn.  Do I have one of those in my bag?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:32:12 UTC">
      <body>You should see me needle. It's a mess so far but will get better.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:32:36 UTC">
      <body>Yes Ed is moody/has phases. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:33:28 UTC">
      <body>It's really weird to watch at times. You never know which Ed you will get.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:33:38 UTC">
      <body>Nope no deer or fawn </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:33:46 UTC">
      <body>Lol. True </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:34:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know! I guess no deer in Japsn hence no emojis!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:34:28 UTC">
      <body>I like being a baby deer.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:42:40 UTC">
      <body>exactly!  Tough for them to migrate to islands </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:42:40 UTC">
      <body>Don't take this the wrong way but if u ever became a stripper u could use Bambi  as your stage name </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:42:40 UTC">
      <body>Excuse me. Adult entertainer </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:55:26 UTC">
      <body>I already have a drag queen stage name: Madonnica. When I'm really naive some people call me Moronica.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:56:22 UTC">
      <body>And last time I was with my teacher in NYC she saw what a little snobby princess I can be. I was prancing around in a dress she said reminded her of a baton twirler or ice dancer.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:56:58 UTC">
      <body>So then recently I gave myself a princess name fit for a prissy but daydreamy and sometimes smug metal cf.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:57:29 UTC">
      <body>Are you ready??? Only three people have heard it so far. It's perfect: Princess Shit Cloud. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:57:37 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 16:57:43 UTC">
      <body>❤❤</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 16:59:44 UTC">
      <body>Lmao. Love those names!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:01:01 UTC">
      <body>Add to the mix: Bambi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 17:01:35 UTC">
      <body>Bambi is so lame and non creative compared to those.  Scratch it off list </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:01:45 UTC">
      <body>Tho I already had a stripes name. It's your first pet plus the street you lived on as a child. That makes me: Peaches Twilight!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 17:01:47 UTC">
      <body>U are well in control of your alter egos</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:01:58 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:02:38 UTC">
      <body>Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:03:12 UTC">
      <body>If you can think of a name for me when I'm in pity party mode, that's a me I haven't named yet!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 17:19:29 UTC">
      <body>I won't give her a name. I just want to put her in basket and put her in the river </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 17:38:08 UTC">
      <body>lol. Yes. No room for her here :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:38:27 UTC">
      <body>To float away forever?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:45:28 UTC">
      <body>You're gonna need a BIG basket!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:46:18 UTC">
      <body>Can I get Chinese class and Ethics with Ed (is there a book??) and Counseling with Helen books from you sometime?? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:47:11 UTC">
      <body>Also can I feed you tiny cakes or something yummy someday after a Sunday PCA shift? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 17:49:27 UTC">
      <body>I already have those books set aside from u.  No need to pay me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 17:51:10 UTC">
      <body>Ok. Let me know when you bring them in. We have till May so no rush!! I am over buying books I don't really need. I have enough books from my English major days!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:01:36 UTC">
      <body>Want me to leave at PCA? I think u have class Thursday nights right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:03:37 UTC">
      <body>I am home at 7 on most Thursdays but not this one. Going to a restaurant called Yang Ming!!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:03:44 UTC">
      <body>cool.  Big date?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:03:44 UTC">
      <body>3-7. Usually out by 7:30ish</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:03:44 UTC">
      <body>Aaaah. Cool </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:03:59 UTC">
      <body>What time do you work Thursdays?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:04:22 UTC">
      <body>Date with my classmates. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:07:01 UTC">
      <body>Maybe the next Thursday I could pick up the books and say hi to you!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:19:26 UTC">
      <body>cool.  Whatever works for u.  Pls Make sure u remind me the day before </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:20:04 UTC">
      <body>I will gladly do that. It will be nice to see your sweet face! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:35:44 UTC">
      <body>And nice to see your spleen deficient student self </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:38:32 UTC">
      <body>Pooping solid my friend! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="131424" time="2013-04-06 18:48:32 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="130962" time="2013-04-06 18:50:57 UTC">
      <body>I feel so good finally! Bob W recommended a different probiotic brand--Sedona--and it's amazing!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 01:34:31 UTC">
      <body>Can I please send you this most amazing video? A friend sent it from a wedding. The wedding singer did everything from Eric Clapton to Vanilla Ice. His Beyonce costume is the tiny thong. Love it. ￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 02:42:05 UTC">
      <body>What the...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 02:56:40 UTC">
      <body>I watched it five times. It is so random and weirdly joyous. Humans giving other humans permission to gyrate. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 02:57:04 UTC">
      <body>I know u watched it at least six times and are trying to book him for your WON graduation party</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:01:02 UTC">
      <body>Oh shit that would be the best! Evidently Janet does karaoke really well. I left the Xmas party too soon...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 03:01:20 UTC">
      <body>no. I can't imagine that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:01:25 UTC">
      <body>I want him at the won graduation!!! Can you imagine?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:02:31 UTC">
      <body>How much do you think it would cost to get him here from Rhode Island??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 03:03:19 UTC">
      <body>With or without the thong?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 03:03:28 UTC">
      <body>I'm thinking August is high demand wedding time. It will be tough to get him here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 03:03:28 UTC">
      <body>Yes lmto</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:03:39 UTC">
      <body>Lmao for real!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:03:55 UTC">
      <body>Or Lmto!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:04:39 UTC">
      <body>Boo!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="131424" time="2013-04-07 03:05:36 UTC">
      <body>But w 15 months to practice I'm sure u can find someone in ur class to do similar show.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:05:51 UTC">
      <body>There is something fabulously wrong with me. I have watched that video 8 times! And I swear god it gets more surprising and funny each time!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:06:33 UTC">
      <body>I hope so!!! Six people so far have put a cat photo into a presentation for me!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:06:44 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="130962" time="2013-04-07 03:07:56 UTC">
      <body>Do you love texting this much? You really are prolific once I get you going!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
