<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140905.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-05 20:45:04 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I'm nervous. From the sudden silence after my text, did those biznitches say happy birthday? Cause I'll cut em if they didn't.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-05 20:47:32 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I didn't receive anything from that group message since my data is temporarily turned off. So I don't know what was said!  Phuong texted last night. Sam did just now.  Haha. Thanks for having my back :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-05 20:49:11 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Sam said that she was able to do something this weekend and Phuong said something like yeah we should. I just said I assumed we'd be doing something for your bday.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-05 20:52:34 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Oh. Ok. I guess we'll see then. It just sucks that it's supposed to be so humid tomorrow like today and it might rain. Sunday's going be beautiful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-05 20:54:20 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Have you ever been to Soho Wings?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-05 21:10:02 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Can't say that I have. Sorry. I think my sister has.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-05 21:11:47 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Oh that's ok. They're really good. But it's out near Glenside. It was a thought if we didn't know where to go if did go out. But I'm not sure if I'm really in the mood for them anyway. But we need go sometime!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-05 21:12:07 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>My sister said and I quote, "deliciouuuuussss"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-05 21:12:20 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. Yes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-05 21:15:18 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I hope we can just stay indoors this weekend. It will be way too hot. I can't deal with all of this. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-05 21:17:11 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I know. I hear you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-05 21:40:28 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hold on, whys your data off?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-05 21:43:08 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I only get 300mb a month. We stayed at Michelle's last weekend to watch shadow and Michael used my phone to watch YouTube. Then left it running in the background all night. So it used up 90% of my data. So I have until the fifteenth until I can turn it back on so I'm not charged $20.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-05 21:43:42 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Ohhhhh I see!! That sucks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-05 21:43:57 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yup.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-05 22:48:35 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Would you maybe want to do lunch on Sunday and hang out for a little? I don't want to pitch the idea if you don't want to do it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-09-05 23:03:20 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I sort of just wanted to take it easy on Sunday and prepare for work. You know how I get. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-09-05 23:04:35 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay! Not a problem. I'm the same way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-09-05 23:05:20 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>So tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-09-05 23:06:39 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I guess so.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-09-05 23:09:02 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>We can always do it another time, but I won't be able to go next Saturday (Courtney's visiting) or the following weekend (mikes birthday) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-09-05 23:12:28 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. It's ok. However it works out Its fine. I'm actually not really into my birthday this year for some reason. It's not a big deal. We shall see how tomorrow goes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-09-05 23:13:42 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

