<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140428.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-04-28 19:16:16 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Gabi I'm stressing about all the spelling errors and the name thing but I don't want to upset anyone because I can see how much work it was. I think Phinn is going to die that his name is misspelled. We can't do anything right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-04-28 19:19:40 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I sent spelling corrections to all of those last night!  I just messaged lois about it again too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-04-28 19:20:32 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>I'm kind of freaking. I hate all this rushing and with spelling errors it looks so unprofessional. And OMG Phinns name spelled wrong that will kill him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-04-28 19:22:56 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Did she send it to the printer? She hasnt responded yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-04-28 19:23:33 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>I don't know. I'm at work are you? If not can you call her?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-04-28 19:24:28 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Im at work for another hour too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-04-28 20:47:37 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Its too late! Theyre already printing them.  I liked it in red and now it looks like a green mountain cabaret poster</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-04-28 20:55:24 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Fuck. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-04-28 20:56:12 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>We'll have to compensate with an amazing show. I'm a little upset we had no chance to give feedback and it wasn't proof read! Hopefully Phinn won't die</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-04-28 21:22:14 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I think maybe what we saw was not the final draft, she said today in an email that she took the names off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-04-28 21:22:47 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>They're on because she just asked me to email the cast explaining why they're on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-04-28 21:22:50 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>:(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-04-28 21:24:05 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Poop</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-04-28 21:29:05 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>And what do we say to that? I asked richard's opinion when lois first brought up names on the poster, he didnt think the cast would be offended by it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-04-28 21:29:51 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Good. I'm trying to let it go. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

