<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130311.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 12:44:30 UTC">
      <body>Hey Dan, it's meg this is my number (still 717!) I will let you know if I make it to the county any time soon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 13:29:52 UTC">
      <body>Cool. I can't have my phone at work (they fire people for it). Only at breaks. The joys of pharmaceutical companies </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 15:56:58 UTC">
      <body>I imagine you to be a good mom. You have the right personality for it. Me, no kids. I never really grew up. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 16:35:34 UTC">
      <body>I try! Kids are really challenging. I don't always feel totally grown up either. Like this week for example, I'm on spring break!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 16:36:45 UTC">
      <body>Ha! I sometimes eat cookies for dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 16:38:33 UTC">
      <body>That's one tough thing about kids, you can never flake on food. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 16:39:13 UTC">
      <body>Her mind would explode if we shared a box of cookies for dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 19:15:50 UTC">
      <body>It's amazing I'm an adult</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 19:21:10 UTC">
      <body>Being married is pretty adult</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 19:30:20 UTC">
      <body>You've never seen us together;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 19:32:20 UTC">
      <body>That's awesome : ) punk rock love</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 20:39:35 UTC">
      <body>speaking of punk rock love...why no love for your duke st apt? I have great memories there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130716" time="2013-03-11 21:26:51 UTC">
      <body>Oh to be young and dumb again. Haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 21:36:55 UTC">
      <body>Totally.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 10:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Where is philly are you? We did the philly naked bike ride in august. We also like going to new harmony or kingdom. Haven't been on south st in years</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 11:08:21 UTC">
      <body>We live in west philly on Baltimore avenue. I was supposed to ride my bike to manyunk today but just woke up to downpour. I have an old paramount that I got in Seattle a few years ago. I heart my bike : )</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 13:28:03 UTC">
      <body>Do you ever see the fresh prince?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 13:32:42 UTC">
      <body>I ride to work when possible. Usually when I'm within a 15mile radius but I've been 105miles from home for a while now. It's crappy but I have a 4person carpool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 15:07:48 UTC">
      <body>Nah the fresh prince moved somewhere on the west coast. I see a mural including him under the el tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 15:09:41 UTC">
      <body>105 miles! Where are you going? I was riding my bike to Bryn Mawr but the route was gnarly, Lancaster ave turns into 40mph right when the bike lane disappears. I might start doing it again in the spring tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 16:01:48 UTC">
      <body>I'm working in danville at a pharmaceutical plant. Probably until may unless I find something closer sooner. Kinda tired of waking up at 3:45. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 16:02:41 UTC">
      <body>Especially now that the weather will be getting nicer. I only worked 4 months last year so I guess I should just be happy to be working...right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 18:39:26 UTC">
      <body>Dan works at Danville. Yeah work is work. I haven't worked since I got to Bryn Mawr because it is so tough there, but I know one day I will have to look for a job again and hate it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 19:16:50 UTC">
      <body>Working is for suckers. Does he work at the hospital? Who is this dan fellow?  He has a nice name</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 19:20:17 UTC">
      <body>It is quite nice, I'm not sure how it is pronounced tho. Dahhhhhnnn? Who knows. I want to go to grad school for maritime archaeology so hopefully when I am all done I will get a job on a boat and never step on dry land again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 22:25:12 UTC">
      <body>I'm pretty sure your legs are far too long to be on a boat. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130664" time="2013-03-12 22:50:13 UTC">
      <body>I could touch the bottom even in the ocean. Spider girl </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130716" time="2013-03-12 22:59:17 UTC">
      <body>I bet you could. I'd like to see that actually</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 10:35:23 UTC">
      <body>What's your drink of choice these days?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 15:23:59 UTC">
      <body>In the next few minutes it will be a coffee and a fresh squeezed orange juice. If I'm at the bar it's usually an IPA and or whiskey. Or champagne and St. Germaine, or really anything.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 15:59:54 UTC">
      <body>I'm not into most ipas. Back in Black is pretty good but I prefer porters and stouts</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:07:25 UTC">
      <body>I like iced cream floats made from porters or stouts</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 16:09:06 UTC">
      <body>Genesis milkshakes at isaacs made by zach (the gay bartender) are the best. I love those on a summer evening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:11:07 UTC">
      <body>Yum I've never had one, sounds good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:11:39 UTC">
      <body>I love so many different drinks on a summer evening. Jalapeño margaritas are good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 16:12:25 UTC">
      <body>I'm also into absinthe. Have you ever tried it?  It's about 140 proof</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:15:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I actually drank a lot of it that my friend brought home from Denmark and then we went to a roller skating party, it was amazing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 16:23:05 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm...let me know if you want some when your in town. I love setting it up. It's almost like a religious event</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:36:03 UTC">
      <body>Should I bring a sacrificial goat?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 16:37:43 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. Probably not. We can build a fire and dance around it instead</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 16:39:23 UTC">
      <body>Sounds perfect! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 19:39:38 UTC">
      <body>Ok...I'll leave it at that. Just say when</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 19:51:54 UTC">
      <body>I'll have to find a place that I can build a fire too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 20:01:47 UTC">
      <body>Oh I thought you had a firepit in your backyard haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 20:03:02 UTC">
      <body>I'll make one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 21:33:49 UTC">
      <body>Actually my yard is pretty small so maybe we'll have to go to the park and use one of the bbq pits</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 22:16:06 UTC">
      <body>My boyfriend has a pretty sweet firepit in his backyard, maybe u guys just have to come to philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 23:26:08 UTC">
      <body>I hear that. I've been listening to a lot of witch and sleep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 23:29:30 UTC">
      <body>Tis the time of the year. But now that spring is coming, I want to listen to Simon and garfunkle haha all over the place</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 23:31:43 UTC">
      <body>Don't get me wrong, I have my jack johnson/josh ritter moments</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130664" time="2013-03-13 23:32:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm past making excuses, the heart wants what the heart wants. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="130716" time="2013-03-13 23:34:20 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure if truer words have ever been spoken (errr...texted)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 13:27:49 UTC">
      <body>How long have you two been together?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 13:29:27 UTC">
      <body>Not very long, since last summer. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 13:36:24 UTC">
      <body>That's cool. Staci and I have been together since 2001. Married in 09</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 13:38:04 UTC">
      <body>Remember makeoutclub.com? That's how we met</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 13:40:57 UTC">
      <body>Wow!! That is crazy. I forgot all about that site. You guys are a totally solid couple! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 13:42:37 UTC">
      <body>We've had our problems but we've learned from them. We are not a typical couple in many ways...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 13:48:04 UTC">
      <body>It's awesome that you have figured out how to make it work. There's no such thing as typical couples, right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 13:50:29 UTC">
      <body>Well we are more liberal than most</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 13:51:27 UTC">
      <body>What does that mean?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 15:58:11 UTC">
      <body>We have a special agreement</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 16:01:39 UTC">
      <body>So cryptic. Well, whatever works. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 16:02:52 UTC">
      <body>We have an open relationship. We have rules. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 16:06:00 UTC">
      <body>That's realistic. It's hard to be with only one person. But deception sucks, so that's really the only way to do it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 16:09:09 UTC">
      <body>We have to know where the other is when they are with someone else. She does better than me (not that I'm keeping score) but that's nature of men and women</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 16:29:51 UTC">
      <body>Are you still there? Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 17:02:30 UTC">
      <body>Sorry, I'm really hung over and just left bed to eat. So you think it's easier for women? But women outnumber men. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 19:16:28 UTC">
      <body>I think its easier for a married women to find a guy that will date her than vice versa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 19:37:26 UTC">
      <body>Most women don't want to get involved with someone that is attached (unless you go to swing clubs but we aren't club people though we do belong to one)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 22:52:42 UTC">
      <body>That kind of makes sense. Relationships are sort of a hassle. But it's nice to have someone to go to things like weddings with and have some one take care of you when you are sick. Without those perks I wouldn't bother forming relationships haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 22:54:53 UTC">
      <body>Plus you picked a pretty conservative town to have a progressive lifestyle Hans</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="130664" time="2013-03-14 22:55:02 UTC">
      <body>Hans=haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="130716" time="2013-03-14 23:00:34 UTC">
      <body>Its not the easiest place to live this life but jobs in other towns are hard to find</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="130716" time="2013-03-15 00:32:40 UTC">
      <body>I had a friend that once she found out she stopped talking to me. I'm not a pervert (mostly). I respect boundaries. It's not like I get on anything that moves</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="130716" time="2013-03-15 00:33:52 UTC">
      <body>I've actually only had naked fun with 2 other women in the 12 years we've been together. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="130664" time="2013-03-15 00:57:07 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, my friend once said that in Lancaster you would be crucified if you slept with one person on Tuesday and another on Sunday. I've had a lot of crazy experiences, so it's hard for me to judge anyone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="130716" time="2013-03-15 01:36:46 UTC">
      <body>I don't care if a guy wants to marry a guy. A hunter wants to shoot their dinner. Etc. As long as I can live my life as I want. Obviously laws are important for</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="130716" time="2013-03-15 01:37:23 UTC">
      <body>Everybody's rights</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="130716" time="2013-03-15 13:36:45 UTC">
      <body>I'm a live and let live kind of guy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="130716" time="2013-03-17 15:33:36 UTC">
      <body>Jameson and french toast with bailey's maple syrup </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="130664" time="2013-03-17 15:36:07 UTC">
      <body>Whoa! Wasted breakfast! I just had egg in a hole with humboldt fog and roasted butternut squash and yogurt</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="130716" time="2013-03-17 18:02:48 UTC">
      <body>I just slepft off my breakfast</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="130664" time="2013-03-17 19:11:25 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's a breakfast that requires a nap</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="130716" time="2013-03-17 19:45:04 UTC">
      <body>I was a bit tipsy. Kind of ruined my plans for the day. Wanted to ride around...getting fat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="130664" time="2013-03-17 19:50:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah day drinking always seems like a fun way to start the day but it always ruins my plans</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="130716" time="2013-03-18 19:26:13 UTC">
      <body>My insurance in $960 a month and is going up to $990 in may. Whatev! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="130716" time="2013-03-18 19:26:35 UTC">
      <body>Tell me something fun...it's just been a no good, rotten day. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="130716" time="2013-03-18 21:12:32 UTC">
      <body>I had to put out a fire! Finally, after 15years all that firewatch training paid off. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="130664" time="2013-03-18 21:23:29 UTC">
      <body>Ugh that is awful. I am so stressed out. Too many things due this week. Where was the fire?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 02:23:37 UTC">
      <body>At work. Ironworkers were torching some steel and some cardboard caught fire</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="130664" time="2013-03-19 03:18:59 UTC">
      <body>Yikes! Dan to the rescue. I'm trying to formulate a debate suggesting that the Elgin marble should stay in the British museum and not be returned to Greece. It's hard to do without sounding racist</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 11:40:53 UTC">
      <body>Is that what you really believe should happen? Or were you told to argue that side?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="130664" time="2013-03-19 11:43:32 UTC">
      <body>No it's just the assignment. I used their financial crisis against them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 11:46:53 UTC">
      <body>It's tough to agrue a point you don't truly believe. I was going to say about the $$. I called off today. It took me 4.5hrs to get home last night. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="130664" time="2013-03-19 11:48:32 UTC">
      <body>Whoa! So overtime and a four and a half hour commute? I would call off too. What are you going to do instead of work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 11:57:18 UTC">
      <body>I need to start working out again. I've been in a rut since I started working again. There is so much to do when I get home because Staci works until 7:30</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 12:00:16 UTC">
      <body>5 cats, 2 dogs, and frankie the have to get fed. Dogs walked. I do the dishes. Shower. By that time it's 7:30. Time to make dinner. Then bed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" participant="130664" time="2013-03-19 14:38:18 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, time goes so much faster when you are older, what is that about? What does Staci do? You guys have a lot of pets</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 15:46:20 UTC">
      <body>She works at the humane league. We have to chronic uti cats. One that needs an inhaler (yup). We have a 16yo jack russell that is on 5 meds for various things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" participant="130716" time="2013-03-19 18:06:12 UTC">
      <body>Staci has a date tonight. Boring!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" participant="130664" time="2013-03-20 13:55:49 UTC">
      <body>So stressed about school </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" participant="130716" time="2013-03-20 15:58:03 UTC">
      <body>Reports?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" participant="130664" time="2013-03-20 16:03:11 UTC">
      <body>Not even. Giant life decisions </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" participant="130716" time="2013-03-20 16:03:53 UTC">
      <body>Oh...lay it on me girl</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" participant="130716" time="2013-03-20 19:19:46 UTC">
      <body>What decisions do you have to make?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" participant="130664" time="2013-03-20 20:03:58 UTC">
      <body>Like my major and grad school and what country we are going to live in. And immediately, my summer internship. I've always studied social sciences so archaeology is really tough for me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" participant="130664" time="2013-03-20 20:04:43 UTC">
      <body>It's so removed from humanity, I don't feel like a riot grrl anymore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" participant="130716" time="2013-03-20 21:12:17 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. We're basically going through the same thing. Only for me it's switching careers. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" participant="130664" time="2013-03-22 13:48:58 UTC">
      <body>It's tue, unions have become such a negative concept, and it's mostly based on stereotypes and prejudices. It's amazing how short sighted the human memory is, at the beginning of the last century we were fighting to get unions, to have weekends and worker</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" participant="130664" time="2013-03-22 13:49:47 UTC">
      <body>It's the same way that people blame poor families on food stamps but not giant corporations with subsidiaries. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" participant="130716" time="2013-03-22 13:51:00 UTC">
      <body>We should have that drink together soon. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" participant="130664" time="2013-03-22 13:51:31 UTC">
      <body>Get all drunk and mad and sing joe hill songs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" participant="130716" time="2013-03-22 13:52:09 UTC">
      <body>Ha! F the system!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" participant="130716" time="2013-03-22 19:16:13 UTC">
      <body>I want to hear you talk about this topic. I bet you get fired up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" participant="130664" time="2013-03-23 17:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeh I'm kind of a class warrior. What are you up to this fine weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" participant="130716" time="2013-03-23 19:13:52 UTC">
      <body>My bff is in from texas (his dad died). Saw him last night. Tonight my friend Dream Weaver (aka ben weaver) is having a house warming party for his new house</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" participant="130716" time="2013-03-23 19:14:09 UTC">
      <body>Tomorrow, errands. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" participant="130664" time="2013-03-23 19:43:03 UTC">
      <body>I'm on my way to a bridal shower now, gag. Then I have a meeting about a program I'm facilitating at school with a friend. We will probably drink beers tho. And then there is a basement show, my friends band is playing. Fun fun fun. Ella is at her grandmo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" participant="130716" time="2013-03-23 21:04:01 UTC">
      <body>Wolavers coffee porter and dogfish head's miles davis</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 01:35:15 UTC">
      <body>Dogfish 90 min imperial IPA, bells two hearted ale</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 01:36:06 UTC">
      <body>Mmm. Bells. I heart oarsman</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 01:46:55 UTC">
      <body>Oarsman, Linenkugels vanilla porter, wolavers coffee porter are easy top 10's for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 01:47:59 UTC">
      <body>How's the show?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 16:02:45 UTC">
      <body>It was good, saw people I haven't seen for a while. Repotting plants today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 16:03:40 UTC">
      <body>I think I'm going to the park before it snows</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 16:03:58 UTC">
      <body>Currently looking for a new job online</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 16:05:14 UTC">
      <body>I'm looking for a summer internship and staying in sweatpants all day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 16:11:16 UTC">
      <body>Nate calls me lamby pajamy when I get in this mode </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 16:12:20 UTC">
      <body>Do you "bah" a lot too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 16:24:06 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 16:25:19 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. What? All I got was a tiny black box...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" participant="130664" time="2013-03-24 16:25:44 UTC">
      <body>It was an emoji of a lamb</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 18:33:14 UTC">
      <body>Shame I missed it. Post ride snack: dark chocolate w/sea salt. I bit salty but still good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" participant="130716" time="2013-03-24 23:00:39 UTC">
      <body>Are sweats your pjs?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" participant="130716" time="2013-03-25 19:17:28 UTC">
      <body>Snow angels?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" participant="130664" time="2013-03-25 22:01:06 UTC">
      <body>More like slush angels. Gray in every direction</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" participant="130716" time="2013-03-25 22:02:45 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. They sure have been getting it wrong lately</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" participant="130716" time="2013-03-25 22:36:42 UTC">
      <body>What did you do today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 09:07:57 UTC">
      <body>￼Here's a pic of my flensburger weizen. It's dee-lish. That probably sounded dirty</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 14:37:58 UTC">
      <body>Were you up drinking beer at five in the morning?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0142" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 16:02:28 UTC">
      <body>Haha! That was last night. My bday present</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0143" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 16:38:23 UTC">
      <body>Happy birthday! What did you do to celebrate?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0144" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 19:11:10 UTC">
      <body>Had a flensburger. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0145" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 19:11:29 UTC">
      <body>Had a flensburger. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0146" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 20:21:40 UTC">
      <body>Whoa, take it easy, not too much excitement!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0147" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 21:12:44 UTC">
      <body>I got up at 3:45 and had to do it again today. I was beat anyway. I'll make up for it if you ever come to town</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0148" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 22:18:40 UTC">
      <body>What birthday is this? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0149" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 22:19:13 UTC">
      <body>35</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0150" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 22:20:49 UTC">
      <body>No wonder you were so tired! This birthday I threw up next to the bed and it smelled like truffles. That's what happens when you mix fancy dinner with rays happy birthday bar</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0151" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 22:22:50 UTC">
      <body>Ha! I've been there. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0152" participant="130664" time="2013-03-27 22:24:06 UTC">
      <body>It's always trouble</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0153" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 22:30:38 UTC">
      <body>When will you be in town</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0154" participant="130716" time="2013-03-27 22:57:58 UTC">
      <body>I want to buy you a drink or 3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0155" participant="130716" time="2013-03-30 12:14:53 UTC">
      <body>A couple linenkugels, a yards brawler, some shots, and an angry orchard. Bday celebration complete. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0156" participant="130664" time="2013-03-30 15:04:46 UTC">
      <body>Weekend warrior! Did you guys go out to celebrate?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0157" participant="130716" time="2013-03-30 15:06:53 UTC">
      <body>Yes maam</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0158" participant="130716" time="2013-03-30 20:00:22 UTC">
      <body>It was a long day for me but a blast. Me and my two favorite ladies (no hanky panky)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0159" participant="130716" time="2013-04-01 09:39:23 UTC">
      <body>It feels like a radiohead and shai hulud day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0160" participant="130664" time="2013-04-01 11:34:17 UTC">
      <body>It's supposed to be really nice today, in the sixties!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0161" participant="130716" time="2013-04-01 13:28:03 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. Stuck inside working at the chemical plant. In the old days I would burn today and ride but I need hours...so sad. #sellout</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0162" participant="130664" time="2013-04-01 14:48:26 UTC">
      <body>Yuck that sounds terrible. You gotta find a new gig</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0163" participant="130716" time="2013-04-01 15:55:44 UTC">
      <body>$33/hr in the check plus a $22/hr benefit package. I just need more work closer to home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0164" participant="130716" time="2013-04-03 13:28:00 UTC">
      <body>What's goin' on lady</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0165" participant="130716" time="2013-04-03 13:28:47 UTC">
      <body>What's goin' on lady</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0166" participant="130664" time="2013-04-03 16:18:29 UTC">
      <body>Not much, grabbing a quick bite. Today is going to be a long day </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0167" participant="130664" time="2013-04-03 16:18:51 UTC">
      <body>How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0168" participant="130716" time="2013-04-03 16:20:34 UTC">
      <body>Meh but better than yesterday. I was sick. What are you having?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0169" participant="130664" time="2013-04-03 16:23:56 UTC">
      <body>Blueberry juice and chickpea soup. And chips. I'm glad you are feeling better, what was wrong?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0170" participant="130716" time="2013-04-03 16:25:28 UTC">
      <body>Head cold going around the job. My partner has been sick for days and was hovering over me when I told him to back off (politely). He didn't listen. I got sick</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0171" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 13:49:43 UTC">
      <body>FRIDAY! Second best day of the work week...thursdays are better (payday)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0172" participant="130664" time="2013-04-05 14:44:42 UTC">
      <body>What are your plans for the weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0173" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 16:04:34 UTC">
      <body>Ride my bike as much as possible, drink excessively, sleep, eat good food</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0174" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 16:04:36 UTC">
      <body>You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0175" participant="130664" time="2013-04-05 16:14:24 UTC">
      <body>Tomorrow im going to forage for ramps, Sunday doing a fundraiser run, tonight I'm going out on a date with my bf which I am very excited for</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0176" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 16:25:48 UTC">
      <body>What kind of ramps?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0177" participant="130664" time="2013-04-05 16:26:52 UTC">
      <body>Like the spring onion variety</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0178" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 16:29:57 UTC">
      <body>Ah. I see. I thought you meant bike jumps</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0179" participant="130664" time="2013-04-05 16:30:28 UTC">
      <body>Haha, nope, that would be cool tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0180" participant="130716" time="2013-04-05 16:31:31 UTC">
      <body>Like Napoleon Dynamite </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0181" participant="130716" time="2013-04-06 02:37:28 UTC">
      <body>It's a manhattan kind of night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0182" participant="130664" time="2013-04-06 14:46:26 UTC">
      <body>Like spring breakers?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0183" participant="130716" time="2013-04-06 14:48:30 UTC">
      <body>Like old fashioned only no muddling</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0184" participant="130716" time="2013-04-08 10:40:39 UTC">
      <body>How was the rest of your weekend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0185" participant="130664" time="2013-04-08 12:23:42 UTC">
      <body>It was good, kinda flew by. How was yours?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0186" participant="130716" time="2013-04-08 13:26:47 UTC">
      <body>Fast but fun. Rode both days. Did some intervals but mostly relaxed riding. Went to the alley kat last night. Pizza and beer. Yum</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0187" participant="130664" time="2013-04-09 00:18:08 UTC">
      <body>Yum is right. There is an awesome pizza shop and brewery a couple blocks from my house, so good. Fig and bacon is my fav</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0188" participant="130716" time="2013-04-09 10:42:37 UTC">
      <body>While that sounds delicious, I haven't eaten meat in a long long time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0189" participant="130664" time="2013-04-09 12:26:37 UTC">
      <body>Good for you! I was vegan for most of my twenties, but then I started eating dairy and then I couldn't explain not eating meat if I ate and used animal products</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0190" participant="130716" time="2013-04-09 13:23:17 UTC">
      <body>Too each their own. I was never militant about it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0191" participant="130664" time="2013-04-09 13:42:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, whatever works. I mostly started when I found out I was going to Cambodia. I knew nothing would be vegetarian, and wanted to break my stomach in gently. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0192" participant="130716" time="2013-04-09 13:44:09 UTC">
      <body>Smart. What's in store this week?  I'm taking tomorrow off. 2pm dentist :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0193" participant="130664" time="2013-04-10 01:43:49 UTC">
      <body>It's all school, all week, as per usual. Only three and a half more weeks to go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0194" participant="130664" time="2013-04-10 01:43:57 UTC">
      <body>Are you getting a check up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0195" participant="130716" time="2013-04-10 01:52:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. A check up. Keep your fingers crossed. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0196" participant="130664" time="2013-04-10 01:54:32 UTC">
      <body>Floss extra good tonight!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0197" participant="130716" time="2013-04-10 01:55:57 UTC">
      <body>I fear it's too late for that. I'm horrible at flossing. I'll do it for a week and then totally ditch it until next check up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0198" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 10:20:01 UTC">
      <body>Aced the dentist. I felt like the hygienist was flirty. Didn't hate it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0199" participant="130664" time="2013-04-11 11:46:28 UTC">
      <body>Who needs flossing?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0200" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 13:31:11 UTC">
      <body>Maybe I have no teeth left to fill?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0201" participant="130664" time="2013-04-11 13:33:38 UTC">
      <body>Do u have a platinum grill?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0202" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 13:34:57 UTC">
      <body>No. Unless you're into that sort of thing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0203" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 13:35:21 UTC">
      <body>I'll get one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0204" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 13:36:04 UTC">
      <body>I think my teeth are filled with mercury. I'm losing my mind (the 5 concussions didn't help)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0205" participant="130664" time="2013-04-11 15:40:44 UTC">
      <body>Five concussion!?!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0206" participant="130664" time="2013-04-11 15:42:10 UTC">
      <body>My friend had four and his last one took him over a year to recover from. Also started getting OCD</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0207" participant="130716" time="2013-04-11 15:58:35 UTC">
      <body>I have a problem with short term memory. More specifically remembering what I'm doing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0208" participant="130716" time="2013-04-12 16:01:06 UTC">
      <body>My dog's 16th bday party is tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0209" participant="130664" time="2013-04-12 19:00:54 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0210" participant="130716" time="2013-04-12 19:13:47 UTC">
      <body>Yes. Tomorrow. I bought a case of leinenkugel summer variety pack and sam smith organic cider. Plus I have a bottle of absinthe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0211" participant="130664" time="2013-04-12 19:21:30 UTC">
      <body>Your dog gets crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0212" participant="130716" time="2013-04-12 19:31:29 UTC">
      <body>So far though only 6 or 7 people rsvp'd out of 30 invites. Boring. It was last minute though (we weren't sure if he was going to make it)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0213" participant="130664" time="2013-04-12 20:08:17 UTC">
      <body>That's a pretty huge party for a dog tho...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0214" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 16:11:12 UTC">
      <body>Skellington loved his party. He got all kinds of treats. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0215" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 16:26:12 UTC">
      <body>Did he get a new car?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0216" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 16:27:34 UTC">
      <body>Unfortunately we decided his legs were too short </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0217" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 16:29:55 UTC">
      <body>Wise conclusion. Was the party fun?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0218" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 16:30:40 UTC">
      <body>Good time. We had a beanbag toss, beer, and cake. What more does one need?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0219" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 16:32:01 UTC">
      <body>That sounds so fun! Was it marrow flavored cake?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0220" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 16:33:15 UTC">
      <body>No no. Haha. Staci made her family's secret recipe or chocolate cake and vanilla icing. I leave the room when she is baking</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0221" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 16:34:11 UTC">
      <body>I thought dogs couldn't have chocolate!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0222" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 16:36:15 UTC">
      <body>Oh. He didn't. We did. He had pig ears that our neighbor brought</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0223" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 16:48:29 UTC">
      <body>Ah! Not bad. I wish I knew someone having a birthday soon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0224" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 19:16:23 UTC">
      <body>I could have another one...I have plenty of alcohol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0225" participant="130664" time="2013-04-15 19:43:45 UTC">
      <body>I can't have any fun until school is done.. Two weeks to go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0226" participant="130716" time="2013-04-15 21:11:28 UTC">
      <body>I'm counting down the days...I hope you visit or we make it down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0227" participant="130716" time="2013-04-18 13:44:13 UTC">
      <body>What's on the agenda this weekend? I have to do work stuff...keep my certifications up to date</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0228" participant="130664" time="2013-04-18 14:23:44 UTC">
      <body>That's not a weekend! I'm going to see Pinocchio with Ella on Saturday, other wise just working on final papers</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0229" participant="130716" time="2013-04-18 15:55:13 UTC">
      <body>That's not much of a weekend either</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0230" participant="130664" time="2013-04-18 16:09:48 UTC">
      <body>I know..I want to get everything done this week because I'm going to a wedding in balti next weekend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0231" participant="130716" time="2013-04-18 16:18:42 UTC">
      <body>Neat. Friend or family? Staying or coming home?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0232" participant="130664" time="2013-04-18 16:23:11 UTC">
      <body>Friends. We are going down Friday and coming home Sunday, with the wedding on Saturday. So excited to drink champagne and not think about ancient Iberia or Arabia!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0233" participant="130716" time="2013-04-18 16:25:12 UTC">
      <body>Ha! Great. I hope you have a blast. His friends or yours?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0234" participant="130664" time="2013-04-18 16:29:28 UTC">
      <body>Mutual, so it's going to be good. So stoked</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0235" participant="130716" time="2013-04-18 16:30:53 UTC">
      <body>That's the best. I don't like going to stacis friends weddings because I don't know anyone...vise versa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0236" participant="130716" time="2013-04-23 11:01:29 UTC">
      <body>Did you get your papers finished?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0237" participant="130664" time="2013-04-23 12:15:49 UTC">
      <body>Nooo so much to do still. How was your weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0238" participant="130716" time="2013-04-23 13:26:04 UTC">
      <body>Short but nice. Didn't do much except for class on saturday and my dads sunday (he moved back from his winter retreat)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0239" participant="130716" time="2013-04-23 19:35:28 UTC">
      <body>Poll: would you pay to have sex with me? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0240" participant="130664" time="2013-04-23 20:02:11 UTC">
      <body>Ummm no probably not. But I wouldn't pay to have sex w anyone, so...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0241" participant="130716" time="2013-04-23 21:12:08 UTC">
      <body>Haha. Ok. I'm looking for a new career</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0242" participant="130664" time="2013-04-23 22:05:16 UTC">
      <body>Maybe you could get a webcam?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0243" participant="130716" time="2013-04-23 22:07:35 UTC">
      <body>Oh? Maybe. That might be fun</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0244" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 10:55:38 UTC">
      <body>How did it go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0246" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:27:38 UTC">
      <body>Alcohol sick?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0247" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:28:10 UTC">
      <body>Yup. Mixing up too many things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0248" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:28:46 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Back to the grind?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0249" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:29:35 UTC">
      <body>Working hard. First paper is due in 24 hours</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0250" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:30:07 UTC">
      <body>What's it on?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0251" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:31:29 UTC">
      <body>The presence of a prehistoric amber trade in the Iberian peninsula</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0252" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:32:33 UTC">
      <body>Where is iberia? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0253" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:33:38 UTC">
      <body>Present day Spain and Portugal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0254" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:35:34 UTC">
      <body>I see. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0255" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:43:06 UTC">
      <body>How wuz ur weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0256" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 13:46:27 UTC">
      <body>Ok. I got sick (for real) on saturday while I was out with my wife and my neighbor (I've had a crush on her for 6 years). We saw dreamgirls at the fulton</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0257" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 13:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Did you vom? What is dream girls?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0258" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 15:59:52 UTC">
      <body>Head cold and lungs too. No vomiting. Dream girls is based on the supremes rise to fame</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0259" participant="130664" time="2013-05-02 16:07:05 UTC">
      <body>Oh no. Bummer. are u feeling better?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0260" participant="130716" time="2013-05-02 16:08:03 UTC">
      <body>I'm still stuffy but I'm coming out of it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0261" participant="130716" time="2013-05-03 16:33:42 UTC">
      <body>They are saying we are going to 6 12 hour days or 7 10's. Ugh. Feast or friggin' famine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0262" participant="130664" time="2013-05-03 16:59:39 UTC">
      <body>Yikes that's terrible! And you have to drive several hours there and back??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0263" participant="130716" time="2013-05-03 19:14:06 UTC">
      <body>We may get a motel room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0264" participant="130664" time="2013-05-03 19:14:43 UTC">
      <body>How long does that last? Hotel party!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0265" participant="130716" time="2013-05-03 19:16:10 UTC">
      <body>Probably 4 weeks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0266" participant="130716" time="2013-05-06 19:17:41 UTC">
      <body>Where were you this weekend? I saw your pic of FB</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0267" participant="130664" time="2013-05-06 19:20:03 UTC">
      <body>Took the beer bus to the Philadelphia union game. Celebrated being done with school by getting smashed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0268" participant="130716" time="2013-05-06 19:21:29 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Do you know billy bennett? He's a huge soccer...err...football fan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0269" participant="130664" time="2013-05-06 19:24:41 UTC">
      <body>No I don't think so. It was super fun, you guys should come for a game sometime. Beer bus is the way to go </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0270" participant="130716" time="2013-05-06 19:26:02 UTC">
      <body>I doubt staci would be into it. She doesn't like sports or beer!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0271" participant="130664" time="2013-05-06 19:31:51 UTC">
      <body>Double bummer. I like futball because it moves quickly, the athletes have to be in shape, and there is lots of chanting in the stands. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0272" participant="130716" time="2013-05-06 19:33:38 UTC">
      <body>You should go to a cyclocross race. They just made it against the rules this year for the racers to drink during the race</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0273" participant="130664" time="2013-05-06 20:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Haha, that's awesome. Is that downhill?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0274" participant="130716" time="2013-05-06 21:05:33 UTC">
      <body>No. It's off-road racing on road bikes basically. From sept-december around here. Huge in europe. Seems they know a good time when they see one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0275" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 02:35:19 UTC">
      <body>Weird do you do it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0276" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 07:59:33 UTC">
      <body>I used to. I was pretty good, won a few intermediate races but pro is extremely hard, less shenanigans. I only ever did one and my goal was to not get lapped</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0277" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 08:00:06 UTC">
      <body>I did manage to stay on the lead lap.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0278" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 12:14:27 UTC">
      <body>I like shenanigans in sports. That's awesome. Let me know when there's a good race coming up!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0279" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 13:23:28 UTC">
      <body>Will do. It's a fall sport</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0280" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 13:25:47 UTC">
      <body>My favorite season!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0281" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 13:31:57 UTC">
      <body>You could youtube cyclocross. They also do a money grab. Spectators put $$ on the course to see if racers will stop to pick it up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0282" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 13:35:20 UTC">
      <body>What! Can you hold out money and people will take it from your hand? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0283" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 13:36:28 UTC">
      <body>Yes but it's better when they put it on the barriers or just in the mud to make them earn it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0284" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 13:38:13 UTC">
      <body>The racers are like strippers? I don't get it, why would they stop? Is there a cash prize for winning?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0285" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 13:41:00 UTC">
      <body>Yes. Like strippers. The guys racing for the prize $$ rarely partake but the rest of the them don't care if they get 19th or 20th. Not much $$ in the sport</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0286" participant="130664" time="2013-05-07 13:44:29 UTC">
      <body>Ah ok, that's funny. Where do they race around here?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0287" participant="130716" time="2013-05-07 13:45:22 UTC">
      <body>All over. There are a bunch of races in the philly burbs, delaware, jersey, and so on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0288" participant="130716" time="2013-05-10 16:31:43 UTC">
      <body>Anything fun this weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0289" participant="130716" time="2013-05-13 09:32:19 UTC">
      <body>￼I have an ouchy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0290" participant="130664" time="2013-05-13 12:32:42 UTC">
      <body>Yikes what happened!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0291" participant="130716" time="2013-05-13 13:24:19 UTC">
      <body>Went down at 25mph on the road</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0292" participant="130664" time="2013-05-13 15:23:36 UTC">
      <body>Are you ok? Your brain ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0293" participant="130716" time="2013-05-13 15:54:41 UTC">
      <body>Mostly just my hip and bike. My pride a wee bit too. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0294" participant="130664" time="2013-05-13 15:56:01 UTC">
      <body>Ouch. How did it happen?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0295" participant="130716" time="2013-05-13 15:57:09 UTC">
      <body>Wet roads. Fast turn. Over zealous</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0296" participant="130664" time="2013-05-13 16:13:02 UTC">
      <body>At least no vehicles were involved. Is yer bike totaled?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0297" participant="130716" time="2013-05-13 16:15:52 UTC">
      <body>I broke a shifter (need parts to fix) and my derailleur hanger (I had a spare) but I was thinking about updating my stuff anyway. Running these parts for 5yrs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0298" participant="130716" time="2013-05-15 19:21:22 UTC">
      <body>Still gimpy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0299" participant="130716" time="2013-05-17 13:42:28 UTC">
      <body>Is school over?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0300" participant="130664" time="2013-05-17 16:35:49 UTC">
      <body>Done done done, just dropped off my final final </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0301" participant="130716" time="2013-05-17 16:37:16 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Time to get smashed? Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0302" participant="130664" time="2013-05-17 16:38:10 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I guess that's what time it is!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0303" participant="130716" time="2013-05-17 16:41:44 UTC">
      <body>Let me know if you wander to lancaster sometime. I'll buy you one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0304" participant="130664" time="2013-05-17 18:46:07 UTC">
      <body>I will be there somewhat soon, I have friends that just moved here from Olympia. Fun!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0305" participant="130716" time="2013-05-17 19:11:55 UTC">
      <body>Cool. Keep me in the loop</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
