<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130504.0040" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135279" time="2013-05-04 19:16:16 UTC">
      <body>Should u/do u want to see ur internist &amp; dentist here during that wk ur home? BS isn't fond of paying out of state &amp; out of plan providers for anything in-plan providers can do. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135279" time="2013-05-04 19:16:16 UTC">
      <body>Emergencies are different </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135279" time="2013-05-04 19:20:32 UTC">
      <body>Can u also try to plan to come to Ocdi the thurs aft u r home at 3:30, pls? Our SW Thea &amp; I would live to include u in a session. Dad has come to the others. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135279" time="2013-05-04 19:20:32 UTC">
      <body>Oppty 4 u 2 plan ahead 2c ur colleagues there b4 or after. And if u haven't seen the lobby outside Pierce Hall in the Admin bldg, I insist u c it! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135080" time="2013-05-04 19:22:43 UTC">
      <body>It is haverfest I have received these and will respond to them later ok? I love you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135279" time="2013-05-04 19:31:12 UTC">
      <body>￼Ok. Have a wonderful time!!! &lt;x3 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2013-05-05 00:47:46 UTC">
      <body>I have seen it! We had orientation there. May 30th is more likely than the 23rd for going to the OCDI. Ideally I should see pcp and dentist but I have no appointments...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 00:57:36 UTC">
      <body>U should absolutely call internist mon am, say u just got the Philly, &amp; beg. I don't wish symptoms on u, but a complaint or 2 will likely get u in faster. Dad sez dental not covered anyway. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 00:57:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah, now u can just send ur teeth to Becca!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 01:04:28 UTC">
      <body>U should find out whether u have employee/staff/community/Quad-Co Alumna access to the UPenn infirmary/clinic/hospital services in some way, esp if at $0 or at least reduced $$.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 01:05:12 UTC">
      <body>Doing ERPs here at home now. You talkable tomw eve?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135080" time="2013-05-05 01:07:00 UTC">
      <body>I get benefits so I'm not sure what those are or what the insurance includes. Probably...don't know when/if I'm meeting w my thesis group to work on our presentation.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 01:07:03 UTC">
      <body>*the Philly JOB</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135279" time="2013-05-05 01:10:24 UTC">
      <body>Let us know. Hope to go to cam tomw. Cam closes at 6. Curfew (gasp--??curfew???) is at 10 sun-Th, and at 11p Fri Sat. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
