<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130101.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-01-01 00:22:13 UTC">
      <body>Have a lovely time out and about tonight Laura Finch. I love you. Welcome Home!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131422" time="2013-01-01 00:28:27 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! Have great yoga xxxxxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-01-01 00:29:23 UTC">
      <body>xoxo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-01-01 13:55:19 UTC">
      <body>Hey lovely. Are you awake? Any chance you'll be in class? Morgan says he'll leave the door open! xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-01-01 23:44:29 UTC">
      <body>Hey gorgeous, how was your New Years? The class last night was fun but a repeat of last year's class. Are you going to yoga Thursday morning? It's my last week without school. Maybe we could have brunch afterwards. What do you think? :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131422" time="2013-01-02 14:24:14 UTC">
      <body>Yes to thurs morning unless I make late evening plans tonight-i have to work around a friend from chicago who is incapable of planning more than five minutes in advance. But theoretically yes to yoga and brunch! You yoging tonight, or do you have work?xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-01-02 17:02:50 UTC">
      <body>I am Zendo-info tonight instead. I will hope to see you Thursday though! Or maybe Friday for embodied yoga anatomy? That class sounds nerdy and fun! xoxo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131422" time="2013-01-03 13:28:04 UTC">
      <body>Omg, your eggs idea sounds amazing! Are you sure?! I can bring eggs if you want,i just bought some yesterday.xx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-01-03 13:57:15 UTC">
      <body>We have eggs, no worries! If you have cheese or salsa though that would help. When do you want to come over? xx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131422" time="2013-01-03 13:59:59 UTC">
      <body>I only have eggs in my house,i haven't really been shopping yet! want me to buy cheese, salsa? nine thirty? I have to leave at ten thirty ish, boo.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-01-03 14:01:37 UTC">
      <body>I think we will be good with what he have on hand. I have Sri racha so that will fill in as salsa. Do you like runny yolks or soft ones or firm ones? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131422" time="2013-01-03 14:08:51 UTC">
      <body>Ooh, runny. This is amazing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-01-03 14:09:17 UTC">
      <body>Perfect! Just like me! See you soon!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-01-03 20:56:33 UTC">
      <body>It was so lovely to see you today!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131422" time="2013-01-03 22:38:13 UTC">
      <body>You too lady lady. Thanks for breakfast deliciousness xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-01-04 21:30:36 UTC">
      <body>Yoga? Also, did Verizon ever come? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131422" time="2013-01-05 00:04:50 UTC">
      <body>I'm making chicken with a boy! Sorry! How was it?xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130962" time="2013-01-05 00:21:06 UTC">
      <body>Ooh love it! Chicken with a boy--sounds so cozy. Class was good but you are correct that there is not an apex pose! It was worth it to do head to knee  and neck release and to oogle Angie's divine dolphin. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130962" time="2013-01-05 14:55:37 UTC">
      <body>Pilates at 11:45? Heart heart.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131422" time="2013-01-05 15:57:19 UTC">
      <body>Ack, sorry, still at chicken man's. Enjoy! Xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130962" time="2013-01-05 15:59:12 UTC">
      <body>Enjoy chicken man for me! If you want to have lunch around 1 let me know, I think I'm treating myself to Atiyah Ola vegan food. It's not broth but its good clean food. xxxxxxxxxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131422" time="2013-01-05 19:51:59 UTC">
      <body>Akk, my phone died while I was replying, just got home. How was pilates?xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130962" time="2013-01-05 20:32:48 UTC">
      <body>It was good. I feel taller. I didn't get one of the special Pilates mats this time and they help hold down your feet so I wasn't able to do quite as much. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130962" time="2013-01-06 19:12:10 UTC">
      <body>How's little Jam doing? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131422" time="2013-01-06 20:39:15 UTC">
      <body>Jamming along, trying to escape to the great outdoors at all times...!xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130962" time="2013-01-06 20:40:25 UTC">
      <body>Oh boy! What a cat! I can't imagine a mouthful of metal! I may want to go to Stephens class (gasp) tomorrow. If I'm not too tired from work. Are you going? Xxxxxxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131422" time="2013-01-06 20:42:29 UTC">
      <body>I switched my limbs day to monday. Boo. Enjoy! Don't do headstands if you don't want to!xx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130962" time="2013-01-06 20:43:45 UTC">
      <body>Oh no!!! Boo indeed! I may Pilates instead! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
