<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130404.0020" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131419" time="2013-04-04 19:48:45 UTC">
      <body>Hey mb. Does metal tend to hold emotional stuff in the body since its spirit is the po? Sometimes i feel like i seem like a hypochondriac and like it tak</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131419" time="2013-04-04 19:48:47 UTC">
      <body>es a lot of effort to keep a relatively balanced body. Random ailment of this week: iritis. Taking steroid drops. Doc said could be random or linked 2 my</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131419" time="2013-04-04 19:48:48 UTC">
      <body> old trouble with lyme.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131419" time="2013-04-04 19:51:43 UTC">
      <body>Or maybe i'm just a complainy earth!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-04-04 22:18:04 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. Good question about metal. I think probably not because physical level ailments occur across the cf spectrum. But maybe? I would think maybe where symptoms exist could be significant maybe? You are not at all complainey! You are lovely!!! I had a to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131419" time="2013-04-04 22:26:20 UTC">
      <body>Ha ha there's always work to do on the self, i'm learning too. I'm joining ur lovely pity party! U deserve it, given all u've been thru lately!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-04-04 22:28:05 UTC">
      <body> You deserve it too! What lifted me out was Pat brought me orange juice from Walmart she hauled on the 64 bus and something inside m lit up with the tangible reminder that someone loves me!!!! Haha and so funny!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-04 22:35:50 UTC">
      <body>You can always call me if you want some laughs or love or anything. I love you and I love talking on the phone!!! xoxoxo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 01:34:22 UTC">
      <body>I just had a great poop for the first time in awhile and felt so good I wanted to run around the block! Pooping is so important!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
