<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140422.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-04-22 18:15:31 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>have you seen the havoc micro bikini question yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-04-22 18:15:40 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>havix</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-04-22 18:15:52 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>oops sorry havic</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-04-22 18:16:49 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Yeah that was hilarious, I didn't have time to write a response though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-04-22 18:18:43 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>I'm fwd it to neil right now just cuz its funny. I'm writing guy back right now..m its funny cuz he's like "I would like to include this model"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-04-22 18:18:48 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>The video looked too pro to me but as long as it's not nudity or overtly sexual I think it's ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-04-22 18:19:04 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Hahahaha!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-04-22 18:22:44 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>man, I have a lot of work this week, I have to do all the QC lists cuz Ann is away. I haven't been able to do any actual scouting in weeks </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-04-22 18:24:27 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>oh one thing I wanted to mention, I don't think xuansong does anything with the "synopsis too long" feed back thing in the QC lists. I would just save th(1/2)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-04-22 18:24:27 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>at for when they are really really long like #166(2/2)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-04-22 18:29:04 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Ok will do. And thanks for the help with the formatting issues. I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-04-22 21:09:58 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>I'm answering steoh sessacs question right now... she must be the infamous #19 who has been posting all those YouTube professional vloggers and such. lol(1/2)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-04-22 21:09:58 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>, if you Google her name you can find her blog and YouTube channel. it seems like she's trying to be a professional vloggrr herself(2/2)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-04-22 21:13:40 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>That's not what we need in the corpus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-04-22 21:15:18 UTC" participant="149353">
      <body>I know. we don't need fucking idiot vlogs. I'm trying to find a nice way to say that to her... its just funny how she apparently is aspiring to be a pro vlogger</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-04-22 23:06:20 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Just tell her vlogs are not useful because the project is about identifying actions</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-04-22 23:07:12 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>I wonder if working on HAVIC made her want to become a pro vloger?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

