<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120704.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 03:34:56 UTC">
      <body>There are people barbecuing at my studio tomorrow would you like to come</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 03:42:43 UTC">
      <body>I would love to! Thank you for inviting me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 03:48:38 UTC">
      <body>Yay.  Ok so I'm going over in the morning to work and it's like very casual beer and bbqing.  I also invited Jeremy too. Have you guys met. He had red dreds?   He's really nice. Dont worry not a set up just I think both you guys are great friends.   I'm thinking around 4ish but you are welcome anytime</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 03:49:11 UTC">
      <body>I think I might even take the bus tomorrow now that I have An iphone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 03:50:24 UTC">
      <body>You should bring work and come early and then we can hang out on the water with all the people</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 03:56:27 UTC">
      <body>Haha that all sounds great, I gotta take it slow since it's my first (!!) time out of the house in like a week, god help me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 03:57:08 UTC">
      <body>Feel like I've been sick forever and have no life and subsequently, am a loser</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 03:59:27 UTC">
      <body>I'll call you domani</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 03:59:55 UTC">
      <body>Maybe we can get coffee early</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2012-07-04 04:00:43 UTC">
      <body>I miss you!  And I too gave no life which is why on this most social of days tomorrow I am going to be at my studio socializing with the people I say hi to on the pier</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 04:06:53 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha aww I miss you!!! A lot. I can't wait to hang</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135401" time="2012-07-04 04:07:08 UTC">
      <body>Also I am still so excited for our trip. So so excited</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
