<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120212.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:34:17 UTC">
      <body>Why you never play me back anymore ):</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:42:24 UTC">
      <body>Took me a while, but I played! Sorry I forever have low battery hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:43:22 UTC">
      <body>Hah okay well I'm not getting it then. You went out tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:44:32 UTC">
      <body>Oh, well you shud get it soon. And yep, you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:45:07 UTC">
      <body>Op just did. What're you doin now? And for a bit, but meh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:46:40 UTC">
      <body>Word, well lastnight fun? And with John, he stayed in tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:48:01 UTC">
      <body>Well yeah for a bit. Ah skyrim? How was your night? I feel like meh Hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:48:48 UTC">
      <body>Why do you feel like that? And yup, but I'm so tired, gonna sleep soon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:50:51 UTC">
      <body>Nice, let you go? And I don't know. Sad, haven't talked to you in forever. Never get what I want, I'm a total fuck up, and have no one to talk to hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:50:56 UTC">
      <body>Don't say that Sara, you're not that okay.  And we are talking tmrw. I felt meh yesterday. It's just we gotta get used to this, it's hard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:54:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah but I am, idk I wish I just had a you to talk to. Or a someone. And we will, maybe. Idk if we will. Shud I let you sleep?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>You dk if we will what? And not even home yet, you're all good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:56:20 UTC">
      <body>If well get used to it. Idk how to. Half of me is but the other half...idk. I'm just this screw up and can't fix myself or put my life together ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 09:57:20 UTC">
      <body>Sara, that's not true. Why wud you say that? And eventually we will get used to it. I know it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 09:59:34 UTC">
      <body>Idk I just always mess everything up and blah. Ojay, I just miss you so much, like just talking to yiu. Crap</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>We can talk tmrw. I was prty down yesterday, things will get smoother and better in time on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 10:04:45 UTC">
      <body>I know we can. Why were you down? When I asked yiu said yiu were fine </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Well I was up late and got sad before going to bed and such for a while. But imma goto sleep soon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 10:07:13 UTC">
      <body>Why sad? And alright, I'll TTY tnrw I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Idk just cuz it's weird getting used to nodes contact and such ya know? And cool, Skype tmrw night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 10:09:17 UTC">
      <body>Well you never try and contact me Johnny, I always talk to you first. You can do that you know. And sure thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Well we agreed to talking on Sunday after he weekend remember? So that's why I didn't and such, plus it's better to get used to ya kno</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 10:11:38 UTC">
      <body>Yes of course, but you can still talk to me whenever Johnny. Oh crap, sobbing at greys, wassup</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 10:12:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah don't do it! But I'll ttyt, and okay I'll keep that in mind. Night Sara! Ciaociao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 10:13:38 UTC">
      <body>Night Johnny, sleep well, hit me up tmrw! Ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:26:20 UTC">
      <body>￼Wtf mate </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:26:40 UTC">
      <body>Damn! Populars!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:27:27 UTC">
      <body>Every single thing on this guys tumblr right now is from me. Literally everything</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:28:31 UTC">
      <body>Really? Why is that? And you can't change it back?:/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:28:48 UTC">
      <body>Weird, meh I've lost so much traffic since the URL change...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:28:48 UTC">
      <body>No it won't let me! Sho weak! And well ever since then I've had very little, might be something else. Idk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Hmm well honestly you've barely been posting anything for like 2 weeks, it might be that. Like I go to check yours out and you have like four new pics</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:35:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. I havnt been having very many runs lately, since midterms are over imma get gnarly again!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:35:26 UTC">
      <body>Well you also don't Skype me and go on tumblr :P midterms were okay tho? I gots one Monday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah midterms were chill overall. And yeah this is true. For what class?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Linguistics, gotta study. But going to lunch now. When did you wanna talk today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Heh I'm going to breakfast now. And like tonight? Hmph your call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:45:33 UTC">
      <body>If its tonight it might have to be a little later than usual but idk, I can keep you posted? And well  going to brunch so there (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 20:50:08 UTC">
      <body>Hah for sure. Ciao for now, we will figure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 20:50:47 UTC">
      <body>Mmk let me know when you're free</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body>I'll check the tracking number inna bit!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Do you know when my package will get here? Gotta prepare myself haha (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:42:49 UTC">
      <body>Okay no worries. But I should be able to talk tonight around 10 or 11 if you're down with that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 22:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Okay, that works for me, tell me when it's good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 22:47:28 UTC">
      <body>For shua! Sounds like a plan man</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:48:42 UTC">
      <body>Alrighty, I'll just text you when I head home and such</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:49:25 UTC">
      <body>Fo shua barrada:P hehe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 22:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Hah you and your Hawaiian slang huh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:54:15 UTC">
      <body>I learn from the best </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 22:54:54 UTC">
      <body>Massively stressed out. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 22:56:00 UTC">
      <body>How's you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:08:48 UTC">
      <body>Alright, got some hw to do. Why so stressed?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:09:31 UTC">
      <body>Midterm tomorrow, two Short papers, one intro, and 100 pages of reading. And just really stressed in general about life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:10:56 UTC">
      <body>Mmm damn, well what's the most pressing and do that first. And anyway in which I can help?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:13:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah just making a study guide now. And no not really. I just, need to focus or something. Life is just really complicated right now haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:15:12 UTC">
      <body>I wish I cud help. And good call, I'm sure your midterm will be chill. And things will get better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:16:13 UTC">
      <body>Yeah idk it's just hard to get back into it. Want this to be over. Wanna be home and it to be summer and I just want so many things hah. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:17:20 UTC">
      <body>For sure, and it'll come faster than you think. And I feel yah, hang in there Sara. Idk what to say :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:19:37 UTC">
      <body>Yeah this month has gone by really fast. Ahh spring break where are yiu?? And nothing to say, Johnny. You are such a good person, really. You are one of those rare truly good people. I'm grateful I met you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:23:44 UTC">
      <body>You are too Sara, you're an amazing person and I'm happy I met you also. And for real! I want break to come so badly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:23:56 UTC">
      <body>Hah me too! I'll see you at least once yeah? For coffee or something? Oh ps how come sometimes on tumblr it goes away when there's like a person who reblogge 20 of your photos? Like someone else jut followed me and reblogged 20 photos and the last one dis</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:25:49 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, but ppl are like...looking at my blog omg. And sweet (: hah is it bad I'm excited?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:25:52 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea? Tumblr is weird sometimes with that, like some reblogs will show up and others won't. And yeah I'm down with coffee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:36:32 UTC">
      <body>Hah that's awesome! Go new scars! And no that's fine, Itll be good ya kno</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:38:38 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it definitely will, and I posted something on your wall, idk if that's weird or not tho....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:44:59 UTC">
      <body>Say something on it so I feel less weird abit it (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:45:04 UTC">
      <body>Sweet photo! And no that's not weird. Pretty sick one tho for sure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="131065" time="2012-02-12 23:45:04 UTC">
      <body>Nice nice, and word up peace dewd. Ciaociao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="131019" time="2012-02-12 23:45:56 UTC">
      <body>Yeah don't leave it hangin hah! And yeah I see it all the time! But I should study now. And I found a Clark Kerr smoking buddy yee (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="131065" time="2012-02-13 05:09:20 UTC">
      <body>Skype in twenty?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="131019" time="2012-02-13 05:10:17 UTC">
      <body>I'm jumping in the shower, can I Skype you after that? Will prlly take twenty hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="131065" time="2012-02-13 05:17:52 UTC">
      <body>Okay coolio. See you then! Ciaociao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131019" time="2012-02-13 05:30:08 UTC">
      <body>Skype me qheneverp</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="131065" time="2012-02-13 05:30:40 UTC">
      <body>Okay, I will in five</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="131019" time="2012-02-13 09:13:00 UTC">
      <body>Are we playing words still?  Ps do your fafsa if you haven't. Pps. For some reason I feel like we're breaking up all over again.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="131065" time="2012-02-13 09:14:40 UTC">
      <body>Yes we are still playing, deciding not to do it. And I'm sorry. But gonna ttyl on Sunday. Ciao Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="131019" time="2012-02-13 09:15:21 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, well thought I'd remind you just in case. Bye Johnny. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="131065" time="2012-02-13 09:16:48 UTC">
      <body>Thanks, bai!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 05:52:34 UTC">
      <body>You know what? We're not talking and I get it, but I can't be friends with you until I say this, so I'm sorry. I know how I fucked up with you, how I always fuck up with everyone, but no one ever gives me credit for the things I do right. And I did so man</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="131065" time="2012-02-14 05:56:16 UTC">
      <body>I know i didn't do everything right Sara, and I understand that and own up to it. Yes of course you did things right, we had the time of our lives. And yes I understand to forgive people and will continue too. I think i did with you to a certain extent. I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 06:01:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm not saying this to be mean, or to hurt you. But you say you forgive things, but you don't forget them. It takes you so long, and I was similar. But I learned from you. And I don't deserve another chance with you, I really don't. But I don't know how t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131065" time="2012-02-14 06:04:48 UTC">
      <body>Well I think time right now is good to have. We can talk again on Sunday about this okay. I won't leave early and you can get everything you want out. Just don't make it into something else okay.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 06:04:57 UTC">
      <body>Don't make it into what? What do I make it into? And I thought the point of this time was to learn to be friends?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="131065" time="2012-02-14 06:06:56 UTC">
      <body>Yes of course, we def need to learn to be friends and I think some time away will help us think and such. Just a week. And like last time when it turned into a fight ya know...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 06:08:30 UTC">
      <body>I'm not saying this to get you to talk to me, last night was just bad. I unloaded on you, I fought with you, it wasn't fair. I was mad because life is unfair, and it's just harsh. It's really just harsh when the person you love can't love you back the way</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="131065" time="2012-02-14 06:15:28 UTC">
      <body>I don't think it will at all, will def take lotsa work. Taking this slow, which I feel is better than fast. I'll tty Sunday Sara, ciao.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 06:16:37 UTC">
      <body>Byee thanks for the sentiment</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 08:05:43 UTC">
      <body>One more thing and then I really won't talk to you until Sunday: I need to know you'll actually talk to me, no holds barred(or whatever the phrase is), give me more than a measly hour. I used to mean something to you. I need to know you won't run away fro</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="131065" time="2012-02-14 08:08:32 UTC">
      <body>Yes Sara, I'll tty for a long time with no limit. And dk the phrase but I get it what you mean.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 08:09:38 UTC">
      <body>Thank you Johnny. Have a good one, take the time you need. Just think and be happy, I want you to be happy. See you Sunday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="131019" time="2012-02-14 08:12:13 UTC">
      <body>Night Johnny. And I do mean it. If you're gonna believe anything believe that I want you to be happy. See you then</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
