<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20131022.0017" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-10-22 14:11:33 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Thanks!  More to come and if you'll be around can use the help.. have to put black tarp on other wall... and still decorate porch.. and shop for those decisions and food/drink for party all while I help stephs nephews make a school video project and bake two cakes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-10-22 14:14:57 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay, that's what I was gonna say next. I can help. Just let me know which day. I work til 11 tonight, til 9 tomorrow night. Thursday night penn has a free event at the Eastern state penitentiary and I'll be home by 11:30.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-10-22 14:16:01 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>But I go in at 3 everyday so I'm free before that. And Friday I work in the afternoon til 5</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-10-22 14:17:02 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>If you need me to pick up stuff before work let me know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-10-22 14:19:48 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Tomorrow night would be good. 9 is still early and thurs I start would at 10 so I can stay up a bit... I did angelos video yesterday (rough draft) and ill be doing joeys video tonight... but even if you pick us up stuff that would help...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-10-22 14:20:30 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I'll let you know some stuff we need</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-10-22 14:22:32 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-10-22 14:24:01 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And we'll give you money for it too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-10-22 14:25:34 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay thanks. So tomorrow before work I'll get them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-10-22 17:31:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea.. are you able to get a friend to drive you? Like you can get the head and cauldron we need at the Halloween store on Delaware ave... or if you have a car can pick up the beer / liquor we need</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-10-22 17:32:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lmk what you'll be able to do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-10-22 17:33:33 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I'm not gonna be able to get help. But I can get stuff like alcohol if it's not too much to carry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-10-22 17:34:35 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok... I figured maybe if like cassie was available or something.  But the cauldron and head won't be heavy to carry so that's one. Maybe bus to Delaware ave then walk the couple blocks? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-10-22 17:36:36 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-10-22 17:36:42 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah everyone's at work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2013-10-22 17:36:57 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok no problem</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-10-22 17:38:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>We'll talk later about if I'm up when you get home... even if you can decorate the window one morning.. have moms ghost town (like xmas village). Just a matter of putting the houses up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2013-10-22 17:39:59 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2013-10-22 17:45:28 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh plus marc maybe up when you get home.  He is punished and not allowed out on week nights</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2013-10-22 17:59:18 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body> Okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2013-10-23 03:48:01 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I'll be home tomorrow morning. Can you leave a list of what you want me to buy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2013-10-23 03:48:43 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>K but I need to tap mac to give you the money</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2013-10-23 12:40:01 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Going to sr tonight and dawns to help with project in case we aren't home when you get home... mom has chicken soup container in her freezer forme if you can pick that up sometime today.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2013-10-23 12:41:29 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Plus we were going to do tacos tonight but might not have time. If you're home then you can cook the ground beef for us. And we'll take over when we get home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2013-10-23 12:41:58 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Take the beef out of the fridge tho. Set it on a plate on the counter so it defrosts all day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2013-10-23 12:46:24 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>What time are you getting home? I don't get home til 10. And did you list things you want me to get?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

