<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141227.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-27 21:56:11 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>I can do evening tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-28 20:07:28 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Hey Julia, are you home? Or would you be able to bring the horses in tonight? I am still in Maryland and I can bring them in but would be rushing back. I can feed tomorrow morning if you wanted me to :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-28 20:07:28 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>If not, totally ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-28 20:10:08 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Hey, I'm around and can take care of them, no problem! I just have beauty out in the paddock cause the fields are soaked, I figure it won't be too c</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-28 20:10:16 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Old for Andy overnight </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-28 20:11:23 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>That sounds awesome! You are so great! Are you sure it's ok? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-28 20:11:26 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>I wanted to check with you - do you know when nick's coming back? I'm around all this week except pm New Year's Eve and am the next day, going to a wedding. Can you do those two? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-28 20:11:38 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Yeah no problem at all!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-28 20:14:20 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Nick said he's coming back New Year's Day I think. I'm around all week except New Year's Eve night as well and New Year's Day too :/ I can do morning or evening Monday Tuesday and morning on Wednesday so whatever works for you. So maybe on New Year's Eve, would you be around to bring them in early?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-28 20:16:13 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>I have to leave around 10am on New Year's Eve and won't be back til late afternoon the next day. I told nick, maybe he made plans? I never know! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-12-28 20:17:04 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>For the other days, if you're coming to ride and want to feed, awesome, if not, I've got it covered, no problem :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-28 20:22:24 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Haha I told nick too and don't think he made plans.  I'll do tomorrow night and Wednesday morning to get them squared away for the day. Hopefully someone can just bring them in that night. If nick doesn't have someone, maybe I can find someone. So you're good with tonight, Monday morning, Tuesday morning and Tuesday night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-28 20:25:55 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ok perfect! I'll plan on those shifts and if anything changes, just let me know. Thanks!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-28 20:26:34 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Should be good! Thanks so much!!!! I have something for you so I'll leave it in the barn Monday night &lt;3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-12-28 20:26:59 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Aw, thanks! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-28 20:44:56 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Robin will be back for New Year's Eve :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-12-28 20:45:47 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Perfect </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-12-28 20:45:56 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Also just FYI - current rations: Andy gets 3/4 of the Gatorade scoop of the pellets, beauty gets 2 Gatorade scoops of the senior </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-12-28 20:46:14 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>(I guessed wrong this morning, haha.) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-12-28 20:46:52 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Haha no worries, they change it a lot. You feeding in the mornings right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-12-28 20:47:32 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Yup! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-12-28 20:47:49 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Sounds good. Thanks for taking tonight!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

