<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130522.0028" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 09:09:20 UTC">
      <body>Hi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 09:15:02 UTC">
      <body>Hi. Looking forward to the long weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 09:16:30 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Going home, haven't seen my family in so long. Hbu?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 09:47:19 UTC">
      <body>Do you have plans for through weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 10:08:55 UTC">
      <body>Nothing too specific. Probably some kayaking, but no major travel. How far do you have to go to see the fam?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 10:12:37 UTC">
      <body>Kayaking? That sounds awesome. I've always wanted to, but I'm not that adventurous lol Im a student at u of m my family also lives in Michigan not too fa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 10:12:49 UTC">
      <body>r, an hour and a halfs drive but we get so caught up with things then suddenly its been months since you've seen your family</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 10:52:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, sometimes it's easier to schedule if you're farther away. You have to plan more.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 10:52:01 UTC">
      <body>I'm on the opposite coast from my family now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 11:01:08 UTC">
      <body>Where's home for you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 11:32:50 UTC">
      <body>Current home is Philly, fam is in oregon, where I grew up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 12:26:47 UTC">
      <body>Oh nice, Philly is a long ways from Oregon. What made you decide to live in Philly if you don't mind me asking. Work? School?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 12:33:59 UTC">
      <body>I'm Sudanese, spent most of my life btween here and Sudan. And still, never been outside of Michigan.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 12:41:20 UTC">
      <body>I moved here for work. I moved around before that for quirk and school, but mostly stuck to the west coast.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:05:59 UTC">
      <body>So what are you hobbies, interests. What do you do for fun?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 13:13:45 UTC">
      <body>I like to read, kayak, walk/hike. What about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:26:40 UTC">
      <body>I'm not really that outdoorsy, I wish I were though lol I read, I work a lot with refugees/asylum and new immigrants and human rights and that not so I d</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:26:40 UTC">
      <body>o a ton of volunteering.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:26:41 UTC">
      <body>But I absolutely love nature. In free time I love to take long walks to just clear my head or just sit by the lake sometimes and enjoy the peace. Sounds</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:26:41 UTC">
      <body>a bit boring I know but with a good book or the right people it can be an amazing experience.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 13:33:12 UTC">
      <body>I'm all for enjoying the peace!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 13:33:49 UTC">
      <body>You said you're a student. What are you studying?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:40:08 UTC">
      <body>Currently a senior double majoring in political science and global health. I'm really interested in public health and medicine. But I have a long ways t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:40:38 UTC">
      <body>o go, a masters in public health and an md and phd ahead of me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:41:58 UTC">
      <body>I'm the oldest in my family and fist to attend university and in our culture thibgs are so different. there's a certain pressure to accomplish everything</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:41:58 UTC">
      <body>. So I have to live up to family expectations in a way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 13:43:03 UTC">
      <body>Which is why my favorite thing to do is break free and take my long walks and enjoy the peace and serenity of nature.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 13:44:28 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like you have a lot of ambition, but also an appreciation for having some balance.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 13:45:15 UTC">
      <body>Having been through a phd myself, I can tell you having that sense of balance will help</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:18:05 UTC">
      <body>Yes, I guess you can say I'm ambitious, my dream job is to be director of WHO. But I want no personal or financial gain out of life. I was taught to appr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:18:29 UTC">
      <body>eciate my blessings and live a simple life. So all this is just simply my way of giving back really.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:20:27 UTC">
      <body>Growing up most of my childhood was spent in my grandparents village, with no running water, daily power outages lasting 16 hours a time, and living on a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:20:27 UTC">
      <body>dollar a day. Teaches you to really appreciate the small things. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 14:22:39 UTC">
      <body>Wow! I wish you well in your endeavors. I guess your experiences would definitely give you a much different perspective than most people in this country!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:30:47 UTC">
      <body>Lol thank you. Much appreciated. What is your Phd in?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 14:46:19 UTC">
      <body>Linguistics. I started as an english major and then went into teaching english as a second language for my masters.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 14:46:19 UTC">
      <body>That meant taking linguistics classes and I totally fell in love with the subject</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:52:35 UTC">
      <body>English major, I initially thought about it, but a triple major and a minor sounds a bit much. Lol one of my dreams is to one day become a published auth</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:52:57 UTC">
      <body>or, travel to third world countries and write books on the people and stories I encounter!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131007" time="2013-05-22 14:53:56 UTC">
      <body>What do you do for a living now? Do you work in academia?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130519" time="2013-05-22 16:36:29 UTC">
      <body>I'm in semi-academia. Not a professor, but still involved in research.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
