<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140429.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-04-29 20:48:59 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>OMG awesome!!! So are we meeting tonight? Or will it be too late?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-04-29 20:50:05 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I think we'll all be there for rehearsal right?  If it has to go late thats fine with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-04-29 20:50:08 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>I'm meeting with Heeney to do photos at 7</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-04-29 20:50:08 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>I will be there. I'm not in the second dance but will def stay if we are meeting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-04-29 21:42:26 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Phinn wants to meet so let's plan on it and hopefully Lois can join</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-04-30 02:57:04 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Don't forget to send me poster so I can email it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-04-30 03:02:49 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I just sent it in an email from my comp, im not sure why it wont send from my pho e</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-04-30 03:03:28 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Got it!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-04-30 11:23:43 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Jessie gave me all the info on the flasks but she said they took 6 weeks to arrive so I guess it's too late. Any ideas? We could try to rush the order?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-04-30 11:24:48 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Lo &amp; Gabi, regarding trading cards. She suggested staying with Fox printing since they've been doing it for years and know the drill. Is that ok with you? She also said we could place a small order first if money is tight and then place a bigger order after the first weekend. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-04-30 11:25:57 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Maybe theres another place that can print on the metal faster? Might even be worth checking with amalgamated culture works(the tshirt place)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

