<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20111221.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 13:12:41 UTC">
      <body>Hey!! How's sd? Are you free to skype at all today or tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 18:22:39 UTC">
      <body>Ahahaha why were you up at 5 am? Well my time. And tmrw I should be! How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:24:55 UTC">
      <body>I'm in Paris and forgot about the time change! I was afraid I woke you up after I'd sent it haha. Anyway I'm great!! The sister thing is a disaster, I'll</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:25:05 UTC">
      <body> fill you in on that when we skype, but I'm seeing Gabriel tomorrow night! Is Johnny back from camping yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 18:36:37 UTC">
      <body>Ahhh are you excited to see him???? And he comes back in a few hours, I gotta go pick him up. Ugh to the sister thing, if it's any consolation the whole parent thing ain't so great either</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:41:29 UTC">
      <body>I'm so fucking excited I've been walking around smiling like a goon for the past few hrs. Have fun with johnny! And that sucks about your parents, I wann</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:42:35 UTC">
      <body>a hear more about it tomorrow if you want to talk. My sister went to the hospital on Friday and she's delirious on all these meds now calling my parents </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:42:36 UTC">
      <body>"mommy" and "daddy". She didn't get to go to Paris and my dad stayed back with her so Xmas should be pretty weird this yr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 18:47:03 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god Jesus, meds for what? And yeah same here, about Xmas. Def not what I was expecting. But ahh that's si cute, I hope it goes well with him!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 18:49:56 UTC">
      <body>Sleeping pills and antidepressants, I don't even know. Thanks though! Can't wait to skype w/ you :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:02:20 UTC">
      <body>Ah gnarls. But for sure, how many hours are you ahead?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:42:28 UTC">
      <body>Ps desperate housewives just skipped five years...the fuck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:45:44 UTC">
      <body>I know so weird!!! Gaby randomly gets fat haha. My friend showed me around the american university of paris today and I met a ton of people from san dieg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:45:59 UTC">
      <body>o. Reminded me of you guys :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:46:36 UTC">
      <body>Awww that's awesome!! Hehe sd is awesome. And yeah she is it's so weird!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:48:07 UTC">
      <body>It's really weird since she randomly gets hot again. Watch out for the bday cake/car/running episode with juanita. So funny! It should be coming up for you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:48:57 UTC">
      <body>Haha ojay, this is the first one from the five year skip. And god this whole deal is so odd! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:50:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah especially with lynette's kids! The whole thing is insanely weird but at least susan and mike are together</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:52:15 UTC">
      <body>Susan and mike aren't together right now. And yeah they're kids are so big and such! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:54:06 UTC">
      <body>Oh riiiight susan's with that painter. I kinda liked him. But I know it's so weird seeing the twins at that age! It gets pretty funny with them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:54:50 UTC">
      <body>Yeah seriously, he's kinda hot bit I wanna know what happened. And yeah they are, and Tom like wants to be with them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:56:34 UTC">
      <body>And soon Tom will end up going to college with them haha. You'll find out what happened soon though! Pay attention to everything w/ Edie and Dave (who is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 19:57:50 UTC">
      <body> really fucking creepy)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 19:59:01 UTC">
      <body>Yes he is! For real! And seriously? Ahaha I totally just saw the Juanita running shit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:00:19 UTC">
      <body>Haha I love it I'm gonna do that to my kids someday. What's up with Celia though? Most useless character other, she never says a word!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:01:47 UTC">
      <body>Idk who Celia is yet. I like Katherine though. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:04:25 UTC">
      <body>She's juanita's sister. And yeah the katherine stuff is good. This must be after the season with dylan and the armoire season, right? Btw girl named dyla</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:05:31 UTC">
      <body>n and guy named dana, the writers need to get their shit together</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:06:54 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for real, Tom and Lynette are funny, I wish they didn't break up. But yeah Dave is such a creep. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:08:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah there was never any reason for them to split up, I was really bummed out when they did that. Is Bree dating Megan Fox's husband yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:09:35 UTC">
      <body>No I don't know who she's with right now. Ugh why do they split up?? Stupid stupid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:11:20 UTC">
      <body>I know! They make it seem like they started fighting but they've always fought. That's pt of why their relationship worked in the first place. Dumbass writers</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:12:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah seriously, they always made up well, stupid they just ran out of ideas</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:15:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah Jane needs to go away and then they can get back together!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:16:05 UTC">
      <body>Yesssss please ughh they suck si hard! Ps what's up with Edie and the guy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:16:19 UTC">
      <body>Is he crazy? Meds?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:17:37 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god who's the one person he wants to kill?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:18:04 UTC">
      <body>Crazy and meds, but there's a twist ending a the end of the season.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:20:38 UTC">
      <body>Mike!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:23:06 UTC">
      <body>Oh of course, everyone is after mike haha. Why so? Hehehehhe I love desperate housewives</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:24:54 UTC">
      <body>He thinks mike killed his daughter in a hit and run but it turns out susan was the one who was driving, so his revenge plan gets all twisted. And I'm sad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:25:04 UTC">
      <body>, this season's the one where edie dies :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:25:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I figured it was. And oh my god wow Jesus he's so sketch</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:27:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah he talks so weird. And the albino look really isn't working for him either</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:28:04 UTC">
      <body>Yeah def not, this whole deal is so odd. "we can be happy here" yeah freak</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:29:31 UTC">
      <body>Yeah and then he tries to befriend all the husbands and they all hate him and think he's psycho, it's pretty funny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:30:04 UTC">
      <body>Jesus Christ, this is so weird hahah. He's such a paycho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:31:23 UTC">
      <body>Haha I know, he's way too sketchy. Hate him and Edie together too, no chemistry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:33:25 UTC">
      <body>Yeah they really don't, but oh my god I love Andrew. "I just heard the milk o bad, I'll be back"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131063" time="2011-12-21 20:36:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah his sense of humor is definitely one of the best on the show!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131019" time="2011-12-21 20:37:14 UTC">
      <body>Yesss I love him, he's si great! And I feel like mike and the painted being friends won't end well</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
