<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141125.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-25 00:42:40 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Hey Lindsey, how does this crit thing work??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-25 02:00:56 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Ugh. So whatever faculty thy can scrounge together come and sit and give feedback. I am going only for my editing students this year. You can come for as little or as much as you want but I think they expect us to atleast come to some.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-25 02:01:36 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Ah.  Are the vid production kids getting crits?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-25 02:01:45 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Sometimes it's fun cause they gossip about students </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-25 02:02:34 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body> Nope. No freshman. If any are sophomores they will</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-25 02:03:03 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Cool.  I like gossip.  I'll try to go for 1/2 a day or something...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-25 02:03:53 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yeah it's more fun when you don't have students screening cause you kinda feel bad for them as they get reemed by Pete</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-25 02:04:44 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>I bet Pete is a real reemer...  And is Wendy the marshmallow she seems to be, or is she rough too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-25 02:05:29 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Actually she's pretty funny and mean too around Pete. She's all like, "I don't get what you are doing. At all."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-25 02:06:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>John gives great feedback and Byron too. More constructive </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-25 02:06:39 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Well that'll be fun then.  Are the full timers there the while time?  Ugh for them.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-25 02:07:24 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Full timers are there all week all the time. So they like to get some different opinions especially with juniors and seniors</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-25 02:08:00 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Jeez, I'd hate to screen like late afternoon on the Thursday.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-11-25 02:08:00 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Cool.  Imna try to show up when you're there.  More fun that way!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-11-25 02:08:06 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>And they get lunch if there are a lot of us</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-11-25 02:08:32 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh man it's the worst. Everyone's so mad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-11-25 02:09:16 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>YESSSS! It will be hilarious. I have no idea what my students are going to turn in</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-11-25 02:09:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>They have to edit chase scenes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-11-25 02:09:33 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>And they are all soooo behind</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-11-25 02:10:08 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Ooh that's fun.  I wanna take your edit class!!  We should talk actually.  Where do you get your ftg?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-11-25 02:11:13 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I have them shoot some stuff then I have footage from Alison's editing class of monk and a nature doc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-11-25 02:12:04 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I want a short film tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-11-25 02:12:31 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Ps I should take your editing class.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-11-25 02:12:42 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Cause you are a real life editor</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-11-25 02:15:53 UTC" participant="153644">
      <body>Yeah a short film would be awesome.  Something with multiple scenes and beg-mid-end structure.  And also something else that they can be creative with in a less continuity-style way.  And sometimes I think that editing all the time doesn't actually help my teaching of editing all that much.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-11-25 02:18:34 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yeah maybe we can find a good short film to cut for structure and share it.  I also like the non continuity because that's what I actually do. We do an intellectual montage with found footage that's always cool but that's about it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-11-25 02:18:57 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Everything else is continuity.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

