<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130524.0029" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:13:32 UTC">
      <body>Hello!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:13:47 UTC">
      <body>Are you available to text?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:14:40 UTC">
      <body>Yes I'm available. How are you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:15:27 UTC">
      <body>Good, how are you doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:15:27 UTC">
      <body>Where are you texting from?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:17:19 UTC">
      <body>I'm going well thank you for asking. I'm testing from Michigan, student at UofM how about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:19:30 UTC">
      <body>I'm in the Philadelphia area. Student at west Chester u. What do you study?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:21:27 UTC">
      <body>Senior studying political science and global health. Hbu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:25:40 UTC">
      <body>Had a pre midlife crisis / epiphany and went back to school for nursing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:27:40 UTC">
      <body>Wow that's amazing that you had the courage and strength to go through school again!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:29:08 UTC">
      <body>How is The nursing program?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:30:46 UTC">
      <body>Haha, it's def an annoyance to do it oer again, but worth it in the end. It's fine, how is your program?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:40:38 UTC">
      <body>What were you doing before you decided to go back to school? My program is just the stepping stone to 50 more year of schooling hahaha I still have to go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:40:38 UTC">
      <body>through masters in public health an md and a phd on infectious disease.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:43:10 UTC">
      <body>But my program now is amazing. It covers aspects of third world public health infectious diseases the history of disease epidemics And hiv/aids. I love it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:43:52 UTC">
      <body>Ok see you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:44:16 UTC">
      <body>That's sounds really amazing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:45:06 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I'm a tad distracted was at a garden store buying a fig tree</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:45:34 UTC">
      <body>I grew up in Sudan before coming here, so I've seen what its like to be in the other end of all this. Its what drives my passion :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 09:46:04 UTC">
      <body>Lol take your time!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:58:28 UTC">
      <body>Okay back. So Sudan is an interesting place to have grown up. I have a friend from Sudan, and have seen some if his photos. You must have an interestingperspective on things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:58:28 UTC">
      <body>We kid with the friend because he comes home with malaria almost every time he comes back from visiting home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:58:28 UTC">
      <body>he shrugs off malaria as if its no big deal. very strange for us as American born</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:58:28 UTC">
      <body>Also to answer your question I was a researcher in a nonprofit taste and smell research co.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 09:58:28 UTC">
      <body>And also my program is only phase 1 as well. I will have to get masters next ad then some post masters work. It is switching to a doctoral program in 2015 also so I need to get I. Under the wire.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:04:29 UTC">
      <body>Lol yes my family is sudanese I was born here but lived in Sudan until I was in first grade then we came here and we go back to visit every year. But yes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:05:14 UTC">
      <body>malaria is like the common cold there, its really no big deal, you get it at least once a month lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:06:19 UTC">
      <body>Haha, amazing because here it is unheard of, it just SOUNDS really scary</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:07:11 UTC">
      <body>What is Sudanese cuisine like?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:12:49 UTC">
      <body>A lot of the Sudanese cuisine is similar to lots of Arab cuisine because of the Arab influence in the region throughout history. but it is amazing! Lol w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:12:49 UTC">
      <body>e use a lot of oils and thick sauces, bad for your cholesterol but amazing. I'm actually grocery shopping for things now, lol making stuffed bell pepper</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:13:09 UTC">
      <body>s. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:15:00 UTC">
      <body>Yummy! I'm on break from school until Tuesday so I have some time to cook this weekend maybe ill google a Sudanese recipe or two!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:15:52 UTC">
      <body>Eating Indian food for breakfast right now... Love the rich spicy sauces :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:16:41 UTC">
      <body>So what type of establishment or organization will you probably end up working in?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:18:15 UTC">
      <body>Yes! I do that all the time lol Indian food is amazing! I actually learned to cook a bunch of dishes, I learned how to make Indian samosas biryani and a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:18:15 UTC">
      <body>bunch of dishes from one of my roommates a few years back.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:20:40 UTC">
      <body>My friend's joke:Q- you know what they call Indian food in India? A- food.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:21:11 UTC">
      <body>I want to hopefully work with the WHO. One of my professors was the dean at the school of public health and he introduced me to the former director of th</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:21:11 UTC">
      <body>e WHO which was amazing beyond words and that has been my dream job for ages now so all this schooling and real world practice is to get me there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:22:05 UTC">
      <body>Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:22:53 UTC">
      <body>Yay! Go you! I really hope it works out, it seems like it will since you clearly have a passion for your work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:26:35 UTC">
      <body>Thank you! So what made you decide to go into the nursing program? Are you interested in a research career or do you want to work in a hospital setting o</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:26:35 UTC">
      <body>r teaching.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:30:59 UTC">
      <body>Actually I am going back for nurse midwifery. There are huge problems with women's healthcare in this country that I would like to address. Rural and und</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 10:39:50 UTC">
      <body>erserved populations are my target cliets. After a career on call, I would like to get my phd in nursing Ed. And "retire" into teaching.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 10:41:39 UTC">
      <body>That sounds amazing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131007" time="2013-05-24 11:19:48 UTC">
      <body>How long do you have to go before you complete your program?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 11:30:46 UTC">
      <body>I will be done part one in December. It was a fat program because it is my second bachelors. 18 months total. Then on to grad school 2-3 years and the midwifery cert. another 6 months. In total, I should be done in about five years.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130710" time="2013-05-24 11:30:46 UTC">
      <body>*fast, not fat</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
