<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130304.0027" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135279" time="2013-03-04 20:39:11 UTC">
      <body>After a coaching session with Steve Staum a few days ago, Dad is leading a minyan service for the 1st time tonite at the Wasserman home. [See Mom kvell  ;)  ]   We'll text you later when we're home &amp; settled. Love u. x</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 03:16:16 UTC">
      <body>Talk? Call me not dad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 20:18:23 UTC">
      <body>Remember to use speakers or 1 side of earbuds--never both. Don't mix drivin' and groovin'. Gotta hear the road. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 20:19:26 UTC">
      <body>Za- just sent u v important info via email. Pls read now. Might send another re: addl traffic resources if I find any. Love u so!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 20:26:40 UTC">
      <body>Baltimore area:
WBAL 1090 AM
All news; traffic on the 5's (3:15, 3:25, etc). 
Don't know breadth of coverage or signal strength--could cover most of route or just a chunk. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 20:28:48 UTC">
      <body>KYW 1060 Philly has traffic on the 2's</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135279" time="2013-03-05 20:38:20 UTC">
      <body>Wilmington, DE area: WDEL 1150AM. Traffic on the 9's. Remember: these stations may not do traffic &amp; weather q 10 mins. if not "drive time" or if Talk or Paid ad programming.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135279" time="2013-03-06 01:53:19 UTC">
      <body>Pls txt on arrival both days. Th&lt;x3.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135279" time="2013-03-06 02:58:05 UTC">
      <body>Yay! Now tell Ms. G. we say hey, go get some good sleep and enjoy tomorrow! Oh, and don't forget to wear ur big girl panties--it should be an amazing day!  ;D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135279" time="2013-03-07 01:09:18 UTC">
      <body>Hey, r u back at HC?? If so, call me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135080" time="2013-03-07 01:09:59 UTC">
      <body>Still in Bethesda, staying til tomorrow. Still want me to call?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135279" time="2013-03-07 01:18:56 UTC">
      <body>Yah--If ya wanna jes' talk about thuh weather or sumthin.  ~8b 
Like didja do anythin' unUsual tday??? Now, or...Dad's at Rachel's for another shiva: R'Michele's dad died. Probly home by 10. &lt;x3 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135279" time="2013-03-07 17:41:04 UTC">
      <body>Great! Thx for letting us know. Snowing lots here...we're getting yours.... &lt;x3 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135080" time="2013-03-07 20:20:28 UTC">
      <body>￼Do you have more of these?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135279" time="2013-03-07 20:32:08 UTC">
      <body>If so, they're at least 6-8 yrs old. The 1st batch I got was from a bicyclists' goods site. The last, I think, was from Lip Ivo; that info is being protected by our 3-headed dog, the hp CPU. If u find resource, pls get me 2 aloes. They had plain &amp; aloe at the time. BTW, if ur drinking enough fluids, ul minimize the dry lips issue; it's usually a 1° sx of dehydration. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
