<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130514.0037" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-05-14 18:36:52 UTC">
      <body>Thanks for that detailed Dr Tan email. Some parts of it I'm not sure I understand, but mostly I've got it. My favorite Jason Winner quote (so far): I don't know why everyone gets such a hard on about Dr Tan. It's not like he made this stuff up himself. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-05-14 18:36:57 UTC">
      <body>Good grief.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 21:54:01 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha.  The problem is that most acu schools don't teach channel acupuncture but what i'll call the herbalist zangfu  form of acupuncture.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 21:54:08 UTC">
      <body>As for new patients I was referring to patients u consider primary treatments for your patient log. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-05-14 22:11:19 UTC">
      <body>Yep I have 3 primary and 1 assist so far. I'm nervous about getting my ten people 4 times...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 22:34:40 UTC">
      <body>That's a great start. Eventually u can always team up w classmates to make sure u treat ea other 4x fill in the gaps if u have any...but then again that will be difficult to trade if u aren't willing to let others treat u.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 22:40:24 UTC">
      <body>That's a great start. Eventually u can always team up w classmates to make sure u treat ea other 4x fill in the gaps if u have any...but then again that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 22:40:25 UTC">
      <body>will be difficult to trade if u aren't willing to let others treat u.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-05-14 22:43:18 UTC">
      <body>Did you have to do that to get your 10?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131424" time="2013-05-14 23:13:23 UTC">
      <body>Not sure I *had* to but I know I did treat a bunch of classmates 4x and vice versa and they were included in my ten.  It's not like we waited until June to do it in panic - we just treated another over the course of the year and got our 4 in in case we ne</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-05-15 01:04:50 UTC">
      <body>That makes sense. Sorry if it was worded weird I just wory about scheduling people since there are weird gaps I between terms and Saturdays are full for an entire month so its hard to tell someone to return weekly when there are no slots.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131424" time="2013-05-15 01:42:07 UTC">
      <body>Lol @ the won </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131424" time="2013-05-15 01:42:24 UTC">
      <body>Wait until your patients get double booked and u have to deal with the won lack of organization </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131424" time="2013-05-15 01:42:24 UTC">
      <body>Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-05-15 01:43:01 UTC">
      <body>There are only 4 of us on Saturdays so only 2 slots. It kind of sucks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-05-15 01:43:12 UTC">
      <body>Oh I can't wait for that! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130962" time="2013-05-15 01:44:23 UTC">
      <body>How much do you know about luo channels and points? They seem really neat!!!! (So dorky.) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131424" time="2013-05-15 02:05:52 UTC">
      <body>They are neat.  Different theories as to how and when to use them.  St40 doesn't resolve phlegm randomly - it's the luo of the spleens 5e pair!!! Deadman says group w sp3 and has list of diff luo source pairings </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
