<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110923.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 14:00:51 UTC">
      <body>Hasn't come! Want to just give me a check in Philly? I think that's easiest and I'm cool w that!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2011-09-23 14:03:13 UTC">
      <body>Aw man, that is so frustrating. What in the world happened? Are you sure that's cool? It's not a small amount! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:14:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm sure it will get here or maybe is lost in mess of farm, but don't want safety of check to be comprised. Np about waiting till Philly - I don't spend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:14:25 UTC">
      <body>$ out here at all and will be a welcome boost to acct in October :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:14:27 UTC">
      <body>Btw! I think I'd like the smallest room. Same Amt (400) as mid size. R u ok w that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:14:29 UTC">
      <body>I just like small spaces :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2011-09-23 17:15:45 UTC">
      <body>Sure! It's all yours. Weirdest thing about that check but I'll cancel it to be safe. Thank you for your flexibility and understanding. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:42:39 UTC">
      <body>But of course!! Do u have to pay a fee to cancel?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131839" time="2011-09-23 17:43:31 UTC">
      <body>I was wondering about that too, it's possible. But better safe than sorry.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 17:44:57 UTC">
      <body>Ok well let me know if so and I'll split w ya or something. Hopefully not! What about the bedroom? Any thoughts? Know you haven't seen then in person.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131839" time="2011-09-23 17:47:47 UTC">
      <body>Oh yea, I meant to say that the bedroom is all yours. I'm indebted to you (literally and figuratively)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2011-09-23 17:50:34 UTC">
      <body>And no worries about the fee, but I really appreciate it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135140" time="2011-09-23 18:54:35 UTC">
      <body>Ok! :) And thanks! The room  mid room is nice, good size, has to use the closet in the hall but has room for a dresser too.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
