<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130515.0075" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-05-15 12:34:42 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>a what this could be or where I should have it towed?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-05-15 12:34:46 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>need some car advice. car is completely dead. doors won't unlock, no lights, and does nothing when I turn the key. ran perfectly fine on Monday. any ide</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-05-15 12:39:59 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>If it does nothing at all the battery must be dead or completely disconnected. You can try having it jump started if it's parked somewhere that's doable</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-05-15 12:40:44 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Otherwise I recommend having it towed to my mechanics at ###########, at #######################. They're totally friendly and awesome :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-05-15 12:43:58 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>cool! I have AAA  so I could call them for a jump, right? guessing I prob need a new battery. should I go to ur garage to get this?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-05-15 12:44:16 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Their number is ############ if you want to call them. If you talk to a guy named #### just tell him your friend ######## always brings her ####### there and says they're the best ;-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-05-15 12:45:48 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Oh yeah, definitely call AAA. They can do full battery replacements on site now, I think. But if they can't or really even if they do, you might want to have the car looked over to make sure nothing is draining on the battery</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-05-15 12:47:21 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>It's weird for one to suddenly die in a day unless you leave lights on our something. Usually you'll notice it being a little sluggish to start and get worse over time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-05-15 12:47:45 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Sorry for novel of texts, hope that helps :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-05-15 12:48:39 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>ent times!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-05-15 12:52:38 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>ok cool! thanks so much. I'll call both places after I walk #### to ############## for her surgery today. Of course these things never happen at conveni</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-05-15 12:52:46 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>today. at least I'm off today. which is a big help.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-05-15 12:52:49 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>It deffinitely helps! I'll call the garage first and tell them my predicament then call AAA to see if they can get me started so I can drop the car off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-05-15 12:54:20 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Let me know if I can do anything! And good luck to you and #### :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-05-15 12:58:52 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>lly by this afternoon both ###### and car will be on the mend.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2013-05-15 12:58:56 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>U have already helped me tons. If I had to have the same conversation w/ my dad it would have been so stressful. I'll let u know how we make out. hopefu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-05-15 12:59:33 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Keep me posted!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

