<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130612.0005" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 11:03:47 UTC">
      <body>Good morning. How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 11:05:15 UTC">
      <body>Frazzled. Stupid alarm didn't go off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 11:14:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh no, are you late for anything?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:14:49 UTC">
      <body>No thankfully. I did have a meeting about 10 minutes after I got to the office though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 13:21:31 UTC">
      <body>Yikes! Rough start. Are you a bio-exorcist?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:23:00 UTC">
      <body>Um... wut?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 13:25:18 UTC">
      <body>Freelance. Like the movie</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:27:11 UTC">
      <body>Freelance the movie? I know of freelance whales...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 13:30:11 UTC">
      <body>Not full time whales? Doing their own thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 13:30:36 UTC">
      <body>Beetlejuice the movie</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:34:04 UTC">
      <body>etting at</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:35:00 UTC">
      <body>Ahhhh right. It just popped into my head when they asked for a username. But yea freelance whales is too hipster for me to have any idea what they were g</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 13:37:49 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, they were just stringing words together. It's every hipsters dream to be a blue whale</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 13:51:13 UTC">
      <body>Haha and fight the Japanese. So why Muggs?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 14:02:37 UTC">
      <body>It was a nickname a friend gave me a long time ago. No one uses it anymore so I thought I would bring it back. With strangers. In text form.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 14:16:45 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha well if you love it THAT much.... so what are you up to today muggsy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 20:20:55 UTC">
      <body>Had a long sunny day. Just getting home and making a quick dinner now. How was your day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 21:33:18 UTC">
      <body>Haha this conversation feels so similar to one I would have with someone I've known for a while. I wonder if this is how chat rooms became popular... tod</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 21:42:30 UTC">
      <body>ay was fine, stayed busy at work so it didn't feel like an eternal day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 21:44:36 UTC">
      <body>I guess it's just nice to check in with someone. Good to hear work went well. Did you get to do anything for fun?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 21:47:01 UTC">
      <body>Have you had any significant others recently? Yea I went to dinner with some friends from my Bible study. I'm leaving my project after 9 months of beinghere every week so people are saying goodbye and stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 22:00:41 UTC">
      <body>I'm currently seeing someone, good guy. Dinner with friends sounds nice, where do you go now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131523" time="2013-06-12 22:52:02 UTC">
      <body>I've been going to Jersey for a while. Near new York though. I didn't think Muggs would be a girls nickname</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130664" time="2013-06-12 22:58:48 UTC">
      <body>Yep, I'm a lady. Did you eat in ny? I want to go to the rain room at the moma</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 09:29:11 UTC">
      <body>Hmm never heard of the rain room. Sounds cool though. Haha we eat in jersey, tons of restaurants so it would be a waste to travel in</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 09:40:13 UTC">
      <body>Are you getting crazy storms where you are?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 09:41:34 UTC">
      <body>No but I hear its bad back in Virginia. Where abouts are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 09:43:31 UTC">
      <body>Downpour just started, it's really dark. I had so many bike errands to run today...It's kind of nice to put my day on hold though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 09:45:08 UTC">
      <body>Do you only bike places?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 09:48:22 UTC">
      <body>I have a car, but I try to mostly bike. Parking is so frustrating in the city, I try to avoid it. Do you bike?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 09:51:33 UTC">
      <body>Yea I really like to bike when I can. I have a sweet road bike that I built myself. Only cost me $50. Do you not want to say which city you are in?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130664" time="2013-06-13 09:55:33 UTC">
      <body>Wow, that's great. I'm in Philly, so center city is always under construction and the streets are terrible. Not to mention über aggressive drivers</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131523" time="2013-06-13 09:58:16 UTC">
      <body>So I have heard! My prof told me they saw someone hit 17 cars in on accident. Also, nice use of the umlaut</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
