<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130710.0048" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131838" time="2013-07-10 23:24:45 UTC">
      <body>Text me your plan and eta!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131838" time="2013-07-10 23:25:40 UTC">
      <body>Ps. No pressure!  Were you able to get my dad's ticket refunded?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137406" time="2013-07-11 13:44:43 UTC">
      <body>How are you??  Not sure yet what time I arrive, will know more when on the road and will keep u posted.  I don't want to interfere with ur routine, I can meet u at playhouse. What's good for you?  Do u have things to do before play? Rehearse? I see play is sold out. I prefer to get there early so I can get a good seat. Don't worry about your dads ticket. I think it's non refundable.  But if u know somebody who needs it, let me know. See you soon! Yeah!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131838" time="2013-07-11 14:13:32 UTC">
      <body>Ok, let me know when you're close. I can meet you anytime and we'll make plans together. Please be careful! Love ya, can't wait to see you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131838" time="2013-07-11 20:21:56 UTC">
      <body>Are u here? I'm rehearsing, I'll be out in 20!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131838" time="2013-07-11 20:22:11 UTC">
      <body>Maybe 15</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="137406" time="2013-07-11 20:22:46 UTC">
      <body>Don't rush</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137406" time="2013-07-11 20:22:51 UTC">
      <body>Take time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137406" time="2013-07-12 03:26:48 UTC">
      <body>Just got home.   In driveway. The play was wonderful!!  I overheard a guy said that he feels guilty and should have paid  200 per ticket. Another lady said it was better then broadway!!!  I agree!  You were fantastic.  Im so happy I went.   Have fun!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131838" time="2013-07-12 03:41:43 UTC">
      <body>Thank u so much for coming!!! &lt;3!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="137406" time="2013-07-12 04:06:57 UTC">
      <body>Loved every minute. Except I really wanted to stay.  I just got into bed now.  If I stayed, I would have gotten home too late.and be too tired. it was harder in the dark. I even made a wrong turn, that cost me a half hour longer.  But, I'm home now safe.  Enjoy the rest of the shows.  Keep me posted. I'm curious if the local paper is going to have reviews.  Just a great show!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="137406" time="2013-07-12 04:20:02 UTC">
      <body>I didn't see the people from the restaurant.  So, they weren't kyle parents!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131838" time="2013-07-12 06:07:29 UTC">
      <body>Whew! They weren't! Thanks again for coming, glad u got home safely. Love ya!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
