<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121105.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135391" time="2012-11-05 19:07:52 UTC">
      <body>By the way I'm really sorry for my behavior at the party last week - I'm usually not like that, and I've been really embarrased about how it all went down - thanks for taking care of me that night - hopefully i can redeem myself somehow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2012-11-05 23:28:15 UTC">
      <body>Oh Andy that's so nice of you to apologize don't worry </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-11-05 23:28:20 UTC">
      <body>It's all cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135391" time="2012-11-05 23:31:52 UTC">
      <body>Well ive been really embarrised about what i did and ive been stressing about it and wanted you to know im usually not like that at all - i owe you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:27:33 UTC">
      <body>U don't owe me. Don't stress!!! One party. Still had a great time. You just got drunk...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:27:45 UTC">
      <body>Don't apologize to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:28:43 UTC">
      <body>The only person who needs to be apologized and thanks is Fabiola   She was the one who took care of you for hours.  I was dancing I didn't even know it was going on. I didn't even know you puked</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:28:56 UTC">
      <body>Until Fabiola said so</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135391" time="2012-11-06 02:30:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah i talked to her too - i just feel like an ass for everything and wanted to make sure you knew i was sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:33:49 UTC">
      <body>Oh well stop feeling like an ass. This was weeks ago</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130622" time="2012-11-06 02:59:45 UTC">
      <body>I want you to know I really appreciate this apology and I want to move on from this.  This morning I left the burner on.  Stupider than getting drunk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135391" time="2012-11-06 03:02:12 UTC">
      <body>Cool - glad your stove didnt burn the place down - i think you're awesome and wanted to make sure we were cool</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
