<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130706.0002" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 11:30:17 UTC">
      <body>Sorry to hear that your dishwasher is still giving you problems...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 11:42:43 UTC">
      <body>Hmm I'm not having dishwasher problems</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 11:44:25 UTC">
      <body>Haha that's good. How did u know the last person i talked to did? Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 11:50:09 UTC">
      <body>Hahah I think your last message to them got sent to me because I got a message that said sorry you're still having dishwasher problems</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 13:12:49 UTC">
      <body>Haha weird... Yeah that whole convo was bizarre. I asked how he was (assuming it was a he) and he was complaining of a sulfur smell coming from his dishwasher. Didnt hear from him for another 12 hours. Then he said it was hard for him to sleep and he bet i could sleep easily because the lord blessed me. Weiiiiiiiirdo.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 13:12:49 UTC">
      <body>Probably drunk in the latter portion of the text convo.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 13:14:46 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha well at least it sounds like he was interesting! How are you today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 13:14:46 UTC">
      <body>Anyway, how's your saturday going thus far?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 13:25:18 UTC">
      <body>It's pretty good I'm on vacation in Arizona going to a rodeo today! Haha should be interesting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 13:25:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm good. Just arrived in pittsburgh abt 30 min ago. I came up for my friend's 21st. She and a bunch of ppl are going to the taylor swift concert so i'mjust chilling on their couch trying to figure out what to do haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 13:27:30 UTC">
      <body>Ooh fun I've never been to Pittsburgh you're not goin to the concert with them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 13:30:10 UTC">
      <body>No. I decided to come up at the last minute since i wasnt scheduled to work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 14:44:13 UTC">
      <body>Ooh well I'm not really a Taylor swift fan so I'd be glad I didn't have to go haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 15:07:18 UTC">
      <body>Lol i dont mind her, but i'm definitely not a die hard fan either.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 15:56:04 UTC">
      <body>Omg it was so ungodly hot in my friends' apt that i had to walk to a cafe to cool off haha. Is it really hot in az?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 15:57:23 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah I heard its like in the 90s and super humid back east! It's in the 90s here but not humid so it's not too bad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 15:58:46 UTC">
      <body>That must be nice haha. Yeah it's really humid and gross. And my friends dont have a/c so it was miserable haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 16:06:12 UTC">
      <body>Ugh yeah that's awful I live in a basement apartment in NYC without a/c it gets so gross and damp down there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 16:12:17 UTC">
      <body>Yuck. Is it ok during the winter?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="132520" time="2013-07-06 16:13:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah my landlord keeps it really hot so it's nice and toasty</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="134923" time="2013-07-06 16:15:09 UTC">
      <body>I lived in an apt my senior year of college that had automatic heat. It got so hot it was unhealthy. It hit at least 95 degrees in my bathroom.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
