<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110611.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135094" time="2011-06-11 02:10:38 UTC">
      <body>Are you gonna get a chance to see tree of life? Also. I think we're having a party at our house tomorrow night. House warming or something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2011-06-11 02:11:44 UTC">
      <body>Yea once im up there I'll do my damndest. Party huh? That could be funnnn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135094" time="2011-06-11 02:13:21 UTC">
      <body>Ok. Let me know. Cause I'd go again. And scotty and jeanne need to see it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2011-06-11 02:14:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh cool, yea. Im moving up for good on Sunday but don't start until next week so I'll have plenty of time. maybe it would make more sense I'd you guys tell me when you can cone up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135094" time="2011-06-11 02:19:45 UTC">
      <body>Still struggling with the iphone keyboard? But ya that makes sense.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2011-06-11 02:20:46 UTC">
      <body>Pfh just 'cone'... Give a bitch a break. I have sausage fingers. Look at tylers for reference </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135094" time="2011-06-11 02:36:03 UTC">
      <body>Also I'd instead of if. I think. Read anything good?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2011-06-11 02:37:47 UTC">
      <body>Blah not really I read articles more than things I should read like books</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135094" time="2011-06-11 03:11:18 UTC">
      <body>I've been reading f scott fitzgerald short stories. Makes me want nyc. And yale. Or nyc and yale in 1910.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131839" time="2011-06-12 00:30:23 UTC">
      <body>When does the party start offich? Half word</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135094" time="2011-06-12 00:49:49 UTC">
      <body>Scotty gets off work at 9:30. So around then I guess. Not sure if there is an official start. Not sure if there is an offich start either. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135094" time="2011-06-12 23:03:55 UTC">
      <body>How's the apartm?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2011-06-12 23:09:11 UTC">
      <body> Its alright. The person who greeted me was really bitchy and made me cry. But now I'm eating dinner with meg.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135094" time="2011-06-12 23:12:17 UTC">
      <body>Oh yikes. Who was the person? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2011-06-12 23:29:31 UTC">
      <body> A friend of my roommate who I still haven't met</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135094" time="2011-06-12 23:33:48 UTC">
      <body>Right. I remember that now. First time seeing megan back?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131839" time="2011-06-12 23:34:23 UTC">
      <body>Yes :) drunk on wine. I had such a good time last night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135094" time="2011-06-12 23:41:38 UTC">
      <body>I had a nice night too. Despite the blueberries and broken lion and tyler sicky and other stuff. Glad you came. Have fun with megan.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131839" time="2011-06-12 23:49:04 UTC">
      <body>Thanks. I like you a lot sam. thanks for having me. And putting up with Tyler</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
