<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130328.0055" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137376" time="2013-03-28 12:48:50 UTC">
      <body>Got into vassar</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132437" time="2013-03-28 22:40:27 UTC">
      <body>What is your computer password </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137376" time="2013-03-29 00:32:06 UTC">
      <body>Send me a text if I don't answer your call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 00:32:49 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 06:51:15 UTC">
      <body>Good morning Soraya. I love you so much and I am thinking of you non-stop. Please check your email when you have a chance. I am sending you a message. From me to you :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137376" time="2013-03-29 07:24:06 UTC">
      <body>I hate this</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 07:26:49 UTC">
      <body>Me too. But it will get better.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 12:30:45 UTC">
      <body>How is everything? Are you getting any support from your close friends? Are you talking to anybody about it? Don't worry about anything right now. You have all the time in the world and many opinions. Be assured that you will end up doing what makes you happy. I am behind you no matter what and will support all your decisions. I am trying to call you but to no avail. I checked the itinerary and you are supposedly having a break right now!!!! I 'll try later between my classes. I love you very much. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137376" time="2013-03-29 12:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Everything is fine-ish? I haven't cried or anything but it sucks obviously. I think I will choose mcgill </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 13:33:50 UTC">
      <body>One day you will either laugh it off and/or regret having been upset about the rejections. Or will never ever get over it!!! Who knows. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 17:23:57 UTC">
      <body>How are you feeling? It seems you haven't been able  to answer the phone. But I would love to hear your voice. Call if you can/want. Love </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 19:15:42 UTC">
      <body>I am almost 87% over it!!!!! :D </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 19:17:13 UTC">
      <body>Not that your college options have  anything to do with me. I was set up!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 21:41:17 UTC">
      <body>Come to think of it. I am guessing that you are relieved that you didn't get into the Thursday universities. Maybe part of you was trying to please... I am not sure, but I think it is a strong possibility. Also I am happy you are with your friends out there at this 'juncture' and not with the moaning groaning parents! Hahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="137376" time="2013-03-29 23:42:12 UTC">
      <body>Feeling better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 23:43:17 UTC">
      <body>This is soda, I love you and I hope everything goes well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 23:43:50 UTC">
      <body>I'm mean soda, you know how auto- correct is. And coffe says hello</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 23:44:39 UTC">
      <body>We are reaching you from firenausle phone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 23:44:50 UTC">
      <body>ttyl</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="137376" time="2013-03-29 23:47:07 UTC">
      <body>Thanks &lt;3 I love you both very much </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="132437" time="2013-03-29 23:47:28 UTC">
      <body>This is mummy. I am delighted that your feeling butter. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
