<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141118.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-18 12:50:08 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Was emmy in her crate this morning? Cause I couldn't remember if her crate was locked and I went to the bathroom later on and she didn't cry!
Also, do you know if you have room for Vermont? Only because he needs to figure out whether to by a ticket for Thursday or Friday. Thursday's tickets are already $40 so he wants to know so he can buy them soon. Otherwise he'll wait till Friday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-18 12:53:17 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Just buy the ticket for Thursday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-18 12:53:58 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>You didn't put her in her crate last night.. I did</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-18 12:54:24 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>....but.....didn't you ask me to put her in her crate? Didn't I put her in her crate? Holy cannoli why can't I remember what I did?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-18 12:55:56 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>You didn't do it. I woke up at like 11 or something and your lights were off and Emmy was still on my bed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-18 12:58:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I went to bed around 12:30. Oh man. My bad. I'm sorry. I must've thought I did it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-18 12:59:58 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lord. You're going crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-18 13:02:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>NO! I figured it out! I was going to put her in her crate but I didn't want her to cry. So I turned off my room light and very quietly went to the bathroom. Tipsy came down and that must've been when you woke up and put emmy in her crate. Cause that was around 11 and I didn't sleep till 1230. I came up, but then I couldn't remember whether you said to put her outside or in her crate so around 11:40 I looked in your room and saw the crate closed and since she wasn't crying I let her sleep. So I thought it was her crate and ended up thinking I had to put her outside. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-18 13:02:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>That was it! My mind is now officially frazzled. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-18 13:04:45 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Haha okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-18 15:47:12 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I just watched the honey badger don't care video like 3 times. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-18 15:49:49 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Hahaha you're crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-18 19:49:25 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>So I hustle my butt to the office and he says "oh let's just leave it" mofo it cold out. Could have told me over the phone lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-11-18 19:52:32 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Really?!?!? Oh that's awful! I'm surprised he didn't want to put them. Probably figured they wouldn't stay. That's annoying. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-11-18 19:53:13 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah. He was actually gonna remove some attachments but since I can get my trays on and off he left it alone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-11-18 19:53:50 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Really?! I wish he'd remove some of mine. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-11-18 19:54:32 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol I'm all ready missing attachments in 3 teeth</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-11-18 21:22:22 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Feel free to watch an episode of angel eyes. I won't be able to watch anything tonight or tomorrow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-11-18 21:24:57 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>I won't watch it lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-11-18 21:29:04 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. On the plus side, all I gotta do is finish citing my PowerPoint which is all of 5 slides, and then I can just study for my exam tonight and tomorrow! Ohhh yeahhh!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-11-18 21:29:31 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol niice</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-11-19 00:57:18 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Watch trailer #1 for a movie called what if with Daniel Radcliffe. The first 10 seconds absolutely had me dying. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-11-19 12:37:20 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>There's 60 in of snow in buffalo, ny. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-11-19 12:41:17 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Oh lord. They can keep all that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-11-19 12:41:36 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Right? I told opa that I wish we had some snow and he told me about buffalo. He was like "you want that?!" But technically it's a snow storm caused by a lake? At least we don't have a lake. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

