<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150210.0018" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-10 00:30:17 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Did you leave yet? Why do I always miss you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-10 00:49:02 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Did I really miss you?! Noooo! It's because of the spotty/shitty reception in my house. If I sit on the couch I lose signal and I don't hear my phone ring. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-10 03:24:31 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Alrighty darling. Time for work. I love you so so much. Have a good night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-10 03:25:17 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I love you too! Still working on my microbio. Feel like I'm going to be here for a while!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-10 03:26:07 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>No no no. Dont do that, baby. That sounds yucky. Finish up quickly and relax!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-10 03:28:18 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I know. My sister wasn't in the mood for helping me so I'm kinda on my own. But it's okay. I don't know what I'm doing and frankly, I don't give a damn! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-02-10 03:29:51 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Woah!! My beau's feelin a little rebellious tonight! Dang haha. Then definitely get it out of the way haha. No need to mess up an evening with hw</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-02-10 03:34:11 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I already had a breakdown doing this. I don't know how to make the graphs and my sister kept saying I don't know so I broke down. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-02-10 03:35:24 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Oh darling no no. Dont worry. Youre doing really well in both classes. Dont let it trip you up. You got this. Dont worry about any silly graphs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-02-10 03:40:46 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Oh but I am! I can't get the graph to look right with the right axis and it's driving me insane. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-02-10 04:08:29 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>:-/ can you leave it for now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-02-10 04:12:23 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Due tomorrow. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-02-10 04:14:27 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Gah ok, my love. Good luck!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-02-10 05:00:59 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I gave up. I got the graphs and I think those are okay but I don't think it's any good. I wound up emailing my lab partner to see if he knows how to fill out a table. If he doesn't, then I'm going to ask adam for help after lab and then send it to him afterwards. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-02-10 05:02:41 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Thatll work. It'll be fine. Its late and youve got a big day tomorrow. Time for some sleeps</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-02-10 05:09:29 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Yes. Omg. I've never been so worked up over a lab assignment before. I think it was because I completely forgot about it and instead of being able to ask crystal all weekend, I was only about to ask her for like an hour and she didn't want to help me and excel kept shutting down, not saving my graphs! Ugh. It was an awful night! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-02-10 05:11:02 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I'm just glad it was Adam's class and not my chem class. Otherwise I'd be afraid to ask for help on the day it's due! But finally time for sleep!!! I love you baby! You be safe getting home!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-02-10 05:12:27 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Its over, my love. Sorry it was so crappy. But youre done! I love you so so much. Sleep well, darling</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-02-10 05:12:57 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Thanks baby! You sleep too eventually...when you get home. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-02-10 05:14:31 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Ha will do. Cant wait. Im in a super shit mood being here...i wanna go home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-02-10 05:28:03 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I know baby. I want you to come home too. Just think of this 3 more months on this and then you graduate!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-02-10 05:28:14 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Well, 4 but that's still okay!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-02-10 05:29:24 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Mmmmhm. Tis the dream :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-02-10 05:30:14 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>:D living it with you!! Okie, going to bed. I love you baby!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-02-10 05:31:34 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Sweetest dreams, my love :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-02-10 22:08:05 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Getting into the car. Sorry. Can I call ya later?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-02-10 22:16:22 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Yes of course!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

