<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140326.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-03-26 01:18:35 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Hi Gabi my son is sick - just woke with a high fever - so I won't make it tonight. Please feel free to call if you guys need me for anything!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-03-26 01:20:25 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>I just realized we have 4 rehearsals before opening week</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-03-26 01:21:04 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Lois when should we start dancing Tuesday nights? We should give the dancers a heads up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-03-26 11:56:58 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Church is out.  Now we're hoping to do fri the 9, load out, load in for a late night show on sat plus sunday for opening weekend at contois.  Weve got 5 rehearsals plus the photo shoot and dress rehearsals.  Lois is finding cigar girls.  Phin needs to work out an insurance issue and get bca to sponsor us.  Im gonna start fundraising and as soon as we have real show dates ill start selling ads.  Im gonna join the costume closet fun on fri.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-03-26 15:21:36 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Ok great thanks. We already have Stephanie as cigar girl one right? I will wait to send email. Isn't it 4 Sundays since we have Easter and photoshoot?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-03-26 15:23:44 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>And yay about costume closet. I need to confirm water is gone!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-03-26 16:33:55 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>We do have steph, lo is looking for one more. We decided to rehearse on easter.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-03-26 16:46:56 UTC" participant="152548">
      <body>Ok. I won't be in town for Easter but I can check with the other dancers</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

