<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121002.0012" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135436" time="2012-10-02 02:34:56 UTC">
      <body>Hey girl, how's your project? a little bird (karina) told me you were in a bit of a panic about it. i'm at home, but if you want to talk it through give me a call or email me images or something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2012-10-02 02:35:13 UTC">
      <body>Oh your nice I'm just a crazy person</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135436" time="2012-10-02 02:39:07 UTC">
      <body>Ha. Ok, just havin' your back. remember that the worst thing that can happen is that you make a bad piece of art. nbd. we're in the lucky position of being somewhere were we can take risks and fail and learn from it. that's why we're here, right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2012-10-02 02:40:52 UTC">
      <body>Haha I know in really fine... Just got super lost for a moment,  it hard not to have my paints and materials all the time. But I get to work with concept.... Just so different to unravel!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135436" time="2012-10-02 02:42:39 UTC">
      <body>Totally! show it to me tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-10-02 02:43:49 UTC">
      <body>Haha. It's not that art doesn't deal with context it's just that there is so much pressure for a solution where I never had to decide with painting- they usually told me.  I just gotta learn to let the abstract ideas guide me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2012-10-02 02:44:17 UTC">
      <body>Come back.  Its cuddle time!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135436" time="2012-10-02 02:48:25 UTC">
      <body>It must be incredibly difficult to work in such a drastically different mode. i'm impressed that you're so outside your comfort zone. if i could teleport i'd be all over studio-cuddle time, but as is, i'm eating cereal in my undies on the couch. pretty cozy. see you tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2012-10-02 02:53:43 UTC">
      <body>Whoa jealous.  Nice </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
