<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150317.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-17 22:59:25 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Can Ingrid and i come to California for a long weekend in early May?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-17 22:59:46 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>She's the pregnant one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-17 23:12:51 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>Of course, and I'll take care of the delivery, if necessary!
</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-17 23:14:04 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-17 23:14:22 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Ok so we are thinking about four days btw the fifth And 11th. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-17 23:14:49 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Do u have miles? Or should buy a ticket and call u back</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-17 23:34:02 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>5 to 11 May OK.
1. If you leave on the 11 it'll have to be either early in the morning from Orange County airport (SNA) or late in the evening from either SNA or LAX because I have a telephone meeting beginning at 1:00 PM and I'll have prepare for it.
2. Saturday evening Desy and I have Season Concert tickets for the philharmonic (great pianist) playing, and if OK I'll get two tickets for you and Ingrid (maybe the experience will have her give birth to a musical prodigy!)
3. May 14 I have to be in Miami for Grand Ma anniversary. Paul and Susan are planning to come down, so check their schedule since I was planning to spend a couple of days with them.
4. As for plane fare or mileage award I'll pay for it either way. If you can get a round trip for $300 or less, I'll pay, if not see how many miles are required both on AA and Delta.
Does Ingrid eat </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-17 23:42:16 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>￼￼￼￼￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-17 23:52:12 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-18 01:38:40 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>yes. she eats rabbit and loves the idea of the philharmonic</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-18 01:39:26 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>can you give me a time frame for monday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-18 02:23:15 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>If you leave out of SNA, as long as I can drop you off no later than11:00 AM , it's OK</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-18 16:10:52 UTC" participant="152234">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

