<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130112.0039" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-01-12 14:47:50 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Sure - I have a lesson at 3 today but I'll be around otherwise, and tomorrow I'll be free after 2 or so. Give me a call whenever!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-01-12 16:06:24 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body>Ok! Thanks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-01-12 16:53:20 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body>I'm actually not riding Louie this afternoon. I forgot I told my boyfriend I'd go to his brothers house with him. So If you want to ride Louie you can! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-01-12 17:12:42 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ok, thank you! Let me check with Tanya, I'll either ride him for my lesson or hack him. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-01-12 18:53:26 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Want me to do anything with the cut - scrub it out or put anything on it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-01-12 19:14:08 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body>Would you mind putting the ice boot one and wrapping it after? The ice boot is in the freezer in the garage and the wrap is on my trunk? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-01-12 19:15:26 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Sure - does the wrap stay on overnight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-01-12 19:16:16 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body> Yes. Thank you very much!!! I'm an airhead and forgot I had these plans this afternoon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-01-12 19:25:53 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>No problem! I'm gonna lesson on dollar &amp; hack Louie. I'll let you know if he feels off at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-01-12 19:26:56 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body>Thanks. The stiffness for the first 10 minutes is normal. Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-01-12 19:48:36 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Yup, Tanya warned me about that!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-01-12 23:01:32 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Hey, Louie did feel off on that left front - ok at the walk, not so much trotting right, really noticeable trotting left. I iced ~20 minutes &amp; wrapped. That boot is great, much easier than cold hosing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-01-12 23:15:12 UTC" participant="153301">
      <body>Thanks! I thought me might be off. I appreciate you taking care I him. And I love the ice boot! It's Tanya's </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

