<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141020.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-20 22:21:58 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Hi Kyle, I know you watch football on Sundays and I'm sorry to ask you but I think your the only person who is available Sundays- do you think you could cover Sunday November 2nd 1-3pm for me? Lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-20 22:22:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Don'thateme! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-20 23:02:13 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>Hey. I don't mind covering your whole shift that day if you want the day off, but it's really not worth anyone's time to ask them to cover two hours. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-20 23:17:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oh ok I don't the day covered - is that better for you?? I'll give you the whole day? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-20 23:17:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I figured that would be worse </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-20 23:17:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Personally, I'd love to come in for just two hourS! So def ask me if you ever need or want that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-20 23:23:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Eh basically I need to cover the gallery 1-6 that day bc everyone is out and our intern is out of the country on holiday or something so let me know if you can do Sunday and if not I'll just close the gallery that day nbd </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-20 23:24:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It isn't like a family emergency so feel free to say no. Just thought maybe you wouldn't mind bc 12-3 is good tip time/it's the busy time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-20 23:25:28 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I can also open and you can come whenever? Like 10-3 just so you don't need to be awake at 7am </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-20 23:34:24 UTC" participant="152771">
      <body>So I'd rather just open-3. I never just wanna come in for a few hours, it's really not worth it to me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-21 01:14:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ok fair enough. I texted w my boss and explained that I simply can't do it so no worries. I'll just keep my shift and bother you when I have an actual emergency/super important thing and really desperately need a Sunday covered </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-10-21 01:14:25 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Bc you're the only person who can do Sundays I was told?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-10-21 01:15:13 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I guess heads up but at Some point I need to visit my grandmother in Romania in coming two months and I'll need 2Sundays covered :/ I'll let you know far far in advance tho </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-10-21 01:16:06 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Thnx and see you soon </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

