<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150212.0023" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-12 21:58:24 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Well, I just made it through the interview. It was challenging but good, I think.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-12 21:59:19 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Congrats! Did you feel
Prepared?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-12 22:01:51 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Yes and no. In hindsight some of the questions were so obvious but I had to talk on the fly because I hadn't really thought about it. But, I feel like I held my ground and did not look foolish. :D thanks again for your help!!! I would have been totally unprepared if it weren't for your guidance!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-12 22:03:37 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I bet you did great! Did they say when they will let you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-12 22:05:38 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>They said they will finish interviews tomorrow and will be in touch in a few weeks. They made it very clear that it will take time on their end to organize the campus visit and asked that I be patient. I guess that's a good sign? Like don't take another offer until you hear from us?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-12 22:06:14 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>The people were sooooo nice. I wanted to beg them for the job but I refrained.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-02-12 22:07:14 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yes that's a great sign! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-02-12 22:07:32 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>They probably have to hire by June. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-02-12 22:07:56 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>But I bet it goes by faster</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-02-12 22:17:36 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Man, I hope so. Hey, I've been wanting  to ask you about your swim routine and see if I can tag along sometime. If the Y lets non members visit.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-02-12 22:22:29 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Well keep me posted! I get to bring a guest three times a month! Texhnically no pool for guests I can't imagine how they would know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-02-12 22:22:41 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>The pool is under used!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-02-12 22:23:09 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>We should try it and play dumb if we get caught! Also SAUNA</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-02-12 22:24:00 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>Awesome!!! Let me know when you plan to go next. I'd LOVE to swim and sauna sometime maybe even once a month with you!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-02-12 22:33:03 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>YES! Maybe next week? Post work swim sauna?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-02-12 22:33:34 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I'm about to get my taxes done by a professional. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-02-12 22:33:39 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-02-12 22:36:48 UTC" participant="153633">
      <body>You are way ahead of me. And good for you for not DIYing it!! Next week would be great. I'm open any night.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

