<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130421.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-04-21 23:59:32 UTC">
      <body>Do u know who honked at u today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131424" time="2013-04-21 23:59:42 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-04-22 00:00:26 UTC">
      <body>Oh yes I do! In your hot shot silver car!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-04-22 00:03:35 UTC">
      <body>You were driving too fast to note that I joined this century and got hand me down skinny jeans from my friend Mary Ebeling (your patient!!). She is so good to me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131424" time="2013-04-22 00:59:36 UTC">
      <body>Mary = so sweet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-04-22 00:59:44 UTC">
      <body>Welcome to this century!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131424" time="2013-04-22 00:59:44 UTC">
      <body>But...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131424" time="2013-04-22 00:59:44 UTC">
      <body>Aren't u supposed to be locked inside all weekend studying?  Hahaha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-04-22 02:06:31 UTC">
      <body>More like drinking booze and watching Hulu! I only have a Rolly final and a Les final. It should be ok! Rolly isn't a regurgitate kind if tester so his exam will reveal how juicy my knowledge is! I like his tests alot. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131424" time="2013-04-22 02:32:06 UTC">
      <body>haha.  Sounds like u are making the best of the situation!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 01:01:18 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 14:33:21 UTC">
      <body>Do you think your voice is more lack of shout than weep? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 14:34:18 UTC">
      <body>Also I just was clicking thru the won calendar and am saved by the bell! I only have to miss one week of Eds summer class because one day falls on July 4 and it appears that the school is closed! Yippee!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131424" time="2013-04-23 21:38:51 UTC">
      <body>Good news for you!  Hmmm re voice. Don't think my voice tails off like a weeper...I guess lack of shout???  Y do u ask? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 22:32:42 UTC">
      <body>I was just thinking about cf last night. Do you feel more wood than metal? Have you been treated on wood? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 22:32:56 UTC">
      <body>I trail off. You don't. That's true. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131424" time="2013-04-23 22:34:40 UTC">
      <body>I've mostly been treated as metal.  Some classmates saw me as earth though.  I feel like a wood metal combo if that makes sense.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 22:38:14 UTC">
      <body>You are sweet and empathetic but I would not go to earth first with you. I always thought wood metal with you. I don't know! I like how hard it is. It lets you keep looking at people and reframing and thinking more. Wood is my first within. But I am defin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130962" time="2013-04-23 22:40:46 UTC">
      <body>Wood and metal are easily confused in some ways. Both have a righteousness and value precision/what is correct.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131424" time="2013-04-23 22:49:36 UTC">
      <body>I admire ur thoroughness.  I sometimes distinguish the two by asking what drives them.  If its to do the right thing or for a feeling of higher purpose then i lean towards saying they are metal. One of my fav 5e questions is 'do u have any pet peeves?'  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131424" time="2013-04-23 22:49:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh oh oh. I had a patient tell me she went to some kind of healer or psychic or something who told her she saw a black hole in her back (she has back problems) and said its from her mother trying to steal her soul.  Holy crap!  What do I do w that??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 01:34:37 UTC">
      <body>Just got back from yoga. How did the metal treatments feel for you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 01:35:36 UTC">
      <body>I really like the pet peeves question. What are your pet peeves??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 02:48:32 UTC">
      <body>My pet peeves = litter bugs Especially smokers throwing butts out the window.   And people thinking physically handicapped people are mentally handicapped </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 02:48:32 UTC">
      <body>You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 02:50:24 UTC">
      <body>Tough to tell re metal tx.  Lung pts work well for me since I tend towards colds respiratory issues but not sure how much they affected me on a deeper level. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 02:50:40 UTC">
      <body>Someday I will get the nerve to follow a litterbug home.  Then spend months collecting cigarette butts outside Walmart etc and go to their house one night to BEEP BEEEP BEEEP wake them up as I dump a ton of butts on their front lawn </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:24:54 UTC">
      <body>Sweet Bob your pet peeve sounds like Wood (justice) to me. I love it. My 73 yr old housemate is metal wood within though (I'm really pretty sure) and she installed trash cans on the corners of 4 blocks nearby bc she hates how trashy it is. She gets really</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 12:26:40 UTC">
      <body>I like your roommate </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:26:58 UTC">
      <body>My pet peeve is aggression (oh boy I'm gonna make a whole list of peeves, I can tell), people who don't follow through, being rude, rich people who are dumb about people with less money, and passive aggressive behavior. Basically rude selfishness kills me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:27:51 UTC">
      <body>She's tough and awesome. And not overly friendly/outgoing as is the metal stereotype. I like her too though occasionally we drive each other crazy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:29:59 UTC">
      <body>I think of wood as seeking justice on a global scale and metal as seeking on a smaller more personal level. Metal wanting what is correct and pure and wanting to be valued. Most of my issues are about not feeling respected either internally or externally.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:31:13 UTC">
      <body>Self esteem (wood) external praise. Self worth (metal) comes from within. I struggle with the second one. Do you get more stuck on one or the other? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 12:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. I'm not sure I agree about the justice distinctions.  What may seem like a personal thing could be taken as a desire for global justice respect etc. in my case the littering is about respect for the environment which is bigger and all more lotions t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 12:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Have a great day!  Good luck w finals!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 12:45:52 UTC">
      <body>More glorious not lotions lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:49:31 UTC">
      <body>Glorious lotions! ☺</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:52:49 UTC">
      <body>I agree all the labeling is dangerous. I think metal takes things more personally (turns them inwards) while wood looks outward more (vision and the turning of yin to yang with the transition if water to wood). Maybe that explains it better. And I do thin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 12:57:27 UTC">
      <body>My teacher Laura had a five element dance party where different CFs danced together. Someone descrubed metal dancing with earth as an insect dancing with a mammal. So now I ask myself if people who I think are metal are insect like. You have a little bit </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 13:03:58 UTC">
      <body>Lol.  I like that u r really embracing this and going beyond the surface. Peeling away layers!   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 13:07:13 UTC">
      <body>It's so fun. I love it. I learn so much from Laura in Maine. You also remind me of my friend Anthony from there who I adore and who you would like too. He's a fabulous wood cf. soft and gentle and really upright (also like you). He and I were on breakfast</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 13:09:20 UTC">
      <body>I have a hard time with cf at school bc everyone is self identified and not even treated on their elent (except two of us) and that is not a good laboratory for cf. In Maine I have 20 or 30 people I can look to as examples of different voices emotions etc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 13:11:57 UTC">
      <body>Also the assumption that I have a weird relationship with my dad bc I am metal is terrible. I can't stand that. I have a hard time with Janice's 10 questions (did you date in high school??) and refused to ask them. I like the pet peeves question alot.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 13:12:52 UTC">
      <body>I will stop texting you now. I promise. ☺ Insect over and out. Laura said I dance like a praying mantis. The influence of the tendons/wood within. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 13:27:55 UTC">
      <body>Wow. Sry i cant keep up w u!!
Omg. That metal = father issues thing is terrible...although I did have issues w mine lol.  But yes i think that assumption is terrible.  Janice is in tough position - tough to get very deep w the timing of her classes in the</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131424" time="2013-04-24 13:28:23 UTC">
      <body>Hoping the praying mantis gets some time in the grass today </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="130962" time="2013-04-24 13:44:19 UTC">
      <body>I will make sure I get some time in the grass!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 01:49:22 UTC">
      <body>There's a lot of funny personality stuff in all the teachers/teaching. I guess it's unavoidable but its tricky. That's why I like learning in Maine. It's more organic and feels more real in some ways. Just got home from school. It's time for bed! Goodnigh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:13:04 UTC">
      <body>I checked the calendar for PCA while at school but needle class went late and I'm not going to make it. I was hoping to be your 6:40 for a pre-Rolly Brown exam tx! Happy full moon. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:14:05 UTC">
      <body>Do you eat ice cream? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:14:39 UTC">
      <body>We could have a post shift ice cream in the summertime! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="131424" time="2013-04-25 22:17:36 UTC">
      <body>Awww what a great idea. Too bad it didn't work out. 

Happy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131424" time="2013-04-25 22:17:36 UTC">
      <body>Not huge on ice cream but never had from grass fed </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131424" time="2013-04-25 22:19:38 UTC">
      <body>Post shift delight may be exactly what I need.  Ty for thinking of me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:28:20 UTC">
      <body>They have nondairy ice cream too but why not load up on milky fat. My favorite flavor there so far is Birch Beer Vanilla. And it's frothy punk! So pretty. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131424" time="2013-04-25 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:52:48 UTC">
      <body>Frothy pink not punk. Appropriate typo! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131424" time="2013-04-25 23:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah punk works too. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 23:16:20 UTC">
      <body>It's true. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
