<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130719.0002" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 12:22:18 UTC">
      <body>Hey there. I've got some work to take care of right now, but how about 2 or 2:30ish?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 13:27:15 UTC">
      <body>Hey that sounds good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:27:41 UTC">
      <body>So, OK. Are u anywhere in the eastern US, on this ghastly heatwave we're having?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 14:28:45 UTC">
      <body>Hahah yeah NYC without a/c but luckily my basement apartment is kind of coolish... How about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:30:17 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah. Philly, and I was in Beantown for the weekend and more.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:30:46 UTC">
      <body>So I've been [bracketing] you ;-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 14:31:38 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah my sister's in Boston she said its awful their her kittens are miserable</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 14:32:05 UTC">
      <body>Oops there**</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:35:45 UTC">
      <body>Poor kitties! Σ&lt;•3X</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:42:54 UTC">
      <body>My cat's unhappy w the weather. She's a calico tabby about 7 years old and very furry. And the big a/c that I used to have for the living room died in s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:43:30 UTC">
      <body>pring and I haven't replaced it, so she's just lying around looking glum.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 14:45:56 UTC">
      <body>Hahah aww poor kitty! My cat had been staying with my mom for a few weeks because I'm moving I miss him!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:49:59 UTC">
      <body>Oh yes, my poor Ista is lonely. When I'm home she hangs around me wherever I am. Sometimes it's "Feeeeeed me!", but even after that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:52:10 UTC">
      <body>F'rex, she'll jump up on my desk &amp; lie on the papers while I'm using the laptop. She used to lie at least partly on the keyboard - one end of her or the</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 14:52:10 UTC">
      <body>other - till I started putting it on the tilting mini-easel.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132520" time="2013-07-19 15:08:33 UTC">
      <body>Hahah aww cats love computers! Especially when we're using them, my cat will only sit on my lap when I'm using my laptop</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:14:56 UTC">
      <body>nsitive) and flop down on my chest facing downhill. So I get a really closeup view of her least attractive part :-P . Of course this happens most often</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:15:31 UTC">
      <body>Oh, when I'm leaning back in the big armchair, she'll jump up on the arm and walk across me (usu. stepping on my solar plexus or something even more se</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:15:31 UTC">
      <body>Faceful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:15:31 UTC">
      <body>when I'm sitting down to read or use the laptop, and I have to reach over or around her to see! I have a folder of webcam shots of this that I call Old</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:17:00 UTC">
      <body>to put on my glasses or shove her forwards, b/c her dander in my eyes will trigger my allergies.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 15:17:00 UTC">
      <body>But I let her do it because she's lonely &amp; furry, and I like her company. Except, if she's giving me the windshield wiper treatment with her tail I have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130583" time="2013-07-19 19:02:14 UTC">
      <body>You available?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
