<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130111.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="134284" time="2013-01-11 21:03:04 UTC">
      <body>Sorry for late notice, but am in Philly this weekend visiting family.  Are you guys around?  Maybe tomorrow morning we could see each other.  Would love </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="134284" time="2013-01-11 21:03:06 UTC">
      <body>to see you guys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130979" time="2013-01-11 21:04:32 UTC">
      <body>Who is this? Just phone # came through</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130979" time="2013-01-11 21:07:54 UTC">
      <body>I thought it might be you, but I thought I had you in my phone.  Yeah we will be around. Kristen has plans in the early afternoon but we could probably meet up in the morning.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130979" time="2013-01-11 21:09:01 UTC">
      <body>Are you going to be Andrea's? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="134284" time="2013-01-11 21:33:55 UTC">
      <body>Just got to Andreas.  I can ride over in morning, or we could meet and grab coffee or you are always invited here</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130979" time="2013-01-11 21:38:28 UTC">
      <body>We are completely cool to stop by over there or if you want to get out you can stop by here. Whatever works best for you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="134284" time="2013-01-11 21:47:52 UTC">
      <body>Cool.  Let me get back to you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130979" time="2013-01-11 21:48:31 UTC">
      <body>Yep no problem.  We will just be here at the house. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 01:07:25 UTC">
      <body>What is Cooper's nap schedule?  Everyone would love to see you guys, but the kids have morning activities.  Does later in afternoon around 4 work?  If no</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 01:07:27 UTC">
      <body>t no biggie.  I could meet you anytime in morning that works best</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130979" time="2013-01-12 01:10:01 UTC">
      <body>He doesn't have a real set nap schedule. Kristen won't be around in the afternoon but I can stop by with him then. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 01:15:24 UTC">
      <body>Well if he doesn't have a schedule, and if it works for him and you guys (and I know the Hawks game is on so you may have plans) we are having my cousin </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 01:15:27 UTC">
      <body>and kids over for lunch on Sunday at noon.  Game will be on.   If not, why don't I just come over to your place in morning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130979" time="2013-01-12 02:11:44 UTC">
      <body>I am actually going down to Scotts on Sunday to watch the game otherwise that would work. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130979" time="2013-01-12 02:19:17 UTC">
      <body>So tomorrow morning prob works best.  We can also meet you for coffee too that way you don't have to come all the way out here. I'm sure you are pretty busy. Whatever works best for you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 02:23:28 UTC">
      <body>I can meet you st your house at 10 if that works.  Just remind me what the turn is off Germantown and what the turn is off that road.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130979" time="2013-01-12 02:24:52 UTC">
      <body>That will work. Left on Dekalb right on Hartranft.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="134284" time="2013-01-12 02:25:24 UTC">
      <body>Great.  See you tomorrow</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
