<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121228.0035" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136115" time="2012-12-28 01:49:16 UTC">
      <body>Hello!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136112" time="2012-12-28 04:35:35 UTC">
      <body>hey! sorry i didn't respond quicker, i was at the hobbit. :) how are you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136115" time="2012-12-28 04:36:43 UTC">
      <body>Haha, it's cool, how was that?  And I'm great, thanks for asking, I had a pretty good Christmas.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2012-12-28 04:47:13 UTC">
      <body>it was definitely a spectacle. so santa was good to you? did you get to see all your family? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136115" time="2012-12-28 04:52:32 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I didn't really get anything, but I didn't really want anything, all I asked my parents for was some help with buying textbooks for the spring.  And yeah, lots of family time, especially with my sister and her kid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136112" time="2012-12-28 05:28:24 UTC">
      <body>aw, yeah, i know you're fond of your little niece. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136115" time="2012-12-28 05:32:43 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, she's da bomb.  So what about you, good holiday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136112" time="2012-12-28 15:25:23 UTC">
      <body>oopsie, i guess i totally fell asleep. we really are on like opposite schedules. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136115" time="2012-12-29 01:57:26 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah, we definitely are, I've been up since yesterday myself, haha, I'm pretty beat.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136112" time="2012-12-29 02:00:44 UTC">
      <body>why no sleep? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136115" time="2012-12-29 02:01:44 UTC">
      <body>Lol I dunno, I just can't sleep sometimes.  Thankfully I'm gonna pass the fuck out soon, so if I suddenly stop replying I apologize.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136112" time="2012-12-29 02:02:06 UTC">
      <body>hey, it's not like i've never done it to you. :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136115" time="2012-12-29 02:03:29 UTC">
      <body>Haha, that's true, I guess I owe you one :p  So what've you been up to, anything exciting happen since we last talked?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136112" time="2012-12-29 02:05:13 UTC">
      <body>for some reason i read that as "since we were last naked"... but actually. and no, not really. i did nothing productive today except eat lunch with my family and walk into town for coffee. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136115" time="2012-12-29 02:07:24 UTC">
      <body>Well, that's certainly not productive, but it sounds fun.  And no, haha, in fact we've never been naked together, as far as I can remember.  It's never too late to start, though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136112" time="2012-12-29 02:14:48 UTC">
      <body>i walked into that one. :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136115" time="2012-12-29 02:21:25 UTC">
      <body>You sure did, come on Lauren, you're making it too easy to hit on you.  Jk it is easy because you're gorgeous.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136112" time="2012-12-29 03:44:18 UTC">
      <body>you're too much, haha. asleep yet? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 01:16:47 UTC">
      <body>Haha, sorry, I very much did fall asleep and forgot to respond when I woke up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 01:18:38 UTC">
      <body>no probsies. what time did you get up? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 01:19:43 UTC">
      <body>5am, I got up and went out on my porch and watched the rain for a few minutes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 03:03:04 UTC">
      <body>those moments are really special. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:26:29 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, definitely, good times, I love the rain.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 06:27:47 UTC">
      <body>i tried to send you a picture of me and katie but it won't send.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:28:36 UTC">
      <body>Aww, bummer, I certainly wouldn't mind seeing you two lovely ladies.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 06:29:42 UTC">
      <body>we're not looking particularly great, just pretty gone, haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:30:23 UTC">
      <body>Haha, well that's definitely fun too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:30:32 UTC">
      <body>Wish I was there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 06:30:56 UTC">
      <body>me too! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="136112" time="2012-12-30 06:31:51 UTC">
      <body>yessss! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:31:52 UTC">
      <body>Maybe next time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="136115" time="2012-12-30 06:32:38 UTC">
      <body>Awesome, just lemme know :)  I would offer to come chill now but I figure it's late and all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:10:17 UTC">
      <body>What's up, Lauren?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:10:51 UTC">
      <body>not a great moment for me, not super happy at the moment. how are you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:11:37 UTC">
      <body>Aww, what's wrong?  And I'm fine, btw.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:16:54 UTC">
      <body>zach, as usual. we haven't talked for a few days and of course when we do i end up making him angry at me. it sucks that i let him control my emotions like this. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:17:27 UTC">
      <body>Wait, who's Zach? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:18:14 UTC">
      <body>that guy i dated at the beginning of the semester. we're friends now or whatever. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:19:56 UTC">
      <body>Oooooh, I see, that sucks :(  Well is he worth all the trouble?  Just on an objective, greater-or-less-than sort of sense?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:22:13 UTC">
      <body>no, he's not. he's a shitty friend, plus we don't really have much in common or enough history to go on to make it work otherwise. and i never know where i stand with him. but i don't really see a way out and i do still care about him (not like romantically, but you know how it is). </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:24:19 UTC">
      <body>Meh, I mean, I guess the heart wants what it wants or whatever, but I say fuck 'em, if a person's not worth the trouble they cause I don't give them the time of day.  I'd hate to see you put so much effort into some ass.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:26:59 UTC">
      <body>i just can't imagine myself doing that to someone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:29:03 UTC">
      <body>I mean, sometimes it happens.  I wrote off a close friend of mine because she was really shitty person, a few years later she had changed a lot and now we're fine.  But if she was still shitty I'd say "Hey, not worth it".  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:29:46 UTC">
      <body>i really admire that. i do. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:31:33 UTC">
      <body>Haha and here I thought you were gonna say I was too harsh.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:43:06 UTC">
      <body>no, i think it's awesome, haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:44:20 UTC">
      <body>Well them follow my example!  Trust me, you're good enough to attract decent guys.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:46:24 UTC">
      <body>i just can't. hoping to work on the "finding better friends" thing this semester, though, for sure. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:47:58 UTC">
      <body>Definitely,  get on that, shitty people aren't worth it!  Just try to be a little meaner, you're nice enough that you can afford it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:49:08 UTC">
      <body>hahaha, i just can't find the balance. i was such a bitch in high school, and i try so hard to suppress that now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:50:03 UTC">
      <body>Aw, I don't remember you being bitchy in high school</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:53:10 UTC">
      <body>then you lucked out. ask anyone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:54:03 UTC">
      <body>Meh, either way, high school was stupid, the things that happened then barely even count.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 04:54:24 UTC">
      <body>preach. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:56:13 UTC">
      <body>GET I GET AN AMEN!  Haha, but seriously, you should declare right now that you're gonna write off Zach since you know he no good for you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 04:59:30 UTC">
      <body>Lol that was supposed to be can I get an amen, whoops.  Sorry, lil high.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 05:06:32 UTC">
      <body>it's cool. i just can't do it. i know i can't trust him with anything, but he did apologize for what he said tonight. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 05:07:57 UTC">
      <body>Aww, well I think you oughta hold out for a guy who doesn't have to apologize, but whatever, it's your life and all, I trust your judgement.  I hope whatever you do makes you happy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="136112" time="2012-12-31 05:09:30 UTC">
      <body>i mean, it's not like i have a set number of spots in my life for people, and i have to drop one friend to pick up another... but thanks. i'm going to bed. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="136115" time="2012-12-31 05:10:27 UTC">
      <body>Alright, well, goodnight then Lauren!  Hope I get to see your pretty face before you go off to school!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
