<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121128.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136203" time="2012-11-28 00:00:00 UTC">
      <body>Someone on the subway this morning vaguely smelled like you and I just needed to share that because I miss your smell sooo much. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136164" time="2012-11-28 01:09:10 UTC">
      <body>Was not expecting that but thanks! Miss u 2. How was your break? Sorry I couldn't see you guys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136203" time="2012-11-28 01:10:17 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah I realize that could come off as very creepy. Our break was really wonderful (but if we had seen you it woulda been betta)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-11-28 06:06:07 UTC">
      <body>(❤) Who did you see and what did you doooo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136203" time="2012-11-28 12:54:24 UTC">
      <body>Well we went to Sasha's thing so I saw Ilya Nick Rocio Sasha and Julia. Nick made us watch a really bad movie. Jordan and I also had dinner with my grandfather. Idk. We spent a lotta time together and that was really nice. 
What were you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:31:18 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like you're a little unsatisfied...? My thanksgiving was good, I got to see my family and baby cousins and sleep in my own bed. It was nice to be home but I kinda felt like just a visitor. Ill have a chance to settle back in in December</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:33:36 UTC">
      <body>No Jordan and I had a really great time together actually. He felt like a visitor too. The best was we were by tech on Wednesday and all the stoop kids had returned and then we walked by connecticut muffin and Daniel was standing there and Nick and I died cus Jordan can't run away </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:33:36 UTC">
      <body>Daniels always present</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:38:02 UTC">
      <body>Lmaoooooo. Fuckin Daniel. That's good though. How is everything at tech these days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:40:25 UTC">
      <body>Bad. Lol. Idk - nothing new. Pretty blah. Parent teacher conferences are tomorrow and my mom was like we are going and I was like we don't need to but oh well. 
What's new at Emory?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:42:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah my parents didn't go senior year. Finals are happening soon and so much writing needs to be done ahhhhh. But in three weeks I'm back home so it's not so bad. Ill get through it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:43:34 UTC">
      <body>You totally will!
I'm like chill who cares but oh well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:44:51 UTC">
      <body>Yeah word. Your grades are pristine no doubt. So I heard they changed it so there's only four marking periods?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:45:21 UTC">
      <body>Yep. That's why parent teachers are now. And actually this year they've dropped. Like a point. Lol not a big deal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:46:29 UTC">
      <body>Yeah you will be fine. That's so weird. Why change something that's not a problem? Ugh. Tech. Are you applying anywhere for regular decision in addition to Cornell </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:48:21 UTC">
      <body>Huh? Why would I only apply RD to Cornell?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:48:53 UTC">
      <body>I thought you applied to Cornell early?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:50:04 UTC">
      <body>No I applied early to Stanford but its a secret</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:51:05 UTC">
      <body>OH yes that's where it was. I didn't tell anyone </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:52:20 UTC">
      <body>It musta been sooo hard </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 02:52:48 UTC">
      <body>&lt;3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 02:53:13 UTC">
      <body>Yeah def especially since I actually remembered the school you applied to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 22:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Did rowley come to class drunk ever?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 23:02:05 UTC">
      <body>LOL no I don't think so. At least I didn't know it. Did she come in drunk today??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 23:02:24 UTC">
      <body>Definitely hungover I'd guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 23:04:16 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah probably hungover. But then again she's kinda naturally crabby</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 23:04:32 UTC">
      <body>She smelled like alcohol and was super disheveled </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="136164" time="2012-11-29 23:16:03 UTC">
      <body>Oh that's awks. She's a bit troubled</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="136203" time="2012-11-29 23:40:31 UTC">
      <body>Yeahhh</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
