<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120713.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 21:33:21 UTC">
      <body>What a wonderful surprise! I have very loose plans that I will happily cancel. Where are you staying?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135122" time="2012-07-13 21:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Oh cool! I'm sorry I didn't think of it sooner. I am staying with my dear friend  and fellow ole Thomas Rusert in glenside. We r free by 9 and will be traveling with his lady from warrington. Is there a place we could meet up? Let us know if u have a car or not. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 21:41:53 UTC">
      <body>I don't have a car, sadly. And despite my PA citizenship I don't know where those places are. Would you maybe be coming into the city?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135122" time="2012-07-13 21:43:28 UTC">
      <body>We are flexible. Where in the city are u? Thomas and I r up for anything around 9</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 21:45:25 UTC">
      <body>Well dont let me impose. I'm in south Philly/center city but can get anywhere :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135122" time="2012-07-13 21:52:00 UTC">
      <body>Are u able to hop on the train and come to glenside around 9 ish? I'm at the whim of friends here ;) there is a cool pub they are wanting o go to tonight and the train ride is just north about 20 minutes from u! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 21:54:24 UTC">
      <body>That sounds great! What's the address of the pub?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135122" time="2012-07-13 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>Thomas say we can pick u up at the train station. We r going to his I laws but will be back by 9</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 21:59:01 UTC">
      <body>Oh that's really generous of you, thank you. I'll be in touch and aim for around 9 :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131839" time="2012-07-13 23:26:57 UTC">
      <body>Those flexible plans may be harder to break than I expected... I'm afraid I'll totally disappoint a friend if I don't keep them. I apologize for not making it out there - I really regret not seeing you. But safe travels and when I'm home I'm sept. I'm looking you up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135122" time="2012-07-13 23:28:00 UTC">
      <body>No worries! It was last minute. Until September then</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
