<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130519.0047" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131588" time="2013-05-19 17:17:43 UTC">
      <body>I feel so bad about ur car but IM glad u weren't in an accident.  But its very maddening I know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131528" time="2013-05-19 17:19:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah :-(  I have a 500 deductible.  I just hope they don't total it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131528" time="2013-05-19 17:21:12 UTC">
      <body>Let me know when you get your cards from fidelity and ally. Once you have access we can transfer money into the money market account and but the cds</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131528" time="2013-05-20 16:02:23 UTC">
      <body>I'm on the metro.  What's going on? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:10:33 UTC">
      <body>(1/3) Sorry. Called by accident. Why r u on metro so late.  Wondering what u were going to do bout ur car.  They mite total.  So I'll get something like I did. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:10:42 UTC">
      <body>(2/3)  U mite be able to make the choice. Usaa is very good.  Did u get a police report?  Must have been a drunk driver. What a mess.  My brother is so bad hasn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:10:45 UTC">
      <body>(3/3) 't slept in 2 days taken to urgent care. New meds not working. He's in a panic. He has that family to support</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131528" time="2013-05-20 16:14:48 UTC">
      <body>I threw up my juice this morning and went back to bed. I hope they don't total it.  I would be so sad. A cop had left a note with a report number when i got to it. Poor Steven. If he goes on disability, Debbie would have to work and the boys. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:19:37 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) That would b a reality check for her.  I always had the feeling he was taken for granted.  I know. That car was great just to drive locally in.  It will s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:19:55 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) omehow workout.  Maybe ur father will help u</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 16:42:44 UTC">
      <body>Juice would make me throw up if I had it on am empty stomach.  Maybe u could eat something first</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131528" time="2013-05-20 16:59:54 UTC">
      <body>You can go online and see what Steven's disability benefit would be.  Also how much debbie needs to work to be eligible for retirement ssi.  I can do it if they want to give my their info on the phone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131588" time="2013-05-20 17:02:13 UTC">
      <body>I wont say anything just yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131528" time="2013-05-21 01:41:49 UTC">
      <body>Have you gotten any ally or fidelity mail? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131588" time="2013-05-21 02:18:16 UTC">
      <body>No. IM concerned about a money market. I can't afford any risk.  Would rather just a CD</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131528" time="2013-05-21 02:26:12 UTC">
      <body>Ok,  they have a high interest savings account.  You just can't write checks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131528" time="2013-05-21 18:26:41 UTC">
      <body>I'm not going to be able to come home this weekend.  Would you guys come here? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131588" time="2013-05-21 19:12:36 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) U can't take the train for Eric's b'day?? N surprise him then we can drive u home. Think about it.  We love u n its not the same w/o u.  Uncle Steven is i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131588" time="2013-05-21 19:12:39 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) n the hospital.  They foundca tumor n looking at his upper spine now then a biopsy.  He couldn't walk or pee.  IM sick</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131528" time="2013-05-21 19:30:38 UTC">
      <body>Oh no. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131588" time="2013-05-21 19:37:02 UTC">
      <body>I know. U never know in life. That's why its imp to spend time together w those that r imp.  Hows that for a little guilt</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131528" time="2013-05-22 04:32:29 UTC">
      <body>How is it going? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131528" time="2013-05-22 15:07:16 UTC">
      <body>Anything new? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 15:08:40 UTC">
      <body>No not yet. As soon as I hear anything I'll let u know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 19:46:03 UTC">
      <body>Can u find a good spinal n lung doctor at Hopkins.  They're thinking of going to Hopkins n doctor agrees.  When u have time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 19:46:16 UTC">
      <body>Pressure is off spine but still can't pee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131528" time="2013-05-22 20:22:20 UTC">
      <body>David Ettinger - lung.  Stuart Grossman - neuro.  Both at hopkins,  peer ranked as top 1% nationwide. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131528" time="2013-05-22 20:24:33 UTC">
      <body>Hopkins has a special brain and spinal tumor center</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 20:24:47 UTC">
      <body>She already ready has Dr. Karma for spine I'll tell her about lung guy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 20:25:29 UTC">
      <body>There transporting him 7or 8 tonite</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131528" time="2013-05-22 23:11:49 UTC">
      <body>Is he going to be in the hospital for a while? Does he need entertainment? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 23:44:58 UTC">
      <body>Don't know anything just yet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 23:46:03 UTC">
      <body>Going to request ur doctors. Patricia researched.   WOW. they r outstanding</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 23:53:02 UTC">
      <body>Maybe u can give me a 2nd tumor spine Guy in case we can't get Stuart grossman</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131588" time="2013-05-22 23:55:27 UTC">
      <body>I'll ask him if he needs entertainment</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 12:00:56 UTC">
      <body>Joe n Ang n maybe Robert mite b coming down to see Steven. U should visit uncle stevel also.  Its embarrassing if u don't. He's in a crisis</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131528" time="2013-05-23 12:09:35 UTC">
      <body>I just picked up my rental car</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 13:03:49 UTC">
      <body>Wonderful. Nothing like good ins</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 13:08:20 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) R they fixing ur car or totaling it?  If u go to hospital I'll meet u. There is a parking garage directly across the street n a bridge to work over. He's </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 13:08:21 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) on 12th FL room 31. Mite be have 2nd surgery today.  Timing is crucial. Keep in touch. Im in a panic have to clean house also</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 13:10:42 UTC">
      <body>Zahedan building</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131588" time="2013-05-23 13:26:37 UTC">
      <body>12 W</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
