<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150215.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-15 13:15:42 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>So I just tried to leave for yoga and got stuck! I can feed today if you want - there's deep snow right where you turn to park so if you come, I would just leave your car on the driveway by the barn.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-15 13:17:45 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Aw man! That stinks! Is the driveway bad or just where you normally park?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-15 13:22:34 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>The driveway up to the barn or so seems ok but snow is blowing and made a big deep drift by the barnyard </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-15 13:23:44 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Hahaha oh geez. I guess if it's bad I should probably just let you feed so I don't get stuck out there lol. Are you ok with that? I can try to do tonight's feeding though if it's better maybe.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-15 13:25:15 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>It is so cold too! I'm just going to leave them in. Why don't you let me know if you feel like coming out for pm, and if not, I'll do it? No problem either way. Pump is frozen again too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-15 13:26:24 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Gah silly thing! I'm not surprised. Yeah I would definitely leave them in! Poor beauty in her little sheet. I'll let you know mid afternoon if ill make it out there. Thank you SO much for being so great!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-02-15 14:01:12 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Sounds good, stay warm!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-02-15 20:54:24 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Hey there! We can take care of the horses tonight :) we'll be at nicks cooking anyways :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-02-15 20:54:24 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>(Hugh my bf and I)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-02-15 21:17:52 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Slash how's the driveway?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-02-15 21:47:15 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Great! The guy came and plowed the driveway so it should be fine. Just let us know if the pump is frozen or anything, we'll be here! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-02-15 21:49:18 UTC" participant="153302">
      <body>Thanks!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

