<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20131214.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-12-14 19:07:44 UTC" participant="153634">
      <body>I don't love Marty and Maeve's gchat. should we come up for a game plan for the website before vacation? or is it not possible?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-12-15 16:02:02 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I can probably work on it right after Christmas?? Or in the 23rd. I can get the laurels together and online.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-12-15 16:02:38 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Ugh I don't even care about aka anymore. I really don't want to do any more filming.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-12-15 16:27:44 UTC" participant="153634">
      <body>yeah me neither, esp with having to setup our backgrounds. I can't believe that doro wrote that Maeve only saw her relationship with Marty as a fun flirting thing, I thought they understood that we both cared, otherwise we wouldn't be so hurt. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-12-15 16:29:52 UTC" participant="153634">
      <body>can you remind me how to sign in? I can resize the grid and make the grid of our photos. so should we make the laurels white with black lettering? the grid lines are black for everything which gets lost but maybe that's ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-12-15 16:32:00 UTC" participant="153634">
      <body>omg!! and where do we go to sign in? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-12-15 16:32:00 UTC" participant="153634">
      <body>ah there it is. good luck moving!! it would be great if our website could be finished before our panel or sooner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-12-15 16:32:20 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>The movers are 2 hours early!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-12-15 16:32:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Omg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-12-15 16:34:31 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I think that's a great goal for the site. It should totally be ready by then!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

