<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130313.0027" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-03-13 23:49:03 UTC">
      <body>ALL OF MY PRO CON LISTS COME OUT EVEN HELP</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:39:51 UTC">
      <body>What's up??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:40:12 UTC">
      <body>Jobs. Penn vs. NIH</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:40:32 UTC">
      <body>You for the NIH job?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:40:32 UTC">
      <body>*got</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Congrats! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Do you still need help deciding?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:41:06 UTC">
      <body>I have calmed down haha...ugh I always end up leaning toward penn and then honking about it and being torn and then leaning towards penn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:41:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:42:22 UTC">
      <body>Slash it actually sounds like you've made a decision already...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:42:40 UTC">
      <body>What's your perspective?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:43:22 UTC">
      <body>I dunno
I...
I'm not ready to give up on either one. I need to talk to professors...I think I'm looking at it from an okay perspective but everyone I ask has a different perspective</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:46:55 UTC">
      <body>That ultimately people from both places get into grad school so even though NIH would give me new skills that would make me marketable (work with kids, neuro, physiological stuff), I'm ultimately not as excited about those things as I am about what is studied at penn. so even though a prof might emphasize direct mentorship and gaining marketable skills, is rather do what interests me more given that I would hopefully get into grad school either way</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:47:26 UTC">
      <body>But I've heard that interests don't matter, research quality/skills and mentorship do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:47:33 UTC">
      <body>Like, in general</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:48:10 UTC">
      <body>But I'm just more interested in the stuff at penn, despite the crazy boss thing and NIH being a more cookie cutter experience</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:48:32 UTC">
      <body>And maybe more renowned outside the OCD/PTSD worlds?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 00:53:05 UTC">
      <body>I think you'll be able to get into grad school either way. And being more interested and committed to your job is going to enable to learn more from it and make more valuable connections. And it's not like your NOT going to be learning good things from the penn job. I don't think the penn is position is bad, or bad enough for you to take the nih position because its what you "should" do. Ultimately doing something related to your interests is going to be the biggest pro in the long run.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:55:05 UTC">
      <body>￼Pro/con list</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:55:05 UTC">
      <body>But really I feel like I would defend penn harder if challenged...but I guess not if everyone else is right, you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135080" time="2013-03-14 00:55:06 UTC">
      <body>That is all true</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 01:03:07 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure what you said in that last text but i feel like  you want to go to penn ( and the debate comes in b/c of NIH reputation and "cookie cutter" experience). In the end, given that this is not a long-term position and that chances are great you'll get into grad school either way, the question is really what kind of an experience do you want to have? ( as opposed to what should i do; because I don't think there's a nothing you should or even have to do). </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 01:04:00 UTC">
      <body>Do you want to have chance to explore a topic your interested in, that you're leaning towards working in? With some goods/bads with regards to environment but a strong support system. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135271" time="2013-03-14 01:06:07 UTC">
      <body>Or do you want an experience in a typical but reputable environment and a new city to challenge yourself that way? </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
