<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140714.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-14 20:22:42 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Basic questions: if I get to a green portal, should I hack it or do anything else? If a green person owns it, does it hurt them if I hack it? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-14 20:43:11 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Hack everything, green or blue! Hacking green portals won't give you AP (points) but it still gives you items. And no  it doesn't hurt anything </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-14 20:45:24 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>One thing to keep in mind: hacking a portal that's much higher level than you will zap your xm pretty fast and will give you items you can't use until yo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-14 20:45:25 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>u reach that level. So when you're low level it's best to try to find low level portals to hack </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-14 21:03:07 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Hmm ok! How do I know what level it is? And thanks for the crash course!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-14 21:04:22 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>No problem! And when you click on the portal there should be an L with a number on the top right. That's the current portal level </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-14 21:06:21 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ok! How do I get more xm and how do I know if I should deploy a resonator?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-14 21:08:53 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Xm is the little blue dots you see on the ground, especially near portals. You'll suck it up as your scanner circle crosses over it. It's tougher to find</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-14 21:08:54 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body> in the burbs though! And at this point in the game you should pretty much be deploying resonators whenever you're able. It's the fastest way to level yo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-14 21:08:55 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>urself up. We can get into more strategy as you move up in the game :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-14 21:09:32 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Interesting! Ok I'll see what I find around here and in Vermont </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-15 18:41:47 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Today's questions: recharging resonators when I can is a good thing? What do I do with a portal key? I have 2! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-07-15 19:08:39 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Yes you can and should recharge resonators whenever you can - it helps the team and gives you AP! Keys let you recharge portals remotely (if you don't ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-07-15 19:08:41 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>ve a key for a portal you can only recharge when you're physically at it) and also let you link portals together. You need a key to the destination porta</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-07-15 19:08:42 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>l (but not the origin portal)  to make a link. Keep in mind that creating a link will use up the key for the destination portal though! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-07-15 19:39:40 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ok thanks! Why do I want to link portals? Also how do I get my name on one? #sexyambition</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-07-15 19:41:55 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>The overall goal of the game is to capture "mind units" by linking portals together to make fields. If you link three portals together in a triangle, you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-07-15 19:41:55 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body> capture all the MUs within it for the team and yourself </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-07-15 19:42:35 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ah ok!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-07-15 19:42:38 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>And when you capture a neutral (gray)  portal by placing the first resonator on it, you gain ownership of it until the other team destroys it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-07-15 19:43:17 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>You can also submit new portals. I'll explain that more next time I see you. It takes forever to get them approved so don't worry about it for now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-07-15 19:43:35 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Got it. Also it told me someone hit me and I lost 100xm! What the fuck. Can I hit them back? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-07-15 19:44:25 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Ha ha. That means a blue portal attacked you, probably when you tried to hack it. Portals owned by the opposite faction can attack you when you hack or a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-07-15 19:44:25 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>ttack them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-07-15 19:45:13 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Shit!! I should hack them anyway though right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-07-15 19:45:28 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Yes, absolutely! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-07-15 19:45:43 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>It's ON</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-07-15 19:47:03 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>And when you start collecting enough bursters (xmp) in your inventory, you can start attacking lower level blue portals yourself. If you can neutralize t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-07-15 19:47:04 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>hem to gray, you can capture them for yourself, </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-07-15 19:47:32 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Just don't bother attacking anything high level right now because it'll attack back like crazy and zap all your xm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-07-15 19:50:56 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Cool! Yeah most of what I've encountered today have been level 1 (although they have like 7 level 1 resonators and 1 level 7 resonator?) so I've been hackin em up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-07-15 19:51:29 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Where are you at today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-07-15 19:52:59 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Pa to ny to Vermont! I got portal keys in Ottsville pa &amp; Catskill ny. What if I get one in Vermont and link them all??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-07-15 19:53:32 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Go for it if you can. Level one portals don't have big link distances though, so it may not work </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-07-15 19:53:52 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>I'll see what I can do!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

