<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120211.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 17:40:30 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) Been desperately waiting for you to call. Should I stop? I know you broke up with me so you wouldn't have to worry about talking, but even if you don't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 17:40:41 UTC">
      <body>(02/03) need it, I still need to hear your voice. If that's out of bounds then maybe I need boundaries. Just still trying to work through so much confusion and </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 17:41:06 UTC">
      <body>(03/03) have nobody to help with that.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2012-02-11 18:50:23 UTC">
      <body>I'll call later today, Tim. Are you parents there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 19:30:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah so I don't know if I'll be able to talk. They're here til Monday. And I hate that you call me Tim </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2012-02-11 20:40:01 UTC">
      <body>I know how painful this is, I really really do. I'm sorry to hurt you. What would you like me to call you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 21:33:14 UTC">
      <body>Me too Mattie. It just feels so formal and distant when you call me that and that makes me feel sick </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2012-02-11 21:46:59 UTC">
      <body>Ok, I hear that. I don't mean to be nor want to be formal or distant.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-02-11 22:32:24 UTC">
      <body>As a friend, Please respect the decision I made. I want to be close to you, but need to feel like we can move forward as friends not try to recapture something that had fallen away.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135117" time="2012-02-11 22:33:32 UTC">
      <body>I know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135117" time="2012-02-12 01:53:44 UTC">
      <body>Are you free late tonight or early tomorrow? Or would you rather not talk? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131839" time="2012-02-12 01:55:20 UTC">
      <body>I'm going out with Alice tonight and work tomorrow early. I do want to talk, though. Especially if it would help you. Late Monday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135117" time="2012-02-12 02:01:25 UTC">
      <body>I guess it'll have to be that. Have fun </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131839" time="2012-02-12 02:02:56 UTC">
      <body>Don't make me out to be negligent please. I've been so busy and dealing with this as best I can. You've had stuff going on too. I can't keep feeling like a sociopath for this. It's not fair.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135117" time="2012-02-12 02:09:41 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I know you've been busy, I honestly understand. I'm not trying to make you feel bad at all. It just hurts so much to feel like you're not going as crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135117" time="2012-02-12 02:10:02 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  as I am. I feel sociopathic. I'm sorry. I want to let you deal with this however you need to.  </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
