<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130429.0051" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 01:44:32 UTC">
      <body>I got into the fafsa info and confirmed she did include McGill in the list of colleges. So I have to ask McGill about it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132437" time="2013-04-29 01:45:18 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 14:08:04 UTC">
      <body>So far they were not helpful. Just said read our website. The website is not very clear and they didn't want help clarify it. To find out if her $10k offer is renewable Soraya has to send them an email so I'm doing that now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132437" time="2013-04-29 14:08:56 UTC">
      <body>So they did not answer questions about fafsa?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132437" time="2013-04-29 14:09:40 UTC">
      <body>Could you send me their number please</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 14:11:07 UTC">
      <body>They said it is on the website but all I saw on the website were us gov loans requiring good credit. These are "direct loan" and "parent plus" loan which are apparently the new names for stafford loans.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 14:34:40 UTC">
      <body>I talked to fafsa. That was easier. They said that McGill determines how much gov loans she will get and Soraya has to contact them for that info. I hope we hear from them today in response to Sorayas email I sent for her (from her email account). The fafsa people said that normally McGill will send a letter with the entire aid package including loan info. I guess we didn't get that earlier because she didn't submit the app form until late. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 14:38:25 UTC">
      <body>I sent just now to McGill from Sorayas account a request that they email her the entire financial aid package today. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 15:00:16 UTC">
      <body>I received McGill s response and its not nearly enough money. I will send it to your email. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132437" time="2013-04-29 15:09:56 UTC">
      <body>I did not receive the email</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="137257" time="2013-04-29 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>I sent it to your gmail</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="132437" time="2013-04-29 15:26:22 UTC">
      <body>Can you send it again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="137257" time="2013-04-30 00:31:45 UTC">
      <body>There is no info about the next step after the plus loan is rejected so call the financial aid office. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="132437" time="2013-04-30 00:32:09 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
