<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140926.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-26 11:26:53 UTC" participant="152765">
      <body>Hey silly, you left so fast yesterday you didn't give me a chance to say thanks properly--my hotel had a false fire alarm evacuation at 4:00 am so I was really out of it! Anyways, don't feel bad about kids not going to bed on time. I should have known that. Is really hard, even I have the hardest time w that. I was more concerned about Lucas coming in and out of the house by himself on Sat. Anyways, they clearly love you. So thanks! Ps: do u know what happened in Maya's rug? It has several stains...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-26 15:49:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>!??? Hmmn nooo </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-26 15:49:25 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I don't think we played much on Maya's rug</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-26 15:50:42 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah I know! I was upstairs w maya watching tv and napping and didn't hear the doorbell ring and def didn't hear him leave. I asked him to pls never do that again, bc it scared me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-26 16:04:20 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Lol they love me because I am a total pushover. If you ever need a free moment though and want to drop Lucas off at
the gallery for a bit, let me know. I always wish he and I had more time to hang out as friends but maya is quite demanding with attention. I always feel like I'm neglecting him (attention-wise) which is why I also apologized to Him about the fact that I didn't hear the doorbell from upstairs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-26 16:05:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Actually, I barely heard the doorbell a few days later either, when I was very attentively Waiting for it bc I knew Lucas was returning. I think I let maya put the volume for strawberry shortcake too loud maybe..lesson learned.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-26 19:35:28 UTC" participant="152765">
      <body>He loves u. We will figure something out. We r in Brooklyn w friends. Hanging out in lovely house. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-26 19:38:54 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I love him too. He really, really reminds me of myself at that age. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-26 19:39:02 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>See you soon !</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-26 20:07:28 UTC" participant="152765">
      <body>:)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

