<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140224.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-02-24 19:07:57 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>(1/2) Any interest in being interviewed about your dream journal / plugging your film on the hairpin? I totally realize your dream journal stuff is private but </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-02-24 19:08:05 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>(2/2) it's also cool and I bet people would be into it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-02-24 22:41:30 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>That sounds pretty cool. I'd be into that. What's the time frame? I'm shooting a book trailer Friday to Tuesday of next week. Lotsa pre pro but after that more time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-02-24 22:43:41 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>Awesome. I can wait till after Tues. It's mostly an issue of what you want said. Also, is there a place I can see your film(s)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-02-24 22:45:15 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yes! I'll email you links and passwords when I get home tonight. It sounds really cool. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-02-24 22:46:43 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>Great. It should be! I think the hairpin is prob a great place to find some new followers. I'm into what they do. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-02-24 22:48:13 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Are you writing for them a lot?! That's so exciting!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-02-24 22:53:26 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>I don't know! I just got the We Want You email earlier today. Haven't worked out the finer points yet, but I am excited.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-02-24 22:54:38 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Congrats!!! That's so cool. Yeah let's kit and set up a time for the interview. Let me know if I can prepare for you in any way. I'll get some links to you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-02-24 22:56:37 UTC" participant="153660">
      <body>Cool, thanks</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

