<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130713.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 20:08:35 UTC">
      <body>Lauren!  I just realized that I've hardly talked to you all summer!  And that is just unacceptable!  How're you doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136112" time="2013-07-13 20:09:25 UTC">
      <body>you're right, that is unacceptable! i'm just about to hop in the shower, though, i'll text you in a bit! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 20:10:14 UTC">
      <body>Word, have fun</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2013-07-13 20:41:00 UTC">
      <body>anyway, i've been really good, though i'm getting to the point in the summer where i want to go back to school. how are youuu? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 20:43:43 UTC">
      <body>Lol, yo dawg, if you already want to go back to school, that just means you aren't finding enough to do in Summerville!  Fix that, have fun!  I'm good too, just trying to amp myself up since I have to work at 7am tomorrow :o</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136112" time="2013-07-13 20:47:08 UTC">
      <body>you're probably right! and it looks like we're both having early mornings, i've been doing this pet-sitting thing and the morning stuff has to happen at like 7:30. :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 20:48:42 UTC">
      <body>Oh man, solidarity, poor us :(  How long will you be doing the house-sitting thing?  I get off work at 2 tomorrow, we should hang out later in the day.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136112" time="2013-07-13 21:16:39 UTC">
      <body>maybe! i'm supposed to have dinner with my parents so i'll have to see when that's supposed to happen. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 21:21:55 UTC">
      <body>Coolcool, if you're busy it's all good. I just thought I'd offer to keep you entertained while you're in Summerville :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136112" time="2013-07-13 21:30:47 UTC">
      <body>thanks. we should hang out soon, though! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136115" time="2013-07-13 21:39:12 UTC">
      <body>Yes, it's been far too long, think of all the good times we've missed, not hanging out!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
