<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141126.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-26 19:21:26 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Hey Victor, it's Eden. How's it going?  So Michael's been annoyed with having to come up with a Christmas list. Haha. He never wants anything! So I'll try to help you out.  I already got him two sweaters/ hoodies and a portable phone charger. I'm also going to get him an hdmi cable and probably another pair of vans sneakers. Oh, and my mom is getting him a new backpack since his is pretty old. He does need cologne.  I don't know how much you want to spend. But he wears lacoste red. I've gotten it on Amazon. It runs around 40 bucks I think. Or, a hip city veg gift card?  We always get shakes and he eats there often for lunch. And he's been wanting a plain black hoodie (size small). I've had no luck in finding one. So there are some ideas. Let me know if any sound good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-26 19:28:41 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Hey!! How's it going?
Thanks!! I really appreciate that! That's a big help. The cologne, the gift card, and the gift card sound like great ideas. I'll look into then and let you know what I went with</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-26 19:29:38 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. Cool :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-26 20:29:18 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>For the cologne, There's two different bottles here and one is like a cylinder, the other is more square. What does his bottle look like?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-26 20:35:04 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>It's the square one.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-26 20:35:59 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Ok thanks. Can I get him the cologne and the hoodie?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-26 20:38:07 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yup!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-26 20:38:21 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-26 20:39:17 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>No problem. Thank you. I wanted to get him everything but I know he doesn't want me to spend too much.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-26 20:44:16 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Oh you don't mind me getting the cologne or hoodie do you? I just didn't know what he wanted and was hoping to start early this year</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-26 20:46:06 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>No. Not at all. It works out great this way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-26 20:48:40 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Cool yea. And it's funny I was gonna ask you for advice or insight on what he'd want but I guess i didn't get a chance lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-26 20:52:27 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I know you weren't the only one asking him what he wants so if Michelle our your mom need ideas, let me know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-11-26 20:53:38 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>Ok cool thanks. I'll pass it on.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-11-26 20:54:13 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>I took off work today and I'm actually about to nap lol. I'll catchya later. Thanks again!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-11-26 20:54:59 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. I took off today and yesterday. It's so bad. See you tomorrow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-11-26 20:55:25 UTC" participant="152123">
      <body>See you :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

