<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120817.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 16:50:51 UTC">
      <body>How long are you gonna be at da party</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 16:57:21 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure those details haven't been worked out, maybe late? Why whats up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 16:58:10 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I can get there until midnight :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 16:59:18 UTC">
      <body>Waaaat thats mad late, have you left maine yet? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:00:34 UTC">
      <body>I knowww. We are on the road but we are having a family dinner in long island with my grandma and uncles and stuff. It's a goodbye party thing. So I won't get back to the city till late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:34:11 UTC">
      <body>Hmm did you let diana know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:35:39 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I did. She said its not too late if the party's still going. So you gotta keep it goin!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:37:00 UTC">
      <body>If anybody is under pressure to leave early, its joygill. But right after that is me. So i'll stay as long as i can!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:38:16 UTC">
      <body>Haha ok great thanks! I know people have their own curfews but I just wanna make sure I see as many people as I can!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:39:17 UTC">
      <body>I know i feel you, how was maine what'd you do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:40:51 UTC">
      <body>It was fine, we were only there for a few days but we were able to go to the beach and play tennis and go into town. What have you been up to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:42:58 UTC">
      <body>Swag did you get to see claire and stuff? I've been fasting and praying mad hard. Pool was cool tho, whooped everyone, ate delicious mexican food and got stoned</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:44:17 UTC">
      <body>Nahh claire lives in Vermont. Oh niiice that was Chelsea's birthday party right? Who was there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:45:41 UTC">
      <body>Me chelsea marianela and diana. We spent the whole time reminiscing and shit it was nice. Played an hour of pool alone tho :( </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:48:04 UTC">
      <body>Aww that's nice. The only problem with going away this week was that everyone decided to plan shit at the end of summer. You had all summer guys, smh slakkin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:49:28 UTC">
      <body>Chill i can't change chelsea's birthday nigga it is what it is. Also this party was not my idea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136210" time="2012-08-17 17:49:48 UTC">
      <body>Basically nothing's my fault and i'm perfect</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136164" time="2012-08-17 17:52:57 UTC">
      <body>Lmao yeah I wasn't blaming you for anything. We already planned our shit for earlier in the summer so we good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="136164" time="2012-08-18 00:46:50 UTC">
      <body>Save me some illicit substances!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="136210" time="2012-08-18 00:50:21 UTC">
      <body>Lmaoooo we got mad folks here dawg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="136164" time="2012-08-18 00:50:43 UTC">
      <body>Ugh pleeeaaazzzeeee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="136164" time="2012-08-18 02:29:53 UTC">
      <body>Hey what time are u leavin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="136164" time="2012-08-19 01:25:03 UTC">
      <body>EID MUBARAK!!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
