<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130513.0054" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 02:44:02 UTC">
      <body>Happy birthday! What did you do today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 04:07:52 UTC">
      <body>i slept through most of it, to be honest. had dinner with my parents and went to see gatsby. thanks for asking. :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 04:17:22 UTC">
      <body>You're welcome. Good to know you can still take comas?! What did you have for dinner? Did you go out or stay in? Also is Gatsby a must see?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 04:19:58 UTC">
      <body>yeah, slept from 2 to 11 and napped from 1 to 5. nuts. panera for dinner, because we're not classy at all. gatsby was okay. it was a little much for me. my mom had never read the book, which i didn't know. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 04:26:26 UTC">
      <body>Wow. You must have needed all that sleep from finals! Have you enjoyed being home? Did you get any presents?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 04:28:53 UTC">
      <body>being home is great, i really needed a break from my real life. i got some cards and some "iou's" from family, but i sort of asked everyone to not give me anything. how was the end of the year for you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 04:43:32 UTC">
      <body>I was very busy with finals and review sessions. And i'll be leaving for germany on tuesday! What kind of ious? Do you feel like you needed a break fromyour real life?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 04:47:43 UTC">
      <body>i hope your students did well on the final! my grandmother wants to send me some clothes, i think, and my dad is buying me bus tickets so i can visit some friends. everything was just getting to be a little too hectic, so i'm glad i'm here where there's almost nothing happening. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 04:56:45 UTC">
      <body>They did well! I'm pleased to know you're taking it easy. How does it feel not being a teenager anymore? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 04:57:37 UTC">
      <body>about the same? is it really supposed to feel that different? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136150" time="2013-05-13 05:07:15 UTC">
      <body>probably not yet but i think it will.  your twenties are an interesting time. Well. I'm going to head to bed. Happy birthday.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136112" time="2013-05-13 05:07:40 UTC">
      <body>thanks. goodnight! :) </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
