<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141019.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-19 15:07:56 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>So I fell asleep around midnight and woke up at 5 something. I forced myself to go back to keep around 6 something and woke up a few minutes ago. Should I count that as having slept 10 hours or having slept 5 hours and then getting a 5-hour nap?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-20 02:48:32 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I consider that a full night's sleep. Congrats!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-20 11:23:58 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Summer, is officially over! What happened to the slightly cold Fall weather cause it freakin' feels like Winter outside! Good morning! Hahah :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-20 11:44:05 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I know.... My house hasn't been this cold in a while... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-20 11:45:20 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm not looking forward to going outside in a few minutes. It looks nice outside but that's what it wants you to think! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-20 11:46:31 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>lol. Yup. Errands?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-20 11:50:46 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>No I slept over my friends apartment in Chinatown. It's nice waking up here, it's a nice view.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-20 11:51:04 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Oh nice! So many sleep overs lately ehh. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-20 12:00:19 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>This one was more unplanned than the last one. I just got really sleepy and began to pass out on her couch. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-20 12:04:49 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I gotcha. Twitter. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-20 12:05:18 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Sorry. Twitter was for someone else. Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-10-20 12:05:20 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Hey, whatever happened to that job interview? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-10-20 12:05:35 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I figured hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-10-20 12:06:14 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm waiting for them to get back to me to schedule it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-10-20 12:06:53 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>It's funny that you ask because I sent them an email just last night to ask them something and to thank them.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-10-20 12:07:23 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I wish I got a name though because I'm addressing whoever it is as HR.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-10-20 12:41:36 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>That's fine. When they respond back, you'll have the name. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-10-20 14:06:38 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hopefully. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-10-20 14:07:05 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I have to say, waking up this early feels good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-10-20 14:09:04 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>That feeling only lasts for a little while...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-10-20 14:13:34 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hahahahah! Wow thanks for letting me know what is to come...well so far this morning has been pretty picturesque. My friend and I went to get breakfast at this cafe called Good Karma. We got bagels that has cream cheese, honey, and apple slices on it. I kind of cleaned out my car and I'm now in my jammies :) who knows, the rest of my day could go downhill from here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-10-20 14:38:56 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Back in jammies?!  That's no good, too comfortable. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

