<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140805.0019" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-05 03:02:27 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey, do you have your bike? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-05 17:29:34 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Do you have your bike?
And I think eden has pants at my house</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-05 19:32:10 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Hey sorry. I do have my bike. I picked it up yesterday. Why?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-05 19:32:18 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And where did you find pants?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-05 20:40:28 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Wow! Yesterday!  Well because we kicked marc out so he passing abd leaving. Stressing weird he going to take things so she wanted to check and make sure marc didn't take it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-05 20:40:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But she noticed it gone yesterday so she noticed it quick lol. And edens jeans in the basement, washer room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-05 20:41:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Packing** not passing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-05 20:58:34 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Wow #### I saw him yesterday when I got it. I asked why he had stuff in bags. He said he was moving in with his aunt but didn't say why. I was even going to ask you why.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-05 21:09:21 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And good lookout, I must say.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-05 21:09:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea he been smoking #### again. As a result he would come home looking high with glassy eyes, then sleeping til 1-2 in the afternoon, haVing mood swings and behavioral changes, then disregarding our curfew and walking in 3-4 in the morning on week nights thinking we were sleeping and didn't know.... trying to get over on us.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-05 21:11:18 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Oh damn</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-05 21:11:36 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And he said he was gonna take stuff?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-08-05 21:12:58 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Then I been showering over Steph's parents bec our bathroom not done.  Her parents drive me home and her mom sees him on the corner rolling a joint. He just left our house and had it before his ride came. That means that he had drugs inside our house!!! For one if he got caught it would ruin my juvenile career.  2nd- stephs brother rodney had a baby. He is going to raise it but Stroh is going to be involved. And with rodney having a jail record and the mother still on drugs DHS is involved with the baby who will be over our house alot. If he got  caught that would ban the baby from our home abd Stroh would lose visitation Rights</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-08-05 21:13:07 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And steph**</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-08-05 21:15:17 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>We were only going to raise his rent (he been paying late but yet has money for drugs).. give him chores.. ground him. But when we confronted him about it he denied it, said the drug test was lying, freaked out and said he'll leave.  Was raising his voice to Steph and disrespecting her like it wadnt her house and like she didn't financially support him for over a year. Well now youre gone. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-08-05 21:16:45 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And no he didn't say he would take stuff but with being not in his normal mind set with the changes he could try to get even and take stuff... that or he could have borrowed it and not return it. He has Steph's baseball equipment in his cousin's car and its been 3 days he has been "forgetting" to get it from the car he is in everyday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-08-05 21:20:43 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Btw... guy going bathroom is also going to fix both bedrooms... starting with rhe ceiling in your room (its collapsing). Going to have to move your stuff during that time so if you can help.  Plus redoing the room and I think im taking the back room. And turning middle room into nursery for baby. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-08-05 21:21:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Not kicking you out but 1- youre leaving anyway and 2- with basement empty you can use that as storage for your stuff so we can use the bedrooms</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-08-05 21:29:01 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah that's totally fun. I definitely wanna help. When are you doing this?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-08-05 21:29:20 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>*fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-08-05 21:31:09 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I saw the bathroom btw. It was looking good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-08-05 21:36:12 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Saw it today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-08-05 21:36:54 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And no date set yet for bedroom renovations but will let you know when it takes place</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-08-05 21:38:55 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yesterday.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-08-05 21:39:07 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay thanks. And what pants did you find</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-08-05 21:58:58 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Jeans. Idk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-08-05 22:10:17 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I don't think they're edens</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-08-05 23:24:45 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh so its abig difference from then and today. . Just saw bathroom.  Im excited for it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-08-05 23:34:40 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I can't wait to see it</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

