<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150403.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-04-03 23:32:16 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>So I'm doing homework aka daydreaming about the day I'll be done with school. Saying how nice it will be to have a social life again when I got super sad that when I get a social life your losing your's to start school </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-04-04 00:08:32 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Yay!! I knew you would! This is one of the reason why I love ya. As long as we keep doing like we are, we are cool. Just schedule the time in, I can't wait for jazz night, it's nuts how it's here again! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-04-04 00:08:37 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Oh no worries. I will most definitely be your wing girl. I got you. I'll always have time for you! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-04-04 00:18:56 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>I know! It flew by!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-04-04 00:20:22 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I feel like my weeks are a blur anymore. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-04-04 00:20:52 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Me too. I don't understand it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-04-04 00:21:20 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>It's sad, its ground hog's day. I need some more excitement but I'm too exhausted </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-04-04 00:22:28 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Haha same here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-04-04 00:23:28 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Preschool is closed for spring break but we still can work because we have to do visits. I took today off and all I did was homework. That's kinda sad- I did get my nails done but still. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-04-04 00:25:19 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol when I have off from work, I clean. We lead such amazing lives haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-04-04 00:25:36 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>It's so pathetic haha. Like I have to catch up on these assignments but I would have liked to enjoy a Friday off. Maybe when we are 30?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-04-04 00:26:26 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>I hope it's not that long!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-04-04 00:27:09 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I hope not either. But that's the goal i put on myself. I want to finish and have my license and board cert by 30. Easy peasy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-04-04 00:27:23 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>You got it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-04-04 00:29:08 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I'm very close but I'm stressing out because I have to figure out how to get a year of experience for licensure and I have a practicum opportunity with the university of penn that I'm trying to figure out if I should take. I have an interview Tuesday. I spoke with her today. But it could effect my work schedule. I'm stressing hard core. I need a life coach. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-04-04 00:30:36 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Omg! Well good luck on your interview! But I mean it's worth having a sucky work schedule. It's a great thing to have on your resume.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-04-04 00:32:00 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Thank you! She said she is willing to work with me so I'm excited for that. I have a meeting with the director on Monday to hear her thoughts. I'm pretty sure I'll have to change programs at work but like you said it's great on my resume and maybe penn will hire me ☺️ it's just tough to figure out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-04-04 00:54:38 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>The good things are never easy lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-04-04 00:55:28 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Oh so true. I'm just being a scaredy cat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-04-04 02:40:00 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Jamaica or punta Cana? Manny is annoying me with telling me about his trip so I think we should just plan our own </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-04-04 02:40:00 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Or maybe San Lucas </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-04-04 02:42:08 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Oh crap I completely forgot.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-04-04 02:42:08 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I'm a tiny bit nervous about us being in a different country alone. Maybe we will just go when he does but stay and do our own thing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-04-04 02:42:37 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Hmm well I'm doing punta Cana for the wedding </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-04-04 02:44:06 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol okay. Just let know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-04-04 02:44:30 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I mean there is probably nothing fun to do in usa </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-04-04 02:45:49 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah probably not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-04-04 02:47:14 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>How many days you think you can take? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-04-04 02:49:12 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Well I'm already using a week for the wedding.. Sooo maybe 3 days during the week and make it a long weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-04-04 02:50:06 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Okay that's reasonable, I don't have tons of leave either. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

