<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130305.0020" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-03-05 14:52:28 UTC">
      <body>So DC is supposed to get 8-12" of snow Wednesday, forecasting "heavy snow and wind" wed. afternoon and evening. If its bad, can I stay with you an extra night? If you're giving me your house key anyway I can just walk back to your place after my interview (I'm guessing you'll still be at work) and figure it out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135080" time="2013-03-05 14:59:43 UTC">
      <body>Slash it is supposed to start getting shitty tonight now - will you still be going to your thing tonight? If not I would come down earlier than 9</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-03-05 17:31:58 UTC">
      <body>Also do you guys have a snow shovel (so I don't get trapped in your driveway)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-03-06 00:14:39 UTC">
      <body>Leaving bc now!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135080" time="2013-03-06 00:14:44 UTC">
      <body>*hc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135263" time="2013-03-06 00:57:36 UTC">
      <body>Awesome, see you soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2013-03-06 22:12:09 UTC">
      <body>Did you go back to work? Also did it stop snowing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135263" time="2013-03-06 22:14:49 UTC">
      <body>No and yes. What's your plan? I have to go back for ~1.5h at some point but will prob hang around here for another hr or so</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135263" time="2013-03-06 22:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Yes to both caffeine is readily available</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135080" time="2013-03-06 22:19:45 UTC">
      <body>Oh. Ok. I am sleepy. I have been asleep since 2:30 and i feel like i just asked you delirious questions but i dont remember what they were. I'm trying to decide whether I feel more guilty about not going home cause its not snowy, or afraid the roads are icy. Probs more the second one. Do you have caffeinated things / is there a coffee shop nearby?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135263" time="2013-03-06 22:21:52 UTC">
      <body>Also right now it's mostly just melty outside but I'd be a little worried that it would freeze over as it gets later and colder</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135080" time="2013-03-06 22:22:55 UTC">
      <body>Yeah okay. Ill be down in a sec</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
