<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120725.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 17:57:20 UTC">
      <body>Sophie, I just got some unbelievably heartbreaking news! Apparently, your friends have opened the same exact business as ours, in the same building, the floor below us! Who are these people, why would they do this!?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2012-07-25 17:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Oh the hot woods. they are doing something very different.  There spaces are a lot more expensive and their operation is run completely different.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Butch just spoke with the woman, it's a recording studio, Gallery and artist lofts! How is it different? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Please, help me to understand, because I am on the verge of tears right now!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Can u talk right now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-07-25 18:20:42 UTC">
      <body>I won't be able to talk this evening.
I have to deal with my car. Etc but don't worry i think you guys offer a very different experience. Plus the more the merrier. There is always room for more and money for more!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:27:12 UTC">
      <body>Please, Sophie call me ASAP, I feel like I've been stabbed through the heart! I would like to know what "experience" they are offering. They know all about our business, all we know is that they are doing exactly the same thing, in the exact same building. Morally, that is wrong on so many levels. I wish u could see this from our point of view, we have put everything we have into this vision, it's like a child to us, please just make some time for me. Please!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-07-25 18:39:45 UTC">
      <body>I will def call you tonight. However I got into a very bad accident yesterday and totaled and am coordinating leaving town today. I just met the hot wood people a few weeks ago.  I don't know the specifics about there business plans but as a consumer And artist feel like you offer two very different experiences</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:44:16 UTC">
      <body>Sorry, about the accident, are u ok? Maybe, these aren't the people ur thinking of. This woman said ur a good friend of hers and u told her what we were doing and they thought it was a great idea and wanted to do the same thing? I think they've been in the building for a cpl of months.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135398" time="2012-07-25 18:44:16 UTC">
      <body>Pls, just call me as soon as u can. I hope u feel better.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130622" time="2012-07-25 20:36:28 UTC">
      <body>Megan talked to butch.... Everything seems fine.  But seriously both of you (you &amp; butch and megan &amp; mike)  are great people.  You guys have a real opportunity to turn the space into a a very magical and special haven for artists. It's exciting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135398" time="2012-07-26 01:08:16 UTC">
      <body>Just really want u 2 know, we're sending great energy ur way and want u to KIT. No hard feelings in any way, pls txt me back that u got this. Much love!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130622" time="2012-07-26 15:05:33 UTC">
      <body>Hey kaki. That's such a nice text!  Thank you and butch for everything and when you guys get the gallery up I'll bring down my work </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135398" time="2012-07-26 15:10:56 UTC">
      <body>K, safe travels!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
