<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130310.0018" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130664" time="2013-03-10 18:32:12 UTC">
      <body>Hey lady, I'm trying to figure out a time to visit people in lanc, when are your best nights for doin stuff?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:17:55 UTC">
      <body>My schedule is seriously all over the place. My shifts range from 530 am-2 to 4-1230 in the am. It's the pits! My days off are usually Sunday/Monday...bu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:17:56 UTC">
      <body>t that varies also. I can work you in whenever though. I'm down with morning hang out! Let me know!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:22:24 UTC">
      <body>Oh man that is terrible! Both shifts are bummers</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:23:08 UTC">
      <body>I love morning handouts. Specially when there are mimosas</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:24:19 UTC">
      <body>Also, Dan ###### wrote me on fb. He mentioned our apt on duke street, yikes!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:25:31 UTC">
      <body>This week I'm bankers hours...8-430 everyday. Which probably means that next week I'm totally fucked...ha. I can adjust easily though. There are 5 people</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:25:32 UTC">
      <body> in my department so switching is fairly easy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:26:52 UTC">
      <body>Oh geez. In my head everyone has forgotten our duke street apt. and holy crap...Dan ######?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:27:58 UTC">
      <body>Right?!? Do you ever see that guy? He said he and his wife (!!) live on Frederick, and he walks by our old place everyday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:28:13 UTC">
      <body>I kind of hate Facebook for those random interactions.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:28:51 UTC">
      <body>Something about that made me queasy... that there are people in this world whose only impression of me are from that window of time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:29:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh God.no I've never seen him. That i know of...Dodd i tell you Jon ##### friended me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:29:30 UTC">
      <body>I know!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:29:46 UTC">
      <body>Hahahaha..that is so funny! Is he still cute?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:32:17 UTC">
      <body>Meh...not the Adonis i had remembered but he aiight.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:32:48 UTC">
      <body>I remember him glowing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:33:17 UTC">
      <body> read: still pretty cute.  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:34:57 UTC">
      <body>I think he used to have like...a sparky aura or something. To read my old journals he was definitely of some godly proportion.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:37:32 UTC">
      <body>I'm sure age killed some of his sparkle. It's easy to have a sparkle when you work at a skate shop and babes visit you all day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:40:09 UTC">
      <body>So Russell is getting married in a month. Went to the wedding shower today. Also Adam seems to think Man got married. For real.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:40:54 UTC">
      <body>Jesus. What the hell??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:41:17 UTC">
      <body>I wonder what that was like</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:41:59 UTC">
      <body>He sent him a wedding gift and everything! I can never tell if he's joking or not. The girls name is Ambrosia and apparently Adam has met her.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:42:59 UTC">
      <body>Right, like is the gift part of the joke? So weird</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Any other good gossip? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:53:21 UTC">
      <body>Um...i don't really talk to anyone. The friends i had around here are all gone or boring. Going to the lounge is terrible. That's the only place i see a </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:53:22 UTC">
      <body>lot of familiar faces, but it's all awkward small talk. I avoid it. a lot of the cool kids got chubby...that's kind of funny. i think that's what happens</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:53:24 UTC">
      <body> when you don't do anything but go to the same bar for ten years. That's me being really catty though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:54:45 UTC">
      <body>I dunno...i think i shouldn't have come back here. I do enjoy my time with the fam. Adams and mine. But aside from family time i don't do much at all socially</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 03:55:42 UTC">
      <body>Please tell me you have good gossip.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:57:38 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha..I'm glad all those fuckers got chubby. I don't have any gossip at all. I like don't or can't really talk to anyone from lanc. Sometimes mark texts me, but that's it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 03:58:04 UTC">
      <body>Do you guys know what you are going to do? How long you are staying around there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:01:53 UTC">
      <body>On fb I think it's kind of funny that all the bitchy younger girls just turned into wives/moms</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:02:13 UTC">
      <body>I dunno. Adams into his trucking thing. Did you even know that is what he's doing? He works with Greg-Hawa's beau-doing shipping. Driving big trucks acro</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:02:14 UTC">
      <body>ss the country. Perfect for him. He gets the travel in while i get to have s home base. I'm trying to get a bit of time in with the marriott. I'm applyin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:02:16 UTC">
      <body>g for a part time accounting position and I'll stay in my current dept part time. I think I'll get it. Then I'll kind of have a "career"...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:02:48 UTC">
      <body>I don't know how long we'll stay though. At least a year...we signed a lease.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:06:38 UTC">
      <body>I love Facebook. it is both terrible and sometimes a huge confidence boost!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:07:12 UTC">
      <body>Whoa that's nuts, he totally looks like a trucker. I'm so over PA. I just want to be done with school, it's fun but so mentally exhausting in so many ways. And I want to be in a place I want to make home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:08:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, Dan told me I looked "fantastic!" And I wanted to be like yeah that's because you are used to Lancaster people haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:08:31 UTC">
      <body>Sucha bitch</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:09:00 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, i feel ya!! We've talked about the northwest often, but sometimes i feel nervous about that because of man and Kaz living there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:09:23 UTC">
      <body>Ha! It's true though! Lancaster is dumpy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:11:00 UTC">
      <body>I can see that. They are kind of a powerful force when together. I keep thinking about that area too, but I don't know. I hope I'm not too cynical to live there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:16:50 UTC">
      <body>Ha! I know. There is that also. I'm used to my "no eye contact, mind your own biz, glass is sometimes empty, i ain't giving you change, get off my lawn"n</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:16:51 UTC">
      <body>orth east- attitude.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:18:33 UTC">
      <body>I don't know if I'm ready for the easy going-ness of the Pacific northwest...I'm kind of hardened!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:18:57 UTC">
      <body>Ha ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 04:19:49 UTC">
      <body>I hate trying to be funny in texts. It never comes out quite right. We should talk on the phone soon.I miss you girl. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:20:49 UTC">
      <body>I know me too. It's like my security shell. Maybe it's like a bad relationship, and once we were off the east coast, we would never look back? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:21:04 UTC">
      <body>I just want to live in warm weather, maybe a beach</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 04:21:34 UTC">
      <body>Haha, no you are totally funny. I miss u too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 20:58:42 UTC">
      <body>Do you still have your list? Or am i the only one who did that.. ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 20:59:49 UTC">
      <body>He keeps texting me and talking about how great our old apartment was hash</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 21:00:03 UTC">
      <body>I mean haha, but hash works too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 21:01:29 UTC">
      <body>I do have a list some where. It has a lot of random entries, like "girl at rave" haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 21:01:36 UTC">
      <body>I should reference that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 21:07:38 UTC">
      <body>Oh God. Yeah the just kissing or just making out ones were the worst. All the nicknames. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 21:08:40 UTC">
      <body>He keeps texting you?!? Weird. I don't remember our place fondly at all. I don't REMEMBER most of it...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="130664" time="2013-03-11 21:12:23 UTC">
      <body>I know totally. He was like "why no love for that apartment? I have great memories" and I was like I have next to no memories</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131057" time="2013-03-11 21:38:10 UTC">
      <body>So true!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
