<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130415.0052" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:05:39 UTC">
      <body>Should I take that personally?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:26:01 UTC">
      <body>Ya know, I can take a hint except when we actually do talk you don't seem to convey any annoyance or frustration with me. If the lack of response was from anyone else i would have stopped calling a long time ago.  Cutting me out like this just seems out character for you, and for friendship i thought we shared. So I guess I'm a little confused. Not sure if I should just forget about u and bill completely at this point. I kinda thought you guys needed me in some way, or at least wanted me around. But I'm not trying to fight if I'm not wanted.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:26:17 UTC">
      <body>I hope you don't take that as mean or manipulative. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:26:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm just confused. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:27:45 UTC">
      <body>I just didn't realize that if we werent sleeping together, if I wasn't so close, I didn't realize we wouldn't talk as much. I guess it's my misunderstanding. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:30:12 UTC">
      <body>Please don't be offended, i  don't think your an ass or mean or anything. And i still love you guys. Always will. I'm just trying to understand.  You really were one of my best friends for so long. I really didn't want to loose that ya know?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 00:52:13 UTC">
      <body>Maybe we can't be friends maybe we can't be phone friends.  Maybe there is some way you can help me manage my expectations. Hopefully. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 19:47:02 UTC">
      <body>Big explosions in boston today </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 19:47:35 UTC">
      <body>Downtown is being evacuated</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 19:54:52 UTC">
      <body>Lots of bombs that haven't gone off yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 19:56:33 UTC">
      <body>Terrifying</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 20:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Call me bomb city</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130622" time="2013-04-15 20:42:09 UTC">
      <body>I love you guys!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135470" time="2013-04-15 20:54:08 UTC">
      <body>We love you too stay calm be mindful of your surroundings</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
