<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130609.0044" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:19:07 UTC">
      <body>It would be pretty awesome if I got past the stage in a breakup where everything associated with the person is ruined. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136112" time="2013-06-09 04:20:11 UTC">
      <body>like, i get that that's a thing for you, but i don't understand it. or breakups. idk. what, specifically, are you thinking of? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:22:27 UTC">
      <body>I was supposed to watch The Jungle Book with Nari because we cant get The Bear Necessities out of our heads, but I just can't</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2013-06-09 04:22:44 UTC">
      <body>who do you associate that with? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:25:34 UTC">
      <body>Nakul. His favorite thing ever is Bhalu. We spent a whole morning watching Tail Spin during finals</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136112" time="2013-06-09 04:26:28 UTC">
      <body>i don't know what tail spin is. so you're still feeling lots of feels about nakul? :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:36:40 UTC">
      <body>It's a tv show about Bhalu flying a plane. Not as many feels, but thinking about the good times kind of sucks. I feel really lost because I had all these plans </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:36:41 UTC">
      <body>for when I went to India, and the comfort of having someone I was close with there, and now I don't. I had rebound romance with Zach, and that kind of helped I </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136378" time="2013-06-09 04:36:42 UTC">
      <body>guess.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136112" time="2013-06-09 04:39:05 UTC">
      <body>if it helps, don't let the fact that those "good time" memories are over make you sad. they were good! you were having fun! try to look back and still be happy about it? this is like stupid advice but it really does make a difference. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
