<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120806.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 00:55:28 UTC">
      <body>Well the wait is over. No more Zach and Molly. Deleted fb for a while but didn't want you to find out through social media. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 01:37:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh sweetheart. I'll be thinking of you. Im proud of you and am humbly there every step of your way. I love you. Let me know f you need anything.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 01:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Thanks. It isn't easy that's for sure. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 16:13:58 UTC">
      <body>How are you today, love?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 16:34:08 UTC">
      <body>Feeling okay. I really think I will be until 1. I reactivate my fb and 2. Garth brooks sings the dance next weekend at the concerts. I cry at that song anyway but I think I will have a breakdown! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 16:41:25 UTC">
      <body>Maybe prep yourself and listen to it a few times? A good cry is sometimes nice too. And maybe you never have to reactivate! But im glad you're ok.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 16:51:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I have been. It is just so so beautiful live that I'm not sure I can make it through! But it isn't for 2 weekends so hopefully I can make it. I went to the DMV today and the guy took my picture three times. I'm scared what it is going to look like! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 16:51:12 UTC">
      <body>I also just might utilize Pearl's fb too. All the people I really care about are friends on that page so I might just avoid my own page for a while. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 17:10:19 UTC">
      <body>You're going to look beautiful. Your worst in a drivers license is still way better than most peoples bests. What are you afraid of on facebook? Seeing Zachs info?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 17:14:40 UTC">
      <body>Him detagging pics and stuff, deleting my friends. And the fact that I think he wants to get with a girl he works with. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 17:17:39 UTC">
      <body>What a guy. Yea, maybe just hide his business too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 17:18:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm not entirely sure if he does. But I just get the feeling. Which would make two breakups in a row that that has happened to me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 17:19:32 UTC">
      <body>Either way, you're better off I think.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 17:19:51 UTC">
      <body>Wait whoa! That's really exciting :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2012-08-06 17:20:26 UTC">
      <body>Yea, and now you get a fresh start :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 17:21:04 UTC">
      <body>But I'm going to ca tomorrow thru Thursday then friday I'm going to Washington state. Then next Tuesday I will start my new job so things are good. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 17:21:04 UTC">
      <body>This breakup had been a long time coming. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135095" time="2012-08-06 17:21:04 UTC">
      <body>Yep. And it is going to be good. I basically get to start my dream career ladder Tuesday so things won't suck forever. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135095" time="2012-08-07 02:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Have you watched weeds yet? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135095" time="2012-08-07 02:29:20 UTC">
      <body>About 5 minutes are good, the other 22 are snoozy! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131839" time="2012-08-07 02:30:46 UTC">
      <body>No not yet, is it worth the download?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131839" time="2012-08-07 02:41:36 UTC">
      <body>Breaking bad has become my happy substite for weeds. So good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135095" time="2012-08-07 02:42:08 UTC">
      <body>I couldn't watch after the second episode with the body and the bathtub. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131839" time="2012-08-07 02:50:30 UTC">
      <body>Yea, you have to push through a little and then it gets really interesting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135095" time="2012-08-07 02:52:48 UTC">
      <body>I was so absolutely disturbed by it. That's what other people have said too that nothing is that bad throughout the rest of the show </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131839" time="2012-08-07 03:03:26 UTC">
      <body>Yea, the violence is outweighed by everything else. It's got a flavor of the first season of weeds a little. Family stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135095" time="2012-08-07 03:09:52 UTC">
      <body>Maybe I will give it another try! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
