<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140920.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-20 16:08:32 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Are you around this week? I'm coming to philly wed or Thursday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-20 16:31:09 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oooh yes! I am nannying and babysitting unfortunately until wed but I think I might be free during day too/ text me when you're here? You can def crash at my place tho even if I'm not there </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-20 16:31:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Sorry I never replied about the ny trip- I wasn't sure if I could but I def can't now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-20 16:31:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I've been insanely busy and it's been awful lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-20 16:31:54 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Im exhausted all the time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-20 16:32:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha I'm sorry these kids woke me up at 7:30am and I'm still bitter </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-20 16:49:29 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Awww. Sorry your so busy! I'll let you know when I know for sure. So, you would be available Thursday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-20 17:40:16 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Ok. We'll stay in touch. I'll come soon. I have my money:) wanted to give you what I owe you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-20 17:40:42 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Maybe ...their parents return Thursday evening but I might be totally exhausted by then so I don't want to make promises ; I will def try tho </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-20 17:41:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Just the Constantly wanting to play omg go to bed go read a book oh wait you can't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-20 17:42:12 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>They are overwhelming! I used to have to nap when they did</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-20 17:42:24 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>I can mail you a check too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-20 17:42:24 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-20 17:42:27 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It's only been half a day and I already feel like I've survived some kind of war </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-21 02:11:48 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>So, I really do want to buy another of your pieces if you have any to sell? Could you send me a photo of one or two that you think I would like? I truly admire your work and I can't imagine decorating my new apt without some. I'm so lucky</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-09-21 02:13:55 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Also, if I send you check for what I owe you, plus interest, and a check for any artwork, can I pay to have the piece I bought + whatever I owe for another piece and have them shipped here? I can pay for shipping
</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-09-21 02:16:02 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ok! I have a show coming up at the Crane though and I want to show all of my recent paintings. I will definitely let you know! I also interviewed to work full time at the fabric workshop museum and if I get that job, you and I should celebrate. It'll be nice not to juggle pt gallery work with Pt coffeeshop stuff :/ </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-09-21 02:16:32 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>It will be so nice. You deserve that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-09-21 02:18:29 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>I understand about your work. I feel bad that I'm not able to offer obscene amounts of money for them, like they are worth. Just know that I will truly treasure and showcase anything of yours. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-09-21 02:19:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Aw! Thanks! No worries! I have smaller, lower priced paintings </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-09-21 02:19:28 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm showing with Brice actually which I'm happy about </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-09-21 02:19:50 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>I can't even daydream of my new apt, without including your paintings in the scheme</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-09-21 02:19:54 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I feel really good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-09-21 02:20:04 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha yay! I'm glad you won that $$ </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-09-21 02:20:18 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I think DC is a really good place for you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-09-21 02:20:32 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>That's awesome, Ingrid! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-09-21 02:20:40 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>For now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-09-21 02:20:48 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>I eventually want to go west coast</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-09-21 02:20:48 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Or europe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-09-21 02:20:48 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Where is your show?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-09-21 02:22:56 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>Will you just send me some photos of what you think I might like and I can send the full check to you the beginning of the week?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-09-21 02:24:22 UTC" participant="152762">
      <body>And want to hear more about your show</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

