<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140830.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-30 17:57:20 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Has Cindy stopped by yet? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-30 23:32:09 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes and she respected and took all my things out of the closet and now I'm rewashing everything again and putting all my clothes in bags </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-30 23:32:31 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼It's like moving in all over again. It's awful </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-30 23:32:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha it's so awful to do this again </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-30 23:32:48 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I really hope it works this time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-31 01:59:28 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Me too!!  Let's secret it!!  Does she have to come back again after you re-wash everything? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-31 02:00:36 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>And again I'm sorry.  I'll compensate you for your time.   I know this sucks.   Thanks again for your patience.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-31 02:01:33 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Did you ask her whether getting rid of the carpet would help? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-31 14:48:46 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I did not ask but I'm sure it will and also I truly cannot believe the other roommates don't have to also do the same thing to their rooms bc that makes no sense to me at all </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-31 14:49:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She didn't find bugs in my room either but they're clearly there or I wouldn't be getting bitten </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-31 14:49:43 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I think for the problem to truly go away, the whole house needs to be done. It seems more expensive and drawn out to keep doing it room by room but that's just IMO </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-31 14:50:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:) I think they just move to the other roommates When I leave to my dads, then they will come back to my room </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-08-31 14:50:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>When I return </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-08-31 14:51:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also this totally sucks haha had I know my room had Just been treated for bugs the month before I moved in, and it had bed bug powder all along it's walls, and I wasn't supposed to put anything against walls or use my closet for a few months, I wouldn't have moved in :( (tho I want to stay now that I'm here bc I like it obv) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-08-31 14:52:09 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(And bc moving again makes me want to cry haha)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

