<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120104.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 03:47:23 UTC">
      <body>Hey have you gotten grades back from es? Idk where to look</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 07:41:00 UTC">
      <body>Yeah go to bearfacts, then click on students, then current term grades. There should be a drop list on the upper right of the page, and you have to switc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 07:42:07 UTC">
      <body>h midterm grades to final grades. That's what worked for me. They make it so confusing though!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 20:04:32 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I just figured it out and felt like an idiot haha. You happy with your grades?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 20:06:18 UTC">
      <body>Yup, 4.0! And I passed env sci, it's a good thing I took it pass/no pass. Are you happy with yours? I have wine and champagne to bring back to Berkeley f</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 20:14:40 UTC">
      <body>rom France btw! See you in a few wks :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 20:43:06 UTC">
      <body>That's awesome! Congrats! And I got all bs which I was expecting, so I'm not bummed or anything. But that's tight! (: see you soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 21:50:50 UTC">
      <body>Oh nice that's good! And I wanna see your new tat. Are you happy with how it turned out?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 21:52:03 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, im super stoked, did I sen you a photo? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 21:55:06 UTC">
      <body>I don't think you did yet. Send one if you have a minute!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 21:56:50 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131063" time="2012-01-04 21:58:41 UTC">
      <body>Omg I love it!! Seriously, it looks so amazing, I'm in shock. This was connor's guy, right? It's so well done!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131019" time="2012-01-04 22:00:44 UTC">
      <body>Haha thanks, I really like it, can't wait for it to heal tho, itches like a bitch right now. And yeah it's him, I'm so happy with it</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
