<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121230.0019" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130706" time="2012-12-30 21:54:54 UTC">
      <body>Kathy has been feeling sick all day and is now feeling worse. We are going to pass on dinner. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130706" time="2012-12-30 21:58:39 UTC">
      <body>Okay if we pick up dog and drill on way home from work tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131505" time="2012-12-30 22:02:39 UTC">
      <body>Ok.  Sorry she's sick.  All will be ready for you tomorrow night if uou can stop for dinner.  Or come tonight if Kathy would enjoy some quiet time.?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130706" time="2012-12-30 22:05:26 UTC">
      <body>We will just grab dog and tools tomorrow, New Year's Eve and all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131505" time="2012-12-30 22:08:05 UTC">
      <body>I forgot.   I'll be leaving about 3 pm, XD might be here.  If not door will be left unlocked. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130706" time="2012-12-30 22:12:38 UTC">
      <body>Does XD stand for Extremely Dangerous?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131505" time="2012-12-30 22:15:16 UTC">
      <body>Yes!  And a great cook for Chinese food.   I've been enjoying his meals.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131505" time="2012-12-31 19:39:48 UTC">
      <body>you get out a little early.   Love, mom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131505" time="2012-12-31 19:39:49 UTC">
      <body>Sweetheart,  i'll leave door unlocked and drill in bag next to door.  Please lock behind you.  X.D. may be here, not back yet from his bike ride.   Hope </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131505" time="2012-12-31 23:42:09 UTC">
      <body>AAA is coming.  Would you like us to pick up Jack and have him come to grandma's house for a surprise overnight.  I can handle one not two.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130706" time="2012-12-31 23:43:30 UTC">
      <body>No thank you, I don't want him to be 'rewarded' for his bad behavior.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130706" time="2012-12-31 23:44:03 UTC">
      <body>He is in his room for the night. No book. No song.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130706" time="2012-12-31 23:45:22 UTC">
      <body>Hopefully when he wakes up, if he ever falls asleep, he will be more compliant.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131505" time="2012-12-31 23:50:32 UTC">
      <body>'m throwing a neighborhood party at 4 pm.  Jack can help.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131505" time="2012-12-31 23:50:40 UTC">
      <body>I'll check in with you once we're started.  Maybe he'll sleep through the night.  You can drop him off tomorrow if it will help..  again, one not two.  I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130706" time="2013-01-01 00:30:01 UTC">
      <body>I'm not rewarding him for being bad. If I drop off one kid, but not the other, how do you think the other kid would feel?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130706" time="2013-01-01 00:30:26 UTC">
      <body>If I send just Craig it is cruel to Jack and Vice versa</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
