<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20111124.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131063" time="2011-11-24 21:55:36 UTC">
      <body>Happy thanksgiving! Let's skype tomorrow or Saturday after you get back to cal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131019" time="2011-11-24 22:38:18 UTC">
      <body>Happy thanksgiving! And I'm so down to see some snow! ⛄haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131063" time="2011-11-24 23:08:08 UTC">
      <body>Haha I can finally send you my weird shit!! 
電話費تسنسغبغصدעדישיריג</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131063" time="2011-11-24 23:09:24 UTC">
      <body>י and snow on saturday sounds like a plan, I'll hit you up then :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:38:43 UTC">
      <body>This mom on the Bart Is feeding her two kids seaweed :D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:41:41 UTC">
      <body>That's so gonna be us someday! How was thanksgiving with johnny's fam? Things are getting weird here my sister is apparently practically suicidal and she</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:41:56 UTC">
      <body>'s coming home from London tonight. Last time we called her a cop picked up her phone and told us that he found her alone having a panic attack.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:42:22 UTC">
      <body>What the fuck? Why what happened?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:44:40 UTC">
      <body>We don't know. She won't even talk to my mom but she's been sobbing all week and won't say what's wrong. My dad's picking her up from the airport now and</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:44:55 UTC">
      <body> we're having a "family meeting" when she gets here so I guess we'll find out then. I'm worried about her though she's usually the together one!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:45:23 UTC">
      <body>Meh that sucks. I hope she's okay:/ did she go there for a boy btw?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:48:35 UTC">
      <body>She went there to see her best friend but there was some guy she met there that she was into this summer that she wanted to see. Nothing happened then bu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:48:46 UTC">
      <body>t I think she was expecting something this time around. That's probably part of her deal. Hit me up when you're free to skype tomorrow and I'll let you k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:48:47 UTC">
      <body>now for sure. And I wanna hear about your trip!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:50:40 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good, I'll be free all say. And I hope she's okay. Ps dining commons closed, kill me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:53:32 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! And that sucks about the dining commons. Is crossroads closed too? And sounds good, I'll probably be down to skype early afternoon so I'll hit yo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:53:47 UTC">
      <body>u up around then.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:54:21 UTC">
      <body>Dude everything is closed. Yay for chipptle!! And sounds good just text me when I should be home in case I find something to do, which is doubtful</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 22:56:16 UTC">
      <body>Haha I'll do that. And hell yeah I think it's a sign to indulge in a burrito!!! That sounds so good right now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 22:57:01 UTC">
      <body>I'm heading there straight from the Bart cuz I'm starving</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 23:00:22 UTC">
      <body>I plan on doing the same thing on Sunday :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131019" time="2011-11-25 23:05:16 UTC">
      <body>I'd be a happy girl of you invite me hah :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131063" time="2011-11-25 23:06:20 UTC">
      <body>Haha consider yourself invited. I'll be there around 2, more details to come soon. Have a good burrito! And watch some desperate housewives tonight :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131063" time="2011-11-26 20:10:38 UTC">
      <body>Hey! Is 1:15 your time chill for skype?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131019" time="2011-11-26 22:00:03 UTC">
      <body>Dude I'm sorry my sleeping schedule is so fucked. I cannot fall asleep at night so I just woke up:/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131063" time="2011-11-26 22:24:12 UTC">
      <body>Don't even worry about it! I figured you were sleeping when I didn't hear from you. I'll hit you up when I get in tomorrow, should be in the early afternoon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131019" time="2011-11-26 22:25:38 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good. When you said afternoon yesterday I was thinking like four, so it's my bad. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131063" time="2011-11-26 22:27:06 UTC">
      <body>It's all good it's 2 hours later for me here so I wasn't thinking about how early it was for you. I'll see you tomorrow!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131019" time="2011-11-26 22:31:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds good, have a safe flight! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131063" time="2011-11-26 22:31:42 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! Have fun tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131019" time="2011-11-26 22:32:01 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha you're funny :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131063" time="2011-11-26 22:48:37 UTC">
      <body>I try haha. Have a relaxing night in bed with the housewives then. Or Ian Somerhalder :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131019" time="2011-11-26 22:48:49 UTC">
      <body>Hehe hehe(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:14:28 UTC">
      <body>Hey when do you get here again?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 21:33:56 UTC">
      <body>Flight just landed! I'll call you when I get to Berkeley if you want to meet up this afternoon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:36:56 UTC">
      <body>Umm yes. I do. I'm dying here Maddie I need human nteraction. I'm hoping the Bart is super super fast cuz I miss you(: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:37:25 UTC">
      <body>Ps if ou want you can call when you're at the Bart here and I can walks over or whatever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 21:38:10 UTC">
      <body>I miss you too!! And that sounds great, I'll hit you up when I get to the station and you can come over</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:38:40 UTC">
      <body>Sweet(: and we can get fiooooood hah see you soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 21:39:43 UTC">
      <body>YES! I'm feeling chipotle, or shitty xr food, whatever. SEE YOU SOON! I'm excited</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:40:54 UTC">
      <body>Chipotle, xr not open. Ps I just got up which is whybim typin retardedly. Anywho, see you later!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 21:42:07 UTC">
      <body>It's cute haha and I'm jealous you've been sleeping all morning. And yessss chipotle I can taste it already</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 21:42:51 UTC">
      <body>I'm stoked! (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:14:06 UTC">
      <body>Just getting on the Bart now, I should be there in an hr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:14:18 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:19:09 UTC">
      <body>Maddie what did Tom do in the first season that Lynette doesn't know abou?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:20:40 UTC">
      <body>The only season 1 thing I can think of is Tom walking in on the babysitter naked! Season 4 gets good with them though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:23:31 UTC">
      <body>No like he told his dad that  he did something after Lynette said she wouldn't forgive him for cheating ever, and he hasn't said anything yet and I'm confused</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:25:01 UTC">
      <body>He has an illegitimate daughter from before they got married so that's probably it. But Lynette doesn't find out until a few seasons later so maybe it's </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:25:42 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah it prlly is that:p well he sucks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:26:07 UTC">
      <body>just a weird foreshadowing reference. Let me know if it turns out to be something else!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:26:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah and the mother if his child is an annoying bitch so get ready for that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:26:38 UTC">
      <body>Haha I'm excited</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:32:31 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god Tom is suck a dick!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:32:39 UTC">
      <body>Such*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:33:13 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha I like what you just typed, and yes he is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:34:14 UTC">
      <body>Haha it was a really great typo and in aboutk send you something unny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:34:54 UTC">
      <body>Yer a wizard Whaley</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:35:36 UTC">
      <body>Haha where did you find that? Great to have an iPhone, huh? :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:36:25 UTC">
      <body>Haha on tumblr. And yess the best. Oh my God ahaha johns friend wants to sleep with gabby cuz he's gay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:44:08 UTC">
      <body>Haha I remember, such a good part of the show! Service sucks in the tunnel as you probably know so I'm most likely getting texts 5 min late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:45:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah don't even worry, I'm the same in the Bart. Aww zack is so sad and cute:/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:46:01 UTC">
      <body>And 3 yrs later zack has a thing for gabby, get ready for that one!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:46:14 UTC">
      <body>Oh Jesus christ come on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:46:57 UTC">
      <body>Haha I know and her reaction is fucking hilarious</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:46:58 UTC">
      <body>Ps I like how Tom and Lynette switch bed sides like every other episode</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:47:03 UTC">
      <body>What does she do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:48:40 UTC">
      <body>He sends her all this creepy secret admirer stuff and she's completely flattered and agrees to meet up with him. She shows up at the restaurant and sees </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:48:51 UTC">
      <body>that it's him and totally flips out, so he offers to pay her to stick around</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:49:12 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god that's hilarious. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:54:38 UTC">
      <body>Andrew is gay!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:55:35 UTC">
      <body>Yeah and Bree would have to be his mom, not the best combination</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:56:05 UTC">
      <body>Baha'is and maisy us getting arrested for prostitution! I love this show</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 22:57:48 UTC">
      <body>I know it's so good! I'm down to watch reruns whenever so let me know the next time you do it, it's been my favorite show for yrs. So funny! Always cheers me up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 22:59:30 UTC">
      <body>Bahaha this show is si fucking great! I love that you enlightened me! And I do it every day ahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:01:28 UTC">
      <body>Glad I could be of service haha you did the same for me with vampire diaries. I never really watch it though, I just pause on ian somerhalder's face :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:02:11 UTC">
      <body>Haha he is si fucking sexy my god. I wanna jump his bones. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:04:07 UTC">
      <body>Me toooo I want him at cal. Yae and her alarm can move out and he can come live with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:05:51 UTC">
      <body>Haha yes that would be si great! And oh Jesus hat happens with Martha hubers siter who knows that Mary Alice is Angela?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:07:42 UTC">
      <body>She's sketchy as fuck, she eventually becomes a series regular and she gets her daughter to marry Paul. He has no idea, it's really funny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:08:03 UTC">
      <body>What the fuck that is so weird!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:09:50 UTC">
      <body>Ps who is Angela? Confusing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:11:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah the show gets weird eventually when they run out of ideas, but it's still worth watching. And the Angela bit is pretty hard to explain but basically</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:11:22 UTC">
      <body> Mary Alice is Angela. She changed her name after she killed Zack's biological mom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:13:23 UTC">
      <body>Yeah they're the same person but why Utah? And who is Dana?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:14:26 UTC">
      <body>The Utah thing makes no sense but Dana is Zack's real name</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:14:38 UTC">
      <body>Dana is a girls name...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:16:55 UTC">
      <body>According to the writers it works for both genders...except it doesn't. Probably trying to throw the viewers off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:17:33 UTC">
      <body>Yeah definitely, kind of dumb haha. Aww Susan and mike:/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:19:49 UTC">
      <body>I know they're adorable! And I'm 2 stops away :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:20:10 UTC">
      <body>Oh yay. I'll come at like four? That chill?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:20:43 UTC">
      <body>Haga Susan is drunk and spilling all of Pauls secrets and she thinks he killed Martha :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:21:47 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's perfect! I'll see you then. And I hope you're hungry because I'm starving. Haha Susan, always such a dumbass, but I love her</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:22:38 UTC">
      <body>She is so my favorite. And I am starving dude no food  all day. And everyone knows Rex slept with maisy see sad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="131063" time="2011-11-27 23:28:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah Rex is an ass but George is actually a psychopath. Has he showed up yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:29:11 UTC">
      <body>Dude yes and he's poisoning Rex!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="131019" time="2011-11-27 23:32:39 UTC">
      <body>Baha'is Lynette in the bouncy house with the other mom</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
