<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130605.0022" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130659" time="2013-06-05 19:26:14 UTC">
      <body>Omg! I LOVE the myth of Sisyphus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130978" time="2013-06-05 21:38:02 UTC">
      <body>By Camus or do you mean the Greek myth? Where are you based?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130659" time="2013-06-05 21:40:24 UTC">
      <body>The myth of Sisyphus who was punished by the gods by having to push a boulder up a hill only to have it roll back down... I'm just south of Philadelphia... You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 09:32:49 UTC">
      <body>Right on. i'm down in north FL, geting pounded by tropical storm Andrea @ the moment. What do you do in PA?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 09:34:17 UTC">
      <body>I'm a copy editor... What do you do? How did you hear about this study?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 09:37:55 UTC">
      <body>I used to live in west philly, was a semi-pro guinea pig, so i did all kind of crazy stuff like this.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 09:42:03 UTC">
      <body>I do electrical work for money. For joy i do all manner of activities involving water, love paddling &amp; scuba. I also enjoy travel &amp; am pretty civicly-engaged.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 09:43:30 UTC">
      <body>Cool... I'm a homebody.. Like reading, crafting and I volunteer with a no-kill cat shelter.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 09:45:02 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Save the kitties!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 09:46:03 UTC">
      <body>I have 2 of my own cats... Do you have any pets?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 10:19:31 UTC">
      <body>I have a beautiful, elderly cat that i'm caretaking for a friend. Definitely an adorer of felines!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 10:26:27 UTC">
      <body>Cool. I have a chihuahua too but he lives with my parents.. He didn't like being separated from his brother and sister</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 11:44:57 UTC">
      <body>Do you enjoy living in the philly area? You from there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 11:55:07 UTC">
      <body>I live in the house I grew up in... I bought it 5 years ago... The neighborhood is changing and I'd like to move away but it's difficult being single andonly bringing in one salary, you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 14:39:44 UTC">
      <body>Totally. I'm in the same boat. No real desire to partner up with anyone, but man it would be nice to have a 2nd income, or at least a sugar mamma!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 14:39:49 UTC">
      <body>I'm actually in the process of trying to buy my grandma's house.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 14:41:06 UTC">
      <body>Yeah... I was trying to hit that 600 million powerball.. Can't believe an 84 year old hit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 14:45:38 UTC">
      <body>Funny, thats the town where my folks live, zephyrhills. I called my mom on the way to work that morning just to make sure i still had to go in! No luck!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130978" time="2013-06-06 14:46:10 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm, maybe that 84 year old is looking for a house boy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 14:46:38 UTC">
      <body>Haha.. Good luck</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
