<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140803.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-03 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Hi! So I'm meeting with the birth center to revisit my video proposal on Tuesday. If post production was more like...dec, would you still be interested in doing the editing ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-03 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>The pay would prob be ~5-6K for a 15-20 min video and 3-4 mini videos made up of footage from the main vid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-03 13:26:33 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hi! I have another disability video with a deadline of january 1, then leaving town for a week but could start working on it mid January (like the 7th). I have a lil questionnaire I can send you that will help me get a realistic timeline together and figure out what kind of files you need at the end. I'll email that to u and we can see if it will work out!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-03 14:27:49 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Okay! All of my info is sorta conjecture at this point, hopefully I will know a lot more after the meeting on Tuesday. Wish me luck!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-03 14:28:52 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>You got this girl!!! Let me know what happens. I'll be thinking of ya Tuesday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-03 14:30:24 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Thanks boo. Also maybe we can swim this week!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-03 14:31:50 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Definitely! I'm in DC tmw night but off all week!!! Swimming!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-03 14:49:36 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Yeah I was thinking more like thurs or from!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-03 14:49:36 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Friday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-03 14:52:01 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>That would be perfect. Good luck Tuesday! I'll send you all the positive energy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-03 14:53:52 UTC" participant="153601">
      <body>Thanks so much! Also I just read through the survey, all good stuff to think about and I will hopefully know more in the near future </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-03 14:56:47 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Awesome. Let me know if you need anything else to prepare. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

