<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141112.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-12 00:16:25 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Have you ever installed a Fiat terrazzo shower base?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-12 00:16:50 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Nope</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-12 00:20:31 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Hmm. It's got a weird drain attachment system that either requires oakum and lead or plastic lead or a silicon gasket which the 2" pvc slides into. Any preference in those options? Actually I can't do lead so either oakum and plastic lead or a silicon gasket?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-12 00:22:35 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Oakum and a two part epoxy is always an option</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-12 00:23:12 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Is the plastic lead stuff ok or epoxy is better?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-12 00:23:28 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>I don't know about plastic lead stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-12 00:24:59 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok. It's a one part thing. I might just go for the gasket but intuitively it seems like it might be prone to leaking over time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-12 00:29:38 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Does the system come with a supplied gasket?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-12 00:30:53 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Nope but you can order one that is specifically for it. This base is fucking heavy. We have to chain hoist it through the open floor joists tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-12 00:31:45 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>That's no joke, can you send me a link to the product, I'd like to look at it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-12 00:34:08 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>Sounds like a German car</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-12 00:34:25 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> 60" x 36" fiat terrazzo Monterey. I can't get a link easily from my phone </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-12 00:35:53 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> It weighs about as much as an Italian car which I think that's where it's from. Craigslist find</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-11-12 00:36:16 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>If there's a rubber gasket specific for it I would trust that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-11-12 00:37:57 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok thanks for the advice.  I'm still entertaining school for plumbing so I should talk to Andrew </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-11-12 01:12:32 UTC" participant="153556">
      <body>There's also a full time school situation but it costs as much as a regular college</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

