<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120129.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2012-01-29 16:25:37 UTC">
      <body>Love you. Let's see each other soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:34:37 UTC">
      <body>Love you too! And yes, I wanna see you. Back on the sobriety bench. Just had an amazing conversation with my grandma in arizona. We've started a project of </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:35:18 UTC">
      <body>Sending letters and projects to each other - in my next letter I'm sharing the poem written by tim otte, an essay I wrote to monic yunus, and your essay about</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:35:44 UTC">
      <body>Art. Yeah yeah yeah!!! How are u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-01-29 16:37:56 UTC">
      <body>Still unemployed and despairing....! So frustrating when I'm doing something job related every day. It's messing with my self worth. But schools good, Tim's ok- he had to get his car fixed so he might be able to afford a visit which is really upsetting. Day by day right now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Hang in there missy - I know the self worth thing can be messy. I noticed when I've been writing to my gma and prof from ocu, the time to do projects just for</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:41:23 UTC">
      <body>Personal reasons does me good - it might not be as impactful for u because I know u get a lot of creative energy from school already. I'm probably available to </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135093" time="2012-01-29 16:41:53 UTC">
      <body>Chat later tonight if u want to. Love you love you love you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-01-29 16:53:17 UTC">
      <body>Love you :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131839" time="2012-01-30 03:36:20 UTC">
      <body>Loosy goosey broadway Jane</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135093" time="2012-01-30 03:38:07 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha!!! Hey sorry I never called u! I took a nap and now I have a guest spending the night, Amanda, just moved here tonight. I don't have plans tomorrow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135093" time="2012-01-30 03:38:17 UTC">
      <body>Night - can we play catch up then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2012-01-30 03:38:49 UTC">
      <body>Oh no worries, I've been busy with stuff today. Tomorrow would work probably - Mel has a guest but I can sneak away</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135093" time="2012-01-30 03:39:59 UTC">
      <body>Kk!! Xoxo gossip girl </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2012-01-30 03:40:35 UTC">
      <body>Next time I'll kill you -A. ( pretty little liars)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135093" time="2012-01-30 03:43:14 UTC">
      <body>Guess what happens when people stop being polite and start being real (that popular reality show from the 90s)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
