<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20131227.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-12-27 02:41:00 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Yo wassup? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-12-27 03:44:24 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Not much. Tired. What's up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-12-27 03:46:37 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Nothing much. I was curious if you bought the Japanese101 subscription. 
</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-12-27 03:47:33 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Also I'm not sure how you eat but I have a Costco card so if you wanted to buy things from there you could tag along with me if you wanted. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-12-27 03:48:01 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>I did. I've used it once lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-12-27 03:49:04 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Never been to Costco. Is it like Sam's club or something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-12-27 03:50:07 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Haha, is it any better than when you used it for the first time? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-12-27 03:50:08 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Yup like Sam's club with a different name. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-12-27 03:53:02 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>It feels mostly like how I used it the first time. I'll probably try to stick with it for a while and see if I change my mind. You buy the Chinese and Japanese subscriptions?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-12-27 03:55:55 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Okay, I feel like it changed but I guess not. I like it because it gives both the applicable content and cultural facts with it. It's corny but better th</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-12-27 03:56:05 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>an most things I have come across.   Yup got both of them. Just need to use them both now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-12-27 03:57:08 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>I didn't know you were trying to learn Mandarin. The phonetics are really tough. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-12-27 04:00:11 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Yeah I kind of started like two years ago and did like 5 lessons from the subscription but stopped. Yeah they are and I think that will be the most diffi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-12-27 04:00:22 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>cult. I don't want to jump right in because my Japanese isn't as stable as I would like.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-12-27 04:07:04 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>You check out those podcasts I sent you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2013-12-27 04:10:00 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>I started listening to the coffee and milk one but i couldn't really get most if it but she was going on a whole about the title.  And I think her favori</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-12-27 04:10:10 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>te phrase is "dame" lol  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2013-12-27 04:11:04 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Yeah, the first one is about giving the podcast a title and how it has a deep meaning lol.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2013-12-27 04:13:25 UTC" participant="153451">
      <body>Lol yeah I guess I need to finish listening to it. They are longer than what I expected lol</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

