<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120604.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 12:19:47 UTC">
      <body>Have fun witcha CSI buddies</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136204" time="2012-06-04 12:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Danksss I like it so far</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 15:03:56 UTC">
      <body>I wanna sign ur yearbo0o0o0o0k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136204" time="2012-06-04 21:28:32 UTC">
      <body>I'm not even out of stony brook yet!! Ahh this is actually the weirdest day of my life. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 21:29:10 UTC">
      <body>Hey how was your day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 21:30:34 UTC">
      <body>Ahhhh omg ok I didn't even know it was at stony brook. Skype tonight, tell me everything</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136204" time="2012-06-04 21:34:56 UTC">
      <body>Like, no. I am passing out as soon as I get home. I heard there was an ice cream stealing fiasco that I missed, though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 21:37:05 UTC">
      <body>Ugh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 21:39:09 UTC">
      <body>That's my response to you not wanting to talk to me. Ice cream was indeed stolen</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136204" time="2012-06-04 21:39:12 UTC">
      <body>Eh?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136204" time="2012-06-04 21:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Ugh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136164" time="2012-06-04 21:47:16 UTC">
      <body>Ugh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-06-05 15:49:02 UTC">
      <body>Gabby wrote the sweetest thing in my yearbook. Wanna cry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136164" time="2012-06-05 17:53:30 UTC">
      <body>June 12 sleepover?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-06-06 03:05:42 UTC">
      <body>I need to be honest with you. I'm trying this new thing where I'm a good friend instead of a shitty one. Since last week when I burst into tears after the concert, I felt very confused and unsettled for the rest of the week. I felt more stress free and competent and in control of things, but I had some strong lingering emotions that would occasionally pop up and I'd feel overwhelmed and sad. I felt that I needed to tell you this or that maybe you could help me, but I didn't know what to say or where to begin, so I just never brought it up, and I had that unresolved feeling I sometimes get when we need to talk about something but haven't yet. Plus, we weren't really seeing much of each other, and when we did you were not really yourself, which kinda annoyed me because I felt like I needed to talk to you urgently even though I had nothing to say. I had a very fun time with you on Friday, but I didn't want you to leave so early the next day because I wanted you to stay with me all weekend and then maybe what I needed to say would come out, plus I thought you had ditched me a little much that week and I felt like you didn't want to see me at all. And then school was happening, which meant lots of work for both of us, but more so for you with your paper, which I understand completely, but with everything else I just generally felt like I wasn't a priority and that I wasn't important and that you didn't care. I'm stupid for getting all worked up in my head and not letting it out, but I didn't know how to. I felt ignored and I saw you caring very strongly for other things and I wondered why it wasn't me. And I know none of that is true on your end, but I became really nostalgic for the days when it was just me and you in your room and we could talk about anything or nothing and focus on each other with no distractions because we were the only people that mattered, and I miss you and I love you so much and I really really need you to be in my life and I don't know what I would do without you. And ever since last week I've just been so sad, not when I think of the future but when I think of the past, and how much things have changed and how quickly they changed and what had to happen for them to change and I just wish things would speed up and slow down at the same time and I wish life wasn't so difficult and confusing and tragic and I really need a big hug and someone to tell me that I'll be alright</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
