<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130314.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 18:36:37 UTC">
      <body>So I was reading more on hogdkins and the thing I said about shortened life expectancy is not true thankfully. Did Kev text you saying she is still gonna go to his house warming party?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130747" time="2013-03-14 18:37:20 UTC">
      <body>Nah kev is ur bul. Liz wont let anything keep her from a party lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 18:44:12 UTC">
      <body>Haha. Trueeee. Well Kev is making a big banner for her that's gonna say "fuck cancer" and were all gonna sign it with well wishes and shit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130747" time="2013-03-14 18:46:05 UTC">
      <body>Damn. I didnt even know they were friends</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 18:47:51 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I was thinking how did that conversation go? Was Kev like "hey Liz I know you have cancer and all but are you still coming to my house warming party?" Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 18:48:25 UTC">
      <body>Are you gonna go? It's not this Saturday but the next...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130747" time="2013-03-14 18:49:25 UTC">
      <body>I dunno. Not sure how i feel bout kev Turner.  Plus Agata will be here and i dun really kno if i was invited </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 18:53:09 UTC">
      <body>What do you mean? How do you feel about Kev? Is it cause you hooked up with his ex?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130747" time="2013-03-14 18:57:46 UTC">
      <body>Lol. I think he bears some type of grudge against me cuz of that but he wasnt her bf at the time. Hes just hard to read. How do u even kno bout that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="132551" time="2013-03-14 19:01:51 UTC">
      <body>You told me about it... I would be happy if you came and brought agata, I wanna hang out with her for real this time!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130747" time="2013-03-14 19:04:07 UTC">
      <body>Oh lol. I dun wanna just show up at his crib. He said it was vip only on fb lol i dunno im leanin more towards no. But ill see wassup on sat i guess</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
