<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130613.0047" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137311" time="2013-06-13 22:28:37 UTC">
      <body>When are you coming back lovey dove?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="137255" time="2013-06-13 22:29:11 UTC">
      <body>Late afternoon on Saturday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137255" time="2013-06-13 22:29:29 UTC">
      <body>How do you make good white rice </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="137255" time="2013-06-13 22:38:32 UTC">
      <body>Mooooom </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="137255" time="2013-06-13 22:38:34 UTC">
      <body>Help! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137311" time="2013-06-13 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body>Ha ha ! 
Passing down Truth!
Wash and soak rice for several hours. If not possible soak in warm/hot (not very hot) water for about half hour. Add about a tablespoon of salt to each cup of rice and let there be about two inches of water above the soaking rice.

That was step one. 
Step two: bring a pot of water to boil. Drain the rice add to boiling water. Stir occasionally. This part is sensitive the rice should be half cooked only. Test by squeezing one grain. Should be hard from inside a little soft from the outside. Drain immediately and wash with cold water.

Step three:
Bring about a cup of water and a cup of oil to boil in the bottom of the big pot in which you are going to steam the rice. Pour the rice gradually into the pot making a mountain shape. Do not push it down. Let it be loose. Make a few holes with the babble of a bog wooden spoon. All the way to the bottom. This helps the steaming.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="137255" time="2013-06-13 22:44:18 UTC">
      <body>How long is this going to take?? I need to make in one hour max!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137311" time="2013-06-13 22:53:43 UTC">
      <body>Fourth step:
Cover the pot and put on high heat for a few minutes. This stage is extremely sensitive. Each pot is different and each fire is different. The purpose of this stage is to make a lot of steam rise without burning the bottom. ( bty you could put potatoes-salt them in stage three). So stay with the pot. Keep checking to see if there is enough steam. If you sense that it is burning or that you are waiting too long add water half a cup at a time ( depending on how much rice you are making) so may be a little more. 

Stage five:
Once steam gets going reduce heat to very low and put a towel on the lid. Check the rice after a few minutes. If the steam is substantially reduced  raise the heat a little. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
