<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120109.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130886" time="2012-01-09 21:07:02 UTC">
      <body>Hi i'm sorry i sent a few messages about bikes which is this?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130755" time="2012-01-09 21:56:17 UTC">
      <body> Sorry, I responded to zac's group txt without deleting the other recipients, my bad!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130886" time="2012-01-10 02:17:53 UTC">
      <body>Wait who is this? I thought i texted zach about a bike?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130755" time="2012-01-10 02:31:29 UTC">
      <body>Kennedy. Zac sent out a group txt about his keg, and iPhones automatically reply all with group txts, and I forgot. So that txt was meant for Zac, I don't even know who this is :-) sorry.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130886" time="2012-01-10 02:58:18 UTC">
      <body>Ha sorry this is gedney! I texted another dude named zac about a bike today, got the wires crossed. Maybe i'll see you at the keg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130755" time="2012-01-10 02:59:29 UTC">
      <body>Ha, sorry bout that. I'm not makin it out tonight but I'm sure I'll see you soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130886" time="2012-10-06 03:37:26 UTC">
      <body>Hey kennedy this its gedney. Kate told me you might be looking for new studio mates. If so no face is def interested  let me know of you wanna discuss</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130755" time="2012-10-07 19:03:58 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Mark just emailed me as well. If you send me yr email I can send you both specs on the space. Hope it works out!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130886" time="2012-11-07 18:49:42 UTC">
      <body>Hey kennedy! When r u free tomorrow? Was gonna try to get the keys from you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130755" time="2012-11-07 20:00:02 UTC">
      <body>I can also do a handoff with mark at work if we can't find a time! I'm crazy busy this week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130886" time="2012-11-07 23:02:10 UTC">
      <body>Hand off at work seems easiest. He told me he's working a lot this week. Do u have his info?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130755" time="2012-11-07 23:02:49 UTC">
      <body>Yup! We can work it out!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130886" time="2012-11-07 23:13:02 UTC">
      <body>Perfect. Have a good time in mexico! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130755" time="2012-11-07 23:13:40 UTC">
      <body>Thx!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
