<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140910.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-10 23:34:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I spoke with both Cindy &amp; Beth.  They thinking having the carpet ripped up should increase our chances dramatically. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-11 15:50:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Neat. I'm hiring movers  to help move my desk - can I have them toss the two tall bureautype things in the living room too? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-11 15:51:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>If I have nicer living room furniture and Leave it in house as gift, can I replace that broken thing we keep mail on with one that is similar but prettier </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-11 15:56:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>As bonus, those things might have bugs and replacing them w new nice pieces might be good move regardless </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-11 20:37:20 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Pls call me when you get a chance &amp; we can discuss it.  Is there one or two of those bureautype things in the living room?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-11 21:12:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Hi! Only one and it's not bothersome but I figured why not buy nicer stuff- I'll leave it there for you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-11 21:17:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The thing the mail is on is def broken for example </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-11 21:17:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm paying the movers don't worry! Just figured it would be free moving </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-11 21:19:29 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Kaushal is moving the other armoire back into his room.  He was never supposed to move them.  I sort of went off on him twice about it.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-11 21:19:52 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I don't mind it in the living room!! It's fine!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-11 21:20:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I agree.  I want to get rid of all the furniture in the living room &amp; replace it with new stuff.  I've just been preoccupied with all that has been going on over there.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-11 21:20:21 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha how about the computer or the tv or the broken thing the mail is on? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-11 21:20:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(I have the movers here anyway/ I guess I'm just asking if there's anything you'd like moved out for free?)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-11 21:21:43 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I actually started an email to you &amp; Alex &amp; Avery going into what I'd like to do at the house.  I was hoping you guys might be able to help.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-11 21:22:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I want to keep the computer &amp; hook it up to a flat screen &amp; hang it above the fireplace.  I want to get rid of everything else. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-11 21:22:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>We'd love to help!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-09-11 21:24:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oooh yeah good plan </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-09-11 21:24:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-09-11 21:29:39 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Lol Cindy said 'ooooh the floor looks so much better than the carpet!'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-09-11 21:29:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It really does look much better </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-09-11 21:30:55 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She's here spraying </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-09-11 21:45:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Would a good compromise be to move the bureau to the room w the pool table !? There's lots of room there </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-09-11 21:47:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I want to bureau back in his room.  I typically love compromises &amp; win / win situations but I don't not want the armoire in any of the common areas.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-09-11 21:49:39 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>It was fine for the last 5 people who lived there including myself.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-09-11 21:49:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>The reason he is upset is he didn't know they came with the room.  The reason he didn't know was initially he rented your room &amp; then decided to switch before I knew the last tenant was moving.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-09-11 21:52:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>The reason I am upset is he asked me if he could move them into the living room 3 months ago. I told him No &amp; he specifically disobeyed me &amp; didn't anyway.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-09-11 21:52:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I sent you an email with a couple couch sets. Not exactly what I am looking but it is in the ballpark. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-09-11 21:52:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I understand </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-09-11 21:52:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>That's unfortunate for everyone. I really don't mind it in living room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-09-11 21:53:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oh! Ok!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-09-11 21:53:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Armoire yess that's the word I was looking for </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-09-11 21:54:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>It's basically a misunderstanding / miscommunication.  But Kaushal has been less then honest with me through out.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-09-11 21:56:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I know you have never met me.  But I really am a pretty nice guy at least most of the time.  But b/c I am nice unfortunately some people have tried to take advantage of me.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-09-11 21:58:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>But it is a mistaking kindness for weakness thing that gets me.  I am not a weak person either mentally or physically. I don't like getting pushed around.  I feel throughout this whole issue Kaushal trying to push me around. He has straight up lied to me more then once.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-09-11 21:58:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Anyway not you problem.  I don't want you to feel like you are caught in the middle of this.  Sorry. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2014-09-11 22:10:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>No worries! Being a landlord is frustrating, especially when your baby (the house) is distant from you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2014-09-11 22:12:07 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I can be tough......  I just spoke with Cindy.  She said things went well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2014-09-11 22:12:25 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Did you ever get a chance to call Beth? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2014-09-11 22:17:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes she said to call Cindy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2014-09-11 22:18:09 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I don't see the email w the couch sets though...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2014-09-11 22:19:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Cindy basically said to wait and see soooo that's what I'll do. I'm replacing some of my furniture too just to be safe (w new stuff obv not stuff from street)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2014-09-11 22:19:49 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And she dusted and sprayed </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2014-09-11 22:21:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>OK. She said you got bit again last night? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2014-09-11 22:22:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah :( but not five in a row like I had been </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2014-09-11 22:23:35 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Cool. And it was a couple days before without a bite? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2014-09-11 22:24:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I think we are heading in the right direction. I'll consult with Beth &amp; see what she thinks is the next step </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2014-09-11 22:24:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>OK. Once we get rid of them then they should be gone for good.  Or until someone else brings one back into the house.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2014-09-11 22:24:13 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yup! Except those days I was 100% living out of trash bags and had bed in middle of floor without Any bedding- just on the plastic </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2014-09-11 22:24:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The bed was like two feet from wall in either direction </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2014-09-11 22:24:31 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Last night was the first night I was semi normal </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2014-09-11 22:24:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I put the bed a bit in corner- tho still 6 inches from wall either direction say </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2014-09-11 22:25:46 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And put pillows and blankets on it tho I first ran them through dryer. I took clothes out of trash bags and put them in furniture and wore them today to 'test'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2014-09-11 22:26:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I got One bite last night.  A huge one behind my leg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2014-09-11 22:26:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Between the first bed bugs attack &amp; this one it was maybe 5 years. But it is just random. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2014-09-11 22:26:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Geez.  I am so sorry.  Really I am. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2014-09-11 22:26:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Maybe but probably a bed bug   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2014-09-11 22:26:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I am clearly super sensitive and get welt like reactions but it was one not three or five in row like it was a week or two ago</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2014-09-11 22:26:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So maybe it wasn't even a bed bug </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2014-09-11 22:27:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Probably </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2014-09-11 22:28:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>It's crazy.  Like 7 - 8 years the only time anyone ever heard of bedbugs was the - Sleep tight don't let the bed bugs bite rhyme.  A few years later &amp; it is a complete epidemic. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2014-09-11 22:33:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2014-09-11 22:41:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I read somewhere that the infestation rates in Philly have gone up 4.5% per MONTH.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2014-09-11 22:45:18 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>They said bedbugs were all but wiped out by DDT after WWII. But DDT also killed all the birds..... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2014-09-11 22:47:05 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>When this is all said &amp; done - lets have a talk - I want to compensate you at least a little bit.  Though I'm sure nothing I can do will make up for what you went through.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2014-09-11 22:47:15 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Anyway I am so sorry.  </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

