<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130606.0015" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130659" time="2013-06-06 20:19:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm having a crap day/week... Just wanna disappear</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130978" time="2013-06-07 10:37:54 UTC">
      <body>I'm really sorry to hear that. Whats going on?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130659" time="2013-06-07 10:38:45 UTC">
      <body>Just everything</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130978" time="2013-06-07 10:41:56 UTC">
      <body>Well feel free to 'chat' about it if it makes you feel any better to get it off your chest. Thats what we're here for after all!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130659" time="2013-06-07 11:16:47 UTC">
      <body>Thanks... I'm swamped at work.. And i missed 3 typis yesterday ... Creditors started calling my house for my sister who I don't even talk to.. I feel like my head is gonna explode... I need to clean the house badly but I don't have the time or energy.. I need a new car but I don't make enough money, I hate my hour commute to work, my boss doesn't know how to use her computer (why is she the boss????)... I need to lose weight but I'm in pain and exhaustedall the time so it's nearly impossible... Im not sleeping well... i had knee surgery in April and now the bills are coming in and im just supposed to pull the money out of my ass i guess...I'm telling you, I just want to curl into a ball and cry until I fade away...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130659" time="2013-06-07 11:16:47 UTC">
      <body>And I made a ton of typos in that... Great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130659" time="2013-06-07 11:16:48 UTC">
      <body>This week needs to be over</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130978" time="2013-06-07 16:52:47 UTC">
      <body>Wow, i'm sorry, that does sound like a lot to deal with. Do you have much in the way of family or community that you can lean on?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130659" time="2013-06-07 17:09:58 UTC">
      <body>They are part of the problem</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
