<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141129.0012" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-29 05:04:10 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Are you alive?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-29 09:50:56 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Lol. Totally am. Sorry. I got back and just passed out... How are you? The mall was packed... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-29 10:20:47 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hahahah glad to know. Yea I was hoping you didn't get into bad altercations at the mall. I'm good. After I babysat and went home, my friend called and I ended up going out with her to a gay club near Center City. It was pretty short notice so I just threw stuff together. It was quite an entertaining night. Got home not too long ago. Did you get anything good?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-29 11:05:53 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I got a snowboarding helmet. Lol. How was the gay bar? I hear they're fun. lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-29 11:13:17 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>This one was actually pretty cool. I went to another one before, it was kind of boring (although that one was a bar/lounge, and the one I went to earlier was a club club). The music was good, they had an event tonight. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-29 11:13:51 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Snowboarding helmet huh? I guess I know what you'll be doing this winter.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-29 11:13:54 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-29 13:05:04 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Yeah, I wanted one for a while and it made sense to get it now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-29 22:15:25 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I haven't been snowboarding in a while. Matter of fact, the last time I went was with you! Hahahah. I already miss the warm weather.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-30 04:35:12 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>We gotta go again! Lol. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

