<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140827.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-27 15:40:13 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>We got permits for versek's and I submitted draw request to the bank today. Should be able to break ground over there next week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-27 19:12:00 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>2 other things: 
1.Niko may need help moving some conference tables. $20-$25/hr for no more than 4 hrs. Friday sometime. 
2. Can I send you out to Shannon's to scope out the work and give me an estimate? Probably just a day of work

Let me know if you are interested in either. No problem if not. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-27 19:38:20 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Last thing: do you have the bora clamp at yr place?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-27 19:48:47 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Hey. The bora clamp is here for some reason.  I start my new job on Saturday so I need to get my teaching materials ready. I can do Shannon's next week if u need me to, but I don't really want to. I would rather just do verseks Wednesdays and Fridays .  I can do sat and Sundays at verseks too if needed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-27 20:00:37 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Ok. Don't worry about Shannon's then. I'll get a schedule going for versek's for you on those days. Did you work out an hourly rate with Versek? I'll need it to work out budget.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-27 20:11:52 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>No should I talk to him or u about it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-27 20:13:07 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I have a bunch of stuff u should look through before I toss it so u should bring the van when u get the bora</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-27 20:15:12 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>You should talk to Brian. You can probably offer him a discount and not even take a hit since you no longer have overhead other than income tax. It doesn't matter to me though just let me know what you guys decide since I've got to bill his bank for it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-27 20:52:37 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I found the kreg clamp and the mini brake as well.  Some stuff u can keep here since I know u are low on room but I gotta make space on my shelves for my tools. And I'd like to get rid of all the cedar so I can have some space on my wood rack if possible</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-27 20:53:51 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Yeah totally. Can I bring the van today? We can get all that stuff out if you want. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-27 20:54:24 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Ok. I'll be there within the hour. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-27 20:54:31 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah that would be great. Trying to get the basement ready to make a ton of frames</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

