<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130531.0005" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:10:49 UTC">
      <body>Looks like there are no purge English speakers but us in this study. Ha ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:10:58 UTC">
      <body>Oops...other, not purge</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130662" time="2013-05-31 12:12:19 UTC">
      <body>Haha. A friend of mine was saying that she got paired with someone twice. I was like, really now? You still in the Dominican Republic?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:14:30 UTC">
      <body>No, i'm back! I turned my phone off for 7 days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130662" time="2013-05-31 12:17:08 UTC">
      <body>Ah, I see. How was the trip? I'm sure it must be beautiful at this time of the year.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:18:58 UTC">
      <body>it was considered the rainy season but it really didn't rain all that much. Yes, it definitely was beautiful. We stayed in two different all inclusive resorts.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:19:59 UTC">
      <body>it was my first time getting the all-inclusive experience so I took full advantage of it, eating 3 full meals a day including dessert. And also participa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:20:05 UTC">
      <body>ting in all kinds of activities. now I gotta get my butt to the gym.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:21:29 UTC">
      <body>it really was beautiful crystal clear water. I went snorkeling, took wind surfing lessons, sailing lessons, even attended Trapez school</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 12:35:08 UTC">
      <body>Trapeze that is...how was your holiday weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130662" time="2013-05-31 12:51:32 UTC">
      <body>(1/2)Pretty boring, actually. Had to meet deadlines, so needed to work. I went for a leisure drive, but that's it. I see you had an adventurous week. Must be</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130662" time="2013-05-31 12:51:32 UTC">
      <body>(2/2)such a drab feeling, going in to work... :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130970" time="2013-05-31 13:44:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I didn't want to come home but I actually enjoy my jobs. Tonight I DJ a kid's pool party so that's kinda fun.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
