<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150112.0031" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-12 01:27:28 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>I think I'm gonna tell nick not to come</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-12 01:28:00 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Awww why not?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-12 01:28:10 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Bc he's a rando hahahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-12 01:29:00 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>That's such a real thing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-12 01:29:08 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Wise decisions</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-12 01:29:32 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Like he seems cool but he's a random person who I literally do not know and idk what I'm supposed to do with him and he could be a serial killer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-12 01:30:35 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body> Yeah. When you take a sec to actually think about it it's a really bad idea. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-12 01:31:01 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>But law school boy is making a comeback! So still positives. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-12 01:31:34 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Yeah I'm gonna see him yayyyy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-12 01:31:44 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Can I like tell nick that your dad is sleeping on our floor that night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-12 01:32:29 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>That's bloody fuckin brilliant. Do it!!!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-12 01:32:55 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>I will</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-12 01:33:47 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Exactly. And if he tries to say it's ok, you know he's a total weirdo. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-12 01:33:52 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Exactly omg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-12 01:33:52 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>He's typing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-12 01:34:14 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Hahahaha omg </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-12 01:35:26 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>This is classic</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-12 01:35:37 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>What's happening?!?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-01-12 01:36:00 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>OMG</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-01-12 01:36:39 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Dude!¡</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-01-12 01:37:08 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>I'm crying </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-01-12 01:37:26 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-01-12 01:37:28 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-01-12 01:38:08 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-01-12 01:38:08 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Aka no</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-01-12 01:38:09 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Hahahahahahahahaha holy shit </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-01-12 01:38:28 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Now I'm crying</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-01-12 01:38:53 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Omg perfffff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-01-12 01:39:35 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-01-12 01:40:12 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-01-12 01:40:16 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>He bought it and is not coming</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-01-12 01:41:49 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Damn. That was so smooth. I dig it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-01-12 01:42:24 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-01-12 01:44:27 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Lolololol. He knowssssss</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-01-12 01:44:32 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼Amen</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-01-12 01:45:57 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Ugh. Boys. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-01-12 01:46:35 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Really though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-01-12 16:25:23 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>OMG DUDE UGH PLS HELP</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-01-12 16:46:19 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>What???</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-01-12 16:46:25 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>I was in the shower sorry!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-01-12 16:46:56 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Wanna see what just happened to me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-01-12 16:46:56 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Okay, so in the last few days I've done A LOT of thinking. I've thought about life, emotions, feelings, love, loss... it's been a very long couple of days in the sense of that I can't stop thinking about things in my life. One topic that continuously keeps coming up is you and I,  and figuring out how things have gotten to be the way they are between us, from what they were not even 2 months ago. Getting over you to the point of having no emotional feelings for you was a weird process that really made me question a lot about my life. Despite that it really has allowed me to go and discover myself, meet other people, even take interests in other girls on a more than "just thinking they're attractive" level. Some of the people I've met are people I am so grateful for and will remain in my life for good now that they've been apart of it.  Despite all of the people I've met and the connections I've built, continuously when I've thought about them i keep on concluding that none of them are anything like what I have with you. It's as if I'm finding out exactly what it means to lust, versus what it means to be in love. This is completely random because until I started thinking, I was so over you and us. What happened in the end of our relationship completely tore me apart as a person, and I was very spiteful for it. In fact I still really have no clue how I feel. But regardless of how I feel one thing has become extremely evident to me, and that's that I am totally, absolutely in love with you. So much has changed, and so much is different but every single scenario that goes through my mind never makes any sense..... unless we are together. And because I know exactly what my heart is saying just based on the evidence it's presented to me through thoughts, I'd be a fool to not tell you all of this. Chloe I can't make you promises about a future that I have no clue about. We cant promise eachother we will love eachother in 1, 2, 5, 10 years because we simply don't know. What I do know is that
our relationship, being in one with you is the happiest I ever was in my entire life. I'll regret it for the rest of my life if I didn't tell you that regardless of if I have romantic feelings for you or not, because honestly I don't even know where my head is currently, I want to work on things with you. We don't need to jump back into a relationship and we certainly don't need to rush into anything else. And if you don't feel the same way that's fine, but I can't make you the promise that I'll be here anymore the way that I am and that's simply because it would be lying to my heart in saying that something that makes me happy is still there. I'm just asking you to work on things with me, the same way we have always worked on things together. Letting real love go isn't something I'm keen on doing, and I know what we had and still do have is real. You don't need to answer me right now, but I want you to think on it, the same way I have, before you go back. Just ask yourself if you're really ready to lose what we have had, that happiness, closeness, that love for good, because you and I both know everything changes permanently the second we go back to school this semester. I do love you to death, and that will never change. I just can't let the chance to be frogs forever walk away without pouring my heart out to you one more time before we ultimately walk into the unknown.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2015-01-12 16:46:56 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>This is just so frustrating to me bc he knows that I don’t wanna lose him out of my life completely but we both know WE WILL NOT WORK RIGHT NOW</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-01-12 16:47:19 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Yes dude! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2015-01-12 16:51:47 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Mother. Of. God. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2015-01-12 16:54:18 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Ok he has to understand that you guys can still keep in touch and not be together. He's just being stupid one last time because he thinks eternity is being decided right now. But it's not. I guess the only thing you can do is try to tell him what you've been telling him, and that's that it's not the right time yet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2015-01-12 16:55:00 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>But he claims thats us “limiting ourselves” by making that decision. Like stfu no it’s not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2015-01-12 17:01:28 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Dude who the hell is the best friend coaching him through this because he's an ass hat. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2015-01-12 17:01:52 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>It’s literally some chick</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2015-01-12 17:02:04 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Jimmy has to be more intelligent than to think this is forever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2015-01-12 17:03:52 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Named carissa or something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2015-01-12 17:03:57 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Fuck that chick. She's probably a stank hoe tryin to get with him. God. I just want to knock some sense into him with a brick. Have you replied yet? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2015-01-12 17:04:00 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Yes I’m talking to him he’s a moron</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2015-01-12 17:05:17 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Has he never listened to a country song before? Like hello. Nothing is permanent. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2015-01-12 17:05:59 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>￼￼￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2015-01-12 17:05:59 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Here’s whats been accomplished</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2015-01-12 17:12:54 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Aka nothing. He doesn't understand that by getting back together you're limiting yourselves. You have to take some serious time off. Experience life. Make fucking stupid mistakes. And then at a point in your life when you realize just how fucking stupid you've been and you know you're too mature and grown up to ever go out and make those mistakes again, that's when you settle down with the person who's been there for you. Who you love not just romantically. But as a friend. So this is the fucking point in life where you guys see if you can remain friends. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2015-01-12 17:13:00 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>God I want to slap him. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2015-01-12 17:16:39 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Lolololololol 
Me: I’m gonna show you what jenna just said to me bc she’s counseling me so I don’t have a melt down bc you’re fucking insane
then I sent him what you just said</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2015-01-12 17:16:40 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>You’re a saint</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2015-01-12 17:18:56 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>I only speak the truth</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2015-01-12 17:19:33 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Lolololol omg. I love you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2015-01-12 17:21:04 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>He’s crazy that’s the thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2015-01-12 17:22:52 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Hahaha. I just don't know how to make him see, dude. I wish this would all just be chill again. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2015-01-12 17:24:05 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>He's not crazy... Just misled. And a boy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" time="2015-01-12 17:24:40 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>But I think I’m making it pretty damn clear</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" time="2015-01-12 17:28:48 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>You are. But boys are just so goddamn dumb. Look at Schuylar puttin shit in my mailbox thinking that'll sweep me off my feet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" time="2015-01-12 17:30:54 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Why are boys like that omg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" time="2015-01-12 17:34:21 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Dude. I don't know. Are you getting anywhere with him or is this just a pointless endeavor?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" time="2015-01-12 17:38:08 UTC" participant="153812">
      <body>Yeah I kinda just averted any continuing crisis I think I appeased him </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" time="2015-01-12 17:41:12 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Ugh. I guess that's all you can do. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

