<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120902.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:12:16 UTC">
      <body>Hi Sophie, I hope your weekend is going well.  I was wondering if you wanted to come over my place for dinner and maybe galavanting around town after for some man-hunting?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:14:59 UTC">
      <body>Oh!!! I really want to hang out!!!! Don't think I'm a flake but I got really ill last night (food poisoning).   I was going to call you last night though!  So I don't think I'll be going fAr from my bed today but maybe Tuesday ????</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:15:37 UTC">
      <body>Wanna meet around campus and creep on freshman art kids... I have to be around in the morning. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:15:55 UTC">
      <body>Or I can come by after my meetings on Tuesday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:16:32 UTC">
      <body>Oh gosh, that's horrible!! What did you eat?! I'm so sorry! If you need me to bring you anything, please let me know, I would be happy to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:17:40 UTC">
      <body>Oh that's so sweet! I'm ok worst is past just really tired and pissed I couldn't get some work done today(I have homework for my tune up classes). I just gotta sleep it off now.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:18:40 UTC">
      <body>Aw, well, get better!  If your up for it, feel better by Tueaday, I would be happy to creep on the little ones.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:20:04 UTC">
      <body>Hahahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:20:25 UTC">
      <body>I'm so glad your in the program </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:20:48 UTC">
      <body>Oh and remember the accent of Nuit I believe ascended from her prevention? I've nailed down my roommates accent to be the same... I couldn't wait until Tuesday to tell you.  Psyched you are too, nice to connect already.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:27:41 UTC">
      <body>Hahahaha that's amazing!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:29:20 UTC">
      <body>And she is only 24, one can only imagine what she will sounds like in 10 years!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:33:47 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god!! Actually I really wanted to tell you a about my fellow DMIer azeem!!!! Oh my god it went so poorly with him.  We have major cultural boundaries!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:33:47 UTC">
      <body>Hahaah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:34:28 UTC">
      <body>Hopefully her boyfriend doesnt leave her... I feel like people like that need regular 'unwinding'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:35:44 UTC">
      <body>HahahahahhahHhhha oh god, that was superb!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:35:44 UTC">
      <body>I was wondering about you two and how it went. I couldn't figure it out based on the presentation.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 18:42:17 UTC">
      <body>Interesting.  He has only been in America a few days, I don't think he was ready to 1. Make eye contact with me 2. Accept me as not being inferior to him.  But I think in a few months, when he has adjusted to the intensity of a pure bred jewish american princess, we may do great stuff together</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:46:24 UTC">
      <body>Ooh WOW, that's heavy, having to accept you as an equal... And of course a full chuckle to accepting you as a princes ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135429" time="2012-09-02 18:46:24 UTC">
      <body>I was laughing so hard when he started to put in a Z axis, followed up by 2 others... It was ridiculous, and even funnier how he had no idea of its hilarity.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130622" time="2012-09-02 19:02:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh man! Poor guy.  </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
