<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121221.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 21:41:34 UTC">
      <body>Hey lady will u be around Xmas day? I'm going to my mums and want to go out with people at night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131057" time="2012-12-21 21:42:47 UTC">
      <body>Yeah! Adam and i should be at my parents or his. Let's do it! I have to work at 5am the next day though, so we can't stay too late.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 21:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Ok! I want a lot of people to go to one place, make it easy peasy! Like shamrock?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131057" time="2012-12-21 21:55:23 UTC">
      <body>Ha. I don't know if Adam is allowed in there! That'd be good though, it's right by our house.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 21:58:40 UTC">
      <body>Hahahaha..yeah I was nervous last time I went, I had memories of being blacklisted. I'm bringing my bf to lanc with me for the first time, want to give him the full experience ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131057" time="2012-12-21 22:23:32 UTC">
      <body>Oh dear...is he ready?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 22:25:31 UTC">
      <body>No he has absolutely no idea how ratty things can get</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131057" time="2012-12-21 22:27:05 UTC">
      <body>Geez. Are you sure you want to take him to the shamrock? Are you sure you want Adam and i going? (kidding.) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 22:39:48 UTC">
      <body>Haha! Of course lovey! Plus, being able to hang is mandatory! I went to his stuffy office party with him, haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131057" time="2012-12-21 23:50:40 UTC">
      <body>Ha ha ha!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130664" time="2012-12-21 23:52:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm so charming haha. School is good for me, semester ended today happy happy happy. How are u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 00:06:58 UTC">
      <body>Oh not bad. Work a lot of crazy hours which is exhausting! But I'm ok. Money makin...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130664" time="2012-12-22 00:45:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, five am, yikes! Where are u working?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 00:46:08 UTC">
      <body>The marriott downtown</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 00:50:44 UTC">
      <body>I work as a telephone operator. I get to wear a blazer and have a 401k. Very fancy. Haha. Seriously, I'm just waiting on rich folks in a new facet...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130664" time="2012-12-22 00:54:16 UTC">
      <body>Wow, a blazer! Are you the operator that answers calls from the rooms? Ha, we are always just waiting on rich people</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 01:04:13 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, incoming calls, inter hotel calls, calls from guests. It's either really stressful or really boring. Today I'm getting paid to play on the internet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 01:04:14 UTC">
      <body>... Speaking of which: is there anything you can suggest? I'm mega bored.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130664" time="2012-12-22 01:08:03 UTC">
      <body>Those are two terrible extremes...when I'm bored I like to look at rich kids of Instagram haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131057" time="2012-12-22 01:12:55 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm. Good idea! Vice often has interesting photos too. Good ol vice.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
