<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130425.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 12:41:25 UTC">
      <body>Ice cream Thursday between 3:30 and 8:00?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131422" time="2013-04-25 19:43:49 UTC">
      <body>Ack, I'm actually on campus from midday until seven thirty on that day. Any other windows?xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 19:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Let me think!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-04-25 22:31:11 UTC">
      <body>What about weds night? I am either going to Morgan's class (are you going)? Or to Zendo. If I go to Zendo it is done around 8:30 and I could meet up with you then. If I go to Morgans and you do too we could go straight there. What do you think?? :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-04-26 13:32:43 UTC">
      <body>This Sunday also works for me. I'm free all day. I may go to Morgans class (Zendo closed this Sunday) but I may be too depleted. We will see.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131422" time="2013-04-26 14:15:36 UTC">
      <body>Sunday is good! I'm free after class for a bit, although I might have to run home and shower before ice cream. Xxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-04-26 14:16:39 UTC">
      <body>Lets do a 1:30 or so ice cream. We could eat something first? I might need real food before ice team after yoga. Or we could do a later in the afternoon date.....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-26 14:16:52 UTC">
      <body>Ice team, haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131422" time="2013-04-26 19:38:55 UTC">
      <body>Oh you're so right! Later in afternoon? I'm free until maybe five? Ice cream dream team!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-04-26 19:40:00 UTC">
      <body>Yes perfect! First step is I will tell you that am if I am coming to yoga or not then we can take the timing from there. Does that sound ok to you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131422" time="2013-04-26 19:41:49 UTC">
      <body>Absolutely xxxx FINCH FAUBLE FANCY ICE CREAM! Perfect sunday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130962" time="2013-04-26 20:19:20 UTC">
      <body>Yes. :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
