<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140710.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-10 17:08:57 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Hey. I was just looking at my calendar and that weekend that Mike will be here in August. The 23rd is that Saturday. I can take off if we decide to go to the beach. I don't know why I thought I was going to take off the following week. I'm just already off because of labor day.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-10 17:15:30 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I don't think that would work cause mike is going home on Saturday. I was thinking Saturday but I keep forgetting that's when he's leaving. I think he's leaving at like 4 or something.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-10 17:16:36 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Oooh. Right. You did say that. I forgot. Man. What day would be better then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-10 17:17:32 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>It would have to the middle of the week but I don't want to make you and Michael take off work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-10 17:40:24 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I know. One day I could do. But I don't know about two. Really,  it just comes down to me wanting to save days if I really need them so I will see.  I can ask Michael. He's off probation this month I think. So he can start using vacation days in August. He'll probably say yes. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-10 17:51:38 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Oooh. I have off on Tuesday the 19th since I'm working that Saturday. So I can take off on that Monday to make it Monday into Tuesday. If that works.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-10 17:52:06 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I just really want a pool!! It would be nice to make this work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-10 17:57:28 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>
I'm in Washington until Tuesday. And we'll be getting back around 2.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-10 17:58:01 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ugh.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-10 17:58:15 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>It doesn't have to be that week. It doesn't have to be days that mike is down. At this point, I just wanna go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-10 17:59:27 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I know. Just need to find a way to get there. It's weird with phuong and I don't trust Dan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-10 17:59:36 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>*Sam</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-07-10 18:01:35 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. I was thinking "who's dan?" Yeah...I don't really trust someone who NEVER offers. It's weird. And every time I say something she says "no one asked me to drive." Very strange.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-07-10 18:02:00 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. Very true. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-07-10 18:05:02 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>But I know what you mean. Ahh. Why doesn't this work? Haha. Mike and I are able to go Tuesday (when we get back), Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday. Assuming I can get a car, which hopefully will work out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-07-10 18:08:22 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. Let me ask Michael if he can or will take two days off. If he says ok. I'll do the same. Maybe Thursday and Friday.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-07-10 18:13:36 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okie dokie!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-07-10 18:15:07 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>And where do you want to go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-07-10 18:16:16 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ah!  I don't know! Haha. Didn't even cross my mind. I guess I don't know what places are nice to stay in down the shore because I never really have before.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-07-10 18:18:58 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hah. Okay. Well if we go to AC there's a groupon for a hotel right on the boardwalk that's $79 a night. I just have to make sure that it's possible to do one night cause it says it's for 4 nights but I don't know if it's up to 4 nights.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-07-10 18:20:18 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>It's not a fancy hotel, but it's pretty nice. Mike and I stayed here senior year.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-07-10 18:21:42 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>We can do fancier ones, but they'll cost more. It might not be bad for one night though. Doesn't matter to me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-07-10 18:22:20 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. Cool. That's like 20 bucks per  person. Let me know about the stipulations.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-07-10 18:23:00 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>What's it called?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-07-10 18:23:19 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay. I'll actually call them when maddie and Sid take a nap. Atlantic palace suites.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-07-10 18:23:46 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. Thanks.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

