<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120728.0017" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136210" time="2012-07-28 23:27:59 UTC">
      <body>Whats up man?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136164" time="2012-07-28 23:30:49 UTC">
      <body>Hey your phone works! How's Detroit?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136210" time="2012-07-28 23:36:05 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah rahi fixed it but it took me a while to get it from him. Detroit is a miserable city but working and chillin is fun and motivating. What about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-07-28 23:48:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I've heard it's a shitty place but that's good that you have something fun and motivating to do. I've been mostly hanging out with my brother, getting driving lesson and watching the Olympics lol. What exactly are you guys doing there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136210" time="2012-07-28 23:53:15 UTC">
      <body>Your brothers back in town? And whats going on in the olympics lmao. Well we've done leafletting, newspaper sales, a march, visiting shit and eating mad </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136210" time="2012-07-28 23:53:25 UTC">
      <body>hard lmao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-07-29 00:17:07 UTC">
      <body>Sounds very active! Is Stevens there? Yeah my bro is here, he does back to school like two days before I do. The opening ceremony of the Olympics was ridiculous but today was the first day and there was swimming and rowing and volleyball. USA is doing well already!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136210" time="2012-07-29 01:59:52 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah man he's here takin leadership and shit. Oh man school starts in about a month like dafuq? Also nice i caught part of the women's volleyball ga</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136210" time="2012-07-29 02:00:01 UTC">
      <body>me us won right</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136164" time="2012-07-29 02:09:32 UTC">
      <body>Yeah we've been dominating volleyball. Yeah I know it's crazy, everything is going to be so different!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136210" time="2012-07-29 03:59:00 UTC">
      <body>Hell yeah i can't wait lmao. Like i love the summer and shit but my life is on stand still gotta keep moving</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136164" time="2012-07-29 04:02:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I get what you're saying. There's gonna be a bit of an adjustment period but I think it's going to turn out great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136210" time="2012-07-29 04:06:21 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah man i figure but i'm just optimistic right now. Imma head to sleep, good night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136164" time="2012-07-29 04:07:29 UTC">
      <body>That's good, keep it that way. Good night!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
