<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130530.0057" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 01:02:03 UTC">
      <body>I think Jacob and I came up with some good ideas for the video.  I'll fill you in tomorrow.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 22:23:34 UTC">
      <body>So our idea was that in the video we should be searching for a tape collection ( a relic from the past).  After I find the tape collection, I'll meet up with Brad and Jacob in a bar.  I'll pour the tapes out of a bag onto a table, and we'll find a tape of "Into the Wild" (our song), and it will end with putting the tape into a Walkman. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:25:14 UTC">
      <body>How will we shoot in a bar?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:26:11 UTC">
      <body>I mean maybe I can just being a camera in. An outdoor bar might be best</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:26:18 UTC">
      <body>Bring*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 22:27:10 UTC">
      <body>I have to check on this, but I think Brad might be friendly enough with some that would let us film inside.  I suppose outside could work as well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:28:52 UTC">
      <body>Oh that would be awesome. So I was thinking to do these scenes of searching around the city with Minimal interference the earlier the better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:29:27 UTC">
      <body>8 am theres no one walking around the city and we could basically go anywhere without distraction</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:29:54 UTC">
      <body>I can go as early as u can if u think that is a good idea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 22:34:50 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, you're probably right.  I can go early as well (not sure about my band mates).  Of course, having people around could also be interesting.  It might help emphasize our out of place appearance. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:39:07 UTC">
      <body>yeah but early u can go into parking lots with no cars. Rooftops etc. Up to buildings without security guards and stuff in the way. Ppl staring at u. Just my opinion. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 22:44:24 UTC">
      <body>Ok, I'll suggest it.  I'm sure I can get them to agree to wake up early.  Hopefully, it won't require bribery :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:47:07 UTC">
      <body>yeah just lemme know. I drove past metuchen the other night to see my Gf. U live pretty far away!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132555" time="2013-05-30 22:51:45 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I'm moving out of here pretty soon, but I work here, so I can't move too far away.  Brad is going on vacation next week.  Maybe when he gets back, we can all meet up, and come up with a plan?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130747" time="2013-05-30 22:54:45 UTC">
      <body>Yep works for me</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
