<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130604.0012" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 10:40:22 UTC">
      <body>Hello Mugs!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 10:41:47 UTC">
      <body>Hi, good morning! How is your day so far?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 11:26:09 UTC">
      <body>Absolutely fantastic! How are you? What are you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 11:43:15 UTC">
      <body>That's wonderful! I'm great, I took a long bike ride this morning and now I am meeting friends for lunch. So far so good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 12:24:49 UTC">
      <body>Wow! Sounds pretty healthy. Are you a student then? I am.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 12:35:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I am, out for the summer..what are you studying?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 12:38:59 UTC">
      <body>Japanese Japanese Japanese Japanese Japanese and more</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 12:42:16 UTC">
      <body>Hbu?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 13:24:13 UTC">
      <body>So much Japanese! I'm studying archeology. Are you taking summer classes?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 13:38:31 UTC">
      <body>Yes. I've been studying Japanese elementary school through highschool and I still believe the best way to retain a language is to immerse yourself</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 13:38:41 UTC">
      <body>what makes you interested in archaeology?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 15:28:13 UTC">
      <body>I'm interested in the function of social inequality, and material evidence of it in ancient cultures.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 15:28:14 UTC">
      <body>So are you in Japan now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 16:46:51 UTC">
      <body>Oh haha I wish. Naw I vagabond the blast radius of our nation's capital. If you are interested in social inequality, have you heard of the pride parade?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 18:59:03 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm which pride is that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:07:26 UTC">
      <body>hahaha that would be gay pride. It's going to be this weekend. I am a strong advocate for economic freedom and social tolerance.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:08:31 UTC">
      <body>But maybe that's my white male cis-scum privilege speaking.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:11:00 UTC">
      <body>Do you participate in activism for causes in the social studies you are in?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 19:32:29 UTC">
      <body>Oh, ok I'm familiar with that one. My only issue with gay pride is that I don't believe in a gender binary, and so I feel like emphasizing sexuality creates imaginary divisions.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:45:52 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry; I am a little confused by your terminology. Could you define your use of gender binary? Do you think the normalization of the LGBT community would be</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:47:18 UTC">
      <body>worse or the same as the status quo for humanity?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131805" time="2013-06-04 19:48:23 UTC">
      <body>I hate strawmanning so I like things to be well defined n:]</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130664" time="2013-06-04 20:45:30 UTC">
      <body>I just don't think that sexuality is polarized. I have had relationships with men and women and neither takes precedence over the other. I don't see it as better or worse.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131805" time="2013-06-05 03:40:54 UTC">
      <body>Ahhh I see a Kinsey scale kind of deal. That's a pretty cool perspective because it removes gender bias from the equation. A lot of people live in the extremes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131805" time="2013-06-05 03:45:40 UTC">
      <body>so that would help to understand the current paradigm. While I do think it may not immediately address the issue of gender bias, moving toward an LGBT tolerant</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131805" time="2013-06-05 03:47:58 UTC">
      <body>community (I hope) would be closer toward a scalar view of sexuality, instead of a polar one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131805" time="2013-06-05 03:49:23 UTC">
      <body>Or sticking with heteronormality</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130664" time="2013-06-05 07:20:32 UTC">
      <body>I was thinking more like Judith Butler--that gender itself is a performance--but yeah, the Kinsey scale is appropriate.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130664" time="2013-06-05 07:25:20 UTC">
      <body>I'm absolutely for tolerance, and I hope the efforts that people are making in this realm take society in that direction.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
