<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130629.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="134862" time="2013-06-29 03:50:21 UTC">
      <body>￼Michael saved that duck from the evil automatic door...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="134847" time="2013-06-29 04:13:49 UTC">
      <body>Awwwwwh that's amazing! Sorry I didn't notice you had texted me a couple days ago till now, trained every day this week ha. But no worries! They've lasted me 6 years that's some serious usage. Ummm I want the purple uv with the red dot, or just purple, you still have my pink?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="134862" time="2013-06-29 04:15:47 UTC">
      <body>Yea I still have pink I think. I know I lost one of each. Bummed but I'm sure their are some super cool ones</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="134847" time="2013-06-29 17:46:55 UTC">
      <body>Okay, pink I care about more. Orange was dying anyway haha yeah I want green and that purple uv with the red at some point. But definitely don't feel obligated to replace mine, I was gonna need a new one soon anyway, like I said. Things that glow trip!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="134862" time="2013-06-29 18:57:42 UTC">
      <body>The purple uv would be coooool. Yes, things that glow trip pho shore!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="134847" time="2013-06-30 05:22:33 UTC">
      <body>Woooooo I'm always down to go!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="134862" time="2013-06-30 05:43:37 UTC">
      <body>Woop.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 02:41:40 UTC">
      <body>￼Rave jellies at above and beyond</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="134847" time="2013-07-01 02:49:53 UTC">
      <body>Hahahah awesome. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 03:50:02 UTC">
      <body>They were cool!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 04:40:11 UTC">
      <body>Also check out Eric prydz, every day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="134847" time="2013-07-01 04:47:31 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah def heard prydz back in like freshman year of high school, sick as fuck right? All those guys have been around forever. You heard of polish ambassador?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 04:49:47 UTC">
      <body>For sure. I had only heard call on me, so caught the end of his set playing every day. It's was incredible. That and some other sets were exactly what I had dreamed of a true rave would be. Heaven. Sounds familiar, should I be searching them now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="134847" time="2013-07-01 05:10:32 UTC">
      <body>Hahahah awh that's so amazing. I'm so jealous. Sounds beautiful and very much so like my old days, makes me miss the fuck out of that too haha. We're in heaven! Mmmmyes. If you want to listen to an amazing artist with a ton of good free songs on soundcloud polish ambassador would be the one. And if you want advice on a particular song you need to hear it would be Sundrops. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 05:13:49 UTC">
      <body>Dude it was beautiful. Everything about it. I remember having a revaluation about why I love this music so much and what my romanticized perfect view of what raves would be like (I think I told you I wanted to obsess about it with you but we never did) but honestly edc was fucking it. Even better actually. Deal, ill get after that meow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="134847" time="2013-07-01 05:15:55 UTC">
      <body>Awh. That's wonderful. I know how you feel, that's what I felt like at waka. Like I was home haha. What do you mean we never did? And this time actually tell me what you think of the song haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 05:18:05 UTC">
      <body>Like home. Such a perfect way of describing it. I brought up to you that we should talk about music but in person cause I was too excited for texts to handle but I probably forgot and we didn't. On that occasion I mean haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="134862" time="2013-07-01 05:18:47 UTC">
      <body>This songs super chilly. Good post edc vacay/pre real world song</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="134847" time="2013-07-02 00:07:13 UTC">
      <body>That's exactly how it feels to me. Ohh I see haha well we can definitely do that. I know right?! It's dank. Also stars come out (Dillion Francis remix) WEEEEEEEEEEEEE!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="134862" time="2013-07-02 00:10:34 UTC">
      <body>Dillon Francis is can't miss. I like his stuff more and more. Have you listened to dog blood at all (skrillex/boyz noise)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="134847" time="2013-07-02 01:53:57 UTC">
      <body>I know right?!?! Hmmm I feel like I have but I shall be sure. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="134862" time="2013-07-02 01:59:20 UTC">
      <body>Blew my mind.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
