<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140426.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-04-26 19:34:32 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Hey John! This is diego. How you been?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-04-26 19:39:06 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Hey, I'm doing good. Just dealing with work and life. 

How are you doing? You graduate this year, right? I hope you're enjoying all the new stuff Drexel built after I left.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-04-26 19:40:20 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Haha nah im done. Im doing an internship right now but ill be back for a masters in computer science on september. We should hang out one of these days man</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-04-26 19:44:13 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>That's pretty cool. Where are you interning? 

You're still in Philadelphia though? I live in Maryland now, so that might be a bit tough. :[</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-04-26 19:45:38 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Oh damn :c haha. Yeah im in phila. Bentley Systems I did a coop with them. Where are you working?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-04-26 19:48:36 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Small hardware company called Annapolis Micro Systems (it's in Annapolis). 

I live in Baltimore though; I can't stand small little towns.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-04-26 19:49:17 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Philadelphia's a better city, by the way. Don't come here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-04-26 19:50:29 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Haha gotcha. Im ok with being in phila. Thats good that you got a job on hardware. What do you do for them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-04-26 19:52:27 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Hahaha ok will take that into account</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-04-26 19:53:44 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>I write Verilog for FPGA and ASIC designs. It's been all right; it can get boring though.

In retrospect, it might have been better to get into software since you can go literally anywhere to do software. Can't go to too many different places in hardware.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-04-26 19:55:21 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Thats true.. well man at least u got a job and you like that stuff right? Well im going back to school because I dont want to deal with the real world ju</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-04-26 19:56:27 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>st yet lol plus I can get more money once im done</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-04-26 20:00:21 UTC" participant="153418">
      <body>Yeah, the real world isn't the greatest thing ever. Long days, overtime..staring at code for 40+ hours a week starts to eat away at you.

Drexel's campus has a lot of new stuff now. You should definitely check it out when you're back there. :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-04-26 20:01:44 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>Sounds good. Yeah it doea eat me. I program 40 hours a week straight up c++ on a source tree thats over 14 GB of files and source code. The thing take 4 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-04-26 20:02:51 UTC" participant="153456">
      <body>hours to compile everything. When you have to debug through that massive code base I just get frustrated</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

