<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130408.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130718" time="2013-04-08 19:42:16 UTC">
      <body>Would you go to a show with me tomorrow night at KFN? It's $8, but I'll buy you a beer. (I'll be in a wheelchair, so that's cool)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130664" time="2013-04-09 00:14:36 UTC">
      <body>What show is it? How long r u here for? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130718" time="2013-04-09 02:18:26 UTC">
      <body>Church shoes. No clue what they are like. They are playing with honey radar, Jowe head. No clue what either of them are like either. Probably punky. A friend that I like from Austin is tour managing them. Mostly I want to see him. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130718" time="2013-04-09 02:20:48 UTC">
      <body>I am in town because I was in a motorcycle accident. I broke my leg and am in a wheelchair. I'm at my parents until the end of April.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130664" time="2013-04-09 03:04:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh moe. I'm glad you are in town, but sorry about your wreck. Whether I can come out depends on how much school work I get done during the day. Can I let u know tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130718" time="2013-04-09 03:17:43 UTC">
      <body>Yes of course. Good luck with your school work. I'd love it if you could make it, but NBD if you can't.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130718" time="2013-04-25 00:01:37 UTC">
      <body>Hello friends, I was hoping to set up a get together sometime this week before I head back to Austin. Let me know what days are better/worse for you. I was hoping to do some karaoke, or bar trivia, or roller skate. Jk I can't skate!! LOL or maybe a kegger</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130718" time="2013-04-25 00:02:56 UTC">
      <body>Also if anyone wants to go to new York on Saturday and drive a cripple to a show in Brooklyn, I'll pay for gas and your time.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
