<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120910.0026" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2012-09-10 00:32:59 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Hey, I'm sorry I flaked here! It was too short a trip. Maybe we'll see you in fairfax sometime? My mom said to ask where Robert is these days.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2012-09-10 00:35:53 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>It's okay.  Well get together eventually.  Robert is moving to Fairfax in a couple weeks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2012-09-10 00:38:44 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body> How was your trip</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2012-09-10 00:51:21 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>It was great! A friend's family has a house in corolla &amp; we've been going the week after labor day. It blows my mind how much it's changed since we were kids! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2012-09-10 01:29:32 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>Yeah.  Do you ever come with your family anymore?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2012-09-10 01:36:15 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Nah, we started going to other beaches bc of epic Saturday obx traffic, &amp; now with Alex and I both out of the house...I was wishing they could see how it is now though! A lot more ice cream places, that's one plus.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2012-09-10 01:37:37 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>The best one is kill devils frozen custard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2012-09-10 01:38:29 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Agreed, we went there twice! So do you live there year round? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2012-09-10 01:52:17 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>You went there twice while you you were here this time?  I live like 5 minutes away.  Ive been bouncing around a lot.  Moved here in 07 for like 3 years.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2012-09-10 01:52:18 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>  Then in va for a couple.  And been back here since november.  Done a bit of fishing on the road too.  Over the last 3 years I spent 3 months in Alaska </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2012-09-10 01:52:19 UTC" participant="153291">
      <body>and 3 months in Florida  </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

