<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141022.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-22 19:26:23 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Thanks for the photo. Did you guys carve your pumpkin yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-22 19:28:00 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I was just about to text you. I emailed you and Sam the rest of the pictures. But the videos are too large to send.  I think we're carving it this weekend. We still need to sketch a design. Did you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-22 19:33:50 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Wow. I do not have the skill or the patience to do something like that. But you do with all those tiny nail designs. Haha.  Good luck with that! I look forward to seeing it :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-22 19:40:51 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Why thank you very much. And I can't wait to see yours!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-23 18:03:39 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oy. So I've just come to the decision that I'm going to stop working next semester and bang out all of my classes so that I can (hopefully) start jefferson in the fall! I have to take 5 courses...2 in the spring and 3 in the summer. The thing that sucks: I have to take a classes at nova and ccp during the summer!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-23 18:05:48 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Well that makes sense. But that does suck having the courses split like that in the summer. When do you apply to Jefferson?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-23 18:08:03 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Their applications just opened like a week ago. The closing date is May 1st but they have a rolling admission so I'll probably submit it sometime between what's left over this month beginning of next month.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-23 18:08:56 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-23 18:09:19 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Ugh! The idea of being broke again is upsetting....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-23 18:11:33 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I know. But you've been working. You should have some savings to get by. It will be worth it in the long run.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-23 18:13:23 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Yeah. I suppose so. Oyyyy</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

