<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140609.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-06-09 14:33:10 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>When's your program end?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-06-09 15:35:50 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>End of July! I was miserable this morning!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-06-09 15:38:39 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay. Hmm the reason I ask is because I just found out the lady in the business office here is leaving at the end of the month. So they are probably gonna post a job listing for someone to work in July but that's probably not helpful for you. Sorry.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-06-09 15:39:13 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And why miserable? Are you over the whole class thing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-06-09 15:41:38 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Haha Sam, it's a variety of English spoken by the young and hip. Translation: No way! I am jealous.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-06-09 15:45:18 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I literally do not have enough time to get all this work and sleep. So I couldn't sleep...again, right before another exam. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-06-09 15:45:23 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*done</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-06-09 15:45:49 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I'm hugging books all weekends now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-06-09 15:46:18 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>And I keep dozing off in class because of it all. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-06-09 15:46:41 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>And where I'm sitting, I'm right in the professors' line of sight.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-06-09 16:05:20 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-06-09 16:06:02 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Did you meet anyone? How do the others seem to be handing it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-06-09 17:06:46 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I talked to different people and some seen to like one over the other. But they generally seem to be good with it. I'm happier with Finance Management. I'm useless with accounting. If I ever say I want to do accounting for a living, please punch me in the uterus.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-06-09 18:20:41 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Will do. I think you have to be a certain type of person to like accounting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-06-09 18:20:59 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Have you gotten any grades back?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-06-09 21:18:52 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>We finished our first course last Tuesday and had an exam. So I got the grade for that. But that was a one credit course and I was stressing out over that. We have our first exam for our 4 credit course on Wednesday and  as of now I feel like I'm not going to be okay by then. It's not even one exam. It's two that they're giving us all at once and we have 3 hours to do it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-06-10 13:00:48 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah that's how my summer course was. It sucks. How did you do on the first exam?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

