<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120102.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 17:10:24 UTC">
      <body>Hey man it's Chris! How the fuck are you!? I'm leaving Philly this evening I was hoping to catch ya last night for a drink. What time you out of work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 17:18:06 UTC">
      <body>Yo man! I'm working til 5ish. You going to still be around or on the road by then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 17:25:20 UTC">
      <body>Not sure I'm with a friend so he's kind of dictating the times. Regardless next time I'm on town or you're up in CT hit me up! Text me when you're out and I'll let you know of I'm still
Here!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 17:28:13 UTC">
      <body>Definitely man! It's been a while. What brought you down to Philly?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 17:33:52 UTC">
      <body>My friends family lives here and she invited me to the eagles game yesterday, and I rather be at the classic so today I'll go piddle around get some pics. I thought of you last week my parents asked how you were so I wanted to hit you up when I got in. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 17:33:54 UTC">
      <body>Good shit. Tell your parents and your bro I said hi. Next time I'm back in CT lets def hang</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 17:36:00 UTC">
      <body>I would love to see ya.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 17:38:02 UTC">
      <body>I was supposed to come up to the Underdog/Supertouch/100 Demons show but got some work last minute I couldn't turn down. Next big show I'll come up so I can see everyone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 17:40:16 UTC">
      <body>It was a blast! But everyone left before underdog</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 17:41:19 UTC">
      <body>I heard, that's so whack and disrespectful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130692" time="2012-01-02 18:30:45 UTC">
      <body>Crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 18:31:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah man and thy ere soooooo awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131321" time="2012-01-02 18:31:28 UTC">
      <body>Youth of today was a blast too and no on there </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
