<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121228.0021" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135263" time="2012-12-28 21:32:48 UTC">
      <body>Any updates on Elise stuff? Also we were wondering, how did the gluten stuff work out?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135080" time="2012-12-28 21:34:35 UTC">
      <body>I don't think gluten is a problem. Do you think I should talk to her tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135263" time="2012-12-28 21:34:56 UTC">
      <body>She is free tonight so yeah that would work. Do you think we should first ask her if she would want to know whether he was dating someone? So glad gluten isn't an issue that would really suck.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2012-12-28 22:39:54 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that sounds like a good idea. Would you mind? Or you can ask her later when I'm around to talk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135263" time="2012-12-28 23:19:28 UTC">
      <body>Will try to ask in an innocuous manner and text you when done</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135263" time="2012-12-29 04:33:03 UTC">
      <body>She said "he'd better not be dating someone" and that she would not want to know if he was, as it would just make her upset. If you think she will def find out anyways and prob in a bad way then mb still think about telling her, but otherwise I think it's best to let it be... What are your thoughts?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2012-12-29 04:34:23 UTC">
      <body>I agree, if that's what she said she would prefer. Ill check with Fairleigh. Can I forward her that text?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135263" time="2012-12-29 04:34:39 UTC">
      <body>Yup</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135263" time="2012-12-30 04:01:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow that's awesome go you! Don't get it while shwasted...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135263" time="2012-12-30 04:05:20 UTC">
      <body>Haha ok just making sure. Looks so good!! :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135263" time="2012-12-30 04:30:56 UTC">
      <body>She's being belligerent.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135263" time="2012-12-30 04:33:04 UTC">
      <body>8=========D ~~*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135263" time="2012-12-30 04:50:08 UTC">
      <body>Have fun coral and Lizzy that was a true masterpiece</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
