<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130514.0040" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131468" time="2013-05-14 13:21:36 UTC">
      <body>Hey! I have a few questions about the rehearsal. What time does it start again and how far is it from the Philly airport? Looks like I'm picking up James for the airport along the way </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131468" time="2013-05-14 13:22:12 UTC">
      <body>Am I even going through Philly to get to the wedding? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131450" time="2013-05-14 13:29:32 UTC">
      <body>Hey! The rehearsal is at 5 on june 7, at the centre bridge inn (2998 n river rd, new hope, pa)...you basically just take 95 the whole way up, so you'll be going right by the philly airport. Google is telling me that from the airport it's just over an hour</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131468" time="2013-05-14 13:33:13 UTC">
      <body>We're looking to book his flight now so this is extremely helpful! I'm guessing we should find a flight that arrives around 2:30p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131450" time="2013-05-14 13:41:14 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that should give you plenty of time! :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131468" time="2013-05-14 13:48:20 UTC">
      <body>Sorry one more question. Are we doing anything Sunday? I'm assuming James should get a 2p return flight on Sunday??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131450" time="2013-05-14 14:11:24 UTC">
      <body>No worries!! We don't have anything planned for Sunday...we'll probably hang out a little with whoever's around, but nothing official!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131468" time="2013-05-14 14:17:17 UTC">
      <body>Perfect! He booked a 2p flight back on Sunday so we'll plan on leaving the area a little before 12n thank you so much for all your help!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131450" time="2013-05-14 14:18:49 UTC">
      <body>Of course!!! Can't wait!!! :-D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131450" time="2013-05-15 13:43:23 UTC">
      <body>I don't know if you watched Mindy project last night...but HOLY HELL</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131468" time="2013-05-15 14:06:29 UTC">
      <body>Okay don't laugh but at 9:30p I turned off the TV, made my lunch and got Ito bed haha I plan on watching it tonight or tomorrow night. It's that good??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131468" time="2013-05-15 14:06:36 UTC">
      <body>Did you watch new girl!?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131450" time="2013-05-15 14:43:12 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha I don't blame you! But yes it was *excellent*...I may have shouted at the tv at one point...and yes new girl was amazing too!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
