<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130315.0025" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 20:25:17 UTC">
      <body>Hey, so I'm going to pass on yoga tonight. I'm completely exhausted but I have your present part 2! Are you still going to yoga? Could I meet you outside</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 20:25:20 UTC">
      <body> before the class?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 20:28:14 UTC">
      <body>What!?! Ugh! Can I help in any way!? Are you sure you can still meet? I'll be quick I promise!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 20:28:14 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure if I'm going to go, major wedding crisis today aghhhh (my salon canceled on me for tmw, leaving me fucked before the shoot basically), but I am more than happy to meet up with you!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 20:32:18 UTC">
      <body>I think the problem was actually just solved!! Hillary's been calling salons arouns here to get me an early morning appt before I head up to pa, and she just got me a cheap one in bethesda. I'm just way too drained for yoga haha, but I would love to see y</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 20:40:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh good! Can I get a rain check on dinner? Maybe one night next week? I really hope you don't take this the wrong way. I'm just tired and want to make su</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 20:40:38 UTC">
      <body>re I have the proper foods/amount of sleep before tomorrow's run. I'm sorry!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 20:43:34 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha not a problem! Trust me, I understand the need to eat the right things before a race!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 21:11:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm going to head out of work now...should we just schedule sth for next week? I'm assuming you're probably still trapped at work? :-\</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 21:14:16 UTC">
      <body>Are you heading straight to the yoga studio? I can run in if you are to give you your gift?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 21:16:16 UTC">
      <body>Ha I don't blame you. Yes, let's definitely meet up next week! Let me know how it goes tomorrow ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 21:16:23 UTC">
      <body>I'm going to skip yoga and just go home, I'm way too drained/angry for a class haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131450" time="2013-03-15 21:18:50 UTC">
      <body>Will do!! And same, good luck!!!! :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131468" time="2013-03-15 21:18:57 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! You too!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
