<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130405.0021" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 01:55:38 UTC">
      <body>We will make our own school via telepathy and texts and dreams. It is awful to not feel good at (actual) school sometimes. I hate that. I have has tears tears tears and humiliation but also pride and glory and nice walks at lunch. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 01:57:13 UTC">
      <body>If you like the telephone you can always call and I will tell you stories about taxidermy or unicorns or other fun stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 01:58:54 UTC">
      <body>I have been thinking about what you said about the Triple Heater having the potential to harmonize the three jiaos and I love that. If anyone can do it, you can. I'll take out the trash (empty the rubbish bins) as best I can.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 02:03:30 UTC">
      <body>Say hello to Earth for me. Put her in a cute and quirky but safe place and watch how spunky sweet her smile is. ❤❤</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131432" time="2013-04-05 03:24:14 UTC">
      <body>You're the best. Thanks Monica. Saving this text until my board exam. Earth says " hi and damn, I thought you'd never move me! Girls getting a rash!"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131432" time="2013-04-05 03:25:20 UTC">
      <body>Earth. So picky. So perfect.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131432" time="2013-04-05 03:26:41 UTC">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 12:13:20 UTC">
      <body>OMG I loved waking up to these texts from you!!! Earth is so stunning. I can't even believe it. I reset my phone display to be her! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 12:18:21 UTC">
      <body>I did have my now dead kitty Lotti as my background but Earth will be a good backdrop for awhile. Here's Lotti! She was the love of my life! Most probably a colon cf too. Bitchy and picky and glamorous with a bum leg, FIV, allergies, picky as hell, and in</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 12:20:37 UTC">
      <body>And look at this photo I took in your bedroom. The yellow light of ghost points (which I have never seen completely yet) leaking out (or in) from the front room ￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-04-05 12:22:47 UTC">
      <body>And one more photo, for Earth. She will be pleased as punch to hear that I felt compelled to actually put on earrings today. I recently cleaned my jewelry box and found these earrings I got from the avon catalogue at age 10. I put them on for her but they</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
