<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130604.0019" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:35:41 UTC">
      <body>How's ur day going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:35:41 UTC">
      <body>Btw, I don't remember ever exchanging names. I'm Wendy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:40:24 UTC">
      <body>(1/2)My day's ok. A couple of things popped up in the morning which needed immediate attention, so it was a little hectic for a couple hours. Should ease out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:40:24 UTC">
      <body>(2/2)later :) How about yours?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:42:38 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I've just known you as jetskiwr :P Hello there, Wendy! I'm Rohan. Btw, are you a big fan of water sports?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:42:44 UTC">
      <body>Easy day. No work. Running errands. Just hit the gym and now I got a 10 pm conference call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:44:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm Wendy and, yes, i'm a pisces and a huge fan of the water</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:45:54 UTC">
      <body>10 pm? Wow! I hope you meant 10 am. You shouldn't work that late. Unless you're a DJ, which you are :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:46:49 UTC">
      <body>Yes, am</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 12:46:49 UTC">
      <body>Oops</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:54:51 UTC">
      <body>(1/2)I find water sports fascinating too. Never really tried them, though. I'm more of a soccer/racquetball and used to play for my school/college. Now I'm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 12:54:51 UTC">
      <body>(2/2)merely a weekend league player. Do you play competitive sport, or just for leisure?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 13:32:20 UTC">
      <body>I played soccer as a kid and played Racquetball for fitness purposes but I don't anymore because I have a torn acl that needs surgery and repetitive side</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 13:32:20 UTC">
      <body>-to-side movement is tough. But I do occasional distance races and i'm training for a half Ironman in Austin in Oct</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 13:37:20 UTC">
      <body>As for water sports, I love to wakeboard and just tried wind surfing in the Dominican Republic. I also used to jet ski a lot as akid.. We had a Kawasaki</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130970" time="2013-06-04 13:37:20 UTC">
      <body>stand up ski. But I don't get the opp to participate in water sports as much as I'd like since I don't have a boat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 18:05:10 UTC">
      <body>(1/2)Yeah, my ankle bothers me a little too. I tape it up usually before running/playing racquetball etc. It definitely helps. You say you grew up in Florida,</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130662" time="2013-06-04 18:05:10 UTC">
      <body>(2/2)right? Did you stay on the coast or further inland?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
