<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140723.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-23 03:05:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Barbara! Have you read 'statements of intent' by Mark Godfrey on the mysterious faux nihilistic female painters of the 80s?  It's about abstract painting but I think you would Really enjoy it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-23 11:20:29 UTC" participant="152747">
      <body>Thank you! I will look it up! And, in the meantime, Charles heard back from the writer who wants to make a movie from The Damned Don't  Cry. He sent me the letter RIchard (the writer) wrote. Of course, he loves Charles, and his take on the book and wants to him involved. I was supposed to be involved!!!!! I am so envious and fearful! Dammit! He'd never have net Richard if it hadn't  been for me!!!! I have to let it go. Aaaarrrrggggghhhhhhh. Godfrey! "Fakeryof gesture" it's going to be a good read!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-23 15:25:21 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Wait... Charles bragged to you-his ex gf- of an opportunity he landed due partially to you? He's a horrible person. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-23 15:25:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also I can promise he is exaggerating </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-23 15:25:52 UTC" participant="152747">
      <body>No, no. I was part if it. He is just letting me know the guy is interested. C was worried because he hasn't heard back. I want to be part if it!!!! But don't know if I still will be.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-23 15:26:51 UTC" participant="152747">
      <body>Hadn't heard back</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-23 15:28:00 UTC" participant="152747">
      <body>No exaggeration-ill send you the letter. In fact, my buddy bob thinks Richard may be hot for Charles. Richard is associate producer of a movie that win at Cannes. It's called "short bus"</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

