<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141207.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-07 18:06:54 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey I have to fill out this book for the police academy, can I use you as a reference? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-07 18:08:33 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Yes ma'am. Why not everybody else does. You're my 3rd person, this year. I should start charging people!! $75 per reference request. LOL </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-07 18:11:34 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>That just goes to show what an honorable person you are lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-07 18:13:27 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Blah blah blah... I'm just going to tell them that you won't crack for awhile while you were pregnant with your third baby. You really showed up for work and when you did it was like in the middle of the day. Oh, and you stole from the company. Slept with the CEO's grandson. And clog up the toilet in the ladies room on numerous occasions. Does that sound about accurate? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-07 18:13:51 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>^were on crack^</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-07 18:14:11 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Stupid invisalign!!!! Effing up my speech.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-07 18:15:59 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lmbo!!!!!!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-07 18:17:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Well I did have to admit to employee theft lol. The book asks you if you've ever committed any crimes and lists like everything possible abd then they give you a lie detector test on your answers.  So last thing I need is my heart rate going crazy over some pens or envelopes I've taken home from work. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-07 18:21:49 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>LOL LMBO!!! :-) :-) :-) :-) :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-07 18:22:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But anyway I need 5 people who know me well and you've known me for about ten years (can't believe its been that long) but two references have to be neighbors and I don't really know anyone on my block bec ive only lived here a year so this morning I had to go around introducing myself to a few lol. That was awkward</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-07 18:22:44 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>You gonna do some serious time for that..... Throw her the book, judge.!!!! Make her do 10 to 20 years. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-07 18:23:04 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-07 18:23:19 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>You can't believe it has been that long. Because it has only been at CCP for eight and a half years.... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-07 18:24:03 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>How long should I tell them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-12-07 18:24:22 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Is this a phone reference. Or paper reference? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-12-07 18:25:09 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>LOL. Stalking your neighborhood ... I bet they look at you like you were crazy. Trying to rob them of their Christmas gifts before the holiday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-12-07 18:25:25 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Crazy white girl on the loose!!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-12-07 18:31:30 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahaha they did.  But one lady said her whole family was either a cop or detective or lieutenant etc. Another neighbor is a retired detective. So that was cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-12-07 18:32:32 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Plus most of my neighbors are older so in the summer they would sit out on their step. They know me just from seeing Steph and myself coming home from work every night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-12-07 18:34:05 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And idk how they will contact you but I started ccp in april 2004. Worked their til july 2012. So you've known me then and now outside of work </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-12-07 18:35:56 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Even though I actually started I'm 2006? Or should I just say the same year that you started - 2004?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-12-07 18:37:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh if you started in 06 that's fine say that.  I was thinking you were already there when I started</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-12-07 18:38:45 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Nah. Started April 2006. .. ok. Sounds good. After I get done sugar coating the kind of person you are, they are going to kick themselves that they didn't hire you earlier to fight the city and clean it up of its crime!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-12-07 18:38:49 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>:-) :-) :-) :-) :-) :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-12-07 18:39:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Whatever they ask you just be honest. It doesn't matter how long you've known me, I just know that you are professional and intelligent so upon questioning you won't act like a fool. You can't say anything I didn't already tell them anyway lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-12-07 18:39:52 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>I sell crack........... and peanut butter.  So you may want to start with me. I'll be the best criminal you never had. I'll give up a good fight and resist arrest. I want pink Nicki Minaj handcuffs.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-12-07 18:40:05 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahahaha ok cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-12-07 18:40:36 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lmbo ahahaha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-12-07 18:41:21 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Gotta go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-12-07 18:41:29 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Ttys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-12-07 18:41:33 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Smooches!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-12-07 18:41:46 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>K ttys</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

