<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141002.0015" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-02 00:21:42 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>￼Hi hunter, so this was the larger second attempt today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-02 00:22:57 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>Sorry for delay, kept getting aide tracked</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-02 00:23:28 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>I separated some internal and external outlines to try to let line them up later by using the red target dot before letting it cut</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-02 00:24:45 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>...tho as you can see there are still some things misaligned in the first cut.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-02 00:26:58 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>Its your call, I can keep going and try to use the red dot for getting a better target on the big outlines (nose, mouth, whole head outline area) with st</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-02 00:27:17 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Hey Toren, thanks for all your effort. It seems like it is going to keep glitching out. So I would not bother investing any more time trying to make this happen. Let me know if you need anything for your time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-02 00:27:18 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-02 00:28:05 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>ill some errors inside.. I could score it too, without it being cut out of something... Tho it still has those same problems</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-02 00:31:19 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>Cool no problem.  Ya unfortunately i just cant get around those glitches.. Our lasers are a little primitive by today's standards too.  No charge for the</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-02 00:31:29 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body> time.  Maybe sometime in the future well work again.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-02 00:32:05 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>Let me know if you want that paper back.  I can leave it with Stephen too.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-10-02 00:32:36 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah I can grab it from steven</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-10-02 00:34:49 UTC" participant="153609">
      <body>Cool</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

