<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120927.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2012-09-27 03:25:16 UTC">
      <body> grad school apps...Business school?my parents are in town this weekend so I'll be pretty busy but probably go out tomorrow night, considering an art show in allston, what are you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135380" time="2012-09-27 17:44:32 UTC">
      <body>Yep, business school, which can hardly be considered school, but fun time writing essays about myself, got very introspective. Tonight, meeting up with some friends for dinner and then heading over to see a dj i like at some bar downtown</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-09-27 17:49:58 UTC">
      <body>My essay for grad school was a huge accomplishment.  It really helped me articulate what I want to develop a career in.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2012-09-27 18:01:59 UTC">
      <body>Well i think I need to mingle with my grad class which means beers at penguins.  If your plans change and you want to hang with some artists let me know.   It should be entertaining we are all very sassy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135380" time="2012-09-27 23:30:08 UTC">
      <body>That sounds fun, I could use a little more artistic sass in my life! I'll let you know how the evening unfolds</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-09-27 23:37:00 UTC">
      <body> We already started. You know if any 90s nights?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135380" time="2012-09-27 23:45:04 UTC">
      <body>Humm, not sure about Thursdays but I've heard of a few on Fridays. Always a nice throwback!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-09-28 01:00:09 UTC">
      <body>Oh well we've disbanded. I'm heading to back to Brookline, a little tipsy, for ice cream. If ur plans fall through and you'd like to joiner me know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135380" time="2012-09-28 03:01:20 UTC">
      <body>So you artists call it in pretty early haha. Still going over here, let's meet up next week...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2012-09-28 03:05:34 UTC">
      <body>Work hard play hard and sleep hard</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
