<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140724.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-24 21:14:58 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>So I saw a bunch of dropped keys around a blue portal and I picked them all up. Y/n?? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-24 21:16:58 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Can be good for linking, which can help you level up quickly! Just don't let your inventory get super clogged up with keys. Decent rule of thumb is to ne</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-24 21:16:58 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>ver hold on to more than 125 or so </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-24 21:27:40 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Do you think some blue dude left them there for someone else and I busted up their plan?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-24 21:27:47 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Cause that would be cool!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-24 21:28:15 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Probably not. Sometimes people dump them when their inventory is full because it's faster than recycling them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-25 18:06:59 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Today I discovered "comm" (someone said welcome!) and subsequently, that all my links are "derp links" :/ I just link everything I can link? Give em hell at the anomaly! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-25 18:25:45 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>Lol. I'll teach you about derp links. Just tell them you have a friend who's going to teach you the ropes after the anomaly and you're sorry if you block</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-25 18:25:47 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>ed anything :)  Who was it? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-25 18:28:34 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Haha oh shit, sorry! I literally link everything I see because I can never tell when it will make a little field and links are nice? Haha. It was 4everseptember (good name!)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-25 18:29:03 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>I'll be in va this weekend but I wish I could come to the ingress party! I'm way more into it than I expected </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-25 18:30:23 UTC" participant="153276">
      <body>That's my friend Annie! She's very nice. You didn't do anything wrong :) </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

