<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141020.0017" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-10-20 00:36:46 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Cuz! Hunters comin' with me for Thanksgiving and he's gonna make his famous collard greens. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-10-20 00:37:11 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hope Andrews arty was a blast!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-10-20 00:37:19 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>*party</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-10-20 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Fantastic. I can't wait!  I am sorry I haven't sent anything out get in regards to thanksgiving. We are definitely doing it at the house. We got a new dining room table. Haha. It will fit most of us. Well we will put the kids at a different table. Haha. And I've kinda kept quiet and distant from my mom. Just keeping things quiet. Better for now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-10-20 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Andrews party was awesome. He's soooo freaking cute it drives me nuts. Hahaha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-10-20 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Oh yeah you and hunter are more then welcome to stay at the house. You won't hurt my feelings if you don't but just want you guys to know our house is open to you to. And want you to feel at home! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-10-20 00:44:09 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>All your kids are so Damn cute! I'm glad it went well! Glad things are going well with your mom. You just needed a lil' break! I'll talk to HB tmw I know her house is being put back together so I'll check with her. I'm glad we are doing it at your place!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-10-20 00:46:54 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Haha a break is right. My mom is off the charts. Hahaha. Not that the whole family doesn't know that already. As for hb house! I saw all the new stuff. LOVE it.  She has to many chairs now and can't put her brain around how to configure the room. It's kinda funny. I keep telling her I'll just load up my car. It's big enough. Hahaha. And she will definite make room for you. She loves you sooo much. You light her day up when you call her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-10-20 00:50:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>We had a nice long chat this weekend.  She seemed a little overwhelmed about the chair situation but happy:) can't wait see the new stuff! Your mom is hard to handle and I only see her a couple times a year! Was she ok at Andrews party?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-10-20 00:52:27 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yes overwhelmed is a good way of putting it!  But the colors are amazing. And her new chair is a to die for. Sooo beautiful and comfy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-10-20 00:53:24 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh I can't wait! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-10-20 00:53:43 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yes mom was ok. I made her be a guest and not my controlling mom. It was hard but I did it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-10-20 00:54:06 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>You are the only one who can do it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-10-20 00:54:10 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>No joke</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-10-20 00:55:53 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>I don't like being like that but I have to keep my sanity. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-10-20 00:56:28 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Yes! You do it's very important. Haha:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-10-20 00:56:59 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Hahaha!  Are you bringing your special turkey? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-10-20 00:57:48 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I might try a new one this year. Not sure yet.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-10-20 00:58:20 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>There are like 15 different tofurkeys now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-10-20 00:58:33 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Oh wow really?  I wouldn't know. Haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-10-20 00:58:56 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Lol. I'm sure they don't have them at the local
Grocery store</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-10-20 00:59:31 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yeah I would agree. Heck I have to be super careful with food for Andrew now. Cause he's allergic to shellfish and eggs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-10-20 01:00:30 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh wow! Practically a vegan! Jk. Let me know if we can make or bring anything. Hunter is a good cook. We can get desserts too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-10-20 01:01:16 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yeah Andrew is my love to eat child but now has limitations. Sucks for sure. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-10-20 01:01:28 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Poor thing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-10-20 01:02:49 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>I will definitely let you know. I'll send out a fb invite in a few days. See if I can get the usual going. We've kinda been waiting on info on Cesar's grandpa. He's been diagnosed with cancer. And it's soooo bad. Nothing they can do. And he doesn't know how bad it really is. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-10-20 01:06:07 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh no. Is it in his lymph nodes?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-10-20 01:06:08 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>It's everywhere. Kidneys, liver, lungs, and I can't remember the rest. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-10-20 01:07:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Wow I'm so sorry. Send Cesar and his family my love. It's got to be really hard.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-10-20 01:08:01 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>He knows he has a tumor. But he doesn't know how bad it is. And the siblings don't want him to know. They don't want him to worry. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-10-20 01:08:37 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Are they going to do chemo or is it too much?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-10-20 01:10:01 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>No it's way to much. And it wouldn't be effective at this point. They have decided to let him just live the rest of his life may it be days, weeks or months however he wants. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-10-20 01:11:59 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>That sounds like the best way. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-10-20 01:12:32 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yeah I agree. Hb said of it were her that's how she'd want to be. It's been a rough and happy year for Cesar's family. So many babies but a lot of cancer concerns. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-10-20 01:16:48 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Yes they are. I mean mia is just the cutest thing ever. Haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2014-10-20 01:17:11 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Well the babies are probably helping bring everyone's spirits up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2014-10-20 01:18:09 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>
She is sooooo cute</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2014-10-20 01:18:56 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>She's getting a fun little personality!  I guess the three kids didn't scare hunter off. Hahaha. Andrew is doing better. Teaching him sign language. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2014-10-20 01:20:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I can't wait to see them. Hunter needs to get more practice! Oh sign language that's awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2014-10-20 01:21:31 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>He just got back from a hunting and fishing trip tonight so we are gonna settle in and watch a movie on our giant amazing TV.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2014-10-20 01:27:28 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Sounds good. Enjoy. I'm about to pump. The story of my life still haha. Love you guys!!!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2014-10-20 01:28:25 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Oh man! Have a good pump! Love you guys too and have a good night! Talk soon xoxo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2014-10-20 01:28:34 UTC" participant="153661">
      <body>Xoxo</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

