<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130531.0041" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 01:46:52 UTC">
      <body>Did you see Anna's email? What say you? Also did you find the lease?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 01:47:57 UTC">
      <body>$80 is a steal...looks like they cost over 100</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 02:05:30 UTC">
      <body>They already sold the other two...it seems like a good decision so I'm gonna email her back</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 02:29:48 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god I am a creepy stalker and this is so bad but I googled Anna and they have THE CUTEST blog about their kid and they are SUCH A CUTE FAMILY okay I should probably stop...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:26:24 UTC">
      <body>Haha ok if you get them that sounds good for downstairs. I am going to buy one off Peter for my room </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:27:41 UTC">
      <body>I found the lease. I will fax it to your dad today </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 13:28:25 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! The sooner the better if possible cause he is probably leaving work around 11 so that we can start loading the truck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:29:31 UTC">
      <body>Fuck. I'm not at work now so I'm not sure I can do that. At this point should I just scan and email it to you when I can? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:29:49 UTC">
      <body>Also when are you getting here? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:30:40 UTC">
      <body>Sorry about my flakiness with this. I've been going through kinda a hard time and it had been making me super annoying to do anything with </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 13:31:34 UTC">
      <body>Tomorrow. I can just get a copy from realty world, no worries.  I'm sorry you're going through a rough time! Is everything okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:34:56 UTC">
      <body>Well this sounds pathetic but rob and I stayed together until your graduation day and then it broke off in a really horrible way. And I haven't really been handling the breakup well and it is confusing because rob says he isn't sure he made the right decision but also is very not ready to get back together </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 13:34:56 UTC">
      <body>It feels stupid to be as upset about it as I have been, but there you go </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 13:37:54 UTC">
      <body>That's okay though. Breakups are rough shit. There is no way you are "supposed to" feel, you know? You are allowed to be upset. And that sounds confusing and emotional. ❤ Anyway I don't think it is stupid to be really upset. And if you want to talk about it more, I'm here!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 15:07:24 UTC">
      <body>￼Any objection? It's this or white. Speak now or forever hold your peace :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 15:30:08 UTC">
      <body>Looks good to me! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 15:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Haha whoops I accidentally texted Anna instead of you. That's not a liner (it's just a curtain for the outside) so I ended up not getting it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 15:39:57 UTC">
      <body>Also #sexisminthehardwarestore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135080" time="2013-05-31 15:39:58 UTC">
      <body>I was told, "just get a boyfriend and have him do it for you" by another customer in line. Ugh. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135293" time="2013-05-31 15:40:48 UTC">
      <body>Ew. Sexism+heteronormativity=no good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135293" time="2013-06-01 13:34:56 UTC">
      <body>When are you arriving? Are you picking up the keys? Should I bring you a check for my share ($1200 right)? Basically, I'm excited we are getting our new place today! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135293" time="2013-06-01 14:56:00 UTC">
      <body>If you wanna pick up the key from real world properties they said it is ready and you can just give them a call. I can also pick them up if you can't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135080" time="2013-06-01 16:16:33 UTC">
      <body>If there is no traffic I should get there between 2 and 3. Yeah I will pay what they need today and you can write me a check. Do you want me to get your key when I pick up mine?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135293" time="2013-06-01 16:21:14 UTC">
      <body>Yes please! Let me know if you have time for me to come over later </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135080" time="2013-06-01 16:24:02 UTC">
      <body>Ill text you when I get there...we will just be moving things so you can come whenever (and help if you want to </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="135293" time="2013-06-01 16:36:16 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good! I am actually helping my sister move some stuff today but I will come when I can</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
