<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141213.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-13 20:13:52 UTC" participant="152776">
      <body>Hey ! Let me know if you want to stop by and get books tomorrow or this week </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-13 22:08:13 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-13 22:10:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-13 22:10:25 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-13 22:10:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ps this is what I'm working on, and I set up a website but it's Absolutely still in the works. I've had quite a few clients already! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-13 22:11:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Mainly MFA students wanting me to edit their thesis papers or some former profs actually asking me to edit their applications to residencies or one MFA student who was applying to be an adjunct prof in sculpture and wanted me to edit his application </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-13 22:12:47 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So if you are interested in working  for me :) aka I'd send you projects- it would just be side gigs obv- let me know and I'll get a bio from you for the site </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-13 22:13:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So far my friend Sofie who has a masters in design theory is helping edit- she's a Great arts writer , and her mother lol who writes for the nytimes occasionally and various mags </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-13 22:13:47 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Are taking any overflow I might start having </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-13 22:13:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Id love some one w an art history grad degree tho </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-12-13 22:14:24 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also my friend Jill who has an undergrad from brown in art history and her grad degree in architecture theory</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-13 22:15:24 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I have architecture (Jill), design (Sofie), and painting (me) and video (Sofie mom) people but no one w a renaissance/art history prior to modernism </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-13 22:15:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-13 22:17:27 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It's $5/pg light copy edits and $8/pg for feed back so it's cheap! Under the going rate for copy editors bc...that's how my friends dog walking business blew up and I'm following her model :) she's making $$$$ by offering a service much cheaper than anyone in Philly </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-12-13 22:29:54 UTC" participant="152776">
      <body>I like the idea ! Can we chat more tomorrow - later this week ? Just have to figure out how much time I have right now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-14 06:53:47 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Later this week is great and this is something that would begin in a few months so no worries! Also, it's very spot and go- no obligation to me or anything- you would just say yay or nay as jobs came in </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-12-14 06:54:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>For now, Sofie and I are handling all the incoming requests pretty fine. I just anticipate more clients and want to have a rough game plan for when that happens </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

