<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140924.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-24 21:10:21 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Hey. I just realized I never responded to your text last week. It was my first day of actual work. Tomaszewsi is married?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-24 21:14:24 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oh no worries! But yeah! It's so surprising isn't it? Haha.
But how has work been?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-24 21:20:46 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I guess it has been several years since his whole pursuit of you. Haha. So it makes sense. But work is good. Other than the fact that 12 hours are hard on me, I like it. Much better than powerback. Nice and clean, looks new,  only six patients max.  My preceptor is good. But she reminds me of Michael's sister. Haha. And I'm a little scared of Michelle sometimes. Haha. But overall I'm doing good. How's biology treating you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-24 21:24:28 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>That's so great! I'm glad you're liking it better, but 12 hrs has got to be just so much fun! It's true though, you do not want to get Michelle angry. Haha. 
Bio is good. I just had my exam yesterday. I did amazingly for someone who just studied most of t in one night, but I could've done better, you know? I have a lab quiz tomorrow, which I wouldn't be so worried about except that it's 30 mins. What kind of quiz is 30 mins?! But I have that and a lab write up that I have to do tonight. Sucks.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-24 21:27:02 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Wow. I don't miss those days. But it's good to hear that you're doing good. I know you were worried.  Good luck on the quiz! I'm sure you'll do fine.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-24 21:27:36 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Thank you very much! So what did you do for michaels birthday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-24 21:31:42 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Nothing yet. I'm waiting for him to get home. We're gonna go to Jose Pistolos for dinner. Cassy, Jimmy, Victor, uyen, and Steven are going. Of course its going to rain.  Haha. Me and my mom got him his own coffee pot to have here since my dad's is do inconsistent. Haha. And I got him sneakers which my mom spoiled it by going through my bank account online during a time when someone stole her credit card info and said, what's vans $80? Ugh! So he's known for some time now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-24 21:36:30 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Aw! That's so awesome! Although yeah, it sucks he found out. Haha. If it makes you feel better, for mike, I actually blurted out "your books didn't come yet! Still coming from the UK!" He had no idea either! I bought him 18 books...12 of which were the freaking history of middle earth (like Tolkien's lord of the rings' middle earth!) Such a nerd!
But I'm so mad I couldn't go! And I'm also jealous that we never get to see each other! Cassy sees you more than me  My green monster is showing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-24 21:39:34 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>18? Haha. That is a bit nerdy. It does suck that you can't go. But it is a Wednesday night and I understand. We do need to try to see each other more! Next weekend is a must.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-24 21:41:09 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body> Sounds good to me!!! I definitely won't make plans that weekend!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-24 21:43:53 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yes. Don't! And I saw Emmy in your window last weekend driving by. She's tiny and cute.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-24 21:47:11 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>That damn dog...can climb to and from the window but can't/won't go down the steps. She's helpless! She really is he opposite of Tipsy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-24 21:52:05 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. That's funny. She's afraid of heights.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-25 15:34:51 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Oh my god! We just planned to get together next weekend but I forgot that me and Michael will be in Boston visiting two of his friends at Harvard. Damn.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-25 15:36:25 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>But we might not be going to wildwood this Saturday. I'm not sure yet. So I can let you know if we're free that day to do something.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-25 15:37:09 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oh no!!! That's okay! I guess we'll have the following weekend. Haha. What are ya gonna do. 
I would totally go this weekend if you can. It's going to be nice!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-09-25 15:37:47 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>So my prof just sent us an email saying that the class mean for exam #1 was 65.96. Hah!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-09-25 15:37:50 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. Yeah. I'll let you know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-09-25 15:38:01 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Wow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-09-25 15:38:11 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>So you're doing great!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-09-25 15:39:17 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I know. He said the grades were all over. Some really high (someone got 100) and some really low.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-09-25 20:53:01 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Can you go out Friday night? John will be here.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

