<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130127.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131419" time="2013-01-27 16:47:50 UTC">
      <body>Oh man. I hope his treatment is grounding and also that u wont have 2 be so burdened by the weight of his difficult situation.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-01-27 19:28:43 UTC">
      <body>Thanks Cara. It's my own fault in part for masterminding this trip to NYC. I'm in charge of arranging housing for us and Ryan is overwhelmed by logistics like bus tickets. And I'm realizing I might want to stay in NYC longer than him. Thanks for hearing m</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131419" time="2013-01-27 19:32:06 UTC">
      <body>Sure thing-i know how stressful travel can be not to mention with all the added worry of ryan's health!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131419" time="2013-01-28 15:17:11 UTC">
      <body>I think i may have witnessed stillness in motion among some of charlie's fam this weekend!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-01-28 15:18:37 UTC">
      <body>Yah!!!! I was lying in bed last night and had a thought. Charlie might be an earth cf!!!! What do you think?? He does sing a bit. And he can navigate center to periphery and back again.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130962" time="2013-01-28 15:19:47 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I've been out of touch. Work and school are both super busy. I would love to treat you. I could come after work around 4:30ish on a Monday or Tuesday or weekends.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131419" time="2013-01-28 15:41:05 UTC">
      <body>Girl pleez, i understand! 2nd year is intense, i've heard. Charlie's got me stumped but u might be right!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-01-28 16:05:03 UTC">
      <body>:)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131419" time="2013-01-29 15:10:43 UTC">
      <body>Hey mb, does clinic obs really last till 4:30? I may need 2 leave b4 then 2 nurse paz.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-01-29 15:17:18 UTC">
      <body>So glad you're coming! Any chance we could lunch at 12:30? Clinical observation is 1:30-4:30 but I'm not sure how long it goes or when Bob shows up. I can try to find out for you. Did I tell you that I'm not in that class. It's for first years. Caroline s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131419" time="2013-01-29 15:22:35 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay! I'm still playing it by ear, so we shouldnt make lunch plans quite yet. We'll see how paz sleeps 2morrow nite!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130962" time="2013-01-29 15:35:35 UTC">
      <body>I can email Caroline and ask what time Bob is arriving if that helps. I can't imagine he would be there more than an hour of the class...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131419" time="2013-01-29 15:36:27 UTC">
      <body>Oh cool-thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130962" time="2013-01-29 15:37:25 UTC">
      <body>:)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-01-29 22:44:03 UTC">
      <body>PS: I wanted to let you know that Ed has threatened to suspend students who have needled outside of school. So we can't talk about inducing labor etc.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131419" time="2013-01-30 16:18:02 UTC">
      <body>Got it. I wont talk about the birth acupuncture to anyone at all. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130962" time="2013-01-30 16:26:45 UTC">
      <body>Thanks lady. Ed is so weird.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131419" time="2013-01-30 16:33:34 UTC">
      <body>Ah, i guess he's just doing his job, but geez. Ur becoming such a pro so quickly its easy to forget ur still a student!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
