<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110705.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:07:18 UTC">
      <body>Yo dude. Do you know any good loan  consultation companies?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:07:57 UTC">
      <body>For what kind of loans?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:09:16 UTC">
      <body>Well I have federal (subsidized and unsubsidized stafford) and private (educational and personal). My knowledge of how this all works is limited...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:15:53 UTC">
      <body>Oh, you are going to love this. So, your president, Barak Obama, nationalized the student loan industry in order to pay for that national health care thi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:15:58 UTC">
      <body>ngy. So as a result, the borrowing cost for education is hundreds of billions of dollars more expensive than what the private market could provide. For e</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:16:03 UTC">
      <body>xample, the student loan nationalization is going to cost me $40,000. But hey, it's all in the name of progress, right? So even though you're carrying a </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:16:06 UTC">
      <body>larger loan burden, you can take solace in the fact your helping people get free, and unlimited, access to health care.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:17:36 UTC">
      <body>I do love that. But. That's not a consolidation company... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:20:35 UTC">
      <body>No, you can't consolidate student loans anymore because of the student loan nationalization. You can still role up all of your loans into one loan based </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:20:39 UTC">
      <body>on the weighted average of your loans. But you don't want to do that because it takes away the ability to pay off the highest interest rate loans first.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:21:26 UTC">
      <body>But ive seen some companies that offer consolidating?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:31:04 UTC">
      <body>Private banks will do it. But they will treat it as a non-collateralized loan with recourse; meaning that the interest rate will be higher than what's al</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:31:09 UTC">
      <body>ready on the loans. More than likely, it will be a floating rate which may look attractive in a zero interest rate environment, but the minute rates star</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:31:12 UTC">
      <body>t going up yo will lose your shorts.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:31:44 UTC">
      <body>So no consolidating for me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:33:28 UTC">
      <body>No, I would say not. I've been watching this space for a while and it doesn't look good. If you need further explanation you can call me tonight or stop </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:33:33 UTC">
      <body>by my office.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:40:12 UTC">
      <body> Ok cool. Once I have real questions I'll do that sometime soon. Where's your office?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:41:29 UTC">
      <body>Top floor of the Wells Fargo building. It's one of the best views in town.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 14:43:40 UTC">
      <body>So if I get Ito an elevator and go to the top floor I'll find you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 14:44:28 UTC">
      <body>Yep. 51st floor.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 16:02:23 UTC">
      <body>Will you be at lunch at 1? Or can I stop by?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 16:29:57 UTC">
      <body>I'm not going to be able to leave for lunch today. But you can stop by if you'd like.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 16:31:00 UTC">
      <body>Do you have some time or would another time be better? Or would it be better if I call tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 16:32:10 UTC">
      <body>What time do you leave work? If you want to stop by after work that would be fine. I'll probably be here late.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 16:37:34 UTC">
      <body>Like 4? Is that ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135124" time="2011-07-05 17:04:10 UTC">
      <body>Yes, that would be fine.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
