<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150301.0035" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-01 00:16:41 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>What is your opinion on wes Anderson </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-01 00:23:11 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>I think he's one of the few brilliant and genuine artists of our time. He's a master storyteller... But that because he has such a distinct style he's being commercialized in a way that could easily become cliche. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-01 00:24:39 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>Well I fucking love him and I hate that no one has heard of him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-01 00:26:59 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>Why do you fear he will become cliche </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-01 00:32:05 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Everyone knows Wes!!! Its only inbred buttfucks that don't know him. He's becoming a cliche because his style is so recognizable. Maybe it's only in film school, but people are constantly making comparisons to his color schemes, framing, characters, dialogue, Etc. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-01 00:32:37 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Don't get me wrong, he's my hero. But since grand Budapest he's everyone's hero. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-01 00:34:08 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>But he does it its a trademark IMO like Abrams and his lens flare or Michael bay and his useless female leads and EXPLOSIONS I'm glad everyone is seeing him I'm want people to appreciate his style. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-01 00:38:58 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Wes is just in a different category of film altogether man.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-01 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>Ik jen he is my number two director, I hope you honestly didn't think I held Michael baymablam on the same level. So you don't like being able to tell a director from watching their work or do you fear it will be copied?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-01 00:48:08 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Nah, I know we feel the same about Michael bay... And I love being able to tell a director by the films look--- that's the ultimate goal. But I just worry that he's going to fall into the Disney demise... Maybe not on that scale, but I can tell you that 75% of up and coming cinematographers aim for the Wes Anderson look. Which is fine I guess, imitation is the highest compliment, right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-01 00:51:11 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>I get you now that is unfortunate. But he will always be the best. Do I introduce Alex to Star Wars or Indiana jones first</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-01 00:52:25 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>He isn't ready for pulp fiction</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-01 00:56:43 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Damn that kid. I'd go Star Wars, you've got something to build to by December, an entire universe and culture to immerse him in. Indiana jones might be easier for him to chew on though... But that 4th one is such a bitter disappointment. Jesus Christ. Make sure he's at a point where he can really appreciate pulp fiction before showing him that masterpiece. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-01 01:04:00 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>What am I building by December</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-01 01:04:00 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>Oh nvm now I know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-01 01:28:25 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>He didn't even know IV Was the first one uncultured fuckhead </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-01 01:46:12 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Hahaha that poor kid.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-03-01 01:47:16 UTC" participant="153876">
      <body>I wanna know if he knows if vader is lukes father of not I can't wait to see his face </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-01 01:52:57 UTC" participant="153848">
      <body>Oh my gosh I bet he doesn't. It's going to crush his world. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

