<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150308.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-08 18:28:19 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey its ########... sorry, I hate messenger too. It doesn't always notify me of new messages</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-08 18:50:06 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Hey. Here r some pics that i cane across. Its a small party maybe 60 people. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-08 18:54:08 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>All the tiered cakes i think we wiuld only need 2 tiers. I was also thinking maybe some cupcakes to match the cake. I want this to be fancy lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-08 18:59:47 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok so I still don't work with fondant, each of those cakes would have to be done in icing and toppers. Is that okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-08 19:00:32 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Would they still look the same</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-08 19:01:38 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Which one do u think?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-08 19:03:09 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>For the most part... Like the first picture would be done with icing. Then I can use ribbon and  artificial gold flowers since icing would be too delicate to work with as far as placing and stacking. That one might be annoying for you since you would have to remove all the non-edible products prior to cutting....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-08 19:04:24 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Hmmm. Ok.  So which other one would give me the least aggravation?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-08 19:07:47 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok lol The 2nd, 3rd and 5th would be all icing and the 4th one would have artificial flowers but not many so wouldnt be a pain... let me work on pricing each one and finding supplies then maybe you could pick based off the prices? I'll get back to you sometime this week since im heading into work right now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-08 19:08:47 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Ill get back to u soon. My mom just walked in</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-08 20:18:29 UTC" participant="153263">
      <body>Ok sounds good. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

