<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130513.0017" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 21:16:19 UTC">
      <body>I deleted the old messages.  Did you figure out how to message them? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 21:18:14 UTC">
      <body>Also I see you haven't deposited my checks yet.  I can directly transfer it and the money will be in your account Thursday.  Should i do that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:11:31 UTC">
      <body>Eric did something then they all came in at once.  Rick was gonna make dinner for mother's day but I didn't respond till late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:11:49 UTC">
      <body>Let u know about check</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:16:05 UTC">
      <body>Is it more than one check?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:17:51 UTC">
      <body>Another should have come today for 150</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:18:35 UTC">
      <body>The last one </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:20:05 UTC">
      <body>Maybe tomorrow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:21:59 UTC">
      <body>I'll just transfer the money and you can throw out the checks </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:24:34 UTC">
      <body>Oh, hmm, i can't do that... Yet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:25:53 UTC">
      <body>I'll just deposit it tomorrow w ur fathers check</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:26:02 UTC">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 22:38:11 UTC">
      <body>You've really got to put some of that in a money market account or some cds.  You should be getting a little interest </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:55:26 UTC">
      <body>I know. But I don't know how long I'll b around:-(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 22:59:33 UTC">
      <body>I asked Eric what he wants. A star wars. Video game a CD n wants to eat a Famous Dave's rest or would money b better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 23:04:16 UTC">
      <body>That's no reason to not have as much money as possible.  I'll get the game, you get the cd, and i'll take us to dave's and we'll give him some money to boot. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131588" time="2013-05-13 23:57:11 UTC">
      <body>We're eating the leftovers. Thank u for dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131528" time="2013-05-13 23:59:06 UTC">
      <body>Yay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131588" time="2013-05-14 00:28:21 UTC">
      <body>Good even the 2nd day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131528" time="2013-05-14 02:08:13 UTC">
      <body>I really love the towels you got me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131588" time="2013-05-14 02:11:12 UTC">
      <body>Oh good. I have such a hard time picking for u.  I have to go opposite of what I like lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131528" time="2013-05-14 02:21:55 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131528" time="2013-05-14 16:26:30 UTC">
      <body>Are you avoiding me? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131588" time="2013-05-14 21:03:35 UTC">
      <body>What why. I been in the backyard pulling weeds</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131528" time="2013-05-14 21:04:40 UTC">
      <body>Oh ok.  I thought you somehow knew i wanted to talk to you about your money :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131588" time="2013-05-14 21:09:54 UTC">
      <body>Oh lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 00:47:32 UTC">
      <body>Can you send me your taxes? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 00:59:07 UTC">
      <body>How</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 00:59:11 UTC">
      <body>N why</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 01:00:41 UTC">
      <body>I'm trying to plan for you,  i want to know how much you paid so i know how much to do to reduce them. Do you only have a printed copy? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 01:22:09 UTC">
      <body>Yesalthou he filed electronically I think.  I wouldn't mind a CD but what good is a Ira for me. My life expentancy is not that long</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 02:02:38 UTC">
      <body>Talk to u tomorrow.  Im exhausted</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 13:58:40 UTC">
      <body>Capital m</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 14:10:29 UTC">
      <body>:-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 14:50:19 UTC">
      <body>Wow, the department of commerce credit union has really high cd rates.  I wish i could sneak you in. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 14:51:34 UTC">
      <body>Do you know how much social security dad gets? I want to figure out how much you would get when benefits kick in. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 15:35:48 UTC">
      <body>I. Think just a little over a 1000.00</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:36:56 UTC">
      <body>At 62, you'd get 33.13 percent of that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:41:04 UTC">
      <body>I'm thinking 4 things for you.  1. Putting 6 months of alimony payments in a money market account with a .84% interest rate.  2. Putting 6000 into cds, a third each in a 1, 2, and 3 year cd.  That way some of it will be available every year,  but you will</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:43:02 UTC">
      <body>3. Put some in an ira,  which you can access without penalty because a doctor will certify that you are totally and permanently disabled. We will put that in very safe and conservative bond index funds. 
</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:44:02 UTC">
      <body>Putting money in the ira will save you as much as 1000 in taxes, or about 15 percent,  which is the best return you will get anywhere. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:46:44 UTC">
      <body>4. Finally, the ira will be at fidelity.  They have an excellent, rewards credit card.  For every 2500 you spend, 50 gets put in your ira,  a 2 percent return.  If you use that for your shopping and what bills you can and pay it off at the end of the mont</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:48:23 UTC">
      <body>Money magazine calls that fidelity card one of the best two best.  They rate Ally bank tops for cds, so we will use them for that and the money market account. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 15:59:36 UTC">
      <body>You in? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:05:27 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) Wait till we discuss all this later.  I still have to pay for my teeth.  Have to pay rick for trees n have him fix kitchen floor in case I sell.  Also hav</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:05:30 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) e to replace front upper window.  It has moisture in from not being taken care of.  Going to b expensive.  Can't leave it cuz it will cause more damage</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:07:22 UTC">
      <body> Don't know what to do. Not sure I can afford this house. Stressing me out.  I have to get thru this dental thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:11:04 UTC">
      <body>Well,  let's hold off on the ira part.   If you spend more than 2500 on your teeth,  that will be tax deductible,  so you won't need it.  Money is still accessible in the money market account and we can make the 1 year cd the no penalty one so it will be </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:20:52 UTC">
      <body>My teeth r going to b in the thousands depending which way I go.  I pray that something can b done w the board of examiners</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:21:56 UTC">
      <body>I have a usaa credit card at 9.9%  not good??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:22:06 UTC">
      <body>If you have to pay,  pay all in one year if you can,  could save you thousands. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:24:27 UTC">
      <body>Still paying on heat n air system. 0 % till Dec</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:25:21 UTC">
      <body>Do u think I should just sell??  Eric I think would b upset</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:25:26 UTC">
      <body>I'm not planning on you paying any interest, just getting the rewards.   At usaa,  you get 25 back for every 3000 you spend.  Fidelity is 50 for every 2500.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:27:38 UTC">
      <body>I don't think you have to sell,  and i think that the longer you wait,  I he stronger the market gets and and the more prices go up.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:28:37 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) Oh wow. Why don't u become a CFA.  U would be good n have the potential to make big bucks n then can afford to help ur mamma LOL.  Actually there aren't t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:28:41 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) hat many in the country</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:36:28 UTC">
      <body>I was thinking about it this past summer.  There would be money in it.  I'd have to work in finance for a few years before i could take the test.  I got the study books. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131528" time="2013-05-15 16:44:44 UTC">
      <body>Can i open the accounts? Just to get started.  We don't have to put anything in them yet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:50:47 UTC">
      <body>I guess so. Im not sure how much because of my teeth n window</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131588" time="2013-05-15 16:51:35 UTC">
      <body>I think u would find it interesting n challenging </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
