<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141112.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-11-12 04:38:27 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:( I got 5 new bites just last night FYI bc I didn't dry my stuff and I attempted to put bed against wall again like a normal human </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-11-12 04:38:55 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Not even all the way, but just...a few inches away from wall so I can put a dresser in here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-11-12 06:19:26 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm going to talk to Kevin in the morning &amp; get the new exterminator out ASAP.  I'll call you to coordinate.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-11-12 07:17:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-11-12 23:55:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I texted Kevin about the other exterminator.  I then called Beth to tell her I was done with Cindy.  Before I told her she told me she thinks she can get over there tomorrow. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-11-12 23:55:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>She said she still isn't really doing steps. But she said she can make it up to your room.   I have her your number.  She said she is going to call you later.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-11-12 23:57:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I told her I didn't want to set back her therapy at all but she pretty much insisted upon it.  As much as I was seriously unimpressed by Cindy.  Beth is amazing.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-11-13 00:22:33 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She called me but I'm confused about what this will change but ok </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-11-13 00:22:45 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She said she'll come tomorrow and dust and that's fine we will see </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-11-13 00:38:24 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Cindy is .......   Lets say overwhelmed.  Beth is like Superwoman when it comes to killing bugs specifically bed bugs.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-11-13 00:39:09 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Is there anyway you could meet her tomorrow?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-11-13 00:39:32 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm not exaggerating.  Beth is incredible.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-11-13 01:01:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>If Beth hasn't blown out her knee she would have gotten rid of the bedbugs a couple months ago.  </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

