<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140530.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-05-30 18:24:46 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Is morel season over?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-05-30 18:32:58 UTC" participant="153562">
      <body>Pertty much, pardner. I came up with nada, no time to hunt... 

I have a print from shawn for you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-05-30 18:35:28 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah, I've been out a fair amount but found nothing. The vegetation is just now getting to the level it was last year when I found a bunch but I don't see shit. Combing really slow but maybe I can move quicker and just look for oysters if there's no chance of morels</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-05-30 18:37:41 UTC" participant="153562">
      <body>Yeah if you get to chamonioux, head to the recycling center and make a right on the trail right before the gate. A quarter down you can climb up into the</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-05-30 18:37:46 UTC" participant="153562">
      <body> center where the fence is down on a giant pile of wood chips. I've found stropharis there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-05-30 18:38:58 UTC" participant="153562">
      <body>The weather is late this year so I wouldn't give up hope but morels are more of an Ohio and west central mushroom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-05-30 18:39:22 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼￼￼Any ideas?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-05-30 18:40:12 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah but I found like 30 of them in one outing last year. I wonder if a mild winter helps the morels</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-05-30 18:43:16 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Did you see those 30lb dryad saddle growing near the recycling center? I am at chamounix . I took that trail last time but couldn't find the wood pile. I'll try again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-05-30 18:50:11 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-05-30 21:24:40 UTC" participant="153562">
      <body>Hey bro I'm back west. Should I stop by or vice versa?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

