<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140602.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-06-02 23:46:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey I'm just getting done work... I'm going to Adobe (on ########) Friday night with a couple of friends if you and some buddies want to come out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-06-02 23:59:21 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body> Ok.. what is adobe?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-06-03 00:01:11 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Bar that serves Mexican food</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-06-03 00:02:33 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Ok.. how many friends should I bring?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-06-03 00:06:34 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>It'll probably just be me, my roommate, and one of our co-workers.. but you can bring as many you want</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-06-03 00:07:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Just curious, how old are you? Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-06-03 00:08:26 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Ok. It sounded like a bunch of people were going.. sounds like fun.. I'm there..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-06-03 02:52:26 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>I'm sorry, I didn't even see your question till now.. I'm 34, how about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-06-03 02:55:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol that's fine.. I never would have guessed that tho lol. You don't look it but I was just wondering in case you had younger buddies.  Younger meaning since Adobe cards. But I can see that won't be a problem tho haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-06-03 02:58:09 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Thx,  I have friends 23 and up.. yeah people say I look mid 20s a lot.. how old are u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-06-03 02:58:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea that's what I was thinking, lol.. I'm 25</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-06-03 03:01:55 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Ok, cool. I like how your always in a cheerful mood.. I need your secrets. .lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-06-03 03:13:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahaha when you work at my day job, you'll also be excited to be anywhere else but there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-06-03 03:19:37 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Lol..that's funny.. I thought your day job was sweet, that bad huh?? Well before you know it you'll be your own boss..  I gotta try a piece of cake...lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-06-03 03:27:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh no, my day job is like a Nazi camp. Its ridiculous but it pays good bec of the OT.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-06-03 13:23:27 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Good morning #####. .lol.. yeah, I definitely feel asleep mid text.. have fun at concentration camp today.. lol</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

