<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130509.0049" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 14:51:47 UTC">
      <body>Does high cholesterol run in our family? Like, genetic-related cholesterol issues?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 14:56:14 UTC">
      <body>Hard to say...moms is low but her body is ah, anomalous...her mother had a huge history of heart related ailments. My cholesterol is genetically high as its been measured after extensive periods of regular exercise and good diet and is still high. My fath</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 14:58:55 UTC">
      <body>Hmmmm..had some blood work done and apparently my cholesterol is slightly elevated...but I'm a freaking underweight vegan (well, mostly)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:04:40 UTC">
      <body>Have you heard if a book called "wheat belly"? It explains that the run of the mill cholesterol blood test is a calculated value and not an actual measurement of the different types of cholesterol. It's possible that you are genetically high but IMHO you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:29:07 UTC">
      <body>I don't want to take anything!! :-I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:30:10 UTC">
      <body>Good attitude although aspirin is fine ;-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:34:22 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha well that I have no problem with</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:35:05 UTC">
      <body>Especially before going to bed after a night of drinking....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:35:33 UTC">
      <body>B vitamins before bed help in that circumstance as well...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:35:43 UTC">
      <body>I did the research...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:42:35 UTC">
      <body>Haha yes, well, I have a bottle of b vitamin complex specifically reserved for those rare occasions...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:43:51 UTC">
      <body>Oh, speaking of, what kind of fancy water do you want at your disposal at the wedding?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:44:26 UTC">
      <body>Planning is everything...speaking of that- you've hit the "less than one month mark"...nervous?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:45:48 UTC">
      <body>Nah just antsy, let the planning be done! Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:46:58 UTC">
      <body>Well we're excited. It's going to be a great weekend...did you spend a night in your new house yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 15:49:11 UTC">
      <body>Not yet...we're getting a new bed so we still have to order it and get it set up...helloo memory foam topper!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 15:50:04 UTC">
      <body>What's this weekend look like for you guys??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 16:03:29 UTC">
      <body>Dan's flying out to new orleans today for his bachelor party...I'm doing yoga and dinner with a friend tomorrow, and have a driving lesson Saturday (I'm learning stick! ) but other than that I'm just hanging out and packing stuff up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 16:05:45 UTC">
      <body>Well have fun and tell Dan to stay safe...well be around all weekend and I know you didn't forget that Sunday is Mothers Day. E is taking M out for dinner but I'm not sure where</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131450" time="2013-05-09 16:07:11 UTC">
      <body>Okay...yeah there's something in the mail, it prob won't arrive until next week though...i'll call sunday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131473" time="2013-05-09 16:07:48 UTC">
      <body>Good child</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
