<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140831.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-31 18:55:51 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>First off I want to apologize again.  If I need to spray the whole house I will.   Part of the issue would be getting everyone to bag &amp; wash everything.  But if it needs to get done it needs to get done.  

This is one of the many reasons I wish Beth was handling this job.   Did you get a chance to call her?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-31 18:57:04 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>No one had ever had an issue with bed bugs in your room before you moved in.  But no one was living in your room when this problem first occurred.   The girl who had been living there had already moved in with her boyfriend a couple months before.  Then Kaushal basically used it as storage while waiting for Oliver to move.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-31 18:58:28 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Only David &amp; Phillip had an issue &amp; I thought the problem was addressed &amp; done with.  We only sprayed your room as a precaution.  No one told me anything about not putting stuff against the walls or using the closet.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-31 18:59:12 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>And this is in no way blaming you - but if I had known about your getting bites right when you moved in I think we could have jumped on this issue earlier before it got out of control.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-31 18:59:43 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>It is possible that a few of the other rooms have bedbugs but it is unlikely.  I have sent out several texts to everyone in the house in the last month or so. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-31 19:06:36 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>On August 14th I sent this text to everyone in the house --  "Have you noticed any bed bugs or any bug bites? Ingrid thinks she may have them.  I'm waiting on a call back from the exterminator."   I sent a couple follow up texts also.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-31 19:07:24 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Oh ok </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-31 19:07:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah it's just annoying to do my room again and feel like it's a bit futile if everyone isn't doing it but I guess we will see </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-31 19:09:01 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm very sorry this experience has left you in Feeling like you want to cry.  I feel you.  If I was a crier I would have been bawling for weeks.  This whole thing has me pulling my hair out.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-31 19:09:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I have to run to work but I can call Beth in the morning.  Again I will do whatever it takes to get rid of this little fuckers.   And Thank you again for our understand thru what has to be a horrible experience.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-31 19:12:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I suspect if Beth was around she would have made you wash / bag everything before she treated the first time &amp; all the bed bugs would have been dead 2 weeks ago.  

I have to go to work now but I'll call Beth tomorrow morning.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-31 19:12:41 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:) I meant thinking of moving would  make me cry bc moving sucks so I obv don't want to do it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-08-31 19:12:47 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I wasn't saying I'm crying now :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-08-31 19:12:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ok! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-08-31 19:13:01 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Sounds good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-08-31 19:14:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I know but I do feel like crying right now!!  Or punching a wall. But the last time I punched a wall I shattered my hand so I know it is a bad idea:-/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-08-31 19:16:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Well I actually punched an oak staircase.  Either way it's a bad idea.   Just feeling Arrrrrgggghhh!!! right now....... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-08-31 19:19:36 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Lol don't punch things! Haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-08-31 19:20:32 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I won't I learned my lesson the hard way.  I never was a big wall puncher but I was very very mad at that moment.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-08-31 19:20:32 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I actually had the presence of mind to punch the stairs instead of the wall b/c I knew I'd have to fix the wall.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-08-31 19:23:28 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha Spoken like a true landlord/property owner! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-08-31 19:23:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I bet I can make you miss Philly </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-08-31 19:23:46 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm at dirty franks w my last drop coworkers </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-08-31 19:24:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-08-31 19:26:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>If I didn't have to go to work I'd go on an absolute ass kicking run.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-08-31 19:26:47 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Awwww. I miss Franks &amp; the Last Drop!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-08-31 19:27:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Is it still the same bartenders?  The two girls &amp; the guy who have been there FOREVER??  Trying to remember their names.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-08-31 19:33:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Lol yes!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-08-31 19:33:18 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Heather is serving </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-08-31 19:33:43 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She's in her forties or something and much hotter than me lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-08-31 19:34:40 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Yeah she is awesome!  I doubt she'd remember me but tell her I said Aloha!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-08-31 20:10:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha ok </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

