<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130517.0019" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 13:24:35 UTC">
      <body>Looks like we're paired again. But yeah there's a small bar upstairs at KFN then two open rooms towards the front of the building</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:08:22 UTC">
      <body>Hey, phone died at work and I tried to switch numbers to my Google Voice number but it didn't continue the convo. Are we still connected?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:10:18 UTC">
      <body>Yep, we are</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:12:28 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Yeah, I've never been to the KFN upstairs, but it seems like they're doing that more often these days than before.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:15:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I think phonographic arts philly booking crew organizes most of the shows up there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:17:56 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Don't know them, but I just might look into it. I just went to Underground Arts for the first time and that place is a pretty solid venue. Been there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:19:10 UTC">
      <body>Oh hell yeah. A friend used to barback there. Who'd you see? Think I've been there 3 times now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:23:49 UTC">
      <body>I was actually playing, but seeing as we're supposed to withhold personal info over the platform, I'm just going to say that you might able to guess which band I'm in.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:26:15 UTC">
      <body>Got you. I saw Hot Snakes &amp; Pissed Jeans once, then PJ again for their record release</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:38:00 UTC">
      <body>Fantomas out of the number one position for me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:38:55 UTC">
      <body>Nice, I played with Pissed Jeans a while ago and they tear it up. They were one of my fave live bands to see. Still, tho, I think that no one has pushed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:39:42 UTC">
      <body>Number 1 position?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:43:09 UTC">
      <body>Awesome. And yeah, their frontman rules haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:43:40 UTC">
      <body>As favorite live band that I've seen.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:44:55 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I got to see Faith No More when they reunited a few years ago, which was really really awesome to see.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:45:22 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, for some reason I got that text in 2 parts and it wasn't in order</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 19:47:24 UTC">
      <body>I was about to say, that last text was pretty long and could've gotten rearranged. The platform does that sometimes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 19:51:44 UTC">
      <body>Alright, good to know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 20:58:38 UTC">
      <body>What's fantomas like?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 21:51:55 UTC">
      <body>It's another Mike Patton project (singer of Faith No More and Mr. Bungle) that is kinda heavy metal mixed with ambience and avant garde.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 21:54:01 UTC">
      <body>When you said they've got a great front man, I originally thought you meant Patton (hence the FNM shoutout), and realized that you meant PJ.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
