<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130203.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-02-03 20:21:44 UTC">
      <body>I want to see you sometime, I'm just not sure exactly when!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131422" time="2013-02-03 20:23:42 UTC">
      <body>I saved you some ice cream.I'm also cooking a chicken right now. It's my new hobby. Give me a time when you're free and I'll try to be free too!xxxx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-02-03 22:25:46 UTC">
      <body>Aw. Are you free tomorrow between 4:40 and limbs? I have a 2.5 lb chicken from the coop we could roast!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 01:59:09 UTC">
      <body>Hey mon fau, I'm on campus until five, but I could come home, grab limbs stuff, and meet for less-time-consuming-than-chicken-event at like five thirty?xx</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 03:34:34 UTC">
      <body>Hi LF, the chicken needs to get cooked. It says on the recipe it will only take one hour. I have some squash soup I could feed you while the chicken roasts? Maybe tomorrow is too tight. Think it over and let me know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 03:35:52 UTC">
      <body>Im sorry our schedules are so opposite. Weds morning 9:00 yoga date is too early for you right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 03:51:33 UTC">
      <body>Actually, I have to be on campus at nine am m,w,f these days. We could do tomorrow and if the chicken doesn't cook in time that's ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 04:38:07 UTC">
      <body>That sounds good. I will see you tomorrow! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 21:24:15 UTC">
      <body>Later is good! What time are you thinking? I'm having a hard time leaving work! So much to do!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 21:30:03 UTC">
      <body>Oh great! When suits? Is seven too late? Be honest!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 21:30:27 UTC">
      <body>6:45? :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 21:38:19 UTC">
      <body>Cancel everything, apparently I am teaching tonight. Grr. I was going to learn the class in my lunch break, but didn't because I thought I wasn't teaching, so now I need to learn it-no time for chicken. I'm so sorry (and annoyed). Can we try again on anot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 21:43:50 UTC">
      <body>Aw! I'm mad too! Certainly yes. Tomorrow night 5-Angie's class I'm free but I think you have a study group?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 22:27:55 UTC">
      <body>Sure thing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 22:27:56 UTC">
      <body>Yup, teach until six and reading group at seven. Boo.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 23:04:12 UTC">
      <body>Idea! When is limbs over? Want to come by then for a bit?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131422" time="2013-02-04 23:12:11 UTC">
      <body>It's over at nine. I could swing by for a quick cup of tea, or is that too late?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130962" time="2013-02-04 23:13:14 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Lets do it! I will save some carcass for you too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131422" time="2013-02-05 02:15:23 UTC">
      <body>One of the students is feeling dizzy so it's a slow exit, sorry.x</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130962" time="2013-02-05 02:16:19 UTC">
      <body>Oh no! That's ok. Stay as long as you need to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130962" time="2013-02-05 02:16:32 UTC">
      <body>xxxxxxxxx.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
