<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120109.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-01-09 19:52:07 UTC">
      <body>I'm actually coming back Monday the 16th at like 330. You should meet me at the bart or cinnaholic so we can catch up(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131063" time="2012-01-09 20:00:04 UTC">
      <body>Just text me when I should leave for Bart and I'll be there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131019" time="2012-01-09 20:02:43 UTC">
      <body>Yee(: I'm stoked! I hope your break is going well!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131063" time="2012-01-09 20:33:21 UTC">
      <body>Me too!! And it's going really well. I hope yours is too. See you in a week!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131063" time="2012-01-10 19:11:26 UTC">
      <body>Would you possibly be down to go to coachella? My parents are getting me tix and a hotel room for my bday! April 13-15</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131019" time="2012-01-10 21:10:37 UTC">
      <body>Can I think on it a few days? Cuz how much are tickets? Idk if I can afford it yet </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131019" time="2012-01-10 21:11:06 UTC">
      <body>But thank you for inviting me, that's super awesome of your parents too!:D you're stoked!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131063" time="2012-01-10 21:12:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah definitely!! I'll check ticket prices and let you know, but that would be so amazing if you could come :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-01-10 21:13:21 UTC">
      <body>Sweet, I'm checking them now then gotta talk to my parents, but I hope I can!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131063" time="2012-01-10 21:14:28 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good! The hotel is on me :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131019" time="2012-01-10 21:18:06 UTC">
      <body>Dude thats sweet, I'll have to talk to my dad. (ps you should buy yourself fix as soon as they go on sale Friday cuz they sol out in like a week last time)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131063" time="2012-01-10 21:21:33 UTC">
      <body>Great let me know when you find out!! And thanks, I already have an account made and an alarm set for when they go on sale Friday. I hope you can go! Fee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131063" time="2012-01-10 21:21:39 UTC">
      <body>l free to tell your dad I bought his bk if that helps, jk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131019" time="2012-01-10 21:33:15 UTC">
      <body>Bahaha I'll be sure to:P I'll let you know what happens</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
