<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130714.0046" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-07-14 22:51:15 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>I've been walking lucky around - he's acting normal, drank a little, still no poop? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-07-14 23:35:41 UTC" participant="153298">
      <body>I thnk the banamine helped. I really think its gas. Up to you if u want to wait to call vet. I think I would wait, but u are there :) I will pay attention to him when I get home !! :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-07-14 23:45:59 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>He seems brighter now &amp; wants to eat grass, so my inclination is to turn him out, wait &amp; see how he is tomorrow morning? Think it's ok? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-07-14 23:52:32 UTC" participant="153298">
      <body>Yes, if you want to turn his group out go ahead so he's not alone. Or u can put him in the square if u rather he be alone and put the nortys out next to him. Whatever you want is fine with me :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-07-15 00:20:57 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Ok, he pooped a normal poop and drank. I turned his bunch out, seems like everything's fine. Thanks for your help, see you tomorrow! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-07-15 01:18:56 UTC" participant="153298">
      <body>Great! Okeedokee! Hopefully he's over the hump. I'm going to tell Beth to bran mash him tomorrow am too, ok? Just to make sure </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-07-15 01:37:45 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Sounds good, thanks. I'll be out after work unless something goes awry :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-07-15 10:18:00 UTC" participant="153298">
      <body>Lucky is up and grazing ferociously this am, all good here! :) bran mash this am and probably back to normal for pm I think. I love banamine! :) have a good day!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-07-15 12:18:20 UTC" participant="152734">
      <body>Oh that's a relief! Thanks :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

