<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130607.0002" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 09:51:22 UTC">
      <body>Hello</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 14:03:08 UTC">
      <body>Hi I apologize for the late response. I have been in meetings all day. How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 15:00:45 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay..no worries I'm well. I'm just leaving work now. How were the meetings?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 15:13:28 UTC">
      <body>Long. Haha I am a researcher that the school of public health In Michigan. So I work with study participants but the meetings are kind of to keep investo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 15:13:28 UTC">
      <body>rs and partners posted on the logistics of the project.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 15:13:28 UTC">
      <body>Where do you work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 16:06:38 UTC">
      <body>Cool I have a 2 gigs working with agressive youth.Resources for Human Development and Devereux.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 16:06:38 UTC">
      <body>What type of education does your position require?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 18:56:45 UTC">
      <body>I'm actually still an undergrad. Senior. But my professor is in charge of the study, and I started working with him when it was still a proposal a few ye</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 18:57:05 UTC">
      <body>ars ago and now I'm a huge part of the project. But generally a position such as this would require a masters in public health.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 18:59:55 UTC">
      <body>Wow..it sounds like an amazing opportunity to have come across.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 19:01:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm taking nursing pre reqs now with the hopes of moving into an accelerated bsn. My undergrad was in social work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 19:04:31 UTC">
      <body>I'm aware that some universities offer grad dual programs involving public health Are u considering grad school?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 19:16:39 UTC">
      <body>Wow, that sounds amazing. What kind of courses are you taking? Yes I am interested in public health, thinking of dual degree maybe but the program I have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 19:16:52 UTC">
      <body>my sights set on is Harvard they have an mph program in global health and infectious diseases. And I'm also premed, so I'm taking lots of science course</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131007" time="2013-06-07 19:17:01 UTC">
      <body>s. Are they somewhat similar to your nursing prereqs?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131717" time="2013-06-07 19:27:51 UTC">
      <body>Nice! I'm doing statistics now... Then a basic bio and a basic chem.. onto anatomay&amp; physiology 1&amp;2, micro bio, nutrition</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
