<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130803.0026" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-08-03 18:56:00 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>Cute!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-08-03 18:56:15 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>Is that for Melissa's ######?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-08-03 18:57:13 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh no.. manager's son turning 5</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-08-03 18:57:48 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>Oo. Haven't heard from her is about 7 months. She called me at ccp after he had her locked up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-08-03 18:58:11 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>They still together?  Anyone even talk to her anymore? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-08-03 18:59:00 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I heard about that stuff.. Lydia told me afterwards. She is about the only one I still keep in touch with</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-08-03 18:59:24 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Erein from time to time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-08-03 18:59:37 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>They were in January when he got he locked up. Then I heard she went back. No one at work claims to still talk to her since the whole Adam situation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-08-03 19:00:56 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea I figured</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-08-03 19:01:42 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>I have her old extension so I get random calls from people for her</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-08-03 19:03:41 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I think she claims to have lost her phone or adonis took it so she claims to not have anyones numbers anymore so she hasnt talked to me since I left ccp</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-08-03 19:04:58 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I saw ettore recently... we had a coffee meet up about 2 months ago and last month I made a cake for her daughter</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-08-03 19:05:51 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>She called me crying saying she is sorry for not being in touch and stuff. Then Erein called her when Nia gram died or something and a man answered saying this isn't her phone anymore. Apparently Freddie paid for her engagement ring</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-08-03 19:06:54 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>It's so weird. I don't feel bad for her. She goes back to him.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2013-08-03 19:08:46 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>I saw her in October walking down cottman ave holding hands with him. Neither of their kids there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2013-08-03 19:09:06 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>She had an apartment up there somewhere</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2013-08-03 19:09:22 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>I told her job lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2013-08-03 19:10:11 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>Took*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2013-08-03 19:10:49 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Makes senses as to why I haven't seen her around here yet then... I was wondering that... i moved from the apt. Got a house now. I moved like 4 blocks away from where she was living</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2013-08-03 19:11:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body> Lol.. I knew you were back at ccp I didn't know which position... I know laura and mia left</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2013-08-03 19:11:39 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>Apparently nia is at her moms. She would take the bus alone from the northeast to south Philly. So I guess her mom said she can stay there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2013-08-03 19:12:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Idk.. its a messed up situation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2013-08-03 19:13:06 UTC" participant="154898">
      <body>When I came back I did Aetna. Then Laura couldn't handle it so they have it back to me. Then she quit or got fired no one knows. (I don't care either) now I am Medicare and commercial (Lisa m did). She is the Aetna girl now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2013-08-03 19:17:30 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Damn lol yea idk either. I think she said quit but anyone could just say that. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

