<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130219.0023" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 21:53:19 UTC">
      <body>￼I bought myself a job interview/adult watch. 42% off! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 21:57:34 UTC">
      <body>Very nice. If you want, I can teach you how to tell time on that kind of watch. ;b</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 21:57:57 UTC">
      <body>I'm gonna have to get used to it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:00:32 UTC">
      <body>So, had u heard of Aaron Beck?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:00:32 UTC">
      <body>Btw the symbol at end of ur last txt was just a square</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 22:02:27 UTC">
      <body>Oh no! But you have an iPhone! They're smileys. The name was familiar. Thanks for the email! They don't look like they do research. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:02:40 UTC">
      <body>We used to call our parents square (not cool)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:06:56 UTC">
      <body>My point is: beyond a full- time job, esp if close by, it's worth getting to know them &amp; their work &amp; for them to [already] know u &amp; your interest/capabilities. Networking. Possibilities of non- research work in that environment</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:09:04 UTC">
      <body>They do computer work, logistics, planning, communications, etc. important to learn all that. Think of what Ali Cocuzzo &amp; Wendy do. Those extra skills can make ur resume shine even more brightly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 22:09:46 UTC">
      <body>Ah. I see. Thanks! :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:15:28 UTC">
      <body>Even volunteering or coattailing goes on that resume. And sometimes the hirer will choose a familiar name, or recall that 4 yrs ago u took the initiative to explore their accomplishments &amp; offerings/services</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:20:29 UTC">
      <body>When I moved from RI to NYC, even though I wanted to work in health care, I accepted the offer to go w a hotel executive to a local reception/short conference. I mingled, listened, shared my hotel experience n interest, collected bus. cards &amp; wrote down details after. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 22:21:10 UTC">
      <body>Yep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:28:16 UTC">
      <body>When u visit or talk w anybody, talk itself up offer to email ur resume. They might remember u for ur green eyes or be impressed that u know about their work. U just never know. Or their spouse or friend could be a grad school dean or the grant-assigner for  ur kind of work. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:28:16 UTC">
      <body>End of #438. I love you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 22:29:22 UTC">
      <body>Love you too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135279" time="2013-02-19 22:32:32 UTC">
      <body>Btw, I used to wear a Skågen just like that one. Nice taste. Wear it in good health. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135080" time="2013-02-19 22:33:56 UTC">
      <body>Thanks :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
