<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130530.0034" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:00:19 UTC">
      <body>Hi! So my dad isn't getting home til 8ish and I'd like to eat dinner with him, so hanging out before dinner works better for me. Is that okay? Do you have any ideas of places to go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:12:22 UTC">
      <body>Hey! Yeah- that'd be great. I'm in harvard square at the moment, nowhere specific in mind. Where is convenient for you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:13:20 UTC">
      <body>I could drive if there is somewhere to park but for Harvard square I could also take the t. I'm about to eat lunch so it'll probably be like an hour and a half. Where do you want to meet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:14:10 UTC">
      <body>Also it's deathly hot out so I'd rather sit inside somewhere and chill (pun sort of intended) than walk around outside</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:16:20 UTC">
      <body>Have you ever been to the thinking cup? It's a cafe near the lowes movie theater near park street</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:17:27 UTC">
      <body>Harvard is busy today for graduation. The diesel cafe in davis is really nice. Pool tables and things, and you can stay as long as you want. And i'm going to davis later anyway. Haven't heard of the thinking cup - will look it up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:17:52 UTC">
      <body>I have a slow texting phone. :-p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:19:20 UTC">
      <body>Is David on the red line? Sounds like there's more to do (pool) than the thinking cup (just a cafe)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:21:45 UTC">
      <body>Yeah- two stops after harvard. Thinking cup also looks nice though. I have a mild preference for davis because it means less travel, but either works.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:22:45 UTC">
      <body>I can meet you in Davis. I'm just eating a sandwich and then ill head out :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:24:03 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good! Where are you coming from? Ie about how long?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 19:25:04 UTC">
      <body>Near the end of the green line. I will check for parking at Elliot but ill probably end up at woodland (so...it will take at least an hour probably)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 19:28:02 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good. See you soon. :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 20:10:30 UTC">
      <body>I just got on the t. See you soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 20:11:06 UTC">
      <body>(Sorry for being late - my mom thought the family credit card was cancelled...she was wrong haha)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 20:16:19 UTC">
      <body>Glad to hear it. :-p no problem at all- just chilling in the cafe. Let me know if you have trouble finding it when you get here- it's on elm street. Also i remembered i have two coupons for free coffee or tea here, and i drink neither coffee nor tea, so they're all yours if you want.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 20:17:03 UTC">
      <body>Awesome! Thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 23:09:51 UTC">
      <body>If it's any consolation, i lost terribly twice to dan. In the first game i didn't sink a single ball until he was on the 8 ball.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 23:10:34 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha that doesn't make me feel better but it is funny :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135304" time="2013-05-30 23:18:49 UTC">
      <body>Did you end up going dumpster diving?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135080" time="2013-05-30 23:19:16 UTC">
      <body>I would've if I'd had more time :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135304" time="2013-05-31 00:03:29 UTC">
      <body>Yeah - too bad. You should check penn when you get there.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
