<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150420.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-04-20 12:05:20 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>Hi Jenny! So excited to see you these next two weeks! I'm sure I already checked with you and you likely have class or plans but just wanted to make sure you don't have any availability on Friday to watch Mads during the day. Let me know whenever! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-04-20 13:18:14 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hey Kath!! I do have a class on Friday, but let me know if you can't find anyone. I don't mind skipping it. It's easier to skip my microbio class because the lectures are recorded and posted online so I can listen to them later. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-04-20 13:28:32 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>What time is your class? I don't want to ask you to skip your class but maybe we could work around your class schedule? Originally I had planned to take the day off since Kim is away but she's sick today, Mads has her 18-month check-up tomorrow and I just think the week is going to become too crazy to take off. I can always check with my mother-in-law so there's no pressure at all! Just thought I'd check!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-04-20 13:32:28 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Oh no! Well my class is literally right in the middle of the day, 12:30. I really don't mind. Let me know. I don't have a time limit I need to know by. You can let me know Thursday if you want.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-04-20 13:48:45 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>If you really don't mind skipping, that would be such a huge help to us!! But if you want to think about it, you can let me know!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-04-20 13:49:59 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Oh please! Going to class or watching maddie? That's pretty much a no brainer (no offense to Adam).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-04-20 13:50:39 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Besides, it's not like I'm failing the class...no worries!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-04-20 13:50:51 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>You are the best, Jenny!!! Thank you so much!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-04-20 13:51:17 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>She is going to be so happy! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-04-20 13:53:05 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Me too!!!! Can't wait!
On Thursday my class ends at 9:45 so I can probably get to you around 10-1015ish. Is that okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-04-20 13:54:05 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>That's perfect!! Take your time! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-04-20 13:54:53 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Okay. So excited to see those two! I'll see you Thursday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-04-20 13:55:25 UTC" participant="154089">
      <body>We're all excited to see you!! Thank you again, Jenny. We really appreciate it! See you Thursday! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

