<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120311.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 02:51:40 UTC">
      <body>Hey dude, just got done working my third double this week and wanted to check in. I hope you're feeling peaceful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:05:56 UTC">
      <body>Hey dude, nice to hear from you. That's crazy. Your stamina is incredible. Why did you want to check in? I'm okay, if not peaceful. I hope you're peaceful too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:10:32 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I don't mean to be catty. Just haven't heard from you in a while and I legitimately get worried for you. Maybe that's out of my place but I can't help l</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:10:41 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ooking out for you Mattie </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:11:23 UTC">
      <body>I'm just trying to be casual. All is well, crazy but well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:12:03 UTC">
      <body>And hearing anything from you is the best part of my day. How's that for telling you things you don't wanna hear.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:12:24 UTC">
      <body>Ok. Well I'm glad you're well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:12:30 UTC">
      <body>Youre Making it hard to reach out to you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:13:51 UTC">
      <body>Why? Because I can't be casual? I'm trying </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:14:48 UTC">
      <body>Reach out however you can.  Please. I'm doing my best to keep it how you want it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:14:55 UTC">
      <body>These texts fall very quickly into crossing boundaries I'm trying hard to respect. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:16:08 UTC">
      <body>I want to be supportive as a friend but won't discuss us as its not productive, so if you'd like to be in contact those are the terms. If you can't do that you'll have to let me know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:17:32 UTC">
      <body>I don't know what the boundaries are. It seems like I can either have my emotions and not talk to you or pretend like I don't have feelings and talk to you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:17:58 UTC">
      <body>I'm doing the latter bc I can't do the former</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:18:12 UTC">
      <body>Anymore that is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:18:44 UTC">
      <body>OK. Well I guess I'll pretend if that's what it takes. I'd rather hear your voice than nothing at all</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 04:19:32 UTC">
      <body>Ok, I'm sorry this is uncomfortable. Im heading to bed. Have a good night </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 04:25:32 UTC">
      <body>Me too. I hope we can talk like we used to someday soon. I truly miss hearing your thoughts. Whatever they may be</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131839" time="2012-03-11 16:01:09 UTC">
      <body>I'm just trying to make sense of this in what makes me comfortable and last night didn't. We can try something else, but I reserve that right. I can't text more than this today, heading to work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:02:59 UTC">
      <body>V vchat? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:03:39 UTC">
      <body>Kidding ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:13:28 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) Ok I understand. I just hope you communicate these thoughts to me,about what makes you uncomfortable and about how we do this. Some conversations about </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:13:38 UTC">
      <body>(02/03) "us" are inevitable. It's better for you and for me. I've just heard so little from you that when I do I just get all worked up. I'm doing my best to sh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:13:48 UTC">
      <body>(03/03) ow restraint. I really want to do this right. Have a good day at work and be peaceful   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="135117" time="2012-03-11 16:14:56 UTC">
      <body>. You're a trooper! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
