<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130428.0019" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 11:52:16 UTC">
      <body>Hope finals went well and u r well on ur way towards relaxation!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 11:55:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh yes relaxing I am. Today I have a yoga date followed by local asparagus (first crop at the coop) and bacon then Little Baby's icecream. ❤</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 12:01:42 UTC">
      <body>Do you know of anyplace within about 2 hours of Brooklyn that is beautiful for hiking/walking around? I'm in charge of planning my friend Arabella's 30th birthday and I want to find something perfect for her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 17:18:56 UTC">
      <body>Good job w finals!  
Doing well. Bit sore from trail run but ok.  Clinic always puts me in good mood and reminds me how good I have it too
Not sure about places near Brooklyn. There has to be websites w that stuff.  Esp up the ny thruway near hunter mount</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 17:28:36 UTC">
      <body>Hope yoga date asparagus bacon and ice cream exceeds expectations! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 20:37:55 UTC">
      <body>I didn't know that you run, but I should have guessed. Yoga and bacon was great indeed! My friend Laura just started eating meat and had not had bacon yet! The tastiest!!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:36:01 UTC">
      <body>The smell can be swell as well   (That rhymes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 21:50:48 UTC">
      <body>Said it. Love it. Ironically I was trying to wash the bacon grease smell off my hands before leaving the house....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 21:51:01 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:54:01 UTC">
      <body>Haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:54:08 UTC">
      <body>Laura is fortunate to have a friend like u </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130962" time="2013-04-28 21:54:35 UTC">
      <body>May have helped me attract a mate though who knows.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>True. Bacon can do that. Sawdust might also. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>yess!  Open one!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131424" time="2013-04-28 21:58:22 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
