<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150301.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-01 01:01:32 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Sent proposal -- dying now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-01 11:54:40 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Hi -- I will be at ZAKTi and then I have to get started on job applications so I figured I could just come by and work at last drop/find out about New York. See you later -- unless of course you're not there so let me know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-01 12:37:23 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Sounds great. I am here but I slept maybe three hours last night. We didn't return until 2am and I begin work at 6am so I might be unable to be very productive or helpful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-01 12:38:23 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>My plan is to go home and sleep and then send that email to Jane and then do some rough draft emails for gallery proposals aka a standard email we would send to galleries letting them know about our services </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-01 12:39:23 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But I can try to tell you about New York. Rita finished her MFA at Rutgers, which has a great painting program, and I met their director </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-01 12:40:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>That was pretty nice. But Sofie was a dumb dumb and blurted the news of my pregnancy the second we walked in so of course no one cared about my career or business or even asked about what I was doing- they just wanted to talk babies </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-01 12:53:50 UTC" participant="152793">
      <body>Oh no!!! Ughh that is so frustrating. And don't worry -- I was coming by because I genuinely liked the chai latte you made me a lot and so I might as well just do work there too. I didn't mean that I needed help on applications haha! So if you're unhelpful...that is exactly what I expected. The painting director sounds cool though, I'm glad you had at least one success of the night </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

