<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130521.0046" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132555" time="2013-05-21 22:16:45 UTC">
      <body>I agree that we should be searching for something.  The interactive map idea sounds cool.  I had a few ideas as well.  1: I think it should start with us all looking at an actual paper map.  I'll then very dramatically point to a spot on the map, and then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 22:21:05 UTC">
      <body>Cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 22:21:45 UTC">
      <body>sounds doable. Maybe u are searching foe 3rd band mate??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132555" time="2013-05-21 22:42:38 UTC">
      <body>Only problem with that is, especially when you see how we look, it might make it too much like the video for Hungry Like The Wolf, by Duran Duran. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 22:48:54 UTC">
      <body>Ohok. Just throwing out ideas</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="132555" time="2013-05-21 22:57:18 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, it's a good idea. I just think it might come across as too similar to that particular video.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 23:01:53 UTC">
      <body>my friend suggested we try some third person first person stuff...likenom filming u film an expedition maybe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132555" time="2013-05-21 23:05:10 UTC">
      <body>So like filming from the actor's perspective? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 23:18:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah maybe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130747" time="2013-05-21 23:49:49 UTC">
      <body>Just thoughts. In that Duran Duran video there are safari guys in the city??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132555" time="2013-05-22 00:14:55 UTC">
      <body>It's all set in Sri Lanka.  Some of it in a town/city, other parts in a wilderness setting.  The singer has a bit of a safari look going.  The rest of the band is looking for the singer, and they find him in the end.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130747" time="2013-05-22 00:15:29 UTC">
      <body>Yeah sounds cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="132555" time="2013-05-22 00:23:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, it's definitely one of the inspirations for this video idea, so I want to be careful to not rip off their concept too much.  But I think this is different.  My song is about the reliance on technology, and uses the wild as a metaphor for simply not </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130747" time="2013-05-22 00:29:50 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I still haven't listened. Been so busy. Have to check it out asap</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
