<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150321.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-21 14:24:00 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>Are you busy today? And have you had your MMR shot?  We're having a little party with just my parents My inlaws, James' best friend and my sister I know it's really short notice- but do you want to come?  It starts at 2:30</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-21 14:26:08 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>I'm sorry I have been so absorbed in mommydom that I have been terrible about keeping in touch</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-21 14:30:24 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>It's Lillian's first birthday today!  If not no worries -  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-21 17:03:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Omg YES I want to come!!!! I have a meeting at 4 so I can only stop by for a bit but I absolutely want to meet her!!! You are totally allowed to be in mommydom and GUESS WHAT Alec and I are expecting a kid too! I was going to call you today to tell you; we haven't told many people! I'll be there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-21 17:04:58 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼Lillian will be a year and a half older so maybe they can play together in a few years!!??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-21 17:04:59 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yay happy first birthday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-21 17:05:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>What is your address again?!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-21 17:06:36 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(Ps if this is too late of a response from me it is ok! I left my phone in the car so I just saw the text now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-21 17:17:54 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>Oh my God! How wonderful!  Congratulations! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-21 17:21:56 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>It's over at 4:30- so Let's just decide on a time to meet up instead-  I'm so happy you!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-21 17:22:00 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body>Lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-21 17:22:20 UTC" participant="152748">
      <body> I meant I am so happy for you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-21 17:47:04 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha yayayay! Yes, let's meet up. Tell me when and I'll drive to you and maybe we can get lunch. See you soon. Tell Lillian happy bday!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

