<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120901.0018" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2012-09-01 01:17:31 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>You're getting a tattoo?! ...it's not of Olivia Munn, is it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2012-09-01 01:18:25 UTC" participant="152378">
      <body>Haha no but...  And please dont judge but it actually has a line from newsroom... I know i know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2012-09-01 01:22:46 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Are you on a mission to civilize?  ;-) Just be careful with writing, it's really, really hard to do well. I'm sure you're going to someone good though   :-)  I will look forward to welcoming you to the inked club!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2012-09-01 01:46:26 UTC" participant="152378">
      <body>(1/2)No but that was a greta line as well. I don't want to spoil it, but you'll recognize it right away. It's corny but I really liked it. As far the skill</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2012-09-01 01:46:31 UTC" participant="152378">
      <body>(2/2)level... I guess we'll wait and see. Fingers crossed :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2012-09-01 01:50:38 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Let me know how it goes! If you need backup, I can call the crazy (but crazily talented) Russian artist at my shop. he's done so much work for my sister &amp; her husband that he came to their wedding, I kid you not. Anyway, good luck! I'm really excited for you  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2012-09-01 01:53:04 UTC" participant="152378">
      <body>no more crazy russians dammit :) I'll let you know how it goes and if I need someone to hold my hand when I go bac kto get it colored</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2012-09-01 01:55:20 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Deal. I even promise not to laugh if the pain bothers you. But I'm sure you'll be fine. In my experience it's really not bad at all. And totally worth it!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

