<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130616.0019" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:13:36 UTC">
      <body>Do I just respond to this text?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:17:10 UTC">
      <body>hello! How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:18:26 UTC">
      <body>I'm good. How are you doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:26:53 UTC">
      <body>I haven't had much luck actually having a text conversation with the others who signed up because they don't really answer!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:26:53 UTC">
      <body>I'm from Philly, and my mom used to work for the ldc language lab.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:26:53 UTC">
      <body>Great! I'm fine too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:26:53 UTC">
      <body>My family went out after church for a fathers day lunch. How's your day going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:28:09 UTC">
      <body>Just spending most of it online. I'm from NYC. I'm looking for a room today.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:30:31 UTC">
      <body>What denomination church?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:31:23 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay. So you're moving to another state or still within NYC? I bet there's a community group on Facebook that has postings for open rooms. I lived indc for years and used a Catholic fb housing group.,</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:31:45 UTC">
      <body>Oh, Catholic. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:33:11 UTC">
      <body>That's cool. I went to Catholic School Ferron k to 12. I don't really subscribe to religion though. I'm looking to stay in nyc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:39:22 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay. I hope you are able to find a place soon. I love being Catholic and just finished a masters in theology at a pontifical university in dc. Actually one of my good friends is the associate chaplain at nyu and he is going to be the celebrant for my wedding this November. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:41:20 UTC">
      <body>That's pretty cool. Congrats on the whole marriage thing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 15:45:00 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! Can I ask what you do in ny?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 15:54:16 UTC">
      <body>I have two jobs. I'm a personal assistant and I also work at a frozen yogurt place.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:00:27 UTC">
      <body>Nice. I bet your frozen yogurt place gets really busy in the summer! I'll be visiting ny to see my priest friend in August with my fiance. Apparently, Ihave to try 4 diff pizza places that he likes there...in the one day we'll be there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:02:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah most of the summer jobs here are all in ice cream and frozen yogurt places. I try not to have too much dairy and gluten. It's not good for the body.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:07:31 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. I remember hearing abt this "fun run 5k" or something in which after each lap, the runner needs to drink a glass of milk haha. That sounds like a drunk college idea.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:07:53 UTC">
      <body>... Probably not too fun.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:09:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's gross. The bacteria builds up and you puke. Plus the stomach only holds about 32 ounces.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:13:12 UTC">
      <body>Yup. :( my dad is actually a marathoner and he ran his first ultramarathon this year. 31 miles for that one! He's already past mid-fifties but his goal is to run marathons in as many states as possible!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:13:58 UTC">
      <body>I'm not a runner though, I get distracted by nature haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:14:50 UTC">
      <body>My boyfriend wants to do a triathlon next year. He's kind of intense.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:19:34 UTC">
      <body>That's amazing. And yeah, intense. Last year for the dc triathlon, it rained hard right before, so they cancelled the swimming part bc overflow if wasteinto the Potomac. :( I was a live in nanny then for a family, and the mom was going to do the swimming part so she was disappointed.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:19:34 UTC">
      <body>Is the triathlon your boyfriend doing in ny?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:20:27 UTC">
      <body>It's in hawaii.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:22:14 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow, that sounds like an ideal place for a triathlon.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:26:58 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm excited for him.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:30:15 UTC">
      <body>I've never been to Hawaii, but as for the tropics, my family's from the Philippines, so we've visited our family a few times.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:31:09 UTC">
      <body>I'm not too into humid weather. I prefer the desert. Nevada is awesome.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:43:17 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah, humidity gets harsh there! The first time I've ever experienced a non-humid but sunny environment was when I visited Denver. I've never been toNevada though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:43:17 UTC">
      <body>What cities did you stay in when you went to Nevada?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:44:51 UTC">
      <body>Las Vegas. I really liked St. Louis, Missouri too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 16:54:42 UTC">
      <body>Oohh I'd like to visit st Louis someday. I have some friends who are in monasteries in st Louis. I bet the food is awesome too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 16:56:15 UTC">
      <body>I was all about the night life when I went.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 17:07:54 UTC">
      <body>I bet it's pretty lively. I'm looking to live in the south after a few more years in dc. Hopefully somewhere in Texas where my fiance's from, but prob Au</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 17:17:04 UTC">
      <body>stin, TX.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 17:17:04 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure if I would leave nyc. Every time I get the idea something pops up and I end up staying.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 17:23:56 UTC">
      <body>Haha, the universe is telling you to stay. Are you originally from NYC?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="132979" time="2013-06-16 17:24:34 UTC">
      <body>Yeah from Queens.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130798" time="2013-06-16 17:29:45 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay. I have to go for now. On my way to a goodbye dinner with another family whose child I cared for. Nice chatting with you! Hope you find a room soon!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
