<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140726.0017" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-26 00:00:00 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Want to grab dinner tomorrow night? Steph is working but we could go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-26 00:05:08 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I would but I'm going to baltimore for the weekend.  Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday, sat or Sunday next week would work. We could also grill up something at my place if you wanted. Im low on cash but I can go out somewhere if it's not too expensive</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-26 00:08:11 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I quit working so I could make some new art, and then I got nailed by the IRS and they decimated my savings</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-26 00:10:52 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I really don't mean to keep dodging you. I'm sorry I'm being so difficult</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-26 00:12:10 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>It's cool. Life is busy. I understand. Maybe Friday night. I'll talk to Steph and get back to you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-26 00:12:31 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>If your not working Sunday, and you want a quick vacation, you could come to baltimore with me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-26 00:13:24 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>I'm going to stay here. Steph has been out of town all week so I haven't seen her. She's working tonight and tomorrow night. We are planning on hanging out Sunday for the first time all week </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-26 00:14:29 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>I'll let you know about Friday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-26 00:14:37 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok thanks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-26 00:19:57 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I'm really trying to channel my wizardry into making my life not busy, but money is always a factor. I know that's not in the cards for you, but I am striving to carve out a situation where I can make my art and not destroy my body doing manual labor for the rest of my life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-26 00:22:43 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>It's understandable. I've been out rollerblading a lot lately (both at the park and rec skating) and I've come to realize that my body isn't what it used to be.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-26 00:23:28 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>I want to get the piece of art that you made that is a circular piece of paper</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-07-26 00:24:13 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Man I have fantasies about skating every time I bike past the new park by the museum on the way to the classes that I'm taking at Moore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-07-26 00:24:43 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I never see people rollerblading</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-07-26 00:25:21 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Yeah. It's still fun, but I wear pads and take it super easy. My trick repertoire is really limited. There's a group of people that rollerblade every Tuesday night </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-07-26 00:25:36 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>I just can't afford to get hurt anymore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-07-26 00:27:49 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I don't have skates anymore or I would at least exercise the thought of doing it. Yeah my insurance is getting cancelled in August because of some beuracratic nonsense so I got to be careful</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-07-26 00:29:46 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Yeah. I went 3 months without insurance before I started this job. I've never been so careful in my life </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-07-26 00:30:59 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I went 7 years without it and only had it for maybe 4 months</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-07-26 00:32:00 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Are you looking for a new job now or do you have other plans? What are you going to school for?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-07-26 00:36:05 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>But luckily I never really needed it til my hands started giving out. I'm applying for teaching positions now. I'm thinking about moving back down south if I can get a teaching job somewhere. In the meantime I'm trying to get a teaching job here but it's really competitive. I've got some income from my room mates but it's not quite enough to keep me fully afloat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-07-26 00:36:16 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>It's super cheap down south</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-07-26 00:36:16 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Where would you go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-07-26 00:39:59 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah I wanna get land and build something semi-off grid if I sell my house and make enough profit. I'm pretty open to where I would go but it would need to be driving distance to a school with an art program. I'm taking classes on Adobe photoshop and illustrator</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-07-26 00:44:14 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I honestly would like to move to the foothills of SC or around Asheville NC. Not Easley but maybe Pickens, liberty or somewhere rural near there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-07-26 00:49:49 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>Yeah. I would hate to go back to Easley </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-07-26 00:53:13 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I'll bet after a few years in rural south I will be dying to move back to a big city but I'm over it now. There is no privacy and the city is so corrupt. I wanna grow my food and have some space to hunt and rip around</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-07-26 01:17:09 UTC" participant="153599">
      <body>There are definitely shitty things about city life. I think I would be alright being close to a big city. Once we have kids, I'm sure the city will get old fast</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

