<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130419.0023" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 23:27:00 UTC">
      <body>Can I spend the night with you again on Sunday May 26? I'm coming up early that morning for study group then hoping to spend the night and head home Monday afternoon. Monday is Memorial Day btw, if that makes a difference...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-04-19 23:29:49 UTC">
      <body>How was your test? I had my last day with Rolly Brown today. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:39:01 UTC">
      <body>My test went well. Im having the come parts.and kinda depressed. I think I'm just tired and wish I had a partner today. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:40:09 UTC">
      <body>My best friend had top surgery on Wednesday and I've been there on and off since then. Its been hard emotionally I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:40:28 UTC">
      <body>You can stay for sure...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:40:56 UTC">
      <body>Isn't Laura coming around then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-04-20 16:52:55 UTC">
      <body>I know that I wish I had a partner feeling all too well. Someone to lie in bed with or to make you lunch. It's hard to know sometimes why you are alone when you are alone. I wonder about that alot. I think I am still a little stuck to my last boyfriend Ja</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-04-20 16:55:28 UTC">
      <body>Thank you for housing me once again. I love your room. It's like a unicorn den! That is when Laura will be there. The study group is the 21-26 and I am coming up for Sunday in the wee hours of the morning to have a day with the study group then I get to s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:56:37 UTC">
      <body>Yes...oh, she said she knew already and is looking very plucky</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-04-20 16:57:11 UTC">
      <body>I hope your friend is doing well. Will you call me if you need me or just want to talk?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-04-20 16:57:40 UTC">
      <body>Earth is so perceptive. I bought the ticket awhile ago. I got a $1 fare!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131432" time="2013-04-20 16:58:13 UTC">
      <body>I will call. Will see what sleep and lunch do for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-04-20 18:31:14 UTC">
      <body>Good. I'm also about to sleep, having just lunched. Yoga sometimes feels great and sometimes makes me dizzy since I am always low on blood.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
