<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130722.0026" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137257" time="2013-07-22 17:20:42 UTC">
      <body>I need to pick up 3 things from my room. I'd lik to pass by in about 10 minutes. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="132437" time="2013-07-22 17:25:05 UTC">
      <body>I am by the airport. Coming back at night.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137257" time="2013-07-22 17:29:11 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="137257" time="2013-07-22 20:09:36 UTC">
      <body>The FMCU account has only $10. I will try to deposit $200 from Wells Fargo unless u object. First Vassar payment was deducted today of $211. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="132437" time="2013-07-22 20:12:53 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137257" time="2013-07-22 20:33:04 UTC">
      <body>When will u be back at the house. I'll be visiting with them until then. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="132437" time="2013-07-22 20:38:55 UTC">
      <body>About 9:30. Not sure of traffic. I will call when I am about an hour away from home.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 01:27:40 UTC">
      <body>Will be in Swarthmore in 50</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 01:27:53 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 03:35:53 UTC">
      <body>I went all the way to giant landsdowne yesterday to fill up with cheap gas and found out that it only works with your bonus card. since we got a new one for me it has a separate no....I am not using the car tomorrow and the coupon expires on Wednesday. You might want to use your bonus card to fill up any of the three cars. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 03:38:03 UTC">
      <body>Also we need to do the 'separation agreement' or whatever it is called ASAP. I am very busy tomorrow but I will look into the logistics of it on Wednesday and will let you know...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 03:39:05 UTC">
      <body>Please do not text me after 10 pm unless it is urgent. Thanks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 03:39:21 UTC">
      <body>I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 03:39:31 UTC">
      <body>*k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:10:56 UTC">
      <body>Could you please tell me How many points is your gas reward? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:14:17 UTC">
      <body>100. And it is not mine. It only works with your card.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:17:13 UTC">
      <body>That will save only 10 cents a gallon. I'd be happy to drop off my card if u want to use it. I don't have the time to go lansdowne. I read that some shell stations also give the discount but I don't if there is one near us participating. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Regarding the separation agreement. Please contact joe and don to see if the lsa has a particular format.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:19:44 UTC">
      <body>The discount is ten cents per hundred points so u must have had lots. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:20:11 UTC">
      <body>You are right. That is what it says on the coupon. But how strange because last time I used the coupon (months ago) I filled up the car with $3! Yes, it is not worth the trip at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:22:05 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:24:14 UTC">
      <body>I am not sure about asking the LSA. They have no legal authority except for marriage documents. At least that is what I understand.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:25:24 UTC">
      <body>You could ask them if a lawyer is needed. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:25:52 UTC">
      <body>I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:26:00 UTC">
      <body>*k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 14:57:48 UTC">
      <body>Joe says we need a lawyer. And that there are online resources.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 14:59:34 UTC">
      <body>I think it is better that you pursue that issue. I am ready to read and consult about the terms once you have a rough draft. As for getting a lawyer we simply don't have the money unless you have </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 15:01:40 UTC">
      <body>Other sources. On that topic we probably will have have not enough money to cover incoming bills in August after we pay th aug 1 mortgage. It all depends on how much unemployment i will get. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 15:01:55 UTC">
      <body>I'll look into it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 15:47:12 UTC">
      <body>You need to sign the amended return. Please let me know how u want to do that. It is easiest if I just wait on the porch because I have to mail the hard copy. Are Lua and reed here today. If so we can do this tomorrow. There will be an additional $555 but it won't be processed for 8-12 weeks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 15:50:36 UTC">
      <body>No Lua and Reed. I am at Penn already. If you could put it on the entrance table I will sign it. How do you want it back?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 15:51:28 UTC">
      <body>Easier way: after you sign just put it in the mailbox at the post office. I will prepare the envelope. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 15:53:29 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 15:55:44 UTC">
      <body>I don't have the kids ss numbers with me here at McCabe. Do u have them at the house where I can find them easily? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 15:58:53 UTC">
      <body>I have them on my iPhone. Should I send them as text or email?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 16:00:38 UTC">
      <body>I'm checking online</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 16:01:49 UTC">
      <body>I am going into my appointment right now. Cannot text till 1:10</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 16:02:49 UTC">
      <body>I'll leave a note to remind you to enter the numbers. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 16:21:20 UTC">
      <body>Before I forget. I suggest u transfer Sorayas $500 into the checking ASAP. I put $200 in yesterday and it is down to 0 already. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 17:13:59 UTC">
      <body>It turned out that she didn't have a full $1000 in her account. That was my mistake. She had $650 in awards and about $250 in gifts. Last time I check she had 300 and some. If you still think you want to take it from her I suggest that you ask her for it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 17:25:20 UTC">
      <body>I don't want to take anything from her. Please be careful how you phrase your ideas. The point here is that we have 0 in the checking and deductions are being made meaning we will be charged $30 or so for each deduction. I raise this issue so we can find the best solution. Another option is to transfer more from the Fargo account. If you agree to that please let me know how much so I can do it ASAP. We have only $300 in there now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 17:33:49 UTC">
      <body>I'll be at the house from 1:45 for about 10 minutes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 17:46:54 UTC">
      <body>I thought you had transferred all from Wells Fargo already. You might as well transfer 200. And we should not use the card at all until further notice. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 17:48:02 UTC">
      <body>I haven't been using the card except when I returned shampoo and then bought the same amount yesterday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 17:48:33 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="137257" time="2013-07-23 17:48:48 UTC">
      <body>I'll transfer 200 ASAP. I am leaving the house and the tax form is on red chest. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="132437" time="2013-07-23 17:49:08 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 12:15:59 UTC">
      <body>Recycling needs to be at the sidewalk by 8:45 this morning. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 12:16:32 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:27:00 UTC">
      <body>Are u going to be out if the house any time this afternoon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 18:27:13 UTC">
      <body>No</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:27:55 UTC">
      <body>Did the tax form get mailed?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 18:28:09 UTC">
      <body>Not yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:28:42 UTC">
      <body>Did you fill in the ss numbers and sign it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 18:29:19 UTC">
      <body>Yes. And Soraya is going to mail it in a few minutes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:29:20 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:34:33 UTC">
      <body>I will need time at the house to see the kids and work on my papers. When is a good tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 18:46:35 UTC">
      <body>I have homework and I need to be home a lot. We will need to come to a more structured agreement. I am working on a separation document, but it needs some time. At least another week. Meanwhile we need to make arrangements. Play it by ear does not work for me. About seeing the kids I suggest that for now (until we write things down) you should contact them directly and arrange to see them elsewhere. About the packing, I suggest that you come up with a deadline by which you will finish the packing (for one year). Also come up with how many times you need to come in to do that. And an approximate duration for the visits. This way we can make a schedule ahead of time. I don't want to be pressured to leave the house last minute. If there is a schedule it will be much easier.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:54:35 UTC">
      <body>I agree with having a more structured arrangement. Until such an arrangement is made I would ask that you be flexible since I was the one who moved. I think by next week an arrangement can be made. The sooner the better for me actually. Once a schedule is made there will be no need for me to make a packing schedule since I could take things during each visit. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 18:56:05 UTC">
      <body>It sounds like you are denying me access to the house and kids until a separation agreement has been settled. If that is what you intend I would disagree with that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:00:09 UTC">
      <body>I still need to come some time tomorrow to check in with the kids and collect some documents. Could you please review and see if you will be out of the house for shopping or other activities. I prefer to come in late afternoon since the kids are not awake until after 1 or even 3 pm. Please also remember that both parties cannot avoid inconvenience. I have no Internet and am trying to complete my own work using the libraries. It is only reasonable that share the inconvenience for the sake if giving both parties access to house and kids. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 19:03:47 UTC">
      <body>I am not denying you access to the kids. You can see them elsewhere anytime you want. You can also see them in the house when you come to pack. All I am asking is that if you need to pack BEFORE the separation agreement is done then we need a packing schedule until further notice. For example a schedule for the coming ten days. Next Tuesday I will at Penn from 1-9 for example.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:18:24 UTC">
      <body>I will come over on Tuesday from 1-3 that is good. After that I have to leave for strayer. But again only Doda is awake at that time. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:18:24 UTC">
      <body>Seeing the kids outside the house is not practical at this time but I don't want to discuss that now.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:20:32 UTC">
      <body>I was not pressuring you to leave the house at the last minute. That is why I asked you about tomorrow afternoon. So here is my suggested packing schedule: Thursday (tomorrow) through Monday 3-5 pm and then tues 1-3. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 19:51:48 UTC">
      <body>Today I started working on Kofi so that he wakes up earlier. I am assuming that you will find a way to see the children outside the house soon. The whole point of separation is for you not to be around me and my dwelling place all the time. Because everything about you makes me extremely nervous.  About the proposed schedule I will have to look at mine and let you know. What about the deadline? When are going to finish packing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:53:59 UTC">
      <body>Excuse me but we did not consult about a deadline. You suggested it.  Also that is not the whole point if the year of waiting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:56:18 UTC">
      <body>You are in the habit if greatly exaggerating everything. I did not ask to be around the house all the time. I asked to be with my children at the house from 3 to 5 only from tomorrow through Monday. I am flexible about those days and times.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 19:58:54 UTC">
      <body>And the same principle applies to you. You can do your studies outside the house just as I a doing. As I said before we both need to bear the burden of inconvenience and to try to be fair about this.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 20:07:28 UTC">
      <body>I'm on my way to moms and will respond later </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 20:24:32 UTC">
      <body>Anyway, is tomorrow from 3-5 good?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 20:30:16 UTC">
      <body>I will let you know later tonight about tomorrow. But Friday through Monday is not good at all. I want to be free to study. Maybe I can let go of one afternoon to take a break. But right now I don't know which day is good. Will let you know tonight. And please think of a deadline or talk to Joe. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 20:32:50 UTC">
      <body>I am already scheduled to meet with PAC next Wednesday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 20:33:20 UTC">
      <body>Great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 20:35:12 UTC">
      <body>"Without an end in sight". Again I point out the exaggeration since I specified from tomorrow through Monday of this coming week. That is a limited set of days. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 20:37:27 UTC">
      <body>What I meant is that you refused to give a deadline. Which means that it is very possible you will ask again and again for similar schedules. I can't read your mind. When you don't give a deadline I have to assume it is open ended.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 20:39:06 UTC">
      <body>We are to consult. It is not right for one party to assume the other must agree with his or her suggestions. I don't know if I agree with deadline in this case especially since I should be able to visit the kids when u are out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 20:46:50 UTC">
      <body>Why do you assume that you SHOULD be able to visit them when I am out??? We never agreed on that and I am certainly not wanting that. I don't know if it is negotiable. Talk to PAC about it on Wednesday. From my point of view I am entitled to sole custody and I am doing you a favor by letting you see them at all. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 21:17:45 UTC">
      <body>Tomorrow is good from 3:30-5:30. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="132437" time="2013-07-24 21:18:35 UTC">
      <body>I am still figuring out a time for you to come on the weekend. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="137257" time="2013-07-24 21:20:00 UTC">
      <body>Thanks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 15:29:02 UTC">
      <body>I've spent all morning on the phone dealing with Soraya's health insurance and it is still not resolved...now I am taking Kofi to the Ortho. I need to spend all my time studying this weekend. I can't promise I will be able to leave the house. If I do it will be to run a short errand or go for a short walk whenever I feel like it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 15:30:02 UTC">
      <body>By weekend I meant  Friday and Monday included. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 16:26:07 UTC">
      <body>BMC just called: me and the kids will be covered for ten months instead of 9 starting aug 1st. But I won't have the info (policy no and such) until I sign the new contract etc. will send you the info once I get it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:27:44 UTC">
      <body>Wong I be covered too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:29:30 UTC">
      <body>*wont </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:38:47 UTC">
      <body>Please respond. Will I be covered by your bmc policy?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 16:39:57 UTC">
      <body>I was driving. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:40:13 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 16:41:48 UTC">
      <body>Remember we had talked about it couple of weeks ago and it is going to be an extra $400 a month to add you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:44:48 UTC">
      <body>I remember now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:47:51 UTC">
      <body>As soon as I get the bmc policy number I will complete the vassar waiver online and that will be settled.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 16:48:05 UTC">
      <body>Great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 16:49:04 UTC">
      <body>Just for your records. The vassar waiver deadline is aug 15 or 16  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 16:50:26 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 17:01:31 UTC">
      <body>It's doda I'm gonna call you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 17:01:52 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 17:17:02 UTC">
      <body>Does your pay check actually show up on the 31st. i.e. when can we withdraw cash morning of 31 or 1?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 17:18:47 UTC">
      <body>I can't say for sure. It varies.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 17:19:07 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 18:43:23 UTC">
      <body>I am working with the congressman's office to hopefully cover Soraya's emergency room bill. If you have any documents that might help such as our lower summer income, whatsoever you can think of, could you please email them to me. I told her I will email her stuff tomorrow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 19:24:48 UTC">
      <body>K </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 19:55:51 UTC">
      <body>I would like to remove the bolts from Kofi and Dora's doors so it will be easier to wake them and for safety reasons. Do u agree?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 20:06:55 UTC">
      <body>I suggest that we keep things as they are for now. In my opinion much change for the boys is too detrimental at this point. Too early. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" participant="137257" time="2013-07-25 20:09:36 UTC">
      <body>Kofi is still asleep after 4. This is something we will need to consult about. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 20:13:31 UTC">
      <body>I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" participant="132437" time="2013-07-25 20:13:38 UTC">
      <body>*k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 00:17:41 UTC">
      <body>Kofi was not sleeping till 4pm. He fell asleep at around 3 because his teeth were hurting him a lot and had taken painkillers.  Also he had not slept at all last night. He has terrible insomnia. I need some time to work on it with him. It is just that a lot is going on and this matter is not life threatening. Otherwise he is doing very well. He is as happy as ever and has come out of his shell a bit.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 00:39:07 UTC">
      <body>Are you going to be able to send me tomorrow any documents regarding our financial hardship for the benefit of the congressman....and the CHIP issue?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 00:39:50 UTC">
      <body>Yes I already put it on my schedule</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 00:40:17 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I did not remember the earlier "k"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 13:51:12 UTC">
      <body>We need to figure out the mail situation. I will leave your mail in the mailbox today and tomorrow. I suggest that you have your mail forwarded automatically. If you have not done so already. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 13:55:31 UTC">
      <body>We will need to consult about that and the house in general. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 14:03:52 UTC">
      <body>What do you mean?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 14:17:50 UTC">
      <body>According to bahai law we have to establish separate residences during the year of waiting. The house is legal yours and mine. I can't sell it or modify it by myself etc. but that doesn't mean that it is your residence during this period. Please explain if you understand it differently. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 14:19:44 UTC">
      <body>It is your residence and you are entitled to your privacy. But there are many issues involved here that I think require consultation. Not only the house but the children etc. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 14:23:31 UTC">
      <body>What are the issues? Could you specify? And what about the children? What needs consultation other than visitation times and the occasional issues that need the consent of both parents? Please be more specific. And I don't understand what all of these things that you are bringing up have anything to do with your mail?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 14:24:53 UTC">
      <body>I don't think all of my concerns can be addressed via text. I think we need to have a proper bahai consultation with a mediator. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 14:25:40 UTC">
      <body>You still did not answer the question about mail.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 14:26:32 UTC">
      <body>Yes I will definitely have the mail forwarded. Thanks for reminding me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 17:19:47 UTC">
      <body>I am assuming you are taking the boys to the theater with our car. That is great, but I am wondering if you could let me know in advance so that I don't plan anything for that time...until we can figure out an easier arrangement for the car. I found out by accident from Shenandoah just now. I  don't need the car today. Thanks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 17:21:04 UTC">
      <body>I will be using moms car. That is why I didn't mention it to you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 17:21:04 UTC">
      <body>But I do appreciate your willingness to consult about sharing the Mazda. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 17:21:31 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 17:23:41 UTC">
      <body>I have assumed all along that we are going to share it. I even remember something about that in the initial separation meeting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 17:25:20 UTC">
      <body>I just forwarded an important email from vassar financial aid. Soraya has to go online and complete two documents. The first one is a promissory note and she may need your help. The second is an informational site that is required. I would like her to complete this today so we don't have to worry about her losing her aid.  I will call her now about. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 17:25:20 UTC">
      <body>Is Soraya at home now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 17:26:25 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 17:27:37 UTC">
      <body>Yes. She is in the shower.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 17:27:43 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 19:02:16 UTC">
      <body>I think Kofi is not doing well because he is bored to death. He has been like this since the beginning of the summer. It is just getting worse. He has no motivation and no friends. When he is awake he is fine. He talks and sings and cooks and practices. I am scratching my brain for ideas for him. Let me know if you can think of something. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" participant="137257" time="2013-07-26 19:03:28 UTC">
      <body>I will. And I'll talk at the movie. I did the address change </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" participant="132437" time="2013-07-26 19:04:24 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0142" participant="132437" time="2013-07-27 00:30:26 UTC">
      <body>The boys forgot to give you your mail. Could you remember to ask them to bring it to you when you drop them off. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0143" participant="132437" time="2013-07-27 02:33:43 UTC">
      <body>Also the $360 that I withdrew last week is almost all gone. Shenandoah eats three peaches at one time. He eats a whole melon by himself in one sitting and he is always saying he is hungry. I had to put gas in the car to drive up to EWR and it is all gone. So $360 was only gas and food and it did not last very long!!! What do we do? We still have four days to go. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0144" participant="137257" time="2013-07-27 03:16:16 UTC">
      <body>I don't know. Maybe tomorrow an idea. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0146" participant="132437" time="2013-07-27 03:27:25 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0147" participant="132437" time="2013-07-27 15:44:39 UTC">
      <body>Any ideas about $? I have to go grocery shopping today.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0148" participant="137257" time="2013-07-27 15:45:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm at work will reply soon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0149" participant="137257" time="2013-07-27 16:44:48 UTC">
      <body>Could you withdraw $50 from FMCU and make do with that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0150" participant="132437" time="2013-07-27 16:45:26 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0151" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 13:24:16 UTC">
      <body>Are u going to be out of the house any time today? I need to pick up a few things 15 minutes. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0152" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 13:31:01 UTC">
      <body>This making me very nervous. We really need to set up a deadline for the packing. And how many more times you need to come to 108. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0153" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 13:35:45 UTC">
      <body>The problem is I don't have much space here at all and I'm still trying to get reoriented  it is very difficult to plan what I need and when especially with changing seasons etc. if we had a lot if storage here it would be very easy. There is space that can be used but I need time to figure out how to use it. Also I don't yet know where to put the filing cabinet and some other bulky things. For now I need 15 minutes today. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0154" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 13:38:34 UTC">
      <body>In that case could you give me a date by which we could come up with a deadline. i.e. deadline of a deadline </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0155" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 13:41:20 UTC">
      <body>I don't know if it makes sense for me to commit to a deadline. I could say that by September 1 I could have most of the stuff I need out but I do not want to commit to a deadline in the sense that after that date I have no right to come and get anything else I might have forgotten. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0156" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 13:47:43 UTC">
      <body>Well we can make provisions for that. For example, I could always send it to you whatever it is. Or alternatively we could agree on a number of times in which you could come for that reason after the deadline. It is the open endedness that does not work for me. Another five weeks of you coming and going is too long for me. Could you think of a closer date than sep 1? And it y</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0157" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 13:48:28 UTC">
      <body>And if your final word is that you cannot commit to anything. Then I have to consult with experts about this.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0158" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 13:54:08 UTC">
      <body>Of course I am obliged to obey whatever is the civil law. On the other hand we are also obliged to follow the principles of consultation which is not possible for me by text. So I propose that we consult properly with a bahai mediator with whom both of us are comfortable. I will ask the PAC about this in Wednesday. Definitely I agree that having stuff sent over by the kids is a good idea. It is just that I have many books and files and other papers and most of that they won't be able to sort through and we don't have space for it here. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0159" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 13:56:16 UTC">
      <body>In the meantime could you please let me stop by for 15 minutes so I can move forward with my chores for today.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0160" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:00:19 UTC">
      <body>You could come in today, but I just got settled down to study. I don't know when I will need a break. I will let you know. I really hope you are not going to ask for this every other day until we reach an agreement (soon). I want this to be resolved by the end of this coming week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0161" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:01:15 UTC">
      <body>I am very willing to sit down with a mediator any time this Coming week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0162" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:02:03 UTC">
      <body>Also if you are not needing the car on Wednesday from about 6 pm I will use it. Please let me know.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0163" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:02:54 UTC">
      <body>I don't need the car on Wednesday after 6pm.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0164" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:03:14 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0165" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:04:12 UTC">
      <body>Please could you arrange for a mediator yourself because as far as I am concerned we don't need one for the packing issue.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0166" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:06:20 UTC">
      <body>I will be happy to but I thought you would want to have a say about who it is. And again I think the principle here at least for me is that we need to consult about everything. Or another way to put it is that if one party wants to consult the othe should agree to do so. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0167" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:08:54 UTC">
      <body>I am agreeing to consult but only because you feel you need to. Somethings are straight forward for me and I don't see the point of mediation. It is a waste of time. But again if it is a complicated matter for you I don't have a choice but to participate. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0168" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:11:05 UTC">
      <body>And about who the mediator will be I will leave it to you. If you come up with someone completely unsuitable to me then you can always ask someone else.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0169" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:11:12 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0170" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:24:00 UTC">
      <body>On the other hand one party cannot push or force the other to consult. It has to be something both sincerely want to do. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0171" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:26:39 UTC">
      <body>I have no problem with consultation in itself. It is just that I don't believe that it is suitable for all and every situation. Sometimes it is not needed. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0172" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Great thanks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0173" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:45:21 UTC">
      <body>I  going to go for a walk from 11-11:45.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0174" participant="137257" time="2013-07-28 14:47:28 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0175" participant="132437" time="2013-07-28 14:47:43 UTC">
      <body>You have mail from last week. It is on the red chest </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0176" participant="137257" time="2013-07-29 13:28:17 UTC">
      <body>Do u have any objections if I spend time with the kids at the house tomorrow 1-4 pm?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0177" participant="132437" time="2013-07-29 13:29:56 UTC">
      <body>I thought we had agreed on Tuesday afternoon already. I was expecting you to do that since last week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0178" participant="137257" time="2013-07-29 13:30:22 UTC">
      <body>Great </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0179" participant="132437" time="2013-07-29 19:51:06 UTC">
      <body>About tomorrow, please try to move things as much/many as you can keeping in mind that you are not going to come to 108 too many more times. You have already packed stuff during at least 6 visits. It is not reasonable to ask for many more. Also please come up with a deadline about the packing ASAP. Maybe after your PAC meeting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0180" participant="137257" time="2013-07-29 19:52:32 UTC">
      <body> I will talk with PAC about these points. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0181" participant="137257" time="2013-07-29 19:52:32 UTC">
      <body>Please do not text me until I contact u on Thursday - unless there is something urgent. Thanks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0182" participant="132437" time="2013-07-29 19:54:27 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0183" participant="132437" time="2013-07-30 15:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Did you recently change the ID or password of our Fmfcu account?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0184" participant="137257" time="2013-07-30 15:15:51 UTC">
      <body>No</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0185" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 14:08:35 UTC">
      <body>I can't access out bank account. I need to buy groceries for today and I have no idea what is going on. If there is no money in the bank and your paycheck has not come in yet, I will have to go and sell the gold bracelet. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0187" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 14:11:12 UTC">
      <body>S for your town </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0188" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 15:28:00 UTC">
      <body>The pay heck has cleared. There is $639. I am calling FMCU to see if we can delay payment for the big loan due aug 5. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0189" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 15:30:15 UTC">
      <body>I will withdraw $130 for the 2 weeks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0190" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 15:31:01 UTC">
      <body>FMCU says they will have someone call me about my request to defer the aug and sep payments. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0191" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 15:38:40 UTC">
      <body>The FMCU pword was set on may 7 according to  the most recent email I have on that topic. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0192" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 15:40:48 UTC">
      <body>Correction the current balance is 693 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0193" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:10:20 UTC">
      <body>I am worried about all the other automatic payments. I don't think that 580 will cover them. And what about daily? What about mortgage? AT&amp;T due aug 15?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0194" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:11:53 UTC">
      <body>I just spoke with Wells Fargo told them there is a delay until unemployment check comes in they said fine and they will call me again next Monday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0195" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:13:58 UTC">
      <body>About AT&amp;T we don't have money for that  my suggestion is u call them and explain your first paycheck won't arrive until end if September and maybe they will allow deferment. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0196" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:15:08 UTC">
      <body>Can we defer most of the payments. I need at least 400 for two weeks. Shenandoah has turned into a gobbling machine. Plus dr hunts check of 170 is going to be cashed this week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0197" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:15:33 UTC">
      <body>I will call AT&amp;T. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0198" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:16:13 UTC">
      <body>What about all those gazillion other bills of the coming two weeks???</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0199" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:16:33 UTC">
      <body>I have already contacted FMCU and Santander. I will talk with Santander on aug 15 and FMCU will be calling me soon. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0200" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:16:57 UTC">
      <body>Who is Santander ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0201" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:17:04 UTC">
      <body>Car payment</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0202" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:18:15 UTC">
      <body>What about aqua and peco? Ortho? Travelers ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0203" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:19:12 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea other than to hope there is enough unemployment money to cover them and mortgage. We had agreed that Soraya would pay us $500 for her half of the laptop. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0204" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:20:02 UTC">
      <body>She did already </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0205" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:20:21 UTC">
      <body>When is the unemployment coming?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0206" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:21:03 UTC">
      <body>When was the $500 deposited in our checking account?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0207" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:22:39 UTC">
      <body>It was in cash sometime in July. You should be able to see it there as a transaction. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0208" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 16:23:05 UTC">
      <body>Cash deposit that is.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0209" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:23:28 UTC">
      <body>I don't know when the uc deposit will arrive. I will try to call them. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0210" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 16:34:21 UTC">
      <body>I just learned that I am getting only $304 per week. The first payment should arrive very soon and should be a double payment so it will be 608. I have no suggestions about the mortgage except that I talk to them immediately and explain the payments are not possible until end of sept. but before I do that I recommend that u call like brown and get his advice about what should be done. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0212" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 17:18:20 UTC">
      <body>I just did the calculations based on 800/month for the whole family for daily. This is the number we would come up with as a minimum. The result of the calculations is 40 per person per week so that means 80 per two weeks. 130 for you alone is too much. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0213" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 17:20:40 UTC">
      <body>I have additional expenses. I am driving soon so can't respond at length have to take into account gas and train tix. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0214" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 17:22:25 UTC">
      <body>What is the deadline to enroll me with bmc insurance </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0215" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 17:23:07 UTC">
      <body>I have train tickets too so does Soraya and the children have incidentals. I can't tell them not to go uptown with their friends to buy a soda for example. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0216" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 17:23:12 UTC">
      <body>Bmc insurance </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0217" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 17:23:25 UTC">
      <body>What do you mean deadline with BMC?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0218" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 17:24:36 UTC">
      <body>I already asked for it and they are going to provide it  aug 1. I don't know anything about deadline </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0219" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 17:41:32 UTC">
      <body>I would like to consult further about the idea if 40.a person later when I'm not driving. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0220" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 18:29:20 UTC">
      <body>Is Soraya still going into the city each week and if so how many times per week</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0221" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 18:33:12 UTC">
      <body>There is a two week break including this one. So she is starting again on the 12 th August. She goes to philly twice a week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0223" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 21:51:17 UTC">
      <body>90 is
Gr check I cashed today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0224" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 21:52:00 UTC">
      <body>But I need to pay back mom $100 she lent me for teeth cleaning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0225" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 22:08:32 UTC">
      <body>Teeth cleaning??? Couldn't you have waited till our salaries come in???? We have no money to feed the children and you go teeth cleaning??? I am outraged.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0226" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 22:10:16 UTC">
      <body>I am sitting here trying to feed them stuff from the pantry, trying to be creative saving every penny for gas and food and you go teeth cleaning????</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0227" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 22:11:21 UTC">
      <body>I have cut down on all wants including deserts and you go teeth cleaning?? What's next?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0228" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 22:59:12 UTC">
      <body>This was a cleaning and checkup with dr Saleh scheduled long ago. I could have changed the date to October but I'm sure dr Saleh would have said that is too long a delay given the risky situation with my teeth. Also since the separation occurred on July 14 I was not remembering matters like that. In any case my mother lent me the money so it works out the same in the end because I can repay her in October.  I'm sure we can consult about funds in more detail later. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0229" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 23:02:08 UTC">
      <body>I would like to pick up a few tools from the garage later tonight. I will of course not be entering the house. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0230" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 23:03:01 UTC">
      <body>Yes please pay her later. We need to figure out our finances for the next two weeks ASAP. Tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0231" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 23:03:27 UTC">
      <body>What tool do you need? Your tool box is in the den!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0232" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 23:03:48 UTC">
      <body>Garden tools </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0233" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 23:04:40 UTC">
      <body>Please answer about the finances and when we are going to discuss that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0234" participant="137257" time="2013-07-31 23:06:40 UTC">
      <body>I'm late I can't do it by text anyway. If u want to talk by phone at about.9 I can do that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0235" participant="132437" time="2013-07-31 23:12:37 UTC">
      <body>No I can't talk by phone at all. I'll wait until you are ready to discuss by text</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0236" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 02:37:52 UTC">
      <body>I will create. Budget using an online tool and u can do the same then we can deal with the numbers more clearly. This is a suggestion from the PAC. I will look for the tool tomorrow and send u the link. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0237" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 02:40:12 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0238" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 15:53:36 UTC">
      <body>Apparently the best online budget tool is mint.com. Please have a look at it. If we decide to use it we have to give the bank name member number and password. But everything I've read says it is secure. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0239" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 16:43:02 UTC">
      <body>I will look at it this afternoon. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0240" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 16:44:03 UTC">
      <body>Do we have any money in the $500 Fmfcu credit line?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0241" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 16:44:04 UTC">
      <body>Did you call unemployment to find out about when your first check is coming?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0242" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 16:44:48 UTC">
      <body>Please check the FMCU website to answer the first question. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0244" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 16:51:05 UTC">
      <body>As a general rule please do not ask me to do anything that you can do with your computer at home.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0245" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 16:51:06 UTC">
      <body>I am trying to reach the uc offices but it is very difficult by phone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0246" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 17:02:00 UTC">
      <body>There is still 217.98 available in the line of credit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0247" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 17:58:05 UTC">
      <body>I confirmed with unemployment people. They made an error and the money should appear in the FMCU account in 2-3 business days so probably Monday. I also confirmed that I am receiving the highest possible weekly payment for anyone which is $573. Nobody can receive any more than that. But the amount is reduced because of my strayer earnings and then taxes are taken out so the uc weekly payment is only 304.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0249" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:00:51 UTC">
      <body>I did they said he is in court today I should try tomorrow morning and/or send email. I have so much to do I haven't gotten around to emailing him.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0250" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 18:01:36 UTC">
      <body>If u email him today I will follow up tomorrow with calling him. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0251" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:02:15 UTC">
      <body>L</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0252" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:02:25 UTC">
      <body>*k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0253" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 18:09:03 UTC">
      <body>I just emailed U the budget forms. Please choose the one u prefer and then we can both work on it and compare figures.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0254" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:10:03 UTC">
      <body>Give me some time I am tired right now. Will get to it today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0255" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 18:12:16 UTC">
      <body>If I don't suggest a time in my texts or emails that means I am not intending any time frame other than what u choose. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0256" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:13:53 UTC">
      <body>K</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0257" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 18:18:39 UTC">
      <body>I've done a quick review. The first one rohdelaw might be best because it is an excel file. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0258" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 18:30:34 UTC">
      <body>Are they gonna pay you weekly or biweekly? On Monday/ Tuesday are you gonna get 304 or 608?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0259" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 18:37:09 UTC">
      <body>Weekly I don't know yet what I will be getting. I forgot to ask. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0260" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 19:02:08 UTC">
      <body>Will there be feast tonight? I think it is important that Shenandoah be involved somehow. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0261" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 19:02:29 UTC">
      <body>He needs to keep some connection with the faith especially at this age. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0262" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 19:18:16 UTC">
      <body>Yes there is feast tonight. It is difficult to teach the kids about the Faith when they have never had any stability in their lives, no bahai friends, and bad example at home etc. I have tried to teach them for years and years. I would sit down with them with note books, tests and exams. I organized bahai class teachers in Beirut (three of them). I pray with them. Listen to talks with them. I initiated them going to Tabarsi Camp etc I can go on and on about how much I have done for them. I have tried to live the example as much as possible. But I cannot force them and I will not. It is what it is. He knows it is his feast but he doesn't want to participate. I wouldn't either if I were him. Who wants to live in tension.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0263" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 19:24:48 UTC">
      <body>So this is another matter for consultation. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0264" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 19:32:21 UTC">
      <body>I will also ask you to stop making negative comments about me once and for all. I am agreeing to communicate with you by text at your request so that we can get things done for the sake of the children. But I will not accept being a target of your negative remarks. If you cannot communicate with me in a civil manner then just let me know so I can contact joe and don and ask them for help. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0265" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 19:41:17 UTC">
      <body>For my part from now on will take care not to mention anything except the practical tasks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0266" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 19:44:26 UTC">
      <body>Yes i think that is a great idea. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0267" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:07:28 UTC">
      <body>I am looking at mint.com and I think I get the gist of it. But I think it is not worth working with it, because we need to separate our accounts and financial matters soon. This will be done through a separation agreement in which we agree on who pays what. This way we will not harass each other about this spending or that. For example, I won't be able to tell you why in the world did you make that decision about teeth cleaning. Meanwhile we have to try to play it by ear until we make the separation agreement. I just need time to find the right attorney and I am too busy with the sociology paper for the next ten days. And about the links you emailed me, what are they about? I mean why do I need to look at them? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0268" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:08:48 UTC">
      <body>We do not have money for an attorney. Ease explain how you plan to pay for that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0269" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:09:20 UTC">
      <body>The PAC suggested that we use those forms to create a budget that fairly distributes the money. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0270" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:09:29 UTC">
      <body>I don't know yet. But I think we need one. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0271" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:10:36 UTC">
      <body>The PAC said usually the lawyers get involved more toward the end of the year but you should talk to the PAC directly about that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0272" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:16:16 UTC">
      <body>The separation agreement will deal with visitation, the car etc as well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0273" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:38:50 UTC">
      <body>One thing that u could do without delay is open your account somewhere and arrange for your paycheck to be deposited there. That will save time once it is decided how to divide up the rest of the summer income. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0274" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:40:31 UTC">
      <body>If there is nothing urgent I would like to hold off on any texting until Monday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0275" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:40:45 UTC">
      <body>I have already done that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0276" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:41:10 UTC">
      <body>I mean my own account</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0277" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Great that makes things easier. Then eventually I can change my account pword and that will be settled. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0278" participant="132437" time="2013-08-01 21:42:51 UTC">
      <body>Well I probably will have to remove myself from yours...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0279" participant="137257" time="2013-08-01 21:43:28 UTC">
      <body>Yep but that should be easy. Okay that is all the texting for now unless it is urgent. Thanks. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
