<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140416.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-04-16 20:58:20 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok. I'm sorry , I just forgot.  Make a list of company tools and the van and your notion of their depreciated value. Keep in mind that I may want to buy you out or you may want to partially buy me out or vice versa so be reasonable with the values. Break down what you want to keep </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-04-16 21:17:52 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Yeah, I am leaning toward buying the van mainly because it already belongs to company so it can just remain, where as if you want it you will need to buy and pay taxes, tags, registration etc.. I think we can come up with a fair value for it either way. Also, the table saw since I don't have one. I'm not too concerned about all the other stuff - I'm sure we come up with fair values for it all and just pick and choose. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-04-16 21:29:44 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Also, I realized I do need that cabinet grade ply in yr basement for shelves I promised Mary-knight pso I can grab that after work tomorrow or Friday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-04-16 21:33:51 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok. I used some of the 1/2" but the 3/4" is all still there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-04-16 21:36:28 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-04-17 16:13:42 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Are u planning on installing fixtures today? We gotta do 2 cleanings, another coat of mud, fabricate a bracket for the sink today. And prime  tomorrow preferably before installing any fixtures</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-04-17 16:14:50 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Planning to install tomorrow am. So if you are just priming tomorrow it'll be fine. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-04-17 16:15:38 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Is Adam going to panama tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-04-17 16:17:04 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>No one at panama tomorrow because they need to get change orders sorted and inspections etc. so adam can go prime there solo if you want and you have a day off. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-04-17 19:42:36 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> Are u planning on taking the van tomorrow? U probably should in case I forgot something . Also you will need the compressor, nail guns, the screw box</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-04-17 19:43:01 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Which are not currently in the van</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-04-17 19:48:20 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Also I think I left my tile bits in the vanity at Marcy's in case you guys needed to drill more holes to mount the vanity. You will need to grab some tile bits if you didn't grab mine from there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-04-17 19:49:27 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Did the sink not get mounted?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-04-17 19:51:22 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>We just finished the last coat of mud which needs to dry and get primed before the sink gets mounted. I fabricated  a bracket for the sink that should work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-04-17 19:52:27 UTC" participant="149372">
      <body>Ok. If Adam can drop the van off at Malcolm that would be ideal. If not I will come get it tonight when I'm done work. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

