<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150330.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-30 22:33:14 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>In a sec</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-30 22:34:22 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Ok well I'm trying to leave studio. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-30 22:34:33 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Might not be able to talk for a couple hours</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-30 23:39:51 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>hey I’m home!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-30 23:40:52 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>K i’m on it. gimme 15</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-30 23:41:06 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>are u reading it or do you want to talk first?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-30 23:41:16 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>i’m reading. it’s good so far. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-30 23:41:33 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>wendy’s brother got pretty good news, so that crisis passed. but he will be starting the trnasplant soon. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-30 23:41:46 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>she is coming to seder. gpa and desy probably not.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-30 23:43:09 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>oh great. elaborate on news re wendy when we talk. I guess grandpa is getting closer to the end. i’m going to go out a lot this summer. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-30 23:47:34 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>can i fly to LAX? or is there a better airport?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-30 23:48:04 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>lax is ok. it’s 10 minutes from desy’s so gpa will get u from there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-30 23:48:04 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>I found two flights each for 164$ to LAX - I would be there for a full week. Do you think that is too long?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-30 23:48:17 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>i am trying to READ YOUR PIECE!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-30 23:48:22 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-31 00:01:53 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>you have to consider that for yourself. what will you do? can you make a schedule to paint or work on a project in addition to being w gpa? if you think of it that way (and have a week free), then it cd be great!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-31 00:02:17 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>i also responded that way - that gpa was getting closer to the ‘end’. it is upsetting. i think dad shd go. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-03-31 01:05:31 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>gpa says he’s coming</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-31 02:22:03 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>hooray! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-03-31 02:22:38 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>jeremy’s dad says they haven’t really ever met jeremy’s gf before. she came in once to use the bathroom. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-03-31 02:24:23 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>ohhh coooll</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-03-31 02:24:38 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>reading ur piece now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-03-31 02:24:47 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>are you watching netflix?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-03-31 02:24:48 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>oh i guess not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-03-31 02:24:49 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>HOLD ON</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-03-31 02:25:12 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>It’s a late afternoon in the fall of  2013. Apple has just released IOS7 and Boston’s Boylston Street Apple store is crowded with customers. Suddenly, the store’s overhead soundtrack stops. Unbeknownst to the shoppers and salespeople, they are about to become victims of an act of artistic intervention. A single clear note - the Apple alert Sherwood Forest - pierces the store. Everyone   pauses, as it plays three times before the sound system’s regularly scheduled Coldplay song resumes. This was the first documented intervention, or Sounding, by anonymous artist and hacker UBIQ: The Robin Hood of Sound. 

UBIQ, short for ubiquitous, is known for his impromptu concert-like interventions in which he usurps control of (semi-)public sound infrastructures in order to broadcast the iconic ringtones and alerts from familiar digital interfaces. His practice raises questions not only about the role of sound in user experience, but about global corporate culture, and subversion in a digital age. 

In one of his initial ventures, White Man Beeps (2011), UBIQ replaced the faux chirp-beep of the walk signal at a pedestrian crosswalk in midtown Manhattan with the sound of a dial-up modem. By doing so, he “re-mixed” the public soundscape with the nostalgia of AIM and Netscape Navigator. Though he acknowledged that the piece was “a shameful act of ignorance that endangered a demographic for whom society does so little …,” White Man Beeps demonstrates UBIQ’s unique brand of subversive audio-assemblage. He reveals our blind acceptance of authority, with a touch of humor. Commenting on the piece, he said: “We walk like sheep when the white man beeps… Can’t we waltz instead?” 

While White Man Beeps may have been a subtle stab at the top-down mechanisms of control inherent in utilitarian devices, UBIQ’s later interventions - Black Friday, at a Wal-Mart in Philadelphia, and his Apple Bombings, at Apple retail stores across the world - appear as direct attacks on consumerism and corporate culture. These works are more ominous, and less playful. 
By shifting the scale of our phones’ tiny nagging alerts to a thunderous, monolithic broadcast, no longer do these melodies seduce users into their own private screens. Instead, they interrupt the shopping experience, and replace it with one that unites the listeners. His soundings quiet the crowd - and in the deafening silence of their aftermath, the public is left to consider the sounds, not as their engineered purpose, but as methods of subversion.

My response to UBIQ comes in the form of an interactive audio gallery installation. iHear (2014) is a black shiny box the size of a Harry Potter novel. From each of fours holes cut into its reflective surface, pokes a small photocell sensor. The photocells, programmed by a Pure Data Extended patch on a hidden computer, use the light level measurements to control the frequency - pitch and speed  -  at which four distinct cell phone ringtones play (from the hidden speakers). Users play the instrument as if it were a theremin; they manipulate the frequency of the four ringtones as they move their hands in the space above the box, thereby decreasing the amount of light hitting the sensors. The effect is a cacophonous chorus, wavering in and out of recognition. 

iHear, as a response to UBIQ, is a reminder of the human ability to listen - to hear the familiar anew. In this regard, iHear acts to empower its users: it asks them to spend a few moments authoring beauty, where it is least expected. 

The narrative of UBIQ is, of course, a fiction. Along with the story above, UBIQ has his own artist website, Vimeo channel, Philly Fox five evening news report, and a 150-page gallery catalogue for his solo show at a Brooklyn-based gallery. The fictional nature of the project brings up questions about the authority of media, and digital media in particular. When we are blind to what’s on the other end of a screen, we want to ask if the potential duplicity of digital reality change our experience of said reality. Though questioning the veracity of media may seem contextually pertinent, it is, by no means specific to our Photoshop-era, and therefore, not the most pertinent reading of UBIQ - an artist who’s work is very much engaged in the contemporary practice of digital media. 

The reason to resort to fiction - in the creation of UBIQ - was, along with his mysterious technical abilities, an issue of control. UBIQ needed a Banksy-meets-Horse_eBooks response to his work, that only “followers”, “hype”, and “buzz” could offer. The call-and-response inspired by today’s interactive platforms, has infiltrated my own artistic practice: I couldn’t conceive of UBIQ’s work on its own. I had to create the subsequent response to his work, as well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-03-31 02:26:43 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>mom - nate wants to know if he can meet dad at the station</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-03-31 02:27:06 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>sure but then it has to be around 6pm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-03-31 03:06:32 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Actually on that day he'll probably leave earlier like around 430 because of the Seder </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-03-31 03:22:40 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>oh ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-03-31 12:09:55 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>i’m ready!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-03-31 12:25:12 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>where are you??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-03-31 12:36:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>My reasoning for UBIQ goes beyond his duplicitous technical prowess. He needed a Banksy-meets-Horse_eBooks response to his work, that only control over his “followers”, “hype”, and “buzz” could offer. The call-and-response of today’s interactive platforms has infiltrated my own artistic practice: I couldn’t conceive of UBIQ’s work on its own. I had to create the public’s subsequent response - the awe, the commentary and the recognition. 
 to his work, as well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-03-31 12:48:45 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Ubiq serves my intention in several ways. First, his technical prowess far surpasses mine. But more important, I needed to orchestrate 21st-century followers and hype to provide a Banksy-meets-Horse_eBooks reaction to his work. The call-and-response of today’s interactive platforms has infiltrated my artistic practice: I couldn’t conceive of UBIQ’s work on its own. I had to generate the subsequent public rejoinder – the flurry of commentary, recognition, and awe. 

</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-03-31 13:03:16 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>isn’t it importantly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-03-31 13:03:20 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>ok I’m much better now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-03-31 13:03:33 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-03-31 13:59:12 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Can I just say</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-03-31 13:59:27 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>We are going to have a ton of attractive hen at out Seder</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-03-31 14:01:18 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>And women!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-03-31 14:01:35 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>but i really appreciate the men</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-03-31 14:02:12 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Clearly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-03-31 14:08:38 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Take out adjunct</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2015-03-31 14:09:07 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Put in 2014 after MFA</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2015-03-31 14:13:44 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Though his technical prowess far surpasses my fathomable skill-set, this was not the reason UBIQ’s soundings were never realized. Instead, the call-and-response of today’s interactive platforms had infiltrated my artistic practice: I couldn’t conceive of UBIQ’s work on its own. I had to generate the subsequent public reply – the flurry of commentary, recognition, and awe. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2015-03-31 14:14:41 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>Gotta do later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2015-03-31 14:15:25 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2015-03-31 16:57:26 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>MY EDITS. BUT NOT SURE. WILL READ WITH THE REST WHEN I GET HOME, around 4. 
Though his technical prowess far surpasses my fathomable skill-set, this was not the reason UBIQ’s soundings remained conceptual. Instead, because the call-and-response of today’s interactive platforms has infiltrated my artistic practice, I couldn’t conceive of UBIQ’s work on its own. I had to generate the subsequent public reply – the flurry of commentary, recognition, and awe. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2015-03-31 21:59:45 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>how are you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2015-03-31 21:59:47 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>u looked at it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2015-03-31 21:59:53 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>we donw/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2015-03-31 22:00:01 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2015-03-31 22:00:07 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>i made changes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2015-03-31 22:00:13 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>but it’s good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2015-03-31 22:00:17 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>oh no</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2015-03-31 22:00:21 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2015-03-31 22:00:23 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>you didn’t understand</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2015-03-31 22:00:23 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>that change</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2015-03-31 22:00:24 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>oh well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2015-03-31 22:00:24 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>never-ending</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2015-03-31 22:00:30 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>and you didn’t read the bio?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2015-03-31 22:00:31 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>it didn’t flow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2015-03-31 22:00:38 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>oh, the bio. wait a sec.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2015-03-31 22:01:55 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>bio fixes here￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" time="2015-03-31 22:04:37 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>is it really “May, 2014”</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" time="2015-03-31 22:04:58 UTC" participant="152236">
      <body>no. it should be ‘in May 2014 from…”</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

