<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150129.0021" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-29 21:11:22 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hey can you just text me when you're leaving? I'll be ready by 530, but I want to make sure I'm awake. Haha. I'm going to attempt a short nap.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-29 21:20:04 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>No problemo!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-29 22:06:47 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Hey! On my way out :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-29 22:15:28 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Coolio!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-30 04:03:21 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Okay, he asked me if I want to partake in an all-you-can-eat sushi thing to which I said in effect, not really. Now he's asking if I'm doing anything tomorrow night. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-30 04:03:26 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Jen I don't know..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-30 16:02:08 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Sorry!  I was asleep. Haha. But if you're really feeling that uncomfortable, I would just say no. If you really believe it's platonic then go! If anything, go in hopes that he'll say something because this way, you can actually tell him once and for all that you're not interested in anymore more than a friendship. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-30 16:04:16 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>If anything, do something that won't be too time consuming or something that wouldn't feel like a date...like Chipotle! Haha. Then afterwards if he says something just tell him.

He might not like it, but it's better than having to dread talking to him because you're afraid he's going to ask you to go out. I don't think he'll stop asking. Eventually if you keep saying no without telling him anything, he's just going to get fed up and not talk to you at all. It seems like you want to keep him as a friend, so just let him down easily. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

