<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110704.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135117" time="2011-07-04 23:43:41 UTC">
      <body>What you up to Martha "these colors don't run" Stuckey? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 00:16:39 UTC">
      <body>What's that nickname about? I'm at megs still but were going to head back to the fireworks sometime</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 00:41:58 UTC">
      <body>I'm giving everyone patriotic nicknames today!  I'll see you at the fireworks hopefully </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 00:58:48 UTC">
      <body>Where are you going to be? Who are you going with? And how was that patriotic?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 01:19:21 UTC">
      <body>I dunno who or where or when. And I can't believe you don't know that slogan. It can be found on bumper stickers and cutoff t shirts throughout this great land</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 01:49:23 UTC">
      <body>What time are the fireworks? My roomies are having a partay so I might roll in late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 02:22:23 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea actually...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 02:27:21 UTC">
      <body>Well we're heading up there now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 03:12:15 UTC">
      <body>You seeing this!!!  We're outside the aster</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 03:29:29 UTC">
      <body>Aaaand now at the soap factory </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 03:58:45 UTC">
      <body>Fail Martha!  I thought you'd be all over this cultural event </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 22:36:47 UTC">
      <body>You feeling up for hangin? Don't let me guilt you if you're not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2011-07-05 22:57:22 UTC">
      <body>Of course I am... I'm still downtown bc a friend was helping me with finance stuff... Stress. Anyway I'm just walking home now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135117" time="2011-07-05 23:01:24 UTC">
      <body>Ahh the life of a working gal. You wanna make some din? Get some ice cream? Take in a cultural event? I'm feeling wiped but am up for just about anything </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 00:06:02 UTC">
      <body>So crazy pants just got home. Maybe your place would be a nice change of pace? I'm not super super hungry either... You decide?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 00:15:10 UTC">
      <body>Aight well I'm getting some steak, potatoes, and green beans. If you prefer, you can just drink wine </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 00:15:55 UTC">
      <body>Fancy! I would eat that. Where?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 00:15:56 UTC">
      <body>Caitlyn has strep but come on over </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 06:42:45 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Thanks for staying up to hash that out. Or at least try. I think it was really good until I started to fade. Whatever we figure out, I am glad to know t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 06:42:55 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) hat it is such a thoughtful decision. And for a woman who has problems with restraint you really had me fooled!  I'll take a lesson </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 06:45:06 UTC">
      <body>That's why I had to kick you out at the end... I like you a lot Tim. Thanks for letting me be thoughtful and restraining at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 06:53:15 UTC">
      <body>Likewise mc. Hope you can clear your head a bit and sleep well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 16:12:20 UTC">
      <body>I think we should be more happy than cautious. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 16:19:16 UTC">
      <body>I think it's one or the other don't you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 16:19:58 UTC">
      <body>Not both simultaneously?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 16:34:02 UTC">
      <body>Cautiously happy? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 16:45:02 UTC">
      <body>Well isn't that what we've been doing? I'm not cautious a about being happy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 17:38:33 UTC">
      <body>And by that I mean yes, you are absolutely right </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 17:51:18 UTC">
      <body>I was just thinking that we were doing more worrying than we should have last night. But that's ok too. I dont want to get weighed down by it though. My boss just bought me a $12 lobster sandwich and I saw jd kuehl on the way home...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 18:05:05 UTC">
      <body>It sounds like that lobster sandwich will be weighing you down plenty, best not to have anything else doing it too. How's jd? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 18:06:11 UTC">
      <body>Luckily there was enough distance between us that I could pretend that I didn't see him. I can send your regards next time though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 18:17:12 UTC">
      <body>Mmmm not necessary. I'm surprised he didn't try to hit on you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 18:17:49 UTC">
      <body>I think Facebook chat is his preferred medium</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 18:29:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh really? Do you know this from experience? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 18:32:48 UTC">
      <body>Jealous?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 18:35:48 UTC">
      <body>Jealous of you, yes.  Did you really eat 12 lobsters in a sandwich? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 18:37:05 UTC">
      <body>What else could I have meant? I mean have you met jd? And it was a 12 dollar sandwich not a 12 lobster sandwich...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 18:41:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh! You had me so excited about a 12 lobster sandwich. I guess yours is a bit classier</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 18:42:12 UTC">
      <body>Hah. The $12 sandwich was big enough.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 21:22:22 UTC">
      <body>So you think I should call Katie or are we just leaving it at cautious happiness? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 21:22:55 UTC">
      <body>Regina is giving me a ride home then I'll call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 21:41:49 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I'm still at work for quite a while </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 21:46:01 UTC">
      <body>Oh no worries. If you would call her under circumstance about what she might be expecting etc etc, yea then its not my place to say either way. But I think we shouldn't let on until we know more about what is going on, you know? Bc we wouldn't be asking for permission as much as informing her out of respect. And informing her right now is more to cover our asses than respecting her. That's my thought anyway. Have you had any brilliant ideas today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 21:46:28 UTC">
      <body>Under any circumstance I mean</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 23:08:39 UTC">
      <body> When are you done working?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 23:14:55 UTC">
      <body>Just got showered </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 23:15:59 UTC">
      <body>Do you want some dinner?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 23:17:55 UTC">
      <body>I was thinking about having some of that tonight. When, where? I have to do a little project so maybe in an hour? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 23:18:44 UTC">
      <body>I just made something sort of Indian. It's ready when you are. (don't get used to this).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 23:19:52 UTC">
      <body>Haha ok! Can it wait an hour or are you hungry? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 23:20:34 UTC">
      <body>No I'll wait... Little project...?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 23:21:50 UTC">
      <body>Cool. I'll tell you bout it over dinner </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="135117" time="2011-07-06 23:22:41 UTC">
      <body>Should I bring anything? Vino? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131839" time="2011-07-06 23:23:19 UTC">
      <body>Yea if you feel like it. I have some but who knows how much will be left in an hour...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 05:11:56 UTC">
      <body>Such a tease.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 05:14:31 UTC">
      <body>Who me? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 05:14:57 UTC">
      <body>I still don't know what's going on in your head. And I did come back! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 05:16:10 UTC">
      <body>Im kidding and I was in the shower and im sorry I missed you. I would've kissed you back. Don't text and drive also.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 05:19:18 UTC">
      <body>Done driving! Aren't we just two proactive folks or what. I'll come back over right now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 05:24:56 UTC">
      <body>Ok maybe that's unreasonable but i honestly would. Just give me a little sign next time, other than falling asleep. You driving me crazy in a good way marth  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 13:35:51 UTC">
      <body>Sorry!! Oh god I am tragic. I'm good for nothing after beer and cheese curds. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:21:28 UTC">
      <body>I think they did me in too, at least ruined my ability to act on my impulses. I really want to go to the walker tonight if you wanna join. Free! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 18:38:56 UTC">
      <body>Im seeing Caro again tonight I think... I also have to write up cover letters and what not for a couple jobs. I really want to though. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:40:40 UTC">
      <body>Hokay well if you change your mind lemme know. Probs gonna go around 7</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 18:41:21 UTC">
      <body>Mmk. Hows the office?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:43:55 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Oh man it has been such a good day. Just talked all morning with the boss and he got me really excited about seeing some art. And he's buying me Lebanes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:44:04 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) e food! How are reg and Carol? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 18:50:41 UTC">
      <body>Reg disappeared for a long time... Carol just schooled me on the street map of downtown while I was trying to answer her question about the farmers market on 'Nicollet mall road'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:55:15 UTC">
      <body>Haha! What a crazy. I'd love to get a few lessons on urban life from her.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 18:57:09 UTC">
      <body>Also, I think you should seriously reconsider your plans for this evening. You can see Carolyn any time ... how often do we get to spend quality time together? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 19:10:42 UTC">
      <body>Timothy. You know I would if Caro wasn't here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 19:25:28 UTC">
      <body>Ya ya ya well we should go some day when you don't have social obligations ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 21:21:57 UTC">
      <body>Well of course.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 21:25:33 UTC">
      <body>You should've heard Regina on the ride home...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 21:26:33 UTC">
      <body>?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 21:29:38 UTC">
      <body>She was telling me things that make her throw up. One is semen. She had stories.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 22:18:21 UTC">
      <body>Wow you guys must be getting pretty close. I can't wait to hear ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 22:37:33 UTC">
      <body>Also I didn't realize how close you live to my work. Just drove by</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 22:37:56 UTC">
      <body>And you didn't stop by?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 22:41:03 UTC">
      <body>I thought you were with Carolyn! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 22:41:23 UTC">
      <body>I am, shes here!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 22:43:26 UTC">
      <body>Well next time I will.  Don't you need some alone time with your friend from afar? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131839" time="2011-07-07 22:44:42 UTC">
      <body>Yes we do need that. Also, she wants to be abandon me for Caitlyn. What are you folks doing later?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="135117" time="2011-07-07 23:03:56 UTC">
      <body>Currently just porch sitting. Caitlyn says she might be down for hanging. Or there's always the walker... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 01:29:55 UTC">
      <body>How's high art, member of the elite?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 01:35:18 UTC">
      <body>Actually very cool. Despite not understanding it at all it definitely moved me. But I've been fulfilled and am back to porching. How are the ladies? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 01:39:17 UTC">
      <body>We're singing. You should get us drunk bc were fun when were drunk.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 01:50:09 UTC">
      <body>Where are you singing? And how could I go about getting you drunk/fun? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 02:02:34 UTC">
      <body>We were at a church with a friend. We may go out? Were on the move</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 02:05:31 UTC">
      <body>Well that sounds like fun. I wish I had some booze to offer but fresh out. If you find yourselves in uptown call me! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 04:31:10 UTC">
      <body>Hey that's a bummer you're aching. Hope you're feeling more like your vivacious self soon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 04:36:45 UTC">
      <body>Yea, I didn't say bc Caro asked and I lied but I have a fever too. maybe I'll get a day off tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 04:40:29 UTC">
      <body>You didn't say wha? Nevermind, just get better! Take a day off, you've been going out late every night. Sleep is so good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 04:41:36 UTC">
      <body>I didn't tell you I had a fever. Maybe I will. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 04:49:16 UTC">
      <body>Well goodnight my sickly friend. Let me know if I can do anything for you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 15:16:23 UTC">
      <body>Hey dude I'm going to be gone until Tuesday so you're not really going to sleep tonight right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 15:41:54 UTC">
      <body>Of course not! But you're not leaving tonight are you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 15:44:48 UTC">
      <body>Feeling any better?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 16:58:13 UTC">
      <body>No im leaving first thing tomorrow morn. I'm super excited.I'm feeling much better actually. Where are you working today? June street?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 19:01:49 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) That's wonderful on all counts! I'm not at June but can't believe you remember that ... actually somewhere in golden valley where I get no service. Any </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 19:01:55 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) good stories from reg today?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 19:03:53 UTC">
      <body>If I have a child and shes a lady I want to name her June. Thats why I remembered. No she's been quiet. But just busted out the doritos and salsa.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 19:41:56 UTC">
      <body>Aww yeah must be Friday afternoon! What's your plan for the eve? Partying hard? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 19:48:46 UTC">
      <body>Well jacks making dinner for Caro and I and then there's a party I guess. I dont know how into the party idea I am.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 19:58:29 UTC">
      <body>That sounds nice. Well if you're receptive to other entertainment I'll try to cook something up. I'd just really like to see you at some point </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 23:11:21 UTC">
      <body>Sorry. Work got bonkers and then I forgot my keys and key card to get back into the office etc etc. Crazy. In any case I want to see you too. I'll text you after dinner?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" participant="135117" time="2011-07-08 23:15:16 UTC">
      <body>Ha! You mean to tell me you don't always have it all together all the time? I refuse to believe it. Gimme a call when you're free or if you make some plans </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" participant="131839" time="2011-07-08 23:21:42 UTC">
      <body>I'm not reading into that. Will do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" participant="135117" time="2011-07-09 03:06:42 UTC">
      <body>What's up Mattie? Did Jack get you drunk?  Say hey to that boy for me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" participant="131839" time="2011-07-09 03:09:12 UTC">
      <body>He says hey back. We're about to bike to uptown. Want to come to a party? I don't know how long I'll stay but maybe for a bit?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" participant="131839" time="2011-07-09 03:11:49 UTC">
      <body>It's at blaisdell an 35th. It's gonna be a big party......</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" participant="135117" time="2011-07-09 14:30:18 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I wish I could explain how I'm feeling right now, somewhere between excitement and gratitude and happiness and exhaustion.  And wishing you weren't leav</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" participant="135117" time="2011-07-09 14:30:23 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ing quite yet. For the record: that was not a high five. It was a "come closer and forget about holding up that bedsheet" ten</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" participant="131839" time="2011-07-09 14:49:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm cool with a high five. Take naps and enjoy your weekend :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" participant="135117" time="2011-07-09 15:52:08 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) OK well I'll try not to read into that... hope you can relax and let me know what you find out about dollywood. It seemed like mecca to all those backwo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" participant="135117" time="2011-07-09 15:52:13 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ods Kentuckians</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 01:57:34 UTC">
      <body>How's that lake sunset? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:06:10 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Ok I promise no more text bombarding while you're on vacay but I've had lots of thinking time today and any lingering apprehension be dammed. I really l</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:06:13 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ike being with you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 02:09:19 UTC">
      <body>You can bombard, it's not a zen retreat. I like being with and hearing from you too. Thanks for saying so.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 02:25:01 UTC">
      <body>Pretty gorgeous. Have to enjoy it now though bc I guess it's supposed to be stormy the rest of the time...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:33:02 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Boo! Well I'll send my sunshine vibes your way. Otherwise it's not the worst thing to hunker down with Dolly and enjoy a summer storm. Did you bring you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:34:31 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) r geetar for a Stuckey fam jam?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 02:35:45 UTC">
      <body>I did actually. I'm writing that cover letter though so pat can get me into C hall. Musicking will have to wait until tomorrow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:46:44 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) To whom it may concern: I am writing to inform you of your interest in the next big thing in admin assistance/impromptu moments of musical genius : me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:46:58 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) I'll begin next Monday at 9. Sincerely, m.c.s.    done </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 02:47:58 UTC">
      <body>that's all you think I'm good for??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:53:02 UTC">
      <body>Marth I have much more but that's all you get for free. Also I can only bang out so much text while I'm on the highway ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 02:54:01 UTC">
      <body>Fucking knock it off Campbell!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:54:49 UTC">
      <body>Maybe throw in "a smile that could charm the pants off the Pope "</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 02:57:54 UTC">
      <body>Ok ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 14:57:55 UTC">
      <body>Stop texting and driving. I like you alive.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 17:09:16 UTC">
      <body>I promise to no longer text and drive. Happy Sunday! Since you declined on going to the walker I'm taking my little bro instead. It's going to be tres romantic </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 17:18:45 UTC">
      <body> That's a good sobertivity. You could also bowl at Bryant lake? That's a bar though I suppose. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 19:14:47 UTC">
      <body>Oh good word! I think we're gonna go to Calhoun. Is </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 19:15:38 UTC">
      <body>it nice there today? It's beautiful here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 19:16:06 UTC">
      <body>It is! It's hot actually. But no clouds at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 19:53:21 UTC">
      <body>Well you're welcome for sending the sunshine your way. Reeled in any big ones? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" participant="131839" time="2011-07-10 19:54:29 UTC">
      <body>My grandparents are law abiding folk so no fishing for any of us unlicenseds</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" participant="135117" time="2011-07-10 20:17:10 UTC">
      <body>Of course. Sounds like a perfect opportunity for some of your classic political subversion.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 00:06:30 UTC">
      <body>Got into a debate about the budget with nana at dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 02:08:28 UTC">
      <body>Did you find some north woods inspiration and write a few songs today? I'm fatiguing of family time ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0142" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:05:34 UTC">
      <body>No songs but it is inspiring. The storms are over and left the craziest sunset. It was out of control. What are you and Brian doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0143" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:18:38 UTC">
      <body>Man, that sounds beautiful! It just started to storm here and it feels so good. We're watching jackass 3, so I got my high art and low brow all in one day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0144" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:19:54 UTC">
      <body>Balance is healthy. Sounds like fun!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0145" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:22:33 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm yeah not my first choice but bonding nonetheless. Also found out that my dad went to the e.r. which really worried Brian and put a damper on the day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0146" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:28:06 UTC">
      <body>What happened? Is he ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0147" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:35:37 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Yeah he's alright. Another person in the church got killed in a car accident and I think my dad just fainted from stress or something. I dunno, it was w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0148" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:37:25 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) eird, he's had a hell of a week.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0149" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:37:54 UTC">
      <body>No kidding. Are you ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0150" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:39:01 UTC">
      <body>Keep it on the dl though I think he doesn't want it to be a big deal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0151" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:39:04 UTC">
      <body>Holy shit we are having a STORM! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0152" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:39:53 UTC">
      <body>I will don't worry. Stay safe and don't make fun for saying so</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0153" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:40:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I just have a new appreciation for how emotionally draining that is. I'm a bit worried about the old man </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0154" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:43:38 UTC">
      <body>I hear you loud and clear. I won't get any crazy ideas from the movie...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0155" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 03:45:17 UTC">
      <body>Yea you know one guy from jackass died recently from drunk driving</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0156" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 03:52:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know, they're not the greatest role models. I'll stick with beaver cleaver </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0157" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 04:07:37 UTC">
      <body>I meant stay safe with the storm though originally. Off to bed. Big day tomorrow! Lumberjack breakfast and a big bike ride.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0158" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 07:45:49 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Nice! I don't know what a lumberjack breakfast is but if it's anything like a big boy breakfast I like the sound of it. Have a fun bikeride and  sleep w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0159" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 07:45:52 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ell. I'd like to be sleeping well with you. And eating lumberjack breakfasts. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0160" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 07:45:55 UTC">
      <body>Night Stuckey </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0161" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 22:22:25 UTC">
      <body> I got some incense for us to enjoy today. Excitedd??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0162" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 22:31:23 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Excited with two D's.  Seriously, I really like that stuff, it relaxes me so much. Did you go shopping in all the kitsch boutiques on your bike ride?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0163" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 22:50:17 UTC">
      <body>Nobody would go on the ride with me! But it was kitchy where we drove.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0164" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 22:54:57 UTC">
      <body>Weeeak. You should go on your own. Or at least find somewhere to be by yourself and your thoughts. That place is so good for that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0165" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 22:56:45 UTC">
      <body>I have done that a little. Its hard to get away from Tyler...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0166" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:06:12 UTC">
      <body>Yes I know how difficult it is for you to pry yourself from the love of your life. Tell him you're going off to find your spirit animal </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0167" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:08:12 UTC">
      <body>He's driving me bonkers actually. My mom just drilled me about your program in Austin. They're onto us.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0168" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:14:13 UTC">
      <body>Oh shit! Panic! Did you tell her you had no idea about anything going on in my life? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0169" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:14:16 UTC">
      <body>Also, my bro asked if there was anything going on with us. I think they're definitely on to us. But how? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0170" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:15:03 UTC">
      <body>No I told her. Now my grandma. Yikes. What'd you tell him?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0171" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:20:12 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Neither confirmed or denied. Craftily averted. Your Grandma? In deep. And you have how many more days with them? I suspect by the time you get back your</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0172" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:20:37 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  entire extended family will know every little detail down to my lackluster  bedroom performance. Can't you talk about politics or something  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0173" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:21:52 UTC">
      <body> Covered politics last night unfortunately... No I'm just answering like it ain't no thang. Throw them off the scent. Might tell them I'm a lesbian.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0174" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:27:06 UTC">
      <body>Yes! I think you should. You can tell them I'm gay too if it's necessary </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0175" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:28:10 UTC">
      <body>If they think were dating then they've already assumed you're gay.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0176" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:30:06 UTC">
      <body>Ouch. I don't know whose ego should be more hurt. Is that really your track record? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0177" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:31:13 UTC">
      <body>No not really. Just a few. My dads feeding my dogs marshmallows by wetting them in his mouth first and handing them off.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0178" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:31:48 UTC">
      <body>And hey, if you are the experimental type that's cool just tell me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0179" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:32:25 UTC">
      <body>I don't know how you'd mean given the context...?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0180" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:33:10 UTC">
      <body>That's really sweet in a carnal kind of way. I'd like someone to do that to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0181" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:35:33 UTC">
      <body>I'm just messing. I'm saying if you like sleeping with gay guys or women that doesn't bother me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0182" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:37:46 UTC">
      <body>I don't know what I'm saying. I think this text convo took an unintended turn </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0183" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:38:42 UTC">
      <body>Let's just leave it at I like who you are</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0184" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:40:26 UTC">
      <body>Hey i respect the offer no need to rescind. But i only sleep with gay guys by accident. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0185" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:40:45 UTC">
      <body>And I know very little about any relationships you've been in but that doesn't really make any difference to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0186" participant="131839" time="2011-07-11 23:45:13 UTC">
      <body>I like to talk about myself so it's not bc I have anything to hide that you don't know it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0187" participant="135117" time="2011-07-11 23:50:29 UTC">
      <body>Haha I know. Although I think you've got some good stories I haven't heard. You're just saving them up for your Dolly -esque memoirs aren't you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0188" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 00:01:16 UTC">
      <body>I'll try them out on you if you're curious. Or if you're not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0189" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 00:14:29 UTC">
      <body>Also I do want to go camping and have never been</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0190" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 00:39:08 UTC">
      <body>Heck yeah, to stories and camping! I've got all the gear.  When,where, who? I'm there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0191" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 00:53:39 UTC">
      <body>Whenever! Whoever! Ive never been to Duluth either</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0192" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 01:53:54 UTC">
      <body>Well dang it's pretty beautiful up there. Have any plans for, say, next weekend? Although you might be cabined out </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0193" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 07:40:01 UTC">
      <body>It's a possibility. I'm supposed to have a rehearsal on Saturday but fuck that and the fleet foxes concert Sunday night. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0194" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 14:51:52 UTC">
      <body>Well maybe not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0195" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 14:53:50 UTC">
      <body>What are you rehearsing for? And do you really have tix? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0196" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 15:00:26 UTC">
      <body> With the band! And yea I keep forgetting but my mom got me tickets when I was in Spain. My bro and I are going</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0197" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 15:30:06 UTC">
      <body>Dang that's awesome. Shannon is too good to you. Well keep camping on the back burner. What are you guys up to today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0198" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 16:43:16 UTC">
      <body>Just finished a ten-er. Now were antique ing in our destination.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0199" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 16:48:31 UTC">
      <body>Nice. Put a bird on it!  And by tenner do you mean ten mile run? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0200" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 16:52:37 UTC">
      <body>Bike. I was pretty proud of my usage.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0201" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 16:55:11 UTC">
      <body>Not bad Stuckey. Exhausted? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0202" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 16:56:53 UTC">
      <body>I'm pretty tired but I also haven't been sleeping too well. And I have to bike back!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0203" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 17:05:30 UTC">
      <body>Well you'll sleep well tonight. That's an impressive day's work. You coming home tomorrow? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0204" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 17:05:51 UTC">
      <body>Tonight actually. What are you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0205" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 17:12:09 UTC">
      <body>I think I'll be working late and maybe going to a bbq if I'm not too exhausted. I'd love to hang but if you're wiped out I understand </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0206" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 17:12:59 UTC">
      <body>Yea, I'll be getting back at around 9 I think. I'll let you know :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0207" participant="135117" time="2011-07-12 17:18:23 UTC">
      <body>Cool well have a relaxing rest of the trip. Take it all in, even the fam</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0208" participant="131839" time="2011-07-12 23:38:11 UTC">
      <body>Just leaving now. Such sad at goodbyes... But it should be like 3 hours or so. Still working?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0209" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 00:21:01 UTC">
      <body>I hear you, not my forte either. Just got home and enjoyed the best part of my day where I take off my pants. Not gonna bbq so I'm free if you are...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0210" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 03:15:57 UTC">
      <body>What the hay Marth? Phone die? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0211" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 15:00:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm downtown. Coffee break? Reg can come too ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0212" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 15:01:52 UTC">
      <body>Hah. She probably won't come but I can come see you for a few. Where are you at?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0213" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 15:15:20 UTC">
      <body>In! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0214" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 15:16:57 UTC">
      <body>I'm on the skyway level by Broadway pizza </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0215" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 15:49:31 UTC">
      <body>I didn't even ask how your interview went!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0216" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 16:04:45 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I noticed! It was good, I'll tell you bout it tonight. I'm gonna be done real early so am down with whenever. We could even go swimming ... just gimme a</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0217" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 16:04:55 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  call when you want to hang</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0218" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 21:17:33 UTC">
      <body>Heyo. I'm back home now. What do you think?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0219" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 21:21:46 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Wait weren't YOU supposed to tell me what you wanted to do? As usual work is going later than planned should be home by five. I have stuff for tacos if </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0220" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 21:21:55 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) you want to come to my place</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0221" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 21:27:08 UTC">
      <body>When did I have to decide?? I'm not super hungry right this second but will be later Im sure. Now you go.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0222" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 21:30:53 UTC">
      <body>Very helpful. So you've offered that you don't want to eat dinner at 5 pm. Good. Want to go to the lake for a while? Also you should pick a movie </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0223" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 21:33:42 UTC">
      <body>Hah I'm sorry. Im a little tuckered out and uncreative. Lake it is. Or cards? I hate cards but I'm in the mood. Or bananagrams.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0224" participant="131839" time="2011-07-13 21:34:02 UTC">
      <body>Should I leave now to avoid traffic?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0225" participant="135117" time="2011-07-13 21:36:56 UTC">
      <body>Cool I can teach you cribbage if you want. Bring bananahrams too. I'll let you know when I leave here and you should leave then </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0227" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 03:37:15 UTC">
      <body>Or are you done? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0228" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 05:35:57 UTC">
      <body>That was a lovely evening Martha. The naan was delicious and I am still thrilled that we are hanging at all. Sleep well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0229" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 15:18:51 UTC">
      <body>Hey, keep next thursday free so you can come see this play with me. Ill pay for your ticket. Cool?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0230" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 15:28:05 UTC">
      <body>Very cool. What's the play? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0231" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 15:29:13 UTC">
      <body>People from Olaf started a theatre company. Megan being one of them. It's called love song I think?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0232" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 15:31:40 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like my kind of play. Hopefully they somehow incorporate the wells Fargo wagon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0233" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 16:58:36 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) You have any interest in the walker tonight? It's free and all my friends are leaving so I have nobody to go with... if you want some Marth or some Meg </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0234" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 16:58:47 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) time that's cool I just really wanna go again, with an artsy companion   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0235" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 17:00:23 UTC">
      <body>That sounds like a plan. I'm meeting a friend for some musicking for a while but I can go after? how late does it go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0236" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 17:06:37 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I think it's open til 9? I don't necessarily want to stay for a long time, maybe an hour or so. But definitely do your music thing for however long the </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0237" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 17:06:42 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) spirit moves ya</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0238" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 17:07:45 UTC">
      <body>I'll let you know. I have to run some errands too. But either way ill see where youre at</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0240" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 21:32:19 UTC">
      <body>No and I think you should go steady with her.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0241" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 21:32:26 UTC">
      <body>Because I came across her on cougarlife and I'm not sure...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0242" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 21:37:43 UTC">
      <body>Well I trust your judgement. She lists her interests as "meditative eating, snow angels, and gluing things". So right up my alley </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0243" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 21:55:34 UTC">
      <body>She didn't list dogs? She's reallllllly into dogs. Match made in heaven.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0244" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 21:59:44 UTC">
      <body>That's true! She did say that she was interested in "housebreaking a dirty dog". I think she's weird.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0245" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 22:00:24 UTC">
      <body>Yea not a euphemism</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0246" participant="131839" time="2011-07-14 22:37:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm worried I may not make it to the walker... Sorry in advance if not. But I still want to see you after if you want.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0247" participant="135117" time="2011-07-14 23:11:51 UTC">
      <body>No worries and absolutely I wanna see you. The deal is you have to sing me your songs cuz I have to get my art fix somewhere </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0249" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 02:36:03 UTC">
      <body>Ok I'll rap on the window </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0250" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 02:59:46 UTC">
      <body>Moonshine! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0251" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 12:33:04 UTC">
      <body>Last night was really wonderful. You can wake up at 630 and drive me to work any day you like. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0252" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 15:06:53 UTC">
      <body>Do you work today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0253" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 15:18:50 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) You know I appreciate those words Marth and I had a wonderful time too. Who knew talking could feel so good. And I think I could get used to six am if i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0254" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 15:19:00 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) t means waking up like that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0255" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 15:19:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah we're in the studio today. Rain's got me in a funk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0256" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 16:02:13 UTC">
      <body>It is gross and supposed to stay gross for a while. In the 100s next week. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0257" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 16:15:19 UTC">
      <body>So I hear. I'm gonna be nasty. Suddenly my cabin sounds like a great idea... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0258" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 16:15:50 UTC">
      <body>Also when's camping? The parks are gonna be open </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0259" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 16:17:40 UTC">
      <body>Youre getting out of town? Who knows for camping. August? I have a family reunion the first weekend. We'll have to compare calendars.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0260" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 17:54:49 UTC">
      <body>Well maybe next weekend I'm going to the cabin, we'll see. But I really do want to camp at some point </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0261" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 18:30:59 UTC">
      <body> We'll find a time. The sky has been so weird today. But hey I get done early.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0262" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 18:50:02 UTC">
      <body>I know shits freakin me out! What time are you done? And are you making plans with Meg? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0263" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 18:51:16 UTC">
      <body>She hasn't said anything so I don't know what she's thinking exactly. I'm done at 330.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0264" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 19:45:19 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) Well my plans involve definitely seeing you, maybe getting inappropriately intoxicated, saying some foolish and offensive things, apologizing, making ou</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0265" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 19:45:24 UTC">
      <body>(02/03) t quite a bit, possibly seeing some music or a movie, finding myself at a houseparty, skinny dipping in lake Calhoun and eating something greasy and del</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0266" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 19:45:29 UTC">
      <body>(03/03) icious. Not necessarily in that order. Or at all. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0267" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 19:49:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh man I already skinny dipped today. Everything else though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0268" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 20:02:54 UTC">
      <body>You have quite the sense of humor Stuckey. Sar cas m. I bet you've never even been skinny dipping </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0269" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 20:06:18 UTC">
      <body>I think I have... I've definitely done other things naked </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0270" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 20:11:16 UTC">
      <body>Do you have the house all to yourself this weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0271" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 20:11:52 UTC">
      <body>Well duh but skinny dipping is better than all the rest</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0272" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 20:12:03 UTC">
      <body>Yes! All by my lonesome </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0273" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 20:12:27 UTC">
      <body>Naked soccer is pretty fun.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0274" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 20:22:33 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Aight I could buy that. But it seems like you're left pretty vulnerable. I've taken some stingers to the midsection and that hurt with clothes on. So I'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0275" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 20:22:43 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) m sticking with skinny dipping. Also, when have you ever played soccer? I would kill to watch that  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0276" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 20:23:06 UTC">
      <body>Why??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0277" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 20:45:22 UTC">
      <body>Is this the beginning of the inappropriate and offensive remarks?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0278" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 21:07:36 UTC">
      <body>When do you work until?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0279" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 22:15:10 UTC">
      <body>Almost doneeee god I want weekend so vaf</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0280" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 22:19:58 UTC">
      <body>Finish up and come over. Don't your bosses know who I am?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0281" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 22:35:29 UTC">
      <body>Actually I told them all about you today so now they do. I have to take Sammie home in uptown so maybe an hour? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0282" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 22:36:24 UTC">
      <body>Did you really? Would it be better if I met you at colfax?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0283" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 22:50:50 UTC">
      <body>If you're cool with that that would be lovely but I'm fine coming over there. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0284" participant="131839" time="2011-07-15 22:51:45 UTC">
      <body>It doesnt matter either way, but you driving that much is crazy... Let me know when I should leave</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0285" participant="135117" time="2011-07-15 22:58:31 UTC">
      <body>Nowish! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0286" participant="131839" time="2011-07-16 21:55:37 UTC">
      <body>How's the presentation?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0287" participant="135117" time="2011-07-16 22:30:38 UTC">
      <body>Mmmm I got a little distracted by a crossword. Doing some now. Whatchu up to? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0288" participant="131839" time="2011-07-16 22:31:20 UTC">
      <body>I just got home. Did you finish it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0289" participant="135117" time="2011-07-16 22:36:21 UTC">
      <body>Nah but I didn't expect to. What's your fancy for the eve?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0290" participant="135117" time="2011-07-16 22:38:13 UTC">
      <body>The Dakota has an outdoor jazz fest if you're up for that. Otherwise I'm thinking of baking some mac and cheese. That's where my head's at</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0291" participant="131839" time="2011-07-16 22:38:17 UTC">
      <body>Nothing specific... Should I come over? Or are you working on stuff now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0292" participant="135117" time="2011-07-16 22:43:10 UTC">
      <body>Come on over in 30 maybe?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0293" participant="131839" time="2011-07-16 22:43:42 UTC">
      <body> Ok, but let me know if you need more time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0294" participant="135117" time="2011-07-16 23:48:42 UTC">
      <body>Hey if you haven't left yet can you bring some bread crumbs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0295" participant="135117" time="2011-07-17 22:49:35 UTC">
      <body>We're racing right? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0296" participant="131839" time="2011-07-17 22:49:47 UTC">
      <body>Quit texting!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0297" participant="135117" time="2011-07-17 22:50:26 UTC">
      <body>Likewise! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0298" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 00:47:30 UTC">
      <body>Hey I just didn't want to make ty uncomfortable and you caught me by surprise.  But that was sweet. Enjoy those helplessness blues</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0299" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 00:48:39 UTC">
      <body>Like clockwork. Don't worry. It's kind of you to think about it. Thanks for hanging and for the ride :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0300" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 14:49:18 UTC">
      <body>I secured today's crossword. No need to do something crazy and bike around town for it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0301" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 15:26:05 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Good work! Did you start it already? I'm working at the studio alone today so if you want I could swing by when I'm done and we could knock that sucker </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0302" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 15:26:10 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) out in no time. Also I was so out of it last night. The a.c. here makes me realize that my brain was only half working all weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0303" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 15:27:23 UTC">
      <body>I hear that. Yea, but let's do it somewhere cool. The heats making me loose it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0304" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:12:14 UTC">
      <body>Dont loose it! "Take me to the river" by the talking heads or "gimme shelter" by the stones? I live my life and make my decisions  through a series of lyrics</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0305" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:13:29 UTC">
      <body>LOSE it. Sorry. What decision are you making with those songs?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0306" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:15:18 UTC">
      <body>Keep cool by seeking a.c. (stones) or dropping into some water (heads)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0307" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:16:46 UTC">
      <body>Ohhh outside vs inside. I vote shelter at some point. Where do you drop into water?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0308" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Word. Calhoun or cedar or Harriet are nice. But a.c. is too. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0309" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:20:40 UTC">
      <body>Also, do I dare mention the thing (or person) you don't want me to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0310" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:22:28 UTC">
      <body>?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0311" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:22:45 UTC">
      <body>Sofie?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0312" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:39:48 UTC">
      <body>That bad, huh?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0313" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:41:31 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Noooo. Well really I just want to hang with you. But I suppose I could get that Sofie thing outta the way. Or maybe I could wait til Wed when Harley get</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0314" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:41:41 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) s back.  I dunno. You think it would be good for you to join us? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0315" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:43:04 UTC">
      <body>I mean I'd rather that too, but she's sort of on your case. Why do you think it would be good if I came with?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0316" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:50:43 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) It would be good because I like being with you. I'm just going to tell her Wed. No pressure to hang today if you don't want to. I just don't want to fee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0317" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 17:50:48 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) l obligated to hang with sof</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0318" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 17:54:11 UTC">
      <body>No no, I want to hang out anytime. I was just mentioning it i guess bc it would maybe look weird if you didn't? Ugh who knows. I don't want to be all calculating as such. Do whatever you think is best and I'll stay out of it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0319" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 19:03:20 UTC">
      <body>Taken care of. Date on Wed. And I appreciate your opinion! Not a big deal at all. Hope you're staying cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0320" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 19:04:56 UTC">
      <body>Yea, but it's your friendship with her and I want to respect that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0321" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 19:10:05 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know but also I wasn't even hanging out with her before you got here so don't feel responsible! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0322" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 19:30:59 UTC">
      <body>Mmk, just trying to be fair. :) so Travis wants to drink some wine around like 7? But can we still do crosswording for a little bit?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0323" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 20:12:07 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Of course. And I'm glad you're drinking with trav. I'll call you when I'm done</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0324" participant="131839" time="2011-07-18 21:43:59 UTC">
      <body> I'm going to sex world with Reg....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0325" participant="135117" time="2011-07-18 22:16:42 UTC">
      <body>Hell yeah. I can't wait to hear about that. Gonna be done in a half hour</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0326" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 01:50:10 UTC">
      <body>How's grilling?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0327" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:03:56 UTC">
      <body>So good marth. Steak and beer. How's the classy crowd? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0328" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:05:27 UTC">
      <body>They're good. Just leaving the restaurant and going to travs.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0329" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:16:20 UTC">
      <body>Okay well I've gotten myself a bit drunk but I think you should come over when you're done with trav</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0330" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:21:21 UTC">
      <body>And we just did the thing where you smack your mouth to make a sound! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0331" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:21:49 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god. Im on my way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0332" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:22:53 UTC">
      <body>Gooooooood</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0333" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:23:31 UTC">
      <body>I was sort of joking, but I'll come over in a bit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0334" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:24:13 UTC">
      <body>Also, do you know any big burly gay men? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0335" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:24:45 UTC">
      <body>OK good one. Come whenever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0337" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:26:09 UTC">
      <body>In town I mean. And please just come out if you're gay and leave me alone.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0338" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 02:33:28 UTC">
      <body>Am I giving off a gay vibe? Once you out yourself as a lesbian. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0339" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 02:34:15 UTC">
      <body>You just said you were gay... Those kinds of gay vibes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0340" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 13:45:15 UTC">
      <body>Nine letter word for how I'm feeling right now. Begins with e and ends with d.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0341" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 13:54:15 UTC">
      <body>Exhausted. Here's the kicker though, you got an hour and a half more than me but im not complaining... Well worth it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0342" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 14:23:39 UTC">
      <body>True but you're at least one and a half times more resilient than me! Got today's crossword? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0343" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 14:26:57 UTC">
      <body>Just secured it. Getting the receptionist trained to grab it for me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0344" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 14:42:05 UTC">
      <body>Very nice. Taking advantage of your peons </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0345" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 14:54:30 UTC">
      <body>I forgot why you said that you didn't have to present today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0346" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 14:56:30 UTC">
      <body>Because we got a really important order for some chairs so building those today. Ill send some pics </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0348" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 15:10:50 UTC">
      <body>Whaaa? Pooties bday today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0349" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 15:30:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh man, you're outside? Nice chair!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0350" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 15:32:05 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah outside it's hawt. And you gotta believe me it will look nice! Is it really your mom's bday? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0351" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 15:32:53 UTC">
      <body>Yea it is. It'd be a weird joke if it wasn't. Will you send me a picture of the finished p?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0352" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 15:34:54 UTC">
      <body>Of course. Did you forget about her bday? Or get her anything? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0353" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 15:35:50 UTC">
      <body>I called her this morning... Didn't get her anything though... Maybe I'll send her a card? But yea I forgot that July 19 was coming up and that it is also her birthday on that day.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0354" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 16:01:38 UTC">
      <body>Rachel, the journalism major, sent me this text: "Can I put your fan going?"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0355" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:28:24 UTC">
      <body>Geez thoughtful daughter you are. Maybe you should at least send her a card! Did you tell rach she may can has that fans? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0356" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:28:45 UTC">
      <body>Holy hail! We're being stormed on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0357" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 16:30:55 UTC">
      <body>I'll see shannie this weekend. Where are you at? Minneapolis? Is it going to mess up my car?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0358" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:33:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah up in st Anthony village. I don't know dude it's pretty crazy but your car should be ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0359" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:34:08 UTC">
      <body>Is it not storming there? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0360" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 16:37:13 UTC">
      <body>Btw im g chatting with Sofie and I'm having a coniption fit. But yea it's really dark. The whole office is at my desk bc I have the most windows.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0361" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:38:33 UTC">
      <body>Haha nice. What kind of fit? The sirens going off! Sheet! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0362" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 16:39:23 UTC">
      <body>Be safe...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0363" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:42:08 UTC">
      <body>Always</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0364" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 16:44:01 UTC">
      <body>Why are you having a coniption fit? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0365" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 16:48:37 UTC">
      <body>Shes talking about how you should come to the cabin and how I should ask you to car pool with me and she's moving to uptown and will be at your house a lot etc etc </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0366" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 17:48:17 UTC">
      <body>When are you coming over to do the crossword today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0367" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 17:58:36 UTC">
      <body>I don't understand ... explain later. Probably working later today but not sure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0368" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 18:16:51 UTC">
      <body>Looks like you guys have been working hard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0369" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 21:45:04 UTC">
      <body>Pretty nice! When do they become chairs?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0370" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 22:29:57 UTC">
      <body>Beautiful! Art! Do you ride those bikes after? Man, you should see how sweaty I am right now. Cleaning just made me so nasty. That tub probably wasn't cleaned for a fucking year.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0371" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 22:38:21 UTC">
      <body>That's nasty but I bet I could give you a run for your money. Just heading out now, you have plans for the Eve?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0372" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 22:39:06 UTC">
      <body>I'm just finishing up stuff here, but nope. Thought about hanging about with my boyfriend. He says hi by the way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0373" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 22:44:32 UTC">
      <body>I'm about to get in the shower. Do you want to come here? Or should I go there? I'm sort of hungry...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0374" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 22:55:23 UTC">
      <body>You have a boyfriend? Tell him I'll fight him for the title </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0375" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 23:00:53 UTC">
      <body>Easy... So? Are you hanging out with your girlfriend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0376" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 23:04:00 UTC">
      <body>I'd like to but it seems like she's busy tonight. Which is too bad cuz I was thinking of cooking her some dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0377" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 23:04:39 UTC">
      <body>What a bitch. I like food?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0378" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 23:06:03 UTC">
      <body>Do you want to take on her role? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0379" participant="131839" time="2011-07-19 23:06:21 UTC">
      <body>Um... I'll eat.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0380" participant="135117" time="2011-07-19 23:12:12 UTC">
      <body>OK well that's a start. You wanna come here or me go there? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0381" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 14:06:17 UTC">
      <body>Ok, you have to hang out with Sofie but... Reg wants me to go out to the farm and check out the a/c. It would be an adventure!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0382" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 15:14:10 UTC">
      <body>Oh hell yes! Do you want to go before or after sof? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0383" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 15:15:34 UTC">
      <body>Whenever works, I don't have plans so we can work around you and sof. Its about 45 mins away though so it'll be a couple hours </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0384" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 15:17:05 UTC">
      <body>If it doesn't work that's ok too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0385" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 15:24:24 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Well I'm hoping to get done early so maybe soon after you get off work? I would not miss this. I wanna see the compound, farmer, and the legend herself.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0386" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 15:24:29 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  And maybe catch a glimpse of the swing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0387" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 17:01:05 UTC">
      <body>Ok, that should work. It's pretty far north so traffic shouldn't be so bad. Do you know when approximately? Also remind me to tell you about what she was searching earlier. Do you know a Claire Vincent?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0388" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 17:04:40 UTC">
      <body>I think I'm gonna try to be outta here by 330 and am definitely going to need a shower. You should think of some good roadtrip music and bring the crossword! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0389" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 17:05:13 UTC">
      <body>I gave the crossword to you! I have yesterday's though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0390" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 17:05:36 UTC">
      <body>And yes I definitely know Claire, she was Molly's roommate. Why? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0391" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 17:06:13 UTC">
      <body>The girl I lived in Vera with knows her... Small world!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0392" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 17:06:58 UTC">
      <body>Ok good I'm about to read that article on my lunch break </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0393" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 17:08:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah she's a strange little woman. Nice though </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0394" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 17:08:47 UTC">
      <body>So is Julie. Also nice. They did gymnastics together</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0395" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 20:20:21 UTC">
      <body>Reg took me home early so I'm ready whenever you are :) she said to bring your swimsuit to jump in the lake...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0396" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 20:35:36 UTC">
      <body>Cool well I'm gonna shower and then should I come over there? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0397" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 20:36:03 UTC">
      <body>Yea it's probably better to leave from here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0398" participant="135117" time="2011-07-20 20:37:03 UTC">
      <body>Alright probably will be about an hour</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0399" participant="131839" time="2011-07-20 20:37:23 UTC">
      <body>Ok :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0400" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 13:19:06 UTC">
      <body>That was super delicious. Sorry about the rush this morning. But more importantly, thank you for yesterday. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0401" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 13:53:52 UTC">
      <body>That was super delicious. And what are you thanking me for? Thank YOU for yesterday. So much fun. How's your sexy dress going over Joan halloway? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0402" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 13:56:50 UTC">
      <body>Nobody has said anything so that's either good bc it's not so crazy or bad bc it's that crazy. I'm thanking you bc yesterday was actually one of the best yesterdays I've ever had and you had something to do with it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0403" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 14:52:29 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Are you sure that it wasn't just the a.c. that had something to do with it? Despite what my lethargy in bed would lead you to believe, I had such a terr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0404" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 14:52:39 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ific time too. You're pretty damn good Marth.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0405" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 15:04:35 UTC">
      <body>No you are. You would not believe the story Reg just told me about what farmer did to get a calf to nurse... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0406" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 15:04:52 UTC">
      <body>I'm about to ask if he's ever killed someone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0407" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 15:08:01 UTC">
      <body>Whaaa? Ok sounds like a good one. Maybe you shouldn't ask that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0408" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 22:03:39 UTC">
      <body>You won't come after Reg asked you to come?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0409" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 22:10:04 UTC">
      <body>Dude I'm still working! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0410" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 22:10:49 UTC">
      <body>I know I know I'm just kidding. But she is in rare form!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0411" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 22:15:38 UTC">
      <body>Damn I can tell</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0412" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 22:55:02 UTC">
      <body>What's the plan for latet freebird? Shall I pick you up? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0413" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 22:55:58 UTC">
      <body>Yea, or you could come! Or not. You have to relax after work. But yea probably you'll have to pick me up...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0414" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 22:57:26 UTC">
      <body>Just getting home and gotta do some stuff but call me when you want a ride</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0415" participant="131839" time="2011-07-21 22:57:42 UTC">
      <body>Will do. Im drunk.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0416" participant="135117" time="2011-07-21 22:58:58 UTC">
      <body>YESSSSS!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0417" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 00:08:15 UTC">
      <body>You wan to head over? In at 508 club</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0418" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:07:16 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Kickin in the front seat sittin in the back seat, gotta make my mind up which seat will I take ... Friday Friday gotta get down on Friday, everybodys lo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0419" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:07:26 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) okin forward to the weekend yeah! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0420" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:07:57 UTC">
      <body>Happy Friday! Love, your 13 year old friend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0421" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 13:08:46 UTC">
      <body>What. Is that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0422" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:10:51 UTC">
      <body>Rebecca black? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0423" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:11:01 UTC">
      <body>Come on culture vulture! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0424" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 13:33:14 UTC">
      <body>Ohhhh ok. Still. 13 year old friend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0425" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:41:24 UTC">
      <body>Because 13 year olds love that song. Cmon Marth </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0426" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 13:41:45 UTC">
      <body>Yea ok, the joke is funny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0427" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:42:30 UTC">
      <body>Also, I could have laid in bed with you for another hour </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0428" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:43:11 UTC">
      <body>Ok so my jokes aren't funny!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0429" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 13:43:48 UTC">
      <body>Hah. I think you're really funny. Quit it. Only another hour?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0430" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:45:14 UTC">
      <body>Well I was going to say a day but thought that might be excessive </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0431" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 13:47:07 UTC">
      <body>Be excessive. I like excessive.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0432" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 13:52:50 UTC">
      <body>I have a hard time with excessive but Id like to try </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0433" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 14:00:10 UTC">
      <body>You know I eat all my meals from a cup</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0434" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 14:16:57 UTC">
      <body>You have a hard time with excessive?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0435" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 14:19:53 UTC">
      <body>I have a hard time with overzealous. But I guess that's different </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0436" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 14:20:24 UTC">
      <body>Saw that vid of the barbarians, looked awk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0437" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 14:24:39 UTC">
      <body>Just watched it. Super awk...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0438" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 14:28:30 UTC">
      <body>But good that they did it. You've got a clever friend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0439" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 15:12:01 UTC">
      <body>He's just not much of a performer. His draw is that he's calm, not raucous. He could use some showmanship</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0440" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 15:17:39 UTC">
      <body>Well that's where he could have used Peter. Or you! Aren't you a self-described "friend of the gays" AND an actor? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0441" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 15:18:34 UTC">
      <body>For real. Yea, I could 'direct' in a way... But I'm ok being help on the outside</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0442" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 15:20:49 UTC">
      <body>You sure you can't convince Galvin to come up to my cabin this weekend? He can hang in nu next weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0443" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 15:21:15 UTC">
      <body>Not if he's up at the other cabin next weekend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0444" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 15:34:13 UTC">
      <body>Precisely my point. I'm just throwing out unreasonable scenarios with the hope that you might bite. Man it's a beautiful summer day. How's the corporate world? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0445" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 15:35:17 UTC">
      <body>You know I want to bite. Ugh. The corporate world is stifling. I feel bad about being a bad worker. Still texting at my desk... Pats here though! About to meet him :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0446" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 15:42:25 UTC">
      <body>Yeahhhh! Please give pickles a big hug and a dramatic lift for me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0447" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:18:24 UTC">
      <body>Hey I remembered: you should ask Galvin if you can borrow his copy of freedom aka America </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0448" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Does he have it in new ulm?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0449" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:28:28 UTC">
      <body>I know he did at one point but you'll have to ask the man. If you want to read it that is </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0450" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:29:13 UTC">
      <body>What about your mom? Has she finished yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0451" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:31:37 UTC">
      <body>I think they were gonna discuss it sometime at the end of July so I dunno? You gonna go say hey? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0452" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:32:24 UTC">
      <body>To your mom?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0453" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:40:04 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, then you could get the book from her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0454" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:40:30 UTC">
      <body>I mean, I said hey to Shan...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0455" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:41:12 UTC">
      <body>I'll see if pat has it, esp if she's going to need it at the end of the month. I'd love to see Eileen!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0456" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:46:08 UTC">
      <body>Well I can definitively say that if you and pickles and Katie paid her a visit she would feel like the coolest mom in the world </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0457" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:46:29 UTC">
      <body>I think she's lonely </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0458" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:46:56 UTC">
      <body>Mmk, well we might do that. :) so it would be even better if you came too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0459" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 17:51:15 UTC">
      <body>You're killing me mad-e. You have no idea how torn I get about these kinds of things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0460" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 17:53:45 UTC">
      <body>Don't do anything because you feel guilt. I'll understand either way, really. Don't want to be that girlfriend. I'm just being selfish and want my main guys in a room together.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0461" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:02:26 UTC">
      <body>And I would do anything to avoid being in a room where ny main girls are together ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0462" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 18:03:06 UTC">
      <body>Are you really avoiding that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0463" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:03:12 UTC">
      <body>Kidding. I'm just torn because I know I would have fun in nu. No guilt</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0464" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:12:45 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) No, not at all! In fact I'm looking forward to it in an odd way. Kind of the same way I look forward to olaf parties: something that needs to be done an</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0466" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:13:21 UTC">
      <body>So the sooner the better </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0467" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:25:39 UTC">
      <body>Ok too far ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0468" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 18:34:22 UTC">
      <body>No no I couldn't tell if you were joking and didn't know which I preferred... Hah. I was just raving a little bit about things during lunch and wanted you to be there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0469" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:41:15 UTC">
      <body>What were you raving about? Gay rights? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0470" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 18:41:33 UTC">
      <body>Shut up. You. And us.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0471" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:54:19 UTC">
      <body>Oh! For some reason I thought you meant ranting. Who were you raving to? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0472" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 18:54:54 UTC">
      <body>Pat!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0473" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 18:55:15 UTC">
      <body>And yiu wanted me there so they wouldnt think you were making it all up like bean? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0474" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 18:56:06 UTC">
      <body>No I was thinking about how it would be nice to be around you, around pat. Maybe bc I was sounding like bean.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0475" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 19:03:42 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) That's sweet of you.  Were you eating a turkey sandwich because that might have had something to do with it. I know what you mean though. How did ge rea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0476" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 19:03:52 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ct? I guess I'd like to know where he stands on the whole thing. Maybe I should ask him...yep.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0477" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 19:15:54 UTC">
      <body> He's excited for us I think. He knows its complicated for us but is happy for us. But it can't hurt to talk to him about it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0478" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 20:38:08 UTC">
      <body>When are you done?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0479" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 20:39:01 UTC">
      <body>Now! I'm so fuckin tuckered </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0480" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 20:39:32 UTC">
      <body>When are you and Galvin getting outta dodge? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0481" participant="131839" time="2011-07-22 20:52:23 UTC">
      <body>Well he ended up not going to the mall so we could stop by if you want?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0482" participant="135117" time="2011-07-22 20:53:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah! I'm shaving and gonna shower but come by whenever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0483" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 00:31:45 UTC">
      <body>Are you there yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0484" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 01:59:52 UTC">
      <body>Hey sorry bout that craziness, just trying to figure out where we were going. Hope you have a lovely time with the crew. Wish we could be hanging </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0485" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 02:15:15 UTC">
      <body>I'm super drunk tim. I want to say things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0486" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 02:30:36 UTC">
      <body>Ok. Well forget it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0487" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:31:31 UTC">
      <body>Noo! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0488" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:31:46 UTC">
      <body>Say things! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0489" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:32:27 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I'm driving but please do...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0490" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 02:46:19 UTC">
      <body>Never</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0491" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:47:03 UTC">
      <body>Plereeasr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0492" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 02:47:37 UTC">
      <body>Are you driving?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0493" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:48:20 UTC">
      <body>Yes but no fair</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0494" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 02:48:33 UTC">
      <body> Stop doing that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0495" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 02:49:42 UTC">
      <body>OK </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0496" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 03:13:10 UTC">
      <body>But you're killing me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0497" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 03:24:27 UTC">
      <body>You're still not there?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0498" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 03:26:54 UTC">
      <body>Late start and then Culvers! But plase let me entertain your thoughts </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0499" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 04:08:33 UTC">
      <body>Stopped for some mt. Dew in pine river. Did you sober up? That would be unfortunate. Howz PG? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0500" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 06:10:29 UTC">
      <body>Goodnight pretty woman. Hope you sleep soundly.@ Wish I could be doing that with you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0501" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 13:07:50 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry to be so unavailable last night. I passed out, clearly... Where's my burrito this morning??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0502" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 16:25:09 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Ha! Well you have yet to "say things ". In lieu of the weekday burrito the chef will be serving the cabin specialty : blueberry pancakes with real maple</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0503" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 16:25:18 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  syrup and a bottomless cup of coffee. You dig? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0504" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 16:44:03 UTC">
      <body>Oo you mean.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0505" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 17:51:35 UTC">
      <body>I'm missing you, boy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0506" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 17:54:08 UTC">
      <body>Likewise, girl. We could be laying in the hammock right now.  Just read a new Yorker article that reminded me of you. It was about GaGa and sasha fierce </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0507" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 17:55:09 UTC">
      <body>Comparing them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0508" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 18:01:59 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. He seemed to be much more of a fan of Sasha's music. Which I tend to agree with. And more a fan of gagas showmanship</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0509" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 18:42:36 UTC">
      <body>I would agree with that. I'm up at Galvin's! It's gorgeousssssss</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0510" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 18:55:55 UTC">
      <body>Say hey to Craig and Cathy! Going on a boat trip!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0511" participant="131839" time="2011-07-23 22:34:48 UTC">
      <body>Guess who is about to get here... I'm nervous.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0512" participant="135117" time="2011-07-23 23:05:46 UTC">
      <body>Just relax and be yourself! Remember you guys are friends and have lots to talk about other than us. Don't feel like you have to put on an act</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0513" participant="135117" time="2011-07-24 02:43:58 UTC">
      <body>Having fun? Call me when you're done? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0514" participant="131839" time="2011-07-24 03:05:39 UTC">
      <body>It's ok. Trying to steer the convo. Guilty conscious dude. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0515" participant="135117" time="2011-07-24 03:08:37 UTC">
      <body>Mmm I'm sorry. Listen, if you feel like you need to get it off your chest please do it. I'm pulling for you...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0516" participant="131839" time="2011-07-24 18:11:07 UTC">
      <body>Hey crazy. When are you getting home?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0517" participant="135117" time="2011-07-24 19:07:27 UTC">
      <body>Crazy huh? I think we'll get back around 8. You? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0518" participant="131839" time="2011-07-24 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure bc im going to katies parents thing... 8 or later.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0519" participant="135117" time="2011-07-24 20:05:44 UTC">
      <body>Well if you're not too tuckered out from all that dancing I'd love to see ya</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0520" participant="131839" time="2011-07-24 20:06:48 UTC">
      <body>Yea, I was hoping to see you anyway</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0521" participant="135117" time="2011-07-24 20:07:37 UTC">
      <body>Good it's a date! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0522" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 02:33:09 UTC">
      <body>Where you at Stuckey? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0523" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 02:33:33 UTC">
      <body>Half hour away or less</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0524" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 02:35:42 UTC">
      <body>NO TEXTING AND DRIVING!!!!!!!!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0525" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 02:35:47 UTC">
      <body>You wanna come over? Or can I come see you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0526" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 02:58:13 UTC">
      <body>You can leave noe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0527" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 02:58:19 UTC">
      <body>Now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0528" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 03:00:27 UTC">
      <body>NO TEXTING!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0529" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 14:43:36 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Martha I couldn't help myself this morning. I get excited to wake up next to such a beautiful woman. My timing can be off so apologies for that but man </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0530" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 14:43:41 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) you make me feel good in so many ways</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0531" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 14:48:27 UTC">
      <body>It's ok, I got to work on time anyway. :) really, no need to apologize unless you feel the need to do something tragically romantic to make up for it. Man, I am beat.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0532" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 17:12:01 UTC">
      <body>Hey! Good luck! Did you do it already? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0533" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 17:28:28 UTC">
      <body>Not yet! We're at the walker installing chairs!thanks! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0534" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 20:14:38 UTC">
      <body>When are you done today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0535" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 21:11:27 UTC">
      <body>Hopefully soon? Five? Wanna shop? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0536" participant="135117" time="2011-07-25 21:14:25 UTC">
      <body>Balllls Katie invited me to this thing in st paul</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0537" participant="131839" time="2011-07-25 21:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Ooooo. When is it? And what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0538" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 14:59:52 UTC">
      <body>I think you should still go
to the cabin...? I think.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0539" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:31:03 UTC">
      <body>I think I should too. If shit gets heavy  I can go off and read by myself. And why do you think? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0540" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:32:25 UTC">
      <body>Well I can't afford to drive myself, I want to be around you, and you should see your friends even if they earn Nigerian money. But it's complicated and might be a mindfuck.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0541" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:37:16 UTC">
      <body>Well I don't think it will be that much of a mindfuck. Tessa wants to drive up together. I know that probably doesn't interest you at all ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0542" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:38:02 UTC">
      <body>Also, I'm going to have to drive back to the cities early Sunday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0543" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:38:38 UTC">
      <body>Did she ask you to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0544" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:40:21 UTC">
      <body>Yeah she asked if I wanted to carpool. I didn't tell her that I have to come back on Sunday though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0545" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:42:09 UTC">
      <body>I think Katie and pat
Fly out on sunday and have to get back early too. I don't know. I sort of really don't want to go.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0546" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:46:41 UTC">
      <body>I know Marth. You really don't have to. But I also don't think it will be that bad. Basically one full day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0547" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:48:27 UTC">
      <body>I'm just not in a good place with it. And I feel like I'm too old to be putting myself in this sort of situation.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0548" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:49:44 UTC">
      <body>What sort of situation? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0549" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:51:23 UTC">
      <body>Going out of my way to hang out with "friends"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0550" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:56:28 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I hear you loud and clear. I really think you shouldn't go if you feel that way. I feel the same way but I do want to spend some time with Galvin and So</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0551" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 15:56:33 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) fie I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0552" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 15:59:37 UTC">
      <body>Yea. Ok. I had caffeine and I think it's making me overly anxious this morning.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0553" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 16:02:47 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Haha really?coffee? Id love to see that! I think either way it will be fine. If you go it's basically spending a full day with a few people you care abo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0554" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 16:02:52 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ut and if you don't you'll just be missing out on a few people you don't care about. Either way, nobody will be offended</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0555" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 17:46:34 UTC">
      <body>What say you to doing some shopping, making some din, and watching a movie with my boy Joe this Eve? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0556" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 17:48:36 UTC">
      <body>Or without joe. I just want to watch Darjeeling </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0557" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 17:49:22 UTC">
      <body>And play with you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0558" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 17:50:39 UTC">
      <body>Music, that is. Play music with you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0559" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 17:54:04 UTC">
      <body>You really want to play music?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0561" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 19:14:47 UTC">
      <body>That's weird...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0562" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 19:20:46 UTC">
      <body>What did he say? I'm ashamedly freaked </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0563" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 19:22:57 UTC">
      <body>I'm talking him down Right now. Ugh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0564" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 19:47:43 UTC">
      <body>If he comes after me you have to protect me you know, it's your responsibility now. When are you done today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0565" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 19:55:45 UTC">
      <body>I'll protect you! Maybe done around five? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0566" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 21:43:40 UTC">
      <body>Come find me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0567" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 21:47:01 UTC">
      <body>I want to! I'm gonna be working late</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0568" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 21:47:15 UTC">
      <body>  How late?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0569" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 22:20:43 UTC">
      <body>Probably home and done showering in an hour? Wanna go then? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0570" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 22:31:54 UTC">
      <body> Mmk, I'll meet you there? The only thing is the target is closer to me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0571" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 22:32:06 UTC">
      <body>You could shower here if you want?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0572" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 22:48:48 UTC">
      <body>Well I have to bring Sammie home and he lives near me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0573" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 22:49:35 UTC">
      <body>Right. I'll just run to target before. Did you say 630?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0574" participant="135117" time="2011-07-26 23:07:24 UTC">
      <body>Maybe 645. ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0575" participant="131839" time="2011-07-26 23:08:53 UTC">
      <body>That's cool I might be later anyway</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0576" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 00:29:10 UTC">
      <body>What's wrong? Sorry to do that to this</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0577" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 00:29:24 UTC">
      <body>To you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0578" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 00:34:44 UTC">
      <body>My anxiety is really bad this week and today. Im going to travis' for a little bit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0579" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 00:40:35 UTC">
      <body>Ok well I'm really sorry I should have been more communicative. Is there anything I can do? Anything I did that I need to not do in the future? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0580" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 01:02:05 UTC">
      <body>Are you upset with me Martha? And do you want a brat? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0581" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 01:14:53 UTC">
      <body>I'll be over in a bit. I'm self medicating. So I probably will want that brat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0582" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 01:17:12 UTC">
      <body>Aha! Gooood! There also might be sour patch kids...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0583" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 12:36:53 UTC">
      <body> Are we ok? Im sorry things have been so stressful.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0584" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 13:01:51 UTC">
      <body>Sir.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0585" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 13:54:48 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Yes ma'am just exhausted in many ways I think. I really appreciate having those convos even if they are draining. Like I said last night, it's still ger</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0586" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 13:54:53 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) y worth it. I just want to see you happier.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0587" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 13:55:30 UTC">
      <body>Also you left your silly band at my house </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0588" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 13:59:00 UTC">
      <body> Fuckkkkk. Sorry :/ babies are just going to start having parties in my belly now. I think we do need to sleep more bc then I'll be able to handle everything better. And like you asked, I won't ask you those things again.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0589" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 17:13:03 UTC">
      <body>Are you holding up ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0590" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 17:15:45 UTC">
      <body>Yeah a lil pooped but good.  Long afternoon ahead. But it's still worth it. You? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0591" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 17:21:43 UTC">
      <body>Pretty tired. And im just feeling bad about yesterday. Im sorry it was such a shit show</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0592" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 17:27:11 UTC">
      <body>Please don't apologize for emotions. Shits hard. Tonight will be fun though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0593" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 17:30:03 UTC">
      <body>I wasn't really apologizing for the emotions as much as how they played out. But yea, let's not get caught up in it. Or I shouldn't. Yea, I think pat is going to meet me at my house? And then we'll bus in? But if he's staying at your house that might not make sense for his car to be at my house</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0594" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 17:33:57 UTC">
      <body>Yeah he should just come to my house. But I can probs pick you up around 6</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0595" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 17:43:59 UTC">
      <body>Mmk, is your house unlocked? Or should he go to urban bean and wait for us?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0596" participant="135117" time="2011-07-27 17:45:58 UTC">
      <body>Dunno if it will be unlocked or who will be there. Maybe he should find a place just in case. What time is he getting up? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0597" participant="131839" time="2011-07-27 17:47:37 UTC">
      <body>530, so he won't be waiting too long</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0598" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 05:14:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow. I'm sorry Martha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0599" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 05:14:23 UTC">
      <body>For what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0600" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 05:23:43 UTC">
      <body>Just wanted to be with you tonight but feel like I gotta tend to Ross </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0601" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 05:24:13 UTC">
      <body>Did you tell him?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0602" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 05:59:49 UTC">
      <body>No but I'm tempted to. I'll try to hold back </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0603" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 12:05:00 UTC">
      <body>I'm pretty sure he already knows for whatever reason. I thought you guys were already talking about it at lyle's</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0604" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 12:49:54 UTC">
      <body>Let's go to Paris.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0605" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 14:38:28 UTC">
      <body>Yes let's go to Paris! But what prompted that? And why do you think Ross knows? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0606" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 14:53:12 UTC">
      <body>Listening to Edith Piaf and wanting to be there in summer. And wanting to be with you. Did you see last night when he shook his head at me and pointed at what I thought was you and me and did the 'my lips are sealed' gesture and giggled when i tried to act like i didnt know what he was talking about. I have no idea what else he could have been referring to...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0607" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 15:06:43 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I totally missed that. How would he know though? I would like to tell him ... last night just wasn't the right time. I am so tired and hungover. I want </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0608" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 15:06:48 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) an easy evening. And hopefully you can be there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0609" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 15:11:59 UTC">
      <body>I think we should tell him too. Especially bc he's going to be here this summer and hiding it for the time we have left would be soul crushing. I think he knows bc Ross can read me and probably you pretty well. And then he did that thing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0610" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 15:13:35 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry you're in bad shape :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0611" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 15:18:29 UTC">
      <body>Aight I def agree. But maybe in addition to Paris, Ireland? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0612" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 15:29:50 UTC">
      <body>I had a physical this morning and she prescribed me adavan. I was like "WHAT my pills were hypNOTics?? AND they're addictive??? No!"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0613" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 15:36:25 UTC">
      <body>Wait what's adavan? Are you okay? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0614" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 15:37:23 UTC">
      <body>Ativan, I spelled it wrong. It's prescribed muscle Relaxers. She thinks im ok, so I hid it pretty well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0615" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 15:45:17 UTC">
      <body>Oho nice! Are you actually OK though? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0616" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 15:49:39 UTC">
      <body>It was just a normal physical, why do you ask?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0617" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 16:07:19 UTC">
      <body>Well you made it sound like you hid the fact that you weren't feeling well </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0618" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 16:49:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh no, I hid the fact I was abusing the drug she prescribed me more of.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0619" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 17:07:09 UTC">
      <body>That's the sign of a good addict. So you're down on Ireland? I guess I could compromise and go with Barcelona </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0620" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 18:30:47 UTC">
      <body>You have any plans for tonight mademoiselle? Is Galvin gonna be around still? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0621" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 18:32:53 UTC">
      <body>Barcelona and Ireland please. I just have to get to the mall and I'll probably go right after work. After that im free :). No pat, no Ross, nobody.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0622" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 18:33:15 UTC">
      <body>Unless you have plans to grill with someone and havent told me yet.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0623" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 18:40:41 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Well maybe not Ross, who knows. And if I have plans to grill I wouldn't tell you until later anyway. Here are some possibilities : making some din, goin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0624" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 18:40:46 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) g to a museum (walker or MIA), watching that movie, or the new episode of weeds, making out, sleeping early, etc. Interested? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0625" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:01:17 UTC">
      <body>Wait, ross really might be there? And all of that sounds good. I want to see your chairs. And weeds. Were two behind now? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0626" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:06:59 UTC">
      <body> And when are you done today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0627" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 19:19:46 UTC">
      <body>Probably done around five or so. And I don't know about Ross, he seemed like he had no plans... I think we're only one behind</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0628" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:20:59 UTC">
      <body>Do you want to hang out with Ross?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0629" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 19:23:51 UTC">
      <body>Mmm I dunno I'd be fine with it but I'd really like to hang out with you since I won't be able to for quite a while </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0630" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:25:38 UTC">
      <body>Yea I don't really want to. Did you tell him you would?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0631" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 19:26:30 UTC">
      <body>No </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0632" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:27:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah. You are a labyrinth. Why did you say he'd be there then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0633" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 19:34:42 UTC">
      <body>I love labyrinths! I just have no idea what Ross was gonna do today. He slept at my house and I don't know if he left </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0634" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 19:40:51 UTC">
      <body>Oh I see. Well. Do you think we could tell him before the cabin?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0635" participant="131839" time="2011-07-28 22:55:10 UTC">
      <body>Where you at? Still working?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0636" participant="135117" time="2011-07-28 23:02:09 UTC">
      <body>Just got home wanna come over? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0637" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:23:58 UTC">
      <body>OK so can my code be any time someone mentions Harvard or public health initiatives or any African country, that's when I would like to run off into the woods</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0638" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 14:25:49 UTC">
      <body>It's like a drinking game. I'll share my drugs and we can get a little bit riskier. The codes not just for sex though...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0639" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:32:15 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Oh I know it's not for sex, that would be irresponsible. Just to let you know that I'm there watching you amusedly and thinking of you fondly. Yes pleas</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0640" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:32:21 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) e to muscle relaxing. I hope you have enough, I'm gonna need it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0641" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 14:33:18 UTC">
      <body>I'll be generous. So what's your code?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0642" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:38:44 UTC">
      <body>What do you mean? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0643" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:40:06 UTC">
      <body>Maybe any time code "doctors without borders" is enacted, you can offer me a drink </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0644" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 14:40:08 UTC">
      <body>What do YOU mean? I was thinking the code would be what we would say. But it can be what other people say if you want</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0645" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 14:42:35 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it's what we say. I plan on bringing that stuff up a lot </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0646" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 14:53:01 UTC">
      <body>:) I want to go back to last night at sunset and just stay there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0647" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 15:08:26 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that was beautiful. You know I'm not so worried about this weekend I think it will be lovely </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0648" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 15:14:32 UTC">
      <body>How are you so sure?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0649" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 15:16:48 UTC">
      <body>I just think there will be plenty of other distractions and we'll be there for like 36 hours. That ain't no thang</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0650" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 16:29:53 UTC">
      <body>Yea. It's just hard to have on my mind. But i could use that positive thinking</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0651" participant="135117" time="2011-07-29 18:31:53 UTC">
      <body>Do you want to be a television or film actress? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0652" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 18:43:29 UTC">
      <body>I mean I wouldn't completely shy away from the idea, but it'd have to be the right piece. Its more based on content than media I guess.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0653" participant="131839" time="2011-07-29 18:43:38 UTC">
      <body>Why?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0654" participant="135117" time="2011-07-30 07:42:03 UTC">
      <body>Let me tell you a little something about Eritrea </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0655" participant="131839" time="2011-07-30 07:43:37 UTC">
      <body>Yea? Francophone? Land locked? How's the health care?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0656" participant="135117" time="2011-07-30 09:36:39 UTC">
      <body>It's repressive and leaves much to be desired. Much like, the current situation </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0657" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 00:12:26 UTC">
      <body>I kind of enjoy watching you be peaceful </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0658" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 05:57:47 UTC">
      <body>Why the long face Martha? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0659" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 06:00:56 UTC">
      <body>No real long face. Just hard to hide. I just want to be with you and talk to you. It's hard to remember this is happening and that you like me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0660" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 06:04:16 UTC">
      <body>OK well this is killing me. I can't wait until I dont have to pretend. Did I totally turn you off this weekend? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0661" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 06:05:09 UTC">
      <body>No not at all. The opposite. Why do you say that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0662" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 06:09:13 UTC">
      <body>Its just hard to read you when we can't have an actual conversation. I wish I was in the room next door ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0663" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 06:10:18 UTC">
      <body>It's hard to have an actual conversation given the circumstances. Did I turn you off?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0664" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 06:17:40 UTC">
      <body>Not at all. Watching you swim and float was exhilaratig. Just wish I could have told you. Goodnight pretty lady </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0665" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 06:44:41 UTC">
      <body> </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0666" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 21:39:01 UTC">
      <body>Hey for all the stress, that was a really nice hour that we did have together this weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0667" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 21:43:26 UTC">
      <body>   It will be my favorite for a while too. Until you get back of course...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0668" participant="131839" time="2011-07-31 22:54:41 UTC">
      <body>Can I watch weeds if I promise to rewatch it with you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0669" participant="135117" time="2011-07-31 23:20:54 UTC">
      <body>Yesss of course. I might watch it too then </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0670" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 02:30:39 UTC">
      <body>Scotty and mundo are devastated that you didn't cone to their workshop...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0671" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 05:00:15 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry if I'm bugging you with too many texts but you're engaged on vacation and I'm lonely in my bed, fending Rachel off unsuccessfully. Miss you, tim. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0672" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 05:14:21 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) andards... goodnight marth</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0673" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 08:38:33 UTC">
      <body>I only got tr second of the two last time... Resent please?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0674" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 13:42:09 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Sorry we stayed in a town that I don't think had cellular telephone service ... and we stayed at a hotel that was disgusting even by my parents low stan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0675" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 13:42:15 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) dards. Just went through the Starbucks drive through which my parents are not good at. They're buggin me Mattie. Hope you're having a lovely Monday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0676" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 13:52:47 UTC">
      <body>Aw man. Try and enjoy the free ride and free coffee and family though. I'm running on empty today... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0677" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 15:20:43 UTC">
      <body>Stay strong! Didn't you sleep last night? You should go to the loring park movie tonight! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0678" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 15:47:46 UTC">
      <body>I was in northfield helping boys with their plays so I got in late. Also I didn't sleep at all saturday night. I think I'm doing open mic tonight actually... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0679" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 15:57:04 UTC">
      <body>Debut of Danny?!?!? Well you are a good friend to them. How was the play? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0680" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 16:07:46 UTC">
      <body>Not Danny... Not sure though. The play will be really great. I was a little weepy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0681" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 16:13:32 UTC">
      <body>Wow, I'm bummed I won't be able to see it. Where's open mic? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0682" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 16:18:49 UTC">
      <body>We could go to a dress rehearsal I'm sure. I think you'd really like it. It's at blarneys.... Ugh. Rachel asked me if her outfit was too slutty again yesterday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0683" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 16:50:14 UTC">
      <body>Did you tell her her face was too slutty? And hey, blarneys will give you a new audience </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0684" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 16:52:00 UTC">
      <body>I didn't but when her tits are up to her chin I'd assume shed know. What state are you in now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0685" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 16:52:21 UTC">
      <body>And how much candy have you eaten?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0686" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 17:09:01 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Almost to Cleveland! And very little candy, unfortunately. I'm waiting for my parents to buy me some since I've been such a good traveller. You've notic</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0687" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 17:09:10 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ed how I have a bit of a sweet tooth? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0688" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 17:11:12 UTC">
      <body>I have noticed. Maybe that's the reason you like me since I don't really and pass the sweets onto you. At least subconciously?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0689" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 17:22:04 UTC">
      <body>You're on to my scheme ... really, you don't like sweets? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0690" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 17:31:13 UTC">
      <body>I'll eat them, I just don't like the really sweet stuff. I like dark chocolate. With raspberries. When do you get there btw?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0691" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 18:33:54 UTC">
      <body>You wouldn't be working outside today kiddo. It's pouring. And blowing all over.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0692" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 19:09:20 UTC">
      <body>Kinda too bad I'm missing it. But it makes me feel a little better.  We're near Erie pa, close to where I used to live. Might go check out the old house</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0693" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 19:59:40 UTC">
      <body>Im supposed to send in my enrollment agreement and it's freaking me out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0694" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 20:10:52 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Well I think that you've thought about it enough. You're either ready to do it or not. You'll be freaked out either way. I wish I could tell you what to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0695" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 20:11:03 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  do but I can't!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0696" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 20:12:35 UTC">
      <body>However, if you're worried about money, I think it's a manageable amount. You should really just be sure that it's something you want to do for two years</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0697" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 20:14:24 UTC">
      <body>Youre right. I think I'm afraid of being alone in a new place again.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0698" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 20:16:55 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Totally understandable. It's hard. But made easier when you have a group of potential friends already in place. Or at least compatriots who are in the s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0699" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 20:17:05 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ame situation </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0700" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 21:55:37 UTC">
      <body>Two discoveries: one I think rachel is obsessive compulsive. Actually I know it. Second, the air conditioner or rain water leaked into my room and ruined my molding... Can you help me cover it up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0701" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 23:44:58 UTC">
      <body>Crap! Yeah I hope so. Is the wood rotting? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0702" participant="135117" time="2011-08-01 23:45:09 UTC">
      <body>Made it safe and sound to grandpa's </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0703" participant="131839" time="2011-08-01 23:57:01 UTC">
      <body>Good to hear. It appears that it's worse than I thought and the water is dripping into the wall and coming out of the bottom... I guess those missing pieces were more important than we thought. My mom said walls dry out all the time but I don't know how to fix it now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0704" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 00:07:00 UTC">
      <body>Also good news, you're not going to miss tylers show. I know you were concerned</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0705" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 00:27:58 UTC">
      <body>Well I guess the quick fix is, unfortunately, to stop using the ac. And when is Tyler's show? I was concerned </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0706" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:16:25 UTC">
      <body>Hey freebird how's open mic night? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0707" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 03:33:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh good. I'm playing guitar and singing actually... Yikes! How's grandpa? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0708" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:35:06 UTC">
      <body>No way Marth! I want to be there to hear it! What are you singing? Grandpa's fine, just about to sleep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0709" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 03:36:31 UTC">
      <body>Contrived derivatives. How long will you be up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0710" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:41:50 UTC">
      <body>I don't know that but it sounds lovely. Reading a bit but going to bed soon. Can't really talk though cuz I'm sharing a room with the rents</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0711" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 03:43:26 UTC">
      <body>Ahh ok. Catch up on your sleep. Do your parents know who you're texting at all hours of the night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0712" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 03:44:34 UTC">
      <body>"This is a song about the American dream. It's called 'Black Picket Fences'."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0713" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 03:44:55 UTC">
      <body>Hash tag open mic night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0714" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:54:49 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Haha did you say that? Brilliant. Sounds like an original.. and Martha, my parents wouldn't even know I'm texting if it were broadcast in front of them.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0715" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:54:54 UTC">
      <body>(02/02)  Hashtag luddite parents </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0716" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 03:55:20 UTC">
      <body>Keep up the revolution, Bob Dylan </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0717" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 04:03:00 UTC">
      <body>Well Hank just decided it was lights out. Goodnight you sultry crooner. Thinking of you. Also, tell me when Tyler's show is </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0718" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 04:11:48 UTC">
      <body>I meant you could tell your parents we were dating if you didn't act like such an international espionage specialist all the time... Stay up and write me secrets............ I'll send you the info for tylers show, but it's the week when you get back so we can find a time. Unless you were bringing another date...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0719" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 04:20:59 UTC">
      <body>I was going to send you clues today! But then I hot rained out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0720" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 04:27:09 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Oh hey Megan! Looks hip! And sounds hip. I just fell asleep and dreamed that we took out my boat in the middle of the night and ran out of gas. Luckily </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0721" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 04:27:14 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) you texted then. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0722" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 04:29:28 UTC">
      <body>I'm gonna go back to sleep and think of the things that we'd do when we realize were stuck at sea for the night ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0723" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 04:32:21 UTC">
      <body>Sweaty dreams, kiddo. Wish you were here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0724" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 04:34:40 UTC">
      <body>Me too. Sweet songs. Shake that egg of yours. Goodnight! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0725" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 13:10:54 UTC">
      <body>I miss terrorizing you in the morning.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0726" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:22:05 UTC">
      <body>I miss it too. I'd much rather be skaken awake by your freshly made up face than by the grating cackle of grandpa's wife. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0727" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:22:36 UTC">
      <body>But how do you terrorize?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0728" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 14:24:23 UTC">
      <body>Just waking you up so early. Especially since waking you up does take a certain amount of effort. And I wish I could let you stay sleeping so soundly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0729" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:28:45 UTC">
      <body>You're right, but your bed is so awesome! And as much as I hate waking up early I like it with you. You're gentle</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0730" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 14:36:34 UTC">
      <body>Grandpa's classy! I do love Renoir. I waited in the rain for hours to see an exhibition in Madrid. Hey they just called me about singing for ben folds!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0731" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:48:22 UTC">
      <body>Heck yeah! You gonna do it? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0732" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 14:52:21 UTC">
      <body>Yea I think so. A last hurrah in Minneapolis at orchestra hall. I guess now I have to listen to ben folds. Also, I just faxed my enrollment agreement!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0733" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 14:53:00 UTC">
      <body>I'm actually really excited now that im not hemming and hawing. I've been reading abouttheir projects all morning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0734" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:57:20 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) YEAHHHHHHH!!!!!! I'm really happy for you Marth. It's going to be a terrific adventure and you will do so well. I'm truly excited for you and want to he</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0735" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 14:57:25 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ar all about the projects. And when is Ben folds?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0736" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 15:01:42 UTC">
      <body>That means quite a lot. Thank you, Tim. Ben and I are duet-ing the 17th of sept.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0737" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 15:13:38 UTC">
      <body>Dang!  Bummer that I'll miss it. You got good times ahead missy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0738" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 15:20:34 UTC">
      <body>I have been feeling pretty lucky lately. ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0739" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 15:22:07 UTC">
      <body>Except for last weekend. I'm banking on karma points for that though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0740" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 15:25:50 UTC">
      <body>Karmas already kicking in. And now you should feel well suited to sing the luckiest </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0741" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 15:27:12 UTC">
      <body>Is it ok if I watch the Darjeeling limited? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0742" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 15:28:42 UTC">
      <body>Of course it's ok. I hope you read that you are whats making me feel lucky too. Just to clarify.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0743" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 15:39:04 UTC">
      <body>Of course. And likewise. I feel pretty damn lucky too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0744" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 15:40:46 UTC">
      <body>Also I'm pitting out left side of my blue Polo which, in s very odd way, makes me miss you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0745" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 15:56:18 UTC">
      <body>If you're thinking me of when you sweat then I guess Im doing something right, I mean, considering.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0746" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 20:11:32 UTC">
      <body>I was just thinking, when we go to new ulm we could camp. We actually only have one more weekend... Ugh.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0747" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 23:05:00 UTC">
      <body>That's so beautiful!!! I love those colors.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0748" participant="135117" time="2011-08-02 23:07:09 UTC">
      <body>It is. We got a storm on our hands! And we have two weekends, right? Still ugh, but better than one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0749" participant="131839" time="2011-08-02 23:12:21 UTC">
      <body>If you leave on Saturday the 20th then it's only one... I mean I'd rather be wrong about it so tell me I am</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0750" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 01:24:07 UTC">
      <body>That is sad! Are you still hanging with her? And I'm gonna leave on that Sunday </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0751" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 01:37:38 UTC">
      <body>Yea, just... Weird. And ok. Sunday it is. How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0752" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 03:36:07 UTC">
      <body>Hey sorry I haven't been able to call... been a crazy night being the big cuz. How are you missy? I miss you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0753" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 03:51:45 UTC">
      <body>It's cool, I just miss you too. It'd be good to hear your voice whenever you have the chance. I'm good. Going to bed at 11 for the first time in weeks! But man, everywhere I go I'd rather be with you than whoever I'm with. It's ruff. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0754" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 16:46:14 UTC">
      <body>Bighgg situation on our hands. Sarah just told me she bought a ticket to mn on the 17th...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0755" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 16:47:57 UTC">
      <body>Ok. Does she know you're leaving the 21st? Does she know about me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0756" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 16:52:37 UTC">
      <body>Yes and yes. I'm pretty pissed at her right now, trying to talk her out of it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0757" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 16:54:41 UTC">
      <body>I don't know a lot about your relationship with her, but if she's coming out to visit you and you don't want her to be there that seems pretty simple. But maybe I dont understand.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0758" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 16:55:13 UTC">
      <body>Why wouldn't she ask first?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0759" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 16:56:59 UTC">
      <body>O have no fucking idea. She claims she did but I'm pretty sure I would remember that convo...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0760" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 16:58:07 UTC">
      <body>So even though you told her not to come she still is?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0761" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 17:00:44 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I ever told her not to come, she just never said she was actually coming. So basically she went and bought a ticket without consulting me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0762" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:01:59 UTC">
      <body>I meant that even though you're trying to talk her out of it she's still coming</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0763" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 17:04:09 UTC">
      <body>Don't know still working on it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0764" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:08:13 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure what you want me to say but thanks for being honest about what's going on. I know you know how I feel but we dont have a lot of time anyway but those last few days are going to be tough enough and i would like to have as much quality time with you as possible. I'd think she would respect that if she knows we're together.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0765" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:15:20 UTC">
      <body>Do you think she has other motives?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0766" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 17:37:05 UTC">
      <body>No I don't. She wants to visit another friend in Minneapolis and wants to drive to tx with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0767" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:42:47 UTC">
      <body>Ok. I am trying to be understanding, tim. I respect your friendship with her. But I'm feeling uncomfortable with the situation. it seems like the boundaries aren't very clear between you and your ex girlfriends and after this weekend especially, I just can't negotiate my unease. Is that fair? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0768" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:46:09 UTC">
      <body>And this might be irrelevant now, but I was talking to Regina about getting some days off to drive down with you. Ugh.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0769" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:47:44 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry you have to manage all of this.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0770" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 17:48:16 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Yeah I absolutely understand. And that's a fair assessment. I feel really upset by this whole thing. Probably my own fault. I don't know what to do abou</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0771" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 17:48:21 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) t this. She seems set on coming even IV she doesn't see me at all. Fuck this </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0772" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 17:55:30 UTC">
      <body>I can call on my break in like 10 minutes unless you'd rather not </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0773" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 18:09:27 UTC">
      <body>Or you can call whenever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0774" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 18:46:07 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Sorry I have pretty unreliable service at the beach. Well I've sufficiently upset two people today if not more. Sounds like she's not coming but not tot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0775" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 18:46:16 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ally sure. I just feel so shitty about the whole thing. Kinda ruining my day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0776" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 18:51:35 UTC">
      <body>I hope it doesn't seem like I'm upset with you. I trust you and your instincts and you haven't done anything wrong. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0777" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 18:55:26 UTC">
      <body>I mean the situation is complex on a lot of levels, and that's not in your control. There's no easy way to navigate it. But try not to see the situation as a failure if people react negatively. Your priority shouldn't be keeping people happy but working towards everyones best interest including your own. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0778" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 18:58:22 UTC">
      <body>Wild Geese 

You do not have to be good. 
You do not have to walk on your knees 
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting. 
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves. 
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine. 
Meanwhile the world goes on. 
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain 
are moving across the landscapes, 
over the prairies and the deep trees, 
the mountains and the rivers. 
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air, 
are heading home again. 
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely, 
the world offers itself to your imagination, 
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting--
over and over announcing your place 
in the family of things.
(Mary Oliver)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0779" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 21:04:17 UTC">
      <body>Man. That is so beautiful. You know that I've always had the problem of trying to please. In all honesty that poem lifted me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0781" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 21:16:58 UTC">
      <body>Are you ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0782" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 22:08:33 UTC">
      <body>I found out what lesbian sex is.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0783" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 22:11:16 UTC">
      <body>Yah I'm OK. I think I just blew everything out of proportion because I just wanted a relaxing vacay day. Thanks so much for your words. And how does it work? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0784" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 22:11:47 UTC">
      <body>I'll never tell.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0785" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 22:31:14 UTC">
      <body> Can you talk today? I'm feeling sort of weird. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0786" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 22:52:49 UTC">
      <body>Definitely. Sometime in the next hour or way later? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0787" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 22:55:20 UTC">
      <body>Maybe in the next hour?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0788" participant="135117" time="2011-08-03 22:58:06 UTC">
      <body>Ok gonna finish up a home run derby and then call </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0789" participant="131839" time="2011-08-03 23:05:03 UTC">
      <body>Whenever works </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0790" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 04:02:45 UTC">
      <body>I know there's lots to talk about but can it wait til tomorrow? I'm exhausted and would be worthless I think. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0791" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 04:05:38 UTC">
      <body>If you're too tired ok, im just super stressed bc my landlord is being a total dick and is threatening to evict us</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0792" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 04:06:35 UTC">
      <body>What why? That's bullshit </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0793" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 04:07:04 UTC">
      <body>Can I call you or would you rather not?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0794" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 04:08:43 UTC">
      <body>Yeah please call </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0795" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 15:48:37 UTC">
      <body>What's the word? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0796" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 15:50:44 UTC">
      <body>Rachel is going in at 11 to meet with him with a check for the full amount. It'd be totally fucked up if he didn't take it but everything has been pretty fucked up so far so...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0797" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 16:23:50 UTC">
      <body>He took the check and apparently was like, "my hands were tied" oh well. How are you? Feeling better?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0798" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 19:59:16 UTC">
      <body>I'm glad it's worked out! No biggie. And I'm feeling much better today. We're in Boston going to the sox tonight! How's your day? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0799" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 21:04:52 UTC">
      <body>Now that im not evicted it's been ok. Have fun at the game</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0800" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 21:17:46 UTC">
      <body>Are you doing anything exciting tonight? I wish you could be coming tonight? And are you still upset about yesterday? I want to answer any questions you have </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0801" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 21:22:43 UTC">
      <body>I wish I could too. Daniel and I are making music and I might go see Steph and tim. I'm not thinking about your ex girlfriends ever again remember? No I'm not upset, but would rather talk in person about it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0802" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 21:24:05 UTC">
      <body>Good good good. That sounds lovely. Say hey to pip and raven </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0803" participant="131839" time="2011-08-04 21:24:53 UTC">
      <body>I miss you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0804" participant="135117" time="2011-08-04 21:25:37 UTC">
      <body>I miss you too missy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0805" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 01:16:04 UTC">
      <body>Rachel used "put it going" in speech today </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0806" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 01:47:46 UTC">
      <body>Did you get a hot dog? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0807" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 01:50:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah fenway frank! You having a good August night? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0808" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 01:51:06 UTC">
      <body>Daniel keeps playing me songs!!! Ack</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0809" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 01:55:12 UTC">
      <body>When I call don't answer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0810" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 02:50:08 UTC">
      <body>Did your team prevail in the grand finale in act IV</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0811" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 02:57:23 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) No, turns out it was a tragedy. But the nice thing about baseball is there's always an encore performance. And the actors were brilliant, the audience w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0812" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 02:57:28 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ent home happy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0813" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 03:03:19 UTC">
      <body>Did you get my voice mail?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0814" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 06:03:04 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Ahahaha! That was such a sweet message. Did I really sound like that? LAME. But sincere. My phone died so I'm sorry I couldn't call. I would have loved </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0815" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 06:03:35 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) to have been ridiculed for my lack of confidence but assured love of both you and baseball. Hope you had a good night and HAPPY FRIDAY!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0816" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 14:00:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm really happy that you're enjoying your vacation. But it's a gorgeous day and I'm selfishly ready for you to be back please.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0817" participant="135117" time="2011-08-05 21:16:35 UTC">
      <body>Hey Mattie busy day here, can I call you after fam reunion? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0818" participant="131839" time="2011-08-05 21:21:18 UTC">
      <body>Yes please :) whenever you're free</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0819" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 02:27:05 UTC">
      <body>How are you entertaining yourself this Friday eve? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0820" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 02:31:13 UTC">
      <body>I'm at my own family reunion! All the cousins together. Its real good. I'm drunk. How are you doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0821" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 03:16:19 UTC">
      <body>Man I wish I was drunk at the Stuckey reunion.  I'm drunk on ice cream</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0822" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 03:18:06 UTC">
      <body>Carthey reunion actually. Can you still call later?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0823" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 03:35:21 UTC">
      <body>Yeah if I can ever get away from my family ... driving me crazay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0824" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 03:46:56 UTC">
      <body>I'll be up reading for a while so you can call whenever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0825" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 04:06:55 UTC">
      <body>I immediately regret that photo. It's like a bad twitter sex scandal. I hope you're drunk </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0826" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 04:09:16 UTC">
      <body>:) it's sweet. And I don't think you're ridiculous I just hope you want to talk to me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0827" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 04:16:04 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!?!?  of course I do. Itd just be tough tonight. There's really no private place to go. If I were with you falling asleep slightly dr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0828" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 04:16:14 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) unkenly I'd ask you to sing me to sleep. Some joni Mitchell or Stevie </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0829" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 09:04:46 UTC">
      <body>Why did Ross call me at one in the morning? He didn't answer when I called back</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0830" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 14:53:28 UTC">
      <body>Nevermind, it was a drunk dial...?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0831" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 14:53:35 UTC">
      <body>Weird. I think he's homeless and desperate for a place to stay. That, or he found out about you and I and needed to talk immediately </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0832" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 14:54:46 UTC">
      <body>Im in new ulm. He was with my brother and cousin I guess. But I had a fear of the latter at 4 in the morning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0833" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 16:11:03 UTC">
      <body>Hmmm interesting ... sorry you had to go through that. Did you have fun? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0834" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 16:53:53 UTC">
      <body>Yea the fun is continuing today. What do you have planned for today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0835" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 16:57:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh hell yeah. Are you up at Georgia's? We're going to the beach again! Will you be day drunk if I call a bit later? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0836" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 17:01:12 UTC">
      <body>Do you want me day drunk?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0837" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 17:02:15 UTC">
      <body>Always </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0838" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 17:24:47 UTC">
      <body>Is that young Libby? She's clearly hammered </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0839" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 17:25:43 UTC">
      <body>Libby says hi and no?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0840" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 21:56:35 UTC">
      <body>I wonder what he would think if he knew you were sending that to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0841" participant="131839" time="2011-08-06 22:38:51 UTC">
      <body>I got a voice mail but I couldn't hear anything... Im sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0842" participant="135117" time="2011-08-06 23:43:40 UTC">
      <body>Haha he'd be pissed! Sorry I dropped the call again. Hope day 2 is going lovely. Get a little inebriated and give those conservative rels a good lesson </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0843" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 00:36:22 UTC">
      <body>No politics yet. Definitely drunk. Libby told me to tell you she likes pickles and cheese but not plain cheese. I want to get you in bed.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0844" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 02:18:18 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Nice! You can tell Libby that I like pickles and cheese, together or plain. But I feel a strong affection for both. I also feel a strong affection for y</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0845" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 02:18:29 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ou and your prowess in bed. You can tell Libby that too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0846" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 02:25:21 UTC">
      <body>She asked what prowess means. When do you get home on Monday again? What's your plan?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0847" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 02:31:26 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Just tell her that her cousin can make a man's head spin and knees go weak. I'm getting back around 3,was thinking it would be fun to come downtown but </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0848" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 02:31:36 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) will have a bag so might have to drop that off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0849" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 02:35:05 UTC">
      <body>Well I'm done at 4 anyway, so after you drop your bag off and things I would probably be done? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0850" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 02:48:20 UTC">
      <body>Yessss I am quite looking forward to it. Should I meet you downtown? Are you going bar hopping with Ross tonight? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0851" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:16:34 UTC">
      <body>Once again nowhere to go to talk. Can I wish you goodnight and tell you I want to be pushed up next to you naked? Just did! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0852" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:19:39 UTC">
      <body>Really though,I'm missing your face </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0853" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:37:24 UTC">
      <body>Also, what's your address? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0854" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 04:45:06 UTC">
      <body>I fell asleep with a book on that face like a cartoon... Sorry. You can meet me wherever on Monday. Which address?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0855" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:46:00 UTC">
      <body>Your house! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0856" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 04:46:14 UTC">
      <body>In Minneapolis?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0857" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:47:03 UTC">
      <body>Yea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0859" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:49:51 UTC">
      <body>Gracie. I'm trying to fall asleep to the producers in the background which is difficult. What were you reading that was so exciting? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0860" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 04:52:47 UTC">
      <body>I got freedom from Cathy galvin though the book had nothing to do with me sleeping. I was climbing trees etc today. Who is listening to the producers so loud so late?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0861" participant="135117" time="2011-08-07 04:55:23 UTC">
      <body>Oh good! I'm excited to talk to you about it. My cousins are watching it. Aaaaah. Goodnight Mattie, sleep soundly and peacefully </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0862" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 04:58:36 UTC">
      <body>Goodnight, love. Take deep breaths until you're relaxed enough to fall asleep. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0863" participant="131839" time="2011-08-07 20:50:14 UTC">
      <body> What's the universe trying to tell you? Are you in Boston?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0864" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 04:16:29 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) I don't know, I was so thrilled though I teared up a bit. It was such an incredible surprise! So sorry I've been unavailable this week but I'll give you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0865" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 04:16:40 UTC">
      <body>(02/03)  a day by day rundown tomorrow. I'm really excited to see you, touch you, smell you, taste you, hear you, and experience you. I'm gonna try to be downto</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0866" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 04:16:42 UTC">
      <body>(03/03) wn when you're done and we can hit the show if you want</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0867" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 04:37:56 UTC">
      <body>Ok, safe travels :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0868" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 12:06:14 UTC">
      <body>Rise and shine! See you in a few...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0869" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 12:16:38 UTC">
      <body>Hours, right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0870" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 12:25:41 UTC">
      <body>Minutes! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0871" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 12:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, hours </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0872" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 13:15:02 UTC">
      <body>Fly safe, boyfriend. I'm excited to have you back </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0873" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 14:49:51 UTC">
      <body>I have butterflies...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0874" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:03:49 UTC">
      <body>Really? About seeing me? Are you nervous? You know I've changed a lot since you last saw me...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0875" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:03:52 UTC">
      <body>I'm quite excited too. But a little tired now... what time is the play tonight? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0876" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 15:06:08 UTC">
      <body>If you got a tattoo without me I'll be so mad. Sleep it off Campbell. You had all week to sleep and ignore me simultaneously</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0877" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:09:58 UTC">
      <body>Ha! I was swamped and had to entertain young children. And don't worry about the tat, I just got one that matches yours, so now we're even </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0878" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 15:12:20 UTC">
      <body>Don't try and distract my me with my own womanhood with the children thing. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0879" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:14:04 UTC">
      <body>What? What about your womanhood and children? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0880" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 15:14:32 UTC">
      <body>I've changed a lot too since you last saw me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0881" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:17:23 UTC">
      <body>Your womanhood has changed? Did Cara have a profound effect on you? That reminds me, yoh have to explain lesbian sex to me ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0882" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 15:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Not going to take the pregnant bait? And I know but a lady doesn't kiss and tell...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0883" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:22:20 UTC">
      <body>Well I had no idea you were a lady! And no, I'm not taking the bait. You wouldn't steal Ellen's thunder</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0884" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 15:31:27 UTC">
      <body>Ok jokester, getting on the plane now. Can't wait to see you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0885" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 15:32:32 UTC">
      <body>Ditto, crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0886" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 17:43:58 UTC">
      <body>Can you tell me when you land?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0887" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 19:44:10 UTC">
      <body>Just landed, way late. Some guy had a panic attack and delayed us. I'll let you know what my plan is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0888" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 19:50:13 UTC">
      <body>You don't think you'll make it downtown?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0889" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 19:51:41 UTC">
      <body>I do but I have my luggage so think I should go home first</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0890" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 19:52:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh ok, then let me know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0891" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 19:54:24 UTC">
      <body>I think I'll bike in maybe, I should make it by 430 on the nose </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0892" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 19:55:02 UTC">
      <body>Well maybe meet me at my house then since I'm done at 4</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0893" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 19:55:11 UTC">
      <body>How's lips doing today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0894" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 19:55:51 UTC">
      <body> All hyped up about some baby pigs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0895" participant="135117" time="2011-08-08 20:02:26 UTC">
      <body>Haha ok, gimme a call when you're done? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0896" participant="131839" time="2011-08-08 20:07:14 UTC">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0897" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 13:18:34 UTC">
      <body>I was wrong about the show, it's tomorrow at 7 instead. Can you make it still?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0898" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 13:34:03 UTC">
      <body>Absolutely! How's corporate? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0900" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 14:04:54 UTC">
      <body>Do you like caramels, like the ones that are sort of hard? I assume so...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0901" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 15:56:02 UTC">
      <body>So! I told Sofie. It sort of just came up... She's cool with it and supportive. Is it ok that I told her?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0902" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 16:56:15 UTC">
      <body>You're killing me...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0903" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 17:37:05 UTC">
      <body>Sorry! Working with the boss today so no texting. Yes! Totally cool </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0904" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 17:46:08 UTC">
      <body>And yes I love caramels. And getting woken up like that. How did it come up with sof? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0905" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 17:47:57 UTC">
      <body>Oh ok, sorry to bug you. It was a little stressful! She was talking about you and Katie. And felt weird offering my opinion considering so I told her bc I wanted to anyway. She said she knew from how I was looking at you at the cabin. And I thought I was being so sneaky.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0906" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 18:05:09 UTC">
      <body>Not bugging me at all! Actually alone now. I'm glad you told Sofie. What was she saying anout Katie? And she was cool with it? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0907" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 18:10:52 UTC">
      <body>That Katie is holding onto something that doesn't exist and can't get over it. Yea she was really supportive and kind. She wants to hang out with us and said you can be affectionate bc she knew you wouldn't. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0908" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 18:11:08 UTC">
      <body>She thinks we need to tell Katie though </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0909" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 18:39:12 UTC">
      <body>Well I think so too. That's kinda a relief! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0910" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 18:39:57 UTC">
      <body>Mmmhmm. Youre welcome. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0911" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 18:50:32 UTC">
      <body>That was a joke. What are you working on today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0912" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 18:54:55 UTC">
      <body>Started out the day with some furniture building, now working on a landscape right on the river. Pretty cool. And thank you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0913" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 21:04:12 UTC">
      <body>I need a stiff drink after today. Clown school couldn't come soon enough</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0914" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 21:47:18 UTC">
      <body>What happened clown? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0915" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 21:50:33 UTC">
      <body>They "promoted" me... But no more money and lots more work. Oh well. Hows the river? Will you be done soon?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0916" participant="135117" time="2011-08-09 22:17:37 UTC">
      <body>Back at furniture, working later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0917" participant="131839" time="2011-08-09 23:33:56 UTC">
      <body>Still at it? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0918" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 13:04:14 UTC">
      <body>Did you get stuck in traffic?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0919" participant="135117" time="2011-08-10 13:35:56 UTC">
      <body>No but heard about that craziness. I wish we were still in bed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0920" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 14:40:53 UTC">
      <body>Ugh me too. Are you outside today? Is it as gorgeous as it looks?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0921" participant="135117" time="2011-08-10 17:13:08 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it's absolutely beautiful marth! How's your hump day? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0922" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 17:17:12 UTC">
      <body>I'm Jealous. I'm learning a lot I suppose! Hey, what are your weekend plans again? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0923" participant="135117" time="2011-08-10 17:23:49 UTC">
      <body>Good to hear! No weekend plans yet, you making some? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0924" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 17:25:26 UTC">
      <body>I haven't heard from Scott about the rehearsal, but maybe that's not super important. But anyway, I was thinking we could go camping maybe. That might be a lot of prep work though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0925" participant="135117" time="2011-08-10 17:33:25 UTC">
      <body>Well that sounds fun! Not too much prep. Lemme talk to my bro about when I can see him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0926" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 20:00:54 UTC">
      <body>Hi handsome. Is 7 still looking ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0927" participant="135117" time="2011-08-10 20:02:16 UTC">
      <body>Ummmm I hope so. I'm away from the furniture so won't know for a bit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0928" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 20:02:52 UTC">
      <body>Ummmmmm make it happen Campbell </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0929" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 23:12:47 UTC">
      <body>How's it looking?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0930" participant="131839" time="2011-08-10 23:14:09 UTC">
      <body>I made dinner either way</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0931" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 04:54:10 UTC">
      <body>Are you coming over soon?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0932" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 04:54:54 UTC">
      <body>Yesss absolutely! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0933" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 04:55:39 UTC">
      <body> Mmk. You'll have to call me to let you in so try to be quick </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0934" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 05:05:21 UTC">
      <body>Don't be nervous just tell him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0935" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 05:29:32 UTC">
      <body>Can I lure you with sex?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0936" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 05:31:45 UTC">
      <body>Yes you can. I'm just talking it over with rossy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0937" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 05:58:26 UTC">
      <body>Here now please. I made you a lunch for tomorrow l</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0938" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 06:23:18 UTC">
      <body>Coming now! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0939" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 06:25:16 UTC">
      <body>Is that ok? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0940" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 14:45:29 UTC">
      <body>Sorry for such a stressful night. I'll make it up to you tonight ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0941" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 15:39:15 UTC">
      <body>It's ok, you didn't do anything wrong. You leaving so soon makes every minute feel really important and I'm reacting to that more than anything. I care about you a lot. You can still do whatever you're going to do for me to tonight though...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0942" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 16:23:21 UTC">
      <body>Steak night with the boys??? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0943" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 16:28:04 UTC">
      <body>I know better than to assume youre kidding, unfortunately. No that's cool.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0944" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 16:39:49 UTC">
      <body>By boys I mean joe and by night I mean hour</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0945" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 16:43:20 UTC">
      <body>By cool I meant cool I like steak unless it's just going to be you two but you got my hopes up with your making it up to me which I assume meant sex which I'll still have with you since you've been such a tease lately.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0946" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 17:20:29 UTC">
      <body>Is your lunch gross cold?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0947" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 18:00:58 UTC">
      <body>It's delicious! Thank you so much. And that is what I meant by make it up to you but then thought that steak might be more enticing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0948" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 18:08:25 UTC">
      <body>You're so resourceful repackaging your plans to seem like a gift to me...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0949" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 18:20:16 UTC">
      <body>Oh come on! I wasn't planning that, it was just a proposal. It can be just me and you ...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0950" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 18:23:29 UTC">
      <body>No I like Joe, that's fine. But you really proposed steak night with the boys to me? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0951" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 18:29:03 UTC">
      <body>I'm proposing steak night with you and I. And Joe might be there. I had no previous plans for steak night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0953" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 18:48:56 UTC">
      <body>In that order? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0954" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 18:49:32 UTC">
      <body>If you were thinking simultaneously, you read my mind</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0955" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 18:53:27 UTC">
      <body>I was!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0956" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 18:54:12 UTC">
      <body>Well good, then steak night with Joe sounds like a great plan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0957" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 19:12:50 UTC">
      <body>I hope you're serious </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0958" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 19:32:49 UTC">
      <body>I'll actually only do steak related activities if Joe is there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0960" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 19:34:37 UTC">
      <body>Oh you're gonna be there too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0961" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 21:25:17 UTC">
      <body>Only if you want me. Also, might have to swing by my cousin's after work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0962" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 21:26:15 UTC">
      <body>Ok, For how long?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0963" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 21:27:19 UTC">
      <body>Not long. Told her I have a dinner date </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0964" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 21:32:39 UTC">
      <body>Yea bc and Joe has a lot to make up for from last night and I'm hungry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0965" participant="135117" time="2011-08-11 21:35:52 UTC">
      <body>Hokay!  What does joe have to make up for? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0966" participant="131839" time="2011-08-11 23:20:00 UTC">
      <body>Hey handsome, is your cousins house close to me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0967" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 15:33:44 UTC">
      <body>The prospect of having a house to ourselves is making me really really excited. And my dogs. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0968" participant="135117" time="2011-08-12 15:38:34 UTC">
      <body>It's a very very very fine house.... me too. Wanna meet those pups</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0969" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 16:44:37 UTC">
      <body>Dont forget your fun bag either, otherwise we'll be buying condoms from Aleda Warta </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0970" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:33:12 UTC">
      <body>This is a text from sofie i just got: Hey martha. Been thinkin. Its hard for me to treat this whole thing as a secret because i dont want Katie to think i chose a side or that i betrayed her trust in any way when she does find out. So i beg you to tell her soon. Its only as big of a deal as you guys make it. :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0971" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:33:31 UTC">
      <body>What I was afraid of...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0972" participant="135117" time="2011-08-12 23:38:48 UTC">
      <body>Man I'm still working for a while...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0973" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 23:41:43 UTC">
      <body>Any idea how long?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0974" participant="135117" time="2011-08-12 23:42:59 UTC">
      <body>Won't be home for at least an hour </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0975" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 23:44:02 UTC">
      <body>Man! Will you still have to work this weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0976" participant="135117" time="2011-08-13 00:06:27 UTC">
      <body>Hope not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0977" participant="135117" time="2011-08-13 00:49:38 UTC">
      <body>You should def not wait for me to eat. I'll probably be home at 930</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0978" participant="131839" time="2011-08-13 00:50:30 UTC">
      <body>New Ulm still?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0979" participant="135117" time="2011-08-13 01:04:59 UTC">
      <body>Yea I think so. You? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0980" participant="131839" time="2011-08-13 01:05:21 UTC">
      <body>I want to</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
