<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130208.0007" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130755" time="2013-02-08 00:45:41 UTC">
      <body>Hi! This is Kennedy from couchsurfing. We can host you tonight and tomorrow if you still need a place! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130943" time="2013-02-08 03:09:06 UTC">
      <body>Thanks so much! Buuuuut I already got some digs for my philly trek! Also I was imagining different types of guess who with walstreet crooks </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130755" time="2013-02-08 03:12:12 UTC">
      <body>They're mostly all food addicted pedophiles or depressed KGB operatives. Glad you found a place!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130943" time="2013-02-08 03:23:07 UTC">
      <body>Either way y'all introduced a novel idea into my monotonous silly life. Much appreciated!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130755" time="2013-02-08 04:01:39 UTC">
      <body>And I'm definitely stealing 'flabble'. Enjoy Philly!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130943" time="2013-02-08 20:31:01 UTC">
      <body>Hey girl, so for some reason the girl I was supposed to stay with isnt picking up her phone, are you still free to host just in case she doesnt get back to me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130755" time="2013-02-08 20:35:47 UTC">
      <body>Sure! I should be home by 6:30, may be headed to west Philly later, but leanin towards staying in so should be around after that!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130943" time="2013-02-08 20:42:48 UTC">
      <body>Oh perfect! Im actually supposed to go to dinner in west Philly to meet an old friend. Where do you live?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130755" time="2013-02-08 20:47:25 UTC">
      <body>At 15th and spring garden. You can take a trolley or the el to city hall and transfer to the broad st line, spring garden is two stops north. I'll letcha know if either Jeremy or I end up out west!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130943" time="2013-02-09 00:17:50 UTC">
      <body>Hey girl! So things worked out with the cs so I dont need a place to stay tonight but let me know if you come out to west philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130755" time="2013-02-09 00:39:20 UTC">
      <body>Great! I'm for sure staying in, had a wild one last night. Have fun!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
