<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130624.0063" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 20:33:59 UTC">
      <body>Furious.  Sean had his partner, Darlene (other Artistic Director and Choreographer of the show) call me back and tell me I have to perform tomorrow.  He either didn't fill her in or told her to handle it - she said, "Well, you've have plenty of opportunities to say no to this before today and we've already agreed."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 20:34:31 UTC">
      <body>*you've had</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 20:37:14 UTC">
      <body>I really don't appreciate people making decisions against how I feel - telling me I have to perform when I've made it clear that I'm worried I'll hurt my voice if I do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 20:38:31 UTC">
      <body>I know I signed a contract, but this isn't opening night, this isn't a show that reviewers are at, this isn't even a show!!! - this is a performance at a retirement home for publicity.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 20:39:25 UTC">
      <body>A short performance that an understudy is even attending!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131838" time="2013-06-24 20:43:11 UTC">
      <body>That's so unfortunate. I'm sorry it happened like that, muff. You have to go, tho :/ You could talk to sean calmly n reach a compromise n mention that u wish he'd communicated openly with you about it. But stay calm, it's the best way to prove your point. Poor muffin!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 23:10:52 UTC">
      <body>Did you get there okay muffling?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131838" time="2013-06-24 23:11:41 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Amazing! !!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137403" time="2013-06-24 23:12:11 UTC">
      <body>Are the people nice to you!?!?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131838" time="2013-06-24 23:46:49 UTC">
      <body>Lol sooo nice so far! I gooozed all over Kate about you! :D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="137403" time="2013-06-25 00:21:18 UTC">
      <body>Ahhhhhhhh haha - did she seem surprised?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131838" time="2013-06-25 14:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Lol I think she knows you're good. She listened intently but I could tell u aren't buds ;)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
