<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130426.0073" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-04-26 17:18:20 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Can i come hunt for tango clothes tonight? What time are you gonna be in the costume closet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-04-26 17:21:49 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>We're doing it tomorrow instead. 8ish?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-04-26 17:22:50 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Oh no! Ill be in plainfield tomorrow, is there any other  time i can come? Tobight? Tonorrow morning?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-04-26 17:23:12 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>Sure, whenevs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-04-26 17:23:12 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>Lemme know, I'll he home around 9 or 10</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-04-26 18:59:08 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>You wanna just text me a list of stuff?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-04-26 19:00:53 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>Im happy to stop by at 9 or 10, but I'm looking for 3or 4 flowy dresses or skirts preferably white but can be other color</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-04-26 19:01:20 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>I can handle that. It would be nice to see you, if you wanna come by, but I can do it. What should we do about your song? Claire?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-04-26 19:06:20 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>For my piece: Regular period street clothing w gas masks, like suits for men flower print dresses for women.  Ill come by at 10, hows that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-04-26 19:37:51 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>I mean the singing. Did you read Erica email? He is not comfortable singing the song bc his character is too sweet. I thought Claire could be stunning and she's not singing at all yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-04-26 19:45:57 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>I told him he doesnt need to be in character or that he can sing it from sad, disillusioned, hopeless sarcasm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-04-26 19:58:56 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>Was that after the email? I think
It might be really powerful from a woman, think about Claire. I got your costumes, have a great weekend, see you sunday, sweets</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-04-26 20:05:20 UTC" participant="152417">
      <body>It was after the email.  Im not sure that Claire has the confidence im looking for.  And Awesome thanks for diggin in the costumes!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-04-26 20:05:20 UTC" participant="152431">
      <body>Indeedy!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

