<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121122.0012" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 17:05:42 UTC">
      <body>Happy Thanksgiving!!! :D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 17:37:14 UTC">
      <body>Thanks, you too!! How've you been?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 17:40:57 UTC">
      <body>I've been good! :) turned in a draft of my thesis but still have tons to do :P how have you been?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 17:48:48 UTC">
      <body>Congrats!! That's awesome. I am good, working a lot this week but usually it's more calm. Making a couple new friends but miss you guys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 17:49:54 UTC">
      <body>Who are they? How's the queer group going? How's work?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 18:48:32 UTC">
      <body>4 people I met through UU or the queer group (or both). It's a little tricky bc I live like an hr away from all but 1 of them, but they are v nice. The queer group is good, haven't had time to go in a while tho. And work is going fairly well, progress is being made.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 18:48:32 UTC">
      <body>How are other classes / your gf / your suite?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 19:12:02 UTC">
      <body>Gf and suite are awesome, psych is great, Spanish is decent, Japanese Buddhism is the bane of my existence :P have you cured cancer yet? That sucks they live far away. What are they like?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 19:41:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh no what's wrong with Japanese Buddhism? I have not cured cancer haha but thanks for the implied vote of confidence. One is a little bit like Lizzy only minus the sexuality, another is me at age 29 had I gone to art school, one kind of like Audrey in mannerisms but more social and just came out to her v Christian fam as queer, and the last went to Pomona and I don't know her quite as well but she seems cool. I mostly hang out with Paige and 2 hc friends who live in the suburbs too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 19:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Ha and there you have a fairly comprehensive description of my life. What are you doing for thanksgiving?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 19:44:01 UTC">
      <body>Which one is Paige? Zach and who's the other one? Thanks for the comprehensive description :) Japanese Buddhism is just not that interesting but it's a lot of work. I'm doing it pass/fail but I still have to turn things in to pass haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 19:46:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh right you're not psychic--Paige is the one who's like Lizzy. Zach and Jeff, I feel super lucky to have them around. Yeah pass fail is tricky.. You can do amazingly little to pass (..it's like 1.7?) but I always felt guilty doing nothing for a class. How is Jen?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 19:50:28 UTC">
      <body>Haha I try to be but alas it doesn't always work :) Lizzy without the sexuality seems strange. I thought it was 1.0? Oh we'll I'm not shooting for that low anyway :P it's cool you get to hang out with them! Jen is pretty good. A little disorganized and sometimes frustrating, but overall it's been good so far. (Or maybe I'm just saying that now that I have a draft turned in...well see what I'm saying after I see her comments on it :P)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 21:30:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah haha well they are both outgoing, fun, like attention, feminist, and friends with me. And I'm sure you did great on your draft, seeing as you are Liza. Has it been stressful or just like another class?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 21:34:54 UTC">
      <body>I mean it has been stressful in that it took awhile to come together, and we hit super crunch mode before our presentation to the department, because before that week we didnt have an actual project, and then we then had a week and a half to write it up in 35 pages. I don't know if its more work but the timing is stressful for sure, and just the fact that its thesis.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135263" time="2012-11-22 21:36:53 UTC">
      <body>Wow that isn't a lot of time. So you guys have to come up with the idea and strategy yourselves?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2012-11-22 21:42:03 UTC">
      <body>No Jen helps. We just wasted the first 8 weeks of the semester talking and going in circles and not solidifying anything whereas we could have used that time a lot better and not had to die and meet ten times the five days before our presentation to figure out what the fuck we were actually doing for our project</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
