<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130624.0034" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:05:01 UTC">
      <body>When do you think youll find yourself in the Phila area again?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:38:52 UTC">
      <body>Oh  I dunno.  Maybe end of August ;(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:41:43 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) Thats cool. I should be back in the area by then.  Ill be gone from the 24th of july to 20 aug myself. Ill be in the yukon of all places! If i dont see </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:42:03 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) the northern lights i will be pissed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:42:29 UTC">
      <body>Ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:42:31 UTC">
      <body>Cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:42:41 UTC">
      <body>Vacation?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:45:33 UTC">
      <body>(1/2) No. Ill be going up with the army.  So i get pay! How cool is that? Im only a reservist so i get all the busy work like driving people around and gaurd </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:45:53 UTC">
      <body>(2/2) duty while the regs do all the cool stuff. But still its a pretty sweet deal if you ask me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:47:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah.  Pay !!!! Dam, I'm working a labor job this summer (cleaning out studios for the school).  So. Not. Fun. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:49:39 UTC">
      <body>Does it pay well? Is it easy?  A nice easy job that puts some coin in your pocket is good. No stress and you have some mony for fun</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130622" time="2013-06-24 18:52:10 UTC">
      <body>The pay isn't bad. It's not enough though. The girl I work with is a fucking cunt. She's Canadian actually. I wouldn't have a problem with it except I'm also taking a class.  Do I can't put in enough hours to feel like I'm living large. But it's still feels like beautiful sweet summer.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 18:55:06 UTC">
      <body>Canadians can be stuck up rude jerks. I should know ive lived with them the past 7 years. No idea where that "sorry" stereotype came from.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135496" time="2013-06-24 21:54:24 UTC">
      <body>So you clean up schools when the kids are gone? What kind of messes do little kids leave you? Im sure there are horrors.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
