<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20141230.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-12-30 03:03:42 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>How did things go?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-12-30 17:25:45 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-12-30 17:34:31 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>That's great to hear.  Glad things worked out. You're not going up there on Saturday are you? I'm definit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-12-30 17:35:01 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body> Yeah I'm going up on Saturday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-12-30 21:34:13 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Are you going to drive or take the bus do you think?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-12-30 21:34:38 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I'm gonna take the bus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-12-30 22:04:41 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Cool let me know when. I get off of work at 1 so I can't go before then. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-12-30 22:29:53 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok I'll probably get megabus for 2pm or so. I'm gonna stop by my friends in Williamsburg beforehand and get something to eat before the opening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-12-30 23:35:23 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>So did Stephen somehow fit some of your work into one of the shows that are opening on Saturday? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-12-30 23:37:02 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah, he said he was going to rearrange both of the galleries and switch a few things out and the photo show is coming down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-12-30 23:39:03 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Oh cool. I hope he doesn't take my stuff down and replace it with yours:)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-12-30 23:39:56 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>No way. I think he is mainly going to rearrange the second gallery and make it even more like salon style</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-12-30 23:41:49 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>I know the latest megabus is leaves at 10 pm. You want to take the train home? I know its expensive but Stephen likes to reimburse people for that stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-12-30 23:41:59 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>.. Which I feel a little weird about but oh well. I'm off to yoga. I'll talk to you later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-12-30 23:42:36 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I'm staying the night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-12-30 23:45:12 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Not the gallery that you are in, the one down the hall. Yeah I prefer more room to see stuff but still I'm glad to be added even if it upsets every other artist. Maybe he'll take down some of the deceased artists stuff. Man there is some awesome old stuff in there though</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

