<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121106.0038" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-11-06 16:20:54 UTC">
      <body>Three years ago today was our first away tournament!!! Whaaaaat?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136210" time="2012-11-06 17:02:01 UTC">
      <body>Lmao wow holy shit, you definitely got that wrong, we didn.t debate in october?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-11-06 17:03:56 UTC">
      <body>Uh maybe we did. But Newark was def on nov 6 2009. Maybe it was our second. But still three years aghhhh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136210" time="2012-11-06 18:10:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah holy shit, our lives were permanently changed by debate. How you spending your election day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-11-06 19:05:09 UTC">
      <body>I've got class all day and step practice tonight but I'm gonna try to watch as much of the election on tv as i can. How bout you? Did you vote???</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136210" time="2012-11-06 19:11:57 UTC">
      <body>Lmao nigga you know i cant vote</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-11-06 19:16:02 UTC">
      <body>I thought you applied for citizenship when you turned 18??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136164" time="2012-11-07 04:57:22 UTC">
      <body>COLORADO</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136210" time="2012-11-07 23:23:47 UTC">
      <body>Its so fucking cold i might as well be living in colorado</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136164" time="2012-11-07 23:24:58 UTC">
      <body>Omg I heard it was snowing, is it true?? It's pretty cold down here as well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136210" time="2012-11-07 23:26:26 UTC">
      <body>Its brick as FUCK and i dont have any gloves hats love</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136164" time="2012-11-07 23:41:08 UTC">
      <body>Ain't got no love to keep you warm?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136210" time="2012-11-07 23:57:09 UTC">
      <body>Nope :( its okay no school for me tomorrow :D</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136164" time="2012-11-07 23:58:27 UTC">
      <body>You haven't had school for like two weeks already. Did you get power back and everything? What about the subways? Just go out and have a snowball fight and forget about these troubles</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136210" time="2012-11-08 02:09:43 UTC">
      <body>Lmao yeah i did miss school for a week and everythings getting back to normal and then this snowstorm comes and ruins everything. And i gotta wake up at5:30 but wutevahh 
whatsup with you man?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136164" time="2012-11-08 03:14:14 UTC">
      <body>Im getting really busy as the end of the term approaches. But ofc there's always time for fun. There's a really interesting work hard/play hard dynamic on this campus. I've been happy with the cold weather but it probably won't ever snow down here :(
I also feel the happiest and healthiest I probably ever have in my life</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
