<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130610.0020" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 17:34:34 UTC">
      <body>Hi!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:04:44 UTC">
      <body>hi! how's it going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 18:05:52 UTC">
      <body>All right, stuck in traffic (I'm not driving :D)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 18:06:00 UTC">
      <body>How are you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:10:40 UTC">
      <body>Pretty good. I just got stuck in the rain on my way home.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 18:12:10 UTC">
      <body>How did you hear about this research?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:16:28 UTC">
      <body>I can't even remember actually! I think someone I know posted it on Facebook? What about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 18:17:40 UTC">
      <body>Someone from my department posted it :) I'm always willing to help out researchers :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:20:05 UTC">
      <body>That's cool. Are you a researcher too?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 18:21:15 UTC">
      <body>I'm doing my phd in history and have always relied on the kindness of sources :) how about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:26:31 UTC">
      <body>Ah, I was a history major in undergrad!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:27:02 UTC">
      <body>Now I do grassroots fundraising and organizing work with a high school student union across the city to fight for public education.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 18:27:54 UTC">
      <body>But sources are still important.. i recently used a rad article about fundraising during the birmingham bus boycott as a teaching aide with students</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 19:12:56 UTC">
      <body>Ah that is awesome! I just took an online course through the acumen fund called "storytelling for change." I'm trying to make my academic talks and class</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:21:27 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow, that's cool! Was the online course good?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:21:27 UTC">
      <body>I want to do a training with this group called the Center for Story based strategy, but I haven't gotten the chance yet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 19:21:27 UTC">
      <body>So what can someone like me do to support public education?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 19:29:52 UTC">
      <body>room lectures more engaging.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:34:20 UTC">
      <body>good question!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:35:05 UTC">
      <body>if you are in Pennsylvania, I'd say call your senator and ask them to roll back the proposed budget for next year</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:35:05 UTC">
      <body>but you are probably not in PA</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:35:54 UTC">
      <body>generally, you can pressure state officials to fund schools more, as many states are cutting back on teachers, &amp; putting more police in schools to make up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 19:46:53 UTC">
      <body>It was great! I can email you the materials if you want. Accountability was tough because my group was split between US, UAE/Canada and Europe. But we google hangouted and I learned useful strategies. Some of the advice seemed a bit over the top but I think you just calibrate to your industry. Also it wasa good excuse to see an old friend every week and make a new one :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 19:46:53 UTC">
      <body>Ugh police instead of teachers? That is horrible. All right I will do one thing for education in new jersey this week.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:46:55 UTC">
      <body>oh and you can donate money to groups like Philadelphia Student Union ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:57:14 UTC">
      <body>that's great! glad to hear it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="130680" time="2013-06-10 19:57:19 UTC">
      <body>and I would love the handouts actually, if you wouldn't mind emailing them to me..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 20:25:11 UTC">
      <body>Ok I'll email/donate when I get home. Still on the rainy road :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="132082" time="2013-06-10 20:26:05 UTC">
      <body>Have you had many other chat comvos/ any idea what they are trying to figure out here?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 10:42:22 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure! I've only had two other chat convos. What about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:05:50 UTC">
      <body>*three</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:19:40 UTC">
      <body>cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:25:45 UTC">
      <body>I've has thee, two with the same person and one where there was no response :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:27:02 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha that longer response didn't go through before. My cell reception at home isn't so great :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:27:54 UTC">
      <body>Ha! Makes more sense now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:28:10 UTC">
      <body>What type of history do you study / research?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:28:49 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha I was like "one word response?!?"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:31:19 UTC">
      <body>Social justice in indian intellectual history</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:33:10 UTC">
      <body>In particular arguing that a writer named Ismat Chughtai created a theory of social justice based on economic justice, sexual justice and social justicein a multi religious context.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:33:22 UTC">
      <body>It's tough to summarize research in a compelling way :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:34:18 UTC">
      <body>whoa! that sounds really cool!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:35:17 UTC">
      <body>are there any english translations of Ismat Chughtai's writing that you'd recommend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:43:43 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha thanks, now to actually write the dissertation :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:43:43 UTC">
      <body>Yes for sure! Her most famous story "The Quilt" is available in translation. She was tried for obscenity in 1946 because this story relates a sexual relationship between two women. I love her autobiography which has recently been translated with the title "a life in words"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:46:13 UTC">
      <body>Oh! I think my best friend - who teaches global women's literature classes - told me about 'The Quilt'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:54:51 UTC">
      <body>I will read that one first, then find the autobiography</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 11:54:51 UTC">
      <body>Thank you for the recommendations...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:54:51 UTC">
      <body>Yes, it has definitely made an impact -- the point of my work is to incorporate it into a broader story about the possibilities for leftist progressive intellectuals from Muslim backgrounds in south Asia. Expanding possibilities for what it means to be Muslim in south Asia.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:54:51 UTC">
      <body>That is great though! I should always refer to the quilt since it does seem to be a point of reference sometimes. Where does your friend teach?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:56:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah sure, my life basically revolves around this writer right now so I'm happy to spread the word :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 11:57:01 UTC">
      <body>Are you hopeful about the future of public education in America?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:08:07 UTC">
      <body>She teaches at Temple University.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:08:07 UTC">
      <body>Huh, that is a good question. I want to be hopeful. I'm not sure if I am though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:08:07 UTC">
      <body>Well, I feel hopeful when I see the inspiring work that high school students are doing. But we are up against some real powerful enemies...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:08:07 UTC">
      <body>There was an article in the Philadelphia Inquirer yesterday that revealed that the Governor wants to turn over the whole School District of Phila to charters..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:08:08 UTC">
      <body>So I am feeling especially despondent right now, as it happens.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 12:39:17 UTC">
      <body>:( I'll try to read that article... There's a lot of debate concerning higher education as well. I feel like somewhere along the way our society forgot about the point of education.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 12:39:27 UTC">
      <body>Have you thought about writing an op Ed in response?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:48:18 UTC">
      <body>No I hadn't thought about it.. But that's a good idea!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:48:38 UTC">
      <body>What are the debates about concerning higher ed?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="130680" time="2013-06-11 12:48:43 UTC">
      <body>Btw, this is by far the mostly interesting of these convos that I've had ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 13:02:57 UTC">
      <body>Same here :) so re: the op Ed. You should do it! You are an expert in this field and can highlight the work of your org. Awesome people are needed in nat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 13:12:00 UTC">
      <body>ional discourse. Also since That article just came out this would be the perfect time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 13:14:52 UTC">
      <body>Re: higher Ed, there is a lot of hype around online education and I'm afraid were about to see the corporatization of higher Ed where only some studentsget in person instruction and everyone else gets cookie cutter programs :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 13:16:44 UTC">
      <body>I can't remember where I heard this first but I believe we've shifted from a society with a capitalist economy to a society in service of capitalist economics.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="132082" time="2013-06-11 13:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Which is why I'm trying to shift the societal conversation towards justice. Let's see what impact I have :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
