<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120806.0015" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 16:18:35 UTC">
      <body>Hey will when should i come over tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 16:31:33 UTC">
      <body>#swag well my dad has a gig tonight that ends at 9:30 so he can only pick us up after that. The train we should be on leaves at 8:30 pm so you can come any time before then or we can meet at penn station</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 16:36:55 UTC">
      <body>So we'll be taking the train or your dad will drive us?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 16:37:49 UTC">
      <body>Train but he will pick us up from the station and reimburse us for our tickets</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 16:38:52 UTC">
      <body>Ohhh he's in long island already haha ok that sounds good. What should i bring?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 16:42:02 UTC">
      <body>Whatevah u want. Bring movies or books or games or anything. Don't forget a bathing suit this time! Also I have about half of a brownie that's kinda stale but pretty strong</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 17:00:39 UTC">
      <body>I won't be home till like 3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 17:29:43 UTC">
      <body>Hehehe awesome. I got some cards and shit, maybe your dad will play because two man card games are hard to find lmao. As for movies we should watch some crazy scary shit so we cant sleep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 17:31:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeahhh I'll bring my laptop so we can get Netflix in my room. Most of the scary movies I own on DVD are dumb as fuck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 17:33:00 UTC">
      <body>Lmfao what was the parking lot movie again that wasn't so bad. Also we got mario kart so we'll be occupied forever. And lastly lets get my ball from alicia lmao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 17:34:36 UTC">
      <body>Haha alright if she's home we'll get it. That movie was called P2. I'm so happy you're able to make it! What time are you comin thru</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 17:54:09 UTC">
      <body>I'm gonna get there at... Eight? Eight is good right. By the time i get there i'm gonna be starving lmao we gotta hit up that gyro guy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 17:58:53 UTC">
      <body>Eight or a little earlier is fine. We should have enough time to get gyros and get to penn station to buy tix</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 19:20:52 UTC">
      <body>Aite, maybe we should meet and eat near penn instead, more food places there? Also how much money do you think i should bring?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-08-06 19:22:17 UTC">
      <body>Uh bring like 20 or 30 bucks? You won't need much after today. Yeah I think we should meet at penn station at 8 cuz there are more food places</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136210" time="2012-08-06 19:36:44 UTC">
      <body>Aight sounds good! See you at eight! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
