<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120925.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 03:58:18 UTC">
      <body>Crystal! It's Sofie - hannibals girl!  Bob just told me that you were on ricki lake!!! I want to see that! That's awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:02:15 UTC">
      <body>I wouldnt go on show, just there when they came to film doc in streets, i wouldnt sign waver so it my blured face. It came to mind couple times recently </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:02:25 UTC">
      <body>and her show coming back, i hav bad feeling it gona be rerunned as show restarts</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 04:04:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh they are pretty good about thAt stuff... They won't want to do reruns. Bob is laughing!  He says they won't show it... Too old.   How are you doing? How's your kid?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:10:53 UTC">
      <body> sean said b4 he cant find it, when reminded recently i looked it up, a tv guide site gave discription wit link but i couldnt pull it up, then saw advert</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:11:03 UTC">
      <body>ise she restarting. I feel like It getting talked up man,  mtv chick was on it, i think it gona pop up. Nika good thanks, is bob in philly. I want c yal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 04:13:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm in boston, bobs in north Carolina! We are video chatting cuz we r hi tech!!!!!  Bob says he loves ya and his phone is on so you should call him. Don't sweat the lake lady.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 04:13:44 UTC">
      <body>She's a filthy whore anyway</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 04:14:54 UTC">
      <body>By the way If u ever want to come to boston you and Nika got a place to stay ( my place is big)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:20:16 UTC">
      <body> Im not really sweating it, if it shows id be like omg and laughing same time. Is she a whore??, thought she a nice girl</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:28:32 UTC">
      <body>Wow, thanks, i never been to boston, didnt know u left new york. I been laying low, gota reevoluate job and shit got real wit fam, but working it out the</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135438" time="2012-09-25 04:28:42 UTC">
      <body>n gota plan some shit. I always wanted to c boston, especially when a friend at destination so more fun</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130622" time="2012-09-25 14:49:08 UTC">
      <body>Yeah come!! my life is pretty boring now, fun but not exciting.  I'm a student again I read and write and sit on my ass and think a lot.  Ricki lake seems like a pretty kinky lady, but what do I know? She's fat then thin, then skinny fat. She's white star jones. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
