<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120910.0012" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 14:58:02 UTC">
      <body>Going for run</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 16:26:46 UTC">
      <body>No I have class from 11 to 10 pm tomorrow no breaks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 16:27:24 UTC">
      <body>Aw I'm just having a hard time transitioning and the live and wedding have really made it harder</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:27:44 UTC">
      <body>Shd I come to Boston tonite or tomorrow ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:27:44 UTC">
      <body>I know I know. I wanna help. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 16:29:06 UTC">
      <body>No there isnt anything to do but wait for it to pass I am just really emotional about the whole thing and a little distrustful about the size of my program.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:29:52 UTC">
      <body>Yes I know. Give it a little time all around. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 16:30:13 UTC">
      <body>I don't think it is going to be successful in the same way it has been on the past.  I'm too inexperienced. The guy is too cocky.  And the woman is too timid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:34:08 UTC">
      <body>you are not giving them or it a chance - wait a bit. either you will all warm up to each other or you will have to talk to the administration to make some kind of change. but i have seen you unhappy at the start of other things that have turned out well once you found your way. it's too early now, but if you can find a 'place' in the program that makes sense for you, you have some leeway to make it happen (b/c there are so few people).</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130622" time="2012-09-10 16:36:04 UTC">
      <body>Also having this long heavy period doesn't help</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:36:16 UTC">
      <body>I had to email myself that MSG and copy and paste bc it was too long</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135397" time="2012-09-10 16:36:16 UTC">
      <body>Yes</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
