<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120325.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 01:36:40 UTC">
      <body>How's zona?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 01:38:19 UTC">
      <body>So good! I hiked 10 miles today. How was last night/seeing Johnny today? Hope you got to catch up on your sleep this morning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 01:41:54 UTC">
      <body>That's awesome! And last night was aight, just chilled. And it was really nice seeing Johnny actually (: and hag only 3 hours</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 01:46:11 UTC">
      <body>Are you for reaaaaal? Whatd she say yo?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 01:50:11 UTC">
      <body>She means well, I just think that next yr is a disaster waiting to happen if she keeps that up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 01:55:18 UTC">
      <body>I know, it's really pissing me off that she's being so judgmental when nothing is even affecting her. I hope everything goes well with your mom tomorrow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 01:56:30 UTC">
      <body>though, definitely call me if you need to talk! And we should skype at some pt during the wk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 01:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Oh def, I'm kinda chillin now but like Monday or Tuesday. And yeahhh like if it affected her id get it, or if we pressured her, but idk dude </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 02:01:06 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I probably can't skype until Tuesday, but I'll hit you up soon! And we'll figure out this whole living situation thing when we get back. Have fun tonight!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 02:01:59 UTC">
      <body>God yes this needs to be put in order, like idk what to do at this point. Def hit me up Tuesday ish tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:03:22 UTC">
      <body>Hehehehhe happy birfday Maddie! You're 18, finally :P not on your wall cuz of Gabriel haha. Ily and have fun in Minnesota!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:10:04 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha ily too, thank youuuu! I'll hit you up Tuesday about skype</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:10:28 UTC">
      <body>For sure (: have fun in MN! Have an awesome bday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:13:39 UTC">
      <body>thank youuuu! feel free to come visit for a few days this summer, apparently my aunt may be able to sneak my friends onto her flight attendant pass. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:14:17 UTC">
      <body>Haha dude that's legit! Well talk about it when we're back! Blah I miss Berkeley</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:14:56 UTC">
      <body> we'll talk about that later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:15:52 UTC">
      <body>Me too, it's nice to have space and stuff here but I miss everybody! Have you heard from alex? Was he hanging out with you guys Friday night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:18:37 UTC">
      <body>Nah he left early, and no I don't think I'll be seeing him over break. I'm just gonna chill and catch up on sleep and such</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:20:13 UTC">
      <body>That sounds like what I'll be doing this week haha. I'm really glad things went well with Johnny though! Miss youuu, I'm excited to talk to you about eve</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:20:22 UTC">
      <body>rything soon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:20:47 UTC">
      <body>Same same (: just wanna be back in Berkeley heh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:23:02 UTC">
      <body>I know, me too. I was gonna go to etd with Vanessa and then we realized it was Saturday, not Sunday, and I can't even fucking go. I can't wait to get bac</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 19:24:06 UTC">
      <body>Ohhh that sucks :/ </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 19:25:14 UTC">
      <body>k, wouldn't mind rolling or hitting up some coop parties that first weekend in April!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 20:14:51 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, sorry I'm talking to my mom right now but I'll hit you up later, </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 20:15:35 UTC">
      <body>Haha wrong person?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 20:46:19 UTC">
      <body>No was just saying that's why I haven't responded</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131063" time="2012-03-25 23:36:18 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, my bad. How was seeing your mom?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131019" time="2012-03-25 23:38:07 UTC">
      <body>It was good, just talked and smoked and watching movies and eating</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
