<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130619.0020" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 16:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Do we have canisters for sugar and flour? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 16:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Also do we have measuring cups and spoons? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-06-19 16:26:34 UTC">
      <body>No canisters, yes measuring things but not more than like a cup or something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 16:27:42 UTC">
      <body>Cool I will try and pick some up </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 17:27:28 UTC">
      <body>Also I have a bookcase here. Do you think you would want one in the living room/do you think we have the space? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135080" time="2013-06-19 18:06:53 UTC">
      <body>If you have one already then we definitely have space for it. If you're thinking about buying one its up to you...I don't need it and there's the shelf under the coffee table but it could be useful to have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 18:19:56 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I already have one </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135293" time="2013-06-19 18:20:22 UTC">
      <body>I will bring it with me when we come down then </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135080" time="2013-06-19 18:22:46 UTC">
      <body>Awesome :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135293" time="2013-06-20 15:28:00 UTC">
      <body>I am bringing home so many cookbooks </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135080" time="2013-06-20 16:07:00 UTC">
      <body>Haha okay :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135293" time="2013-06-20 18:44:16 UTC">
      <body>Also may bring a papasan chair for the living room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135080" time="2013-06-21 17:34:11 UTC">
      <body>Hey Lizzy! So Anna might stay over tonight...when are you getting here tomorrow, and how does that work with your parents coming (or does it not matter)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135293" time="2013-06-21 21:03:54 UTC">
      <body>We could get there as early as 10am but no later. It is tots fine if Anna is there! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-06-21 21:13:26 UTC">
      <body>Sweet. Also do you have a casserole dish?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135293" time="2013-06-21 21:15:44 UTC">
      <body>No unfortunately :( </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2013-06-21 23:30:31 UTC">
      <body>So Anna is breaking up with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 02:41:28 UTC">
      <body>What?! Omg I am so sorry I just got this </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 02:41:39 UTC">
      <body>Are you still awake/do you want to talk?? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 02:44:00 UTC">
      <body>Becca is here and when she leaves I will probably just go to bed. I'm mostly trying to keep myself distracted. I will see you tomorrow!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 02:45:21 UTC">
      <body>Ok sounds good. Please let me know if you need anything. You are one of my favorite people and in a few weeks it will feel better I promise though I know it feels like shit now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 02:46:03 UTC">
      <body>Thanks &lt;3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:12:05 UTC">
      <body>Guess who left her fancy sunglasses here</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:12:57 UTC">
      <body>Someone who probably isn't going to get them back now? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:13:37 UTC">
      <body>Hahahaha if she wants them she can come get them and deal with that awkwardness</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:14:04 UTC">
      <body>#breakupfail</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:15:25 UTC">
      <body>Seems fair. Or we can give them to a homeless person or wipe our butts with them or make a bonfire of which they are part </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:15:37 UTC">
      <body>Or you know be mature or whatever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:19:04 UTC">
      <body>I was considering smashing them with a hammer or throwing them at the side of the house

But I might just be mature or whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:20:27 UTC">
      <body>I think the hammer smashing is tots legit. I mean, she really should have thought it through if she didn't want that to happen to them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:21:22 UTC">
      <body>Seriously</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:29:04 UTC">
      <body>But actually, do whatever would make you feel best with the glasses. Fuck what she would think </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:30:04 UTC">
      <body>I'm not currently feeling vindictive enough to give her that kind of fuck you...they were really expensive</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:30:39 UTC">
      <body>Like if she was cheating on me I would smash them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 03:31:12 UTC">
      <body>That makes sense. You could always send them if you didn't want to see her, or have her pick them up when you're not home </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 03:33:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm not gonna put in the effort to send them or do scheduling. If she wants them she can come get them. Ill figure out leaving them outside vs. opening the door and handing them to her later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 12:38:57 UTC">
      <body>FYI my dad my sister and I are going to dinner tonight at Local 44. You are invited if you are interested! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 12:57:12 UTC">
      <body>Also we should get to the apt more like noon, give or take </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 13:43:40 UTC">
      <body>Sure! And ok. I don't know when they are heading out but want to go to bed bath and beyond tomorrow maybe?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 13:47:44 UTC">
      <body>Sure! I should be free from when after our couch is delivered tomorrow (at 10ish) until I need to cook communal dinner in the late afternoon </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 13:49:52 UTC">
      <body>Also I think we should be getting to local 44 earlyish (3:30 or 4) and are going to stick around for a couple hours if that helps your Saturday planning </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 13:49:52 UTC">
      <body>I mean I wouldn't want you to start a new season of something and then have to leave, that would be cruel </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 13:50:47 UTC">
      <body>What plans haha...bed? Ice cream? Netflix?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="135080" time="2013-06-22 13:52:19 UTC">
      <body>Haha okay fair. Any suggestions of what I should watch? I never watch tv so I have no idea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 13:59:02 UTC">
      <body>Hm. I am currently obsessed with mad about you (a 90s sitcom of which I am bringing home the first season). Mad Men is highly addictive, and Big Bang theory is good for a laugh </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="135293" time="2013-06-22 13:59:18 UTC">
      <body>I also watch too much New Girl but wouldn't actually recommend it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="135293" time="2013-06-23 00:12:48 UTC">
      <body>In my room dozing off. However, should probably not actually go to bed at 8:15 so if you want to watch some episodes of something let me know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="135293" time="2013-06-23 00:12:48 UTC">
      <body>Don't worry about waking me up if that is what happens </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
