<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120626.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-06-26 04:55:36 UTC">
      <body>So we graduate tomorrow. Das cray.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136210" time="2012-06-26 14:07:21 UTC">
      <body>I Wish i knew sad songs on the harmonica so i could play them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-06-26 15:53:14 UTC">
      <body>Play them graduation blues. My grandma is coming to the ceremony and it's also her birthday! She's 76 omg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 01:34:53 UTC">
      <body>My grandma remembers you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136210" time="2012-06-27 01:55:32 UTC">
      <body>Really? I saw someone but it didn't look like your grandma... Your dad was really nice i miss that guy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 02:35:32 UTC">
      <body>Yeah she was probably standing next to him, but she remembered you. I saw your parents tonight, they were really nice too. Hopefully we will see a lot of each others parents this summer when we hang out erry daiiii</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136210" time="2012-06-27 02:36:55 UTC">
      <body>Ayyy i'm with it when are you leaving for atlanta?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 02:37:17 UTC">
      <body>August 25th is move in day!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136210" time="2012-06-27 02:40:19 UTC">
      <body>Ooo soap then we got mad time. Vacationing over the summer?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 02:44:19 UTC">
      <body>I have like two trips planned that are about three days each, so not really lol. How bout you? Toronto?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136210" time="2012-06-27 02:55:23 UTC">
      <body>Yeah going there like next week, and hopefully some other places spread out over the summer. Looking for a JOB thats what i need</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 03:39:14 UTC">
      <body>Oh word, have fun! Yeah I gave up trying to find a job lmao, but good luck! Im just chillin this summer. Anything from the met? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-06-27 15:01:21 UTC">
      <body>Yo I'm not gonna be at home for the Spain Portugal game. Keep me updated!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
