<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150306.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-06 13:38:38 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Ingrid, i love you! I hope you find some time today to relax and push out all those other voices. I have full confidence that your baby is going to be healthy, and your pregnancy will get easier and that Alec and you will be happy together. Don’t worry about pressure from your father/coworkers, just try to enjoy your doctors appointment. maybe even try crying a bit...(GASP) it might feel like a nice release!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-06 15:19:28 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>You have no idea how much this means to me or what perfect timing it was. Alec's mom freaked out at camper idea and told him he needed to man up and a baby needed a permanent home ASAP and he freaked and started having second thoughts for the first time last night right before our sonogram this morning ...it was really rough. He just deals with Constant criticism and Everyone telling him he isn't good enough and will fail, and it is starting to get to him. It makes me sad. I don't WANT a permanent home. Maybe never. I don't know why everyone is trying to force him into being a person I never even wanted and wouldn't want as a dad anyway.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-06 15:19:28 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-06 16:45:59 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>So rough. Poor alec!!! How's the appointment???</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-06 16:46:04 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Can I call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-06 16:51:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>I just finished! Super cute baby totally healthy so far and very active! I'm 3 months and ￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-06 16:51:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Hard to see in pic but it's little arms and legs moved and it rolled over and was so cute! Don't know sex yet! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-06 16:51:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Saw the little heart beating and heard it and it was so cute </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-06 16:51:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>I'll call later on! Taking Alec to lunch w me. I feel bad for him bc every single person he's told has told him he's making a mistake and will fuck up and he's not good enough as he is </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-06 16:51:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>I can't imagine going through that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>The only
People who didn't immediately tell him he was making an awful mistake was his moped crew </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>And his family except they're also telling him he is being a dead beat dad and needs to step up </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>(Step up to what? If he got a job now, he'd just have to quit in 4 months.)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Also he Has another job lined up! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>I seriously have no idea what people even want of him </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-06 16:53:20 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Everyone is just criticizing him All the time and calling him dumb and selfish </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-06 18:12:53 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Omg that fetus looks like a fetus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-03-06 18:14:14 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Look cancel all those voices out. Ask Alec what he wants for himself and his child. You need to trust his answer and not listen to anyone else. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-06 18:48:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>seriously, respect him and trust his ability to know himself. if you let those voices in you’ll be doing a disservice to him and your future with him. bc at the end of the day alec and you are building a life together. no one else is living this life but you two. so who the fuck cares</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-03-06 18:48:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>let those people live their lives</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-03-06 18:48:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>you have to live yours</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-03-06 18:48:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>wether you buy a camper or not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-03-06 20:33:27 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Yeah well last night he started having second thoughts and saying it is bc literally no one thinks he's good enough and now he's worried they're right </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-03-06 20:34:02 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>It was a horrible night haha but them the appt was good and I mean...it is too late!! He can have second thoughts but he passed the mark of when he can do that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-03-06 20:34:10 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Bc now it is happening haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-03-06 20:34:24 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>*then </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-03-06 20:34:49 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>How was your day?! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-03-06 20:35:01 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>my mom doesn’t think its that bad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-03-06 20:35:04 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>being  on the road</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-03-06 20:35:05 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>And yeah my fetus looks like a fetus lol but sooo cute!!! It's little legs and arms moved </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-03-06 20:35:10 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>His mom flipped </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-03-06 20:35:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>And said he had to man up </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-03-06 20:35:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Bc a baby needs a house and stability </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-03-06 20:35:12 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>(Why????)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-03-06 20:35:29 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>A CHILD needs that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-03-06 20:35:38 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Once they start School in like 4/5 years </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-03-06 20:35:43 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>A 1 yr old can do whatevs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-03-06 20:52:40 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Why don't u wait and see.... My mom says that stability makes things easier. Just be patient. Work on one thing at a time. Focus on getting through this pregnancy. Don't discuss plans with anyone unless u want their two cents. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-03-06 20:53:03 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>If you want to buy a camper this weekend do it! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-03-06 20:53:27 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body> you can also wait until after you have the baby... Campers will still be around. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-03-06 20:54:03 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>I do think that that first month you'll probably be very tired and it will be easier to be at your dads. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-03-06 20:54:19 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Or at least the first three weeks. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2015-03-06 20:55:16 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>And then, once you meet the little and you see what it feels like to be parents you can have done clout when grandparents are trying to shove words of wisdom down your throats. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-03-06 20:58:34 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Cause the thing is you don’t know what kind of parent you are going to be. or who that baby is going to be. Its like starting a painting right? you can guess about the colors and brushes you’ll need but often that stuff only gets revealed when you start the painting and it starts telling you what it needs. And also remember, your DAD LOVES YOU and ONLY WANTS THE BEST FOR YOU. Try to be kind and patient with him. Let him know you hear him and understand him, but let him know that when the time comes you are going to do what you need to do.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2015-03-06 21:03:47 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>❤️thanks!!! Yeah I'm not worried about us at all. It is so hard to drown out all the negativity, with everyone telling us we are doing it all wrong and this was a mistake bla bla </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2015-03-06 21:04:06 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>My dad literally said I was making a huge mistake to choose to do this w Alec </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2015-03-06 21:04:47 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>And Everyone has told Alec he won't be able to handle it, except his mom and moped crew. And even his mom is like NO you need a full time job and Ingrid shouldn't be working :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2015-03-06 21:04:58 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>We need to never talk to anyone else ever again </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2015-03-06 21:05:53 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>What a bummer that he and I have no anxieties, and ALL our issues are us having to defend ourselves to everyone else </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2015-03-06 21:06:05 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>It's not like he and I fight or have any worries about this at all </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2015-03-06 21:06:19 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>We are just constantly being criticized. Him far far worse than me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2015-03-06 21:06:51 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>It is so dumb. I am going to erase people from my life over this</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2015-03-06 21:08:19 UTC" participant="149389">
      <body>Anyone that wasn't supportive and polite- anyone who chose to tell me or Alec that I was 1.ruining the planet 2.dumb and ruining my life and the babies life   is being immediately cut out of my social media once i give birth and i will never speak to them again even politely </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2015-03-06 21:30:40 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>“What a bummer that he and I have no anxieties, and ALL our issues are us having to defend ourselves to everyone else” &lt; omg this is amazing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2015-03-07 12:47:34 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>This is trashy:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2015-03-07 12:47:40 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2015-03-07 12:47:56 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>And his thighs look fat</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

