<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120526.0009" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-05-26 18:01:59 UTC">
      <body>Yoooo Claire wassup</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136237" time="2012-05-26 20:46:29 UTC">
      <body>Hey! umm, not much is up! i'm upstate right now, i'm coming home tonight! the end of the year is actually really stressful and work-filled!!
how are you?? what's up? i saw that you were in grease at your school! how was that??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-05-26 21:01:00 UTC">
      <body>Oh awesome! Yeah I know, I have two papers due next week and there are only 10 days left of the school year...wtf. I'm doing well, and grease was a lot of fun! It really helped take my mind off of school. Are you excited for smith?? Also we all have to hang out this summer or during regents week!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136237" time="2012-05-26 21:05:38 UTC">
      <body>Yeah i have final papers/projects for all my classes due in the next two weeks!! it's soo dumb!!
that's awesome!! yeah, i'm really excited about 
Simth!! where are you going? chicago? (sorry i forgot!) yeah, i really want to see everyone at some point this summer!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-05-26 21:12:10 UTC">
      <body>Haha Ryan's going to Chicago. I'm going to emory in Atlanta Georgia! I'm pretty excited as well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-05-26 21:32:08 UTC">
      <body>I know lolol ABD told me! I don't know her at all tho, awks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136237" time="2012-05-26 21:54:34 UTC">
      <body>Haha, yeah! well, it's a big school!! are you pumped to get some southern hospitality??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-05-26 22:33:32 UTC">
      <body>Lolol yeah! People are telling me that I'm crazy for going to the south because it's such a different culture but I'm actually really excited and not scared</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
