<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120121.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:13:05 UTC">
      <body>Gd it, Greys and the crying!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:14:40 UTC">
      <body>Sad to say I haven't watched it in forever! What's the new drama?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:16:06 UTC">
      <body>Oh god, so much as usual.  Death, dying, and bereavement.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:16:48 UTC">
      <body>Of course. Remember when you found me sobbing over Greys right before graduation?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:18:11 UTC">
      <body>Too well. And then you played two seconds of it and I started weeping!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:18:56 UTC">
      <body>Haha we were a mess. Do you ever miss our lost extravaganza?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:20:04 UTC">
      <body>ALL THE TIME. Also thinking about that. And snackz. And hearing noises from 'that guy' in your room</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:23:12 UTC">
      <body>Like the random guitar playing.... I wish we could go back to our lost days! I miss you like crazy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:23:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god yes! No wonder we were a wreck, they were taking away heaven!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:25:20 UTC">
      <body>Totally. Our own little happy place- lost, nutella and a pretty fantastic friendship :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:27:19 UTC">
      <body>Ughhhhhhh TEARS did I mention there were babies in greys. Nostalgia will throw me over the edge!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:29:36 UTC">
      <body>Omg babies. Did I tell you that this summer I'm in clinical with babies and kids AND in labor and delivery!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:37:40 UTC">
      <body>HOW WILL YOU DO IT?????? I'd die all the time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:40:14 UTC">
      <body>I suppose that be part of it. But hopefully it'll be weighed out by the good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:40:16 UTC">
      <body>Im just hoping its not super sad all the time but it might be. Do you have plans for presidents day wknd?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:40:38 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I have plans, but I'm fucking really broke. But you should come here!!!! And do nothing with me!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:42:24 UTC">
      <body>That would be super fun! Have you been to dc before though? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:42:37 UTC">
      <body>In middle school... Which doesn't count. I really really want to come I just need to come into some money first.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:48:48 UTC">
      <body>I can help you get down here (hey tax return!) because I'd really love to come up but I'll probably have to do a little homework that weekend and itd be annoying to carry my books all the way up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:49:34 UTC">
      <body>Oh my my my, that's super generous of you. Let's talk about specifics and such. Do you have the specific dates of that weekend?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Feb 18,19 and 20th. Do you have the Monday off (the 20th)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 01:56:54 UTC">
      <body>Nope... Doesn't look like it based on my school google calendar, but that could be wrong. I'm counting on getting this job so that might be a factor too. But FUCK I want to make it happen!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 01:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Me too! Its been so long since I've seen you. Well we can play it by ear until it gets close :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135106" time="2012-01-21 02:01:36 UTC">
      <body>No worries! Life is hectic right now- I totally understand.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131839" time="2012-01-21 02:01:53 UTC">
      <body>I wish I could answer on the affirmative right now! But yes, by ear. Boooo life.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
