<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120720.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:17:04 UTC">
      <body>Hey baby what weekends are u performing??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:18:00 UTC">
      <body>Sept 7-16 every night at 8 :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:20:37 UTC">
      <body>I would say the second weekend of shows will be stronger and it doesn't matter to me otherwise! :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:21:20 UTC">
      <body>Ok, perfecto, is there a weekend u prefer having a guest??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:21:20 UTC">
      <body>Ok, perfecto - I will let u know when I sit down and look at my calendar. Yeah for fall in Philadelphia!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:22:01 UTC">
      <body>Woo!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:27:25 UTC">
      <body>Watching batman with Heath ledger is really emotional especially after last night's news</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:27:44 UTC">
      <body>That sounds tragic!! Get yourself outside and push those endorphins around with. Jog. That story is CRaZy!! I am enjoying my first Friday off and then going on a second date tonight :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:38:31 UTC">
      <body>With who?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Someone who messaged me on okcupid. He is very handsome, kinda dorky, 26. Italian. He is cooking tonight... Whatever!! Haha but the Fernando saga draws on as well with mutual declarations of attraction and long conversations at night.... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2012-07-20 16:57:26 UTC">
      <body>Agh do we actually love those situations?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135093" time="2012-07-20 16:59:44 UTC">
      <body>I do but I'm smart enough to know that if something happens I'm not going to do any secretive half ass shit. He wants to go on a date and see if in fact this could work because now there is so much energy built up. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
