<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150102.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-02 22:34:58 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>My bus gets to ny at 4 so maybe around 5pm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-02 22:40:35 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>If u r going to be at work, I could just meet u at the opening</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-02 22:42:28 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>I'm off and will be at home all day... So feel free to call and come over when you arrive</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-03 00:41:01 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>I'm gonna invite a couple of my friends/colleges to the opening? We have alot of admirers of your work...that cool? 5 ppl plus jui and I. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-03 00:44:52 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>There's a FB post in tgr stephan romano page looks like it isn't a problem if ppl come, right...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-03 00:50:58 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-03 00:51:03 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah that's great. I am trying to finish this guy up tonight, and frame it in the morning. It's the coyote skull that is the same size as the laser-cut you have. I tried 3 times to do a Lasercut of it but it would cut over the lines and fall apart every time. I'm going to do a hand cut edition of three. You and Zui have first dibs, if you want it, but I can't sell it for the same price as the other since it's taken me over two days to cut out just one of them and I still have to frame it. I'm not sure what my retail price will be for it but I could sell it to you for $400. I'll bring it up if I finish it in time so you can at least  see it and decide then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-03 00:54:09 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>Jui likes it! She says she wants it in a white frame tho </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-03 00:54:45 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>I think our realtor might come... He likes your stuff could sell to him </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-03 00:54:55 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-03 00:54:59 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Yeah, I have a white frame already made for it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-03 00:56:38 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>Nice</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-03 00:58:16 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Ok well I'll try to finish it and bring it. No pressure to buy it or anything. I had just talked to Zui about this one as a laser cut a long time ago and it wasn't able to happen</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-03 00:59:48 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>There's no replacing the hand cut I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-03 01:04:34 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>Best of luck finishing . See you tomorrow!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-03 01:04:58 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>Thanks, looking forward to it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-03 21:38:19 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>You in NYC yet?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-01-03 21:42:26 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I m walking to your house now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-01-03 21:43:06 UTC" participant="153589">
      <body>Ok see ya soon</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

