<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140317.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-03-17 16:22:37 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I have a job interview on wed! Case manager position for criminals out on parole</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-03-17 16:23:30 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>That's great! Where's it at?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-03-17 16:26:27 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Bridgeton NJ... sucks bec its an hr commute but my #1 reason for buying a car was so I can apply to career-related positions outside of Philadelphia since there are no openings locally. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-03-17 16:28:09 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>If I get this position in NJ, when Philadelphia does have an opening , I would be considered before anyone else since I already work for them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-03-17 17:20:44 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah that's true. I would still do it if you get it. I was still gonna take the job in Princeton just to have a better chance later</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-03-17 17:58:35 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea I'm gonna accept if I get... I found out about the agency thru a patient who works in federal. She told the lady dr that I'm cool with here that she works in federal so the dr told her how I'm trying to get into Justice fields. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-03-17 18:00:18 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>So the patient approached me with advice. Mentioned this agency and said everyone who gets into probationary work comes from this agency or similar ones. But that's where their experience comes from.... so I applied and they called me a few days later for an interview</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

