<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130702.0044" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="137255" time="2013-07-02 22:05:00 UTC">
      <body>The sipps tell me you know about hiking trips/programs. Is that true/if so tell me more</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:06:16 UTC">
      <body>Yes I do! Are you taking time off before college too? Or are you just looking for something in the summer </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="137255" time="2013-07-02 22:07:05 UTC">
      <body>More just for the summer. Like a week long or two week long trip </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:09:01 UTC">
      <body>Ok well the programs I'm looking at for the fall have lots of summer trips too, KNOLS and outward bound. They're aren't really any week long trips, most are 3 weeks, but they're some 2 week ones too. If you want me to help you I'm free tonight </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Also those 2 are kinda regimented, cause they're like the most well known, so u better hop to it as far as signing up. Also I want to go backpacking for a few days really bad this summer, and I'm looking for backpacking buddies! And I also really want to visit the sipps and hike up there too!! Just for a few more options!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="137255" time="2013-07-02 22:22:16 UTC">
      <body>Yes yes all this sounds great to me!!! I'm not free tonight boo but I shall do a lot of research! :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:23:53 UTC">
      <body>Yes yes! And let me know about anything else! Also I think I'm gonna call Angelina, who's with Anna Harris, who did KNOLS last year, if your interested in they're programs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:24:00 UTC">
      <body>I feel ya! I hate sitting around here, I gotta do something too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="137255" time="2013-07-02 22:25:03 UTC">
      <body>I was wondering what it is that Anna Harris did!! Yes I would love to hear about what she did and whether or not she enjoyed it. I just really want to get out there this summer </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="137328" time="2013-07-02 22:26:15 UTC">
      <body>Feel free to come over anytime and well call, I'm literally doing nothing</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
