<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120616.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-06-16 21:26:44 UTC">
      <body>I'm at dorianes right now and she's not having a good time but I can call you after. I got your message and I guess I just don't understand why we're fighting or whatever but I'll call you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131019" time="2012-06-16 23:23:11 UTC">
      <body>Anyway I can call you in a bit, I'm in Johnny's car right now. I'll call when I get to his house. I hope you're okay though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131063" time="2012-06-16 23:53:57 UTC">
      <body>At a concert, I'll call you in 5 when I find a quiet spot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131019" time="2012-06-16 23:54:17 UTC">
      <body>We can talk after? Don't wanna make you leave your concert</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131063" time="2012-06-17 00:01:17 UTC">
      <body>I'll have a break in 10-20, I'll hit you up then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131019" time="2012-06-17 00:01:47 UTC">
      <body>Alrighty then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131063" time="2012-06-17 00:16:39 UTC">
      <body>Oops not finding a quiet spot, I'll hit you up later or we can talk tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131019" time="2012-06-17 00:17:10 UTC">
      <body>Text me later I might be out but tomorrow works (: I hope you're all good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-06-17 03:32:46 UTC">
      <body>Anyway you should tell me what you're referring to at least so you're not blindsiding me because I honestly have no idea what you're referring to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131019" time="2012-06-17 23:36:48 UTC">
      <body>I haven't called yet cuz it's fathers day and I've been with Johnny's family like all day but I'll call you asap</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131063" time="2012-06-17 23:38:30 UTC">
      <body>K sounds good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131019" time="2012-06-18 03:15:59 UTC">
      <body>Hey I'm sorry I didn't think this would take all day. I'll call tomorrow around noon or one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131019" time="2012-06-18 23:41:46 UTC">
      <body>Okay just message or something what you wanna say, I think that would be easier and I'll either call you once I've read it or respond to it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131019" time="2012-06-19 18:59:37 UTC">
      <body>Are you kidding me dude? You're the one who wanted to talk and now it's lording over my head and you're not gonna respond? Come on</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
