<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150126.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-26 01:04:59 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Alrighty, my darling. Time for werk. Hows your evening going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-26 01:05:49 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Going good. Watched running man and now I'm going my microbio homework I forgot about! HAH!
I'm sorry you're at work!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-26 02:21:15 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Let it snow let it snow let it snow!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-26 04:53:58 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I love you!!!! Going to bed now! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-26 14:18:38 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Good morning, darling lovely :) Sorry i didnt text last night. Was super busy. Hope you get to stay inside today, cozy and happy! Love you!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-26 14:21:25 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hehe. I'm at the library. Haha. I've been here since 8 and I'll stay until 1:24. At that time I'll hop on the train and go home!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-26 14:23:00 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Reaaally?? They cancelled and my baby is still being super productive? You is amazing! Couldnt do it haha.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-26 14:25:01 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>They didn't cancel :(
I'm only being productive because I got a ride to villanova. Hahahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-26 14:26:56 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Oh haha. Well then. Yik. But no worries. You'll be home before you know it. And then under the blanket on the couch!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-26 14:28:09 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Yes!!! Plus hopefully no classes tomorrow will be pretty nice. And I'll use all that time to study (womp womp...no I won't) and I'll be ready for my exam on Thursday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-26 14:31:06 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Haha fingers crossed for no class! And you'll rock it. No sweat :) Not getting any winter action here...just sleety junk. No help. Just gross </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-26 14:33:46 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hahaha. I hear Wayne is currently in a blizzard warning. I'm jealous. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-26 14:34:59 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Haha yeah theyre supposed to get walloped. Doggies are ready haha. And you'll get plenty :) There will be enough to get rid of school for a day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-26 14:35:33 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I want 2 days!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-26 14:35:44 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hahaha. Jk. I'll be grateful for whatever I get. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-26 14:36:53 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Ah greedy woman!! But i hear ya haha. That would be sooo nice. Good luck haha. Like you said. Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-26 14:56:07 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>:D I love you! Have a good night baby!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-26 14:59:27 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Haha oh no. Im with you today. Daytime schedule :-p Couldnt sleep again. So...f it, im up. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-01-26 15:00:05 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hahaha. Whoa!!! I wouldn't be able to do that. I'd be done. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-01-26 15:01:22 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Haha suuure you could. We'll try it one day...for a good reason. Like a vacation haha. But im sure i'll smack a wall of sleepy in the afternoon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-01-26 15:03:32 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Hahaha. Probably! I like it! I wanna go on vacation with you! I have the best times when I'm on vacay with you. Seriously. Whenever I think about times we spent just you and me, I get giddy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-01-26 15:04:30 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Haha i like it! I like giddy you :) And i live for those times haha. Lets do it again :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-01-26 15:05:15 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! I can't wait!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-01-26 15:07:54 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Meee neither!! Keep yo summa dresses and bathing suits ready :) Or your english lady outfits...those just might be handy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-01-26 15:09:27 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Haha. I wish!!! Gotta be classy like kate Middleton. I'm not there yet!
But I wanna buy another bathing suit. I like the one I saw online!!! I wanna buy it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-01-26 15:10:37 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Oh hell yes you are. Kate Middletons got nothing on you. And im sure that bathing suit you saw was lovely haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-01-26 15:13:27 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>MUAHAHAHA. I'm gonna be the queen on bathing suits! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-01-26 15:22:53 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>In my world, you already are. Bathing suits, maxis, sweats, t shirts. Queen.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-01-26 15:23:30 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Haha. I like how sweats are in that mix.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-01-26 15:24:13 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Hehe those are important :-p You a hottie in dem</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-01-26 15:29:04 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Haha. You're cute. I lobe you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-01-26 15:29:14 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>Ohhh. That's a new one. I lobe you. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-01-26 15:29:46 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Oh geee wiz. I lobe you too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-01-26 18:34:10 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>This idiot on the train just put my $20 on the ticket clip and walked away. So I took it off because I didn't want someone to just take it. This freaking jerkoff just scolded me for taking the money off. He then proceeded to tell me to put it back and walked away again. 
Wtf is up with that?! I'm seriously biting my tongue to a point where I think it might be bleeding. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-01-26 18:44:54 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Ah jeez baby, get outta there. Dumbasses. Hope that got resolved. Get home darling. Please please</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-01-26 18:45:19 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>It did...but...it was a little embarrassing :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-01-26 18:48:18 UTC" participant="153414">
      <body>Sorry baby :-( Dont let it bother you. Ignore it. Im in class right now tho, i call ya when i get out! I love you, so much</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-01-26 18:48:28 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>I love you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-01-26 21:27:39 UTC" participant="153412">
      <body>They keep lessening the snow totals. Doesn't make me optimistic about having off tomorrow :(
Not they're saying 4-10 inches :(</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

