<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120908.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130925" time="2012-09-08 18:28:15 UTC">
      <body>Hey Kennedy! I just got your email, ill definitely be able to be your friends lighting board guy. Can you throw me her number? I don't think ill be able </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130925" time="2012-09-08 18:28:16 UTC">
      <body>to film your show though, my dslr isn't good for long term recording and I don't have the right lens for it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130925" time="2012-09-08 18:28:58 UTC">
      <body>Id rent a proper camera from my school but its closed for rentals until october. Sorry :( ill try to find someone else who can though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130925" time="2012-09-14 19:06:06 UTC">
      <body>Hi! Im having a bit of an internet emergency and I lost the wifi password. Could you be my hero and throw it at me? Ill give you guys cash for the past c</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130925" time="2012-09-14 19:06:07 UTC">
      <body>ouple months tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130755" time="2012-09-14 19:24:11 UTC">
      <body>And no worries! Just slip it under the door. Hope you can make it out to our show next week!0</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130925" time="2012-09-14 19:25:13 UTC">
      <body>Ill be there! Thanks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130755" time="2012-09-14 19:26:14 UTC">
      <body>Sweet!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130925" time="2012-09-18 15:23:42 UTC">
      <body>Hey, I just saw your post on facebook do you need any assistance for your show tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130755" time="2012-09-18 15:59:33 UTC">
      <body>Thank you! I took a lot of pain meds and got thru yesterday, and feeling much better today. But thanks! Hope you can come see it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130925" time="2012-09-18 16:00:22 UTC">
      <body>What's the address and time? Well be there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130925" time="2012-09-29 01:46:40 UTC">
      <body>Hey, Paige and I just slipped some cash under your door for Internet. The network disappeared. Did anything change with it? 

Thanks,
-Jason</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130755" time="2012-09-29 20:04:40 UTC">
      <body>Heya, we're camping, don't have phone service consistently. Dunno what's wrong with the net, sorry :-( we'll be back and can fix on Monday. Thx for the payment!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130755" time="2012-10-02 17:59:41 UTC">
      <body>Internet should be back, just needed to be reset, sorry bout that!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
