<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150323.0018" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-23 20:24:32 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>Oh no! Is she okay? - please let me know if you need anything </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-23 20:24:32 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>I will def give you a report back </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-23 20:25:14 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hey! I can't make it tonight my mom went in to the hospital and I'm debating going up to Vermont tonight:( take notes for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-23 20:26:19 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I'm just getting out of class to messages from my sister. Something with an infection from a tooth.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-23 20:26:40 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>That makes sense! If you go tonight - travel safe - lll check in with you tomorrow and see how your doing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-23 20:26:55 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Thanks. I'll feel better once I talk to someone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-23 20:27:58 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Okay thanks!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-24 15:01:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hey! My mom is good. She had an emergency root canal last night from an abscessed tooth. She can't talk but is ok! Hope the reading was great! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-24 15:17:12 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>I was really good. I saw that they recorded it and I think it would be really worth watching. So glad you mom is okay. Emergency root canal sounds awful! Did you drive up? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-24 15:19:21 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I stayed. She said "wait til she breaks a hip" to come up. Ha. I'll check the site for the recording! Did you go to dinner?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-24 15:27:52 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>I did! I got to hear some good stories - I will tell you all about it. I think her talk has some really good storytelling advice </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-24 15:28:00 UTC" participant="153645">
      <body>I got excited about the possibility of you sending her your script for feedback - she seems super approachable </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-24 15:31:19 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>So awesome. I can't wait to talk to you about it</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

