<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140610.0008" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-06-10 00:46:50 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Hey, how was your day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-06-10 01:02:12 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Day wasn't bad, but found out some bad news about my doctor office literally two hours ago (company might be closing). So the job search begins before its too late.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-06-10 01:04:43 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Oh no.. don't worry, you'll find something...like my mother always says everything happens for a reason..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-06-10 01:10:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol yea my roommate always says that too... I mean I definitely have enough experience to get another job but searches are still annoying. I've already been doing searches for a position in a justice field (its already been two years and nothing).  Now I have to search justice positions and regular jobs like clerical and administrative just in case my place does close and justice doesn't work out as quickly as necessary.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-06-10 01:10:31 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But how was your day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-06-10 01:15:33 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>It's was cool.. the rain made it suck along with the drive home..now it's all better... took me until now to finish running errands and get to the gym..tomorrow is gonna be long, working twice</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-06-10 01:23:46 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>So u excited about making all these cakes?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-06-10 01:27:47 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea I'm just glad the rain stopped by the time I left work because it was really coming down right before... I hear ya tho (long day), I'm working open to close mon thru wed which is 11 hours.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-06-10 01:28:56 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>U at the pizza place tomorrow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-06-10 01:29:20 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>One cake order is simple but the other one I'm extremely excited for. She left the design completely up to me but asked that something resembles her invitations (baby shower). I can't wait to do that order, can't wait til she sees it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-06-10 01:31:17 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Nah, I'm done oogies for this week. I'm working my dr office 830-730 tomorrow and wed, then thurs and fri I'm baking after the dr office.... don't have oogies until sunday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-06-10 01:32:07 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Nice.. send me a pic when you're done. I'd like to see your skills..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-06-10 01:40:39 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Will do!.. So what you have planned for the rest of the week? Anything interesting? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-06-10 01:45:13 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Just work, then the gym.. that's about it,.. I'm looking forward to hanging out with you though, whenever that may be..lok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-06-10 01:54:41 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol as soon as my schedule opens up ill let you know... I need to get back at the gym, its been about two months. Time won't allow tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-06-10 02:01:26 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>That's fine with me..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-06-10 02:14:36 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Do you belong to any gyms??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-06-10 02:57:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Planet fitness</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-06-10 03:00:43 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Cool that's one of the gyms I go to.. I'll go with u sometime if u want..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-06-10 03:02:25 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Do you do cardio? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-06-10 03:03:02 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Hell yeah... I can run my ####off</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-06-10 03:06:07 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahaha ok bec that's all I was working on when I Would go. Treadmill, elliptical, and those stepper things... I use to actually jog a minimum of 4 miles, 3x a week. I need to get back to that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-06-10 03:07:16 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Nice.. you look like your in good shape. .. I'm more into bodybuilding but that requires cardio </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-06-10 03:13:55 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea I'm not so sure bodybuilding is for me, lmao... but I would like to get back to my old weight just so I can fit back into my clothes lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-06-10 03:14:43 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>So how long did it take for you to get to where you are now (with all the muscles)?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-06-10 03:16:02 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>I've been weight training for 18 years</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-06-10 03:18:00 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Really?? Like I said u look fit...u trying to lose weight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-06-10 03:21:57 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh ####!! (Warm up) lol... and yea lol, I knew I'm not fat or anything but I put on a few pounds, therefore increasing in clothing sizes. I have a whole wardrobe of clothing I no longer fit in, most clothing not even used one.  I just wanna fit back in my old clothes. Like lose 15 lbs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-06-10 03:24:32 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Oh that's easy...you could do that quick..</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-06-10 03:26:19 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Speaking of wardrobes. ..I'm curious to see how you look when you go out, with those pretty eyes </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-06-10 03:30:05 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahaha I can assure you its nothing spectacular, but you'll just have to see for yourself one day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-06-10 03:32:16 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Especially right now, I rarely go out anymore and don't fit half my clothes so its not like I have many options to wear. I have some stuff that fit but I refuse to buy all new clothes bec the more that fit me, the less ill try to lose weight. Lack of clothing is like a motivational factor lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-06-10 03:34:04 UTC" participant="153781">
      <body>Well if I can help in anyway let me know and I'm sure you look amazing. .nice try. .lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-06-10 03:35:46 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ahahahaha</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

