<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121029.0032" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-10-29 03:23:40 UTC">
      <body>Hey, how was your holiday? Being 18 is crazy. I miss you. Call me when you can.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136210" time="2012-10-29 18:46:20 UTC">
      <body>Yooo whatup! How many lottery tickets have you bought in the past twenty four hours? Ill call soon we're storm proofing right now. This hurricane has ben pretty light so far but who knowz this could be katrina</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-10-29 19:35:54 UTC">
      <body>I'm for sure going to CVS sometime this week to buy lotto tickets and cigarettes JUST BECAUSE I CAN. Stay safe! Some places have started to get hit pretty hard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 04:05:39 UTC">
      <body>Hey you did it! And you're alive!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 04:08:03 UTC">
      <body>Yeah son and im not even leakin jizz. It feels kinda weird thinking i cant see priya rai again but oh well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 04:08:52 UTC">
      <body>Are you just stopping indefinitely</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 04:11:07 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea lmao
i dont know if im gonna fap this week or this m</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 04:11:17 UTC">
      <body>onth or ever again. I just wake up every morning and im like “dont </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 04:11:32 UTC">
      <body>fap today” 
if i become a demi god in the process thats cool!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 04:16:15 UTC">
      <body>I'm not so sure that's the way you achieve demi god status lmao. You might as well fap all night since all of America might be flooded by tomorrow morning</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 04:18:25 UTC">
      <body>Im gonna be so tempted during this storm with nothing to do, but i will not be broken! Also yeah it is. Hercules became that way by acquiring all the seen dont you read</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 05:01:08 UTC">
      <body>OMG how could I forget abt Hercules. You should watch scary movies all night instead. That's what I would do </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 05:02:40 UTC">
      <body>No internet :( and all the movies on tv suck ugh. Wat u doin at emory</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 05:07:26 UTC">
      <body>Hhggghgh this week is gonna be really busy. I was just hangin with some people in the hall but I decided to lie in bed because I need to wake up early tomorrow to finish my work instead of stay up late tonight cuz my brain stopped working</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136210" time="2012-10-30 05:11:52 UTC">
      <body>Go to sleep son itd be better if we talked tomorrow! Its gonna be real bittersweet rebuilding western civilization. Good luck on your hw while i am cleaing the debris off the chrysler building. Ill give you a call soon while im not busy consolidating my post apocolyptic empire. Good night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136164" time="2012-10-30 05:13:09 UTC">
      <body>Haha sounds great. Good night!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
