<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130211.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131424" time="2013-02-11 23:14:10 UTC">
      <body>Was nice seeing ya yesterday!  Hope you are feeling good enough to go to class this week &amp; soak up all the glorious stuff the WON has to offer!  b</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 02:46:21 UTC">
      <body>Never fear! I wouldn't miss the wonders of the Won for much! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:04:59 UTC">
      <body>Ooh! I forgot the latest gossip! Lynn interrupted our class all dramatic to announce "the cat was out of the bag" </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:05:49 UTC">
      <body>It was totally awkward and bizarre since she has only "taught" us for about an hour anyways!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:06:35 UTC">
      <body>It reminded me of everything you had previously said about her. (No connection to her but she is totally sure she is connected.)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 03:14:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh my!  CLASSIC!  All dramatic?  I have no doubt that that's exactly how it was.  Often with a lead-in that's all fabricated like that one probably was.  Perhaps the news that she WILL be back to teach you will help soothe your rebellious qi!?!
FYI - I'm </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:16:37 UTC">
      <body>So did I actually get ear stomach? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:18:15 UTC">
      <body>I might have a party at halfway point. I have been thinking about that a lot. This is week seven coming up so halfway through week eight is halfway! I'm so bad at math that I really thought last semester was halfway bc it was semester four of nine! I'm go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 03:33:20 UTC">
      <body>lol @ your math and need fr good accountant - you're funny.  Look at u and your text images!!  Go Monica go!

If I remember correctly I went w Ear Liver and shenmen.  You could probably try ear seed or press tack on ear stomach and esophagus (right next t</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:41:19 UTC">
      <body>Do you know about emoji icons? They are the best! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 03:43:47 UTC">
      <body>Don't be too impressed... Most of my icons involve hearts and animals btw. Some of my friends are really sophisticated with their emojis but I figure you can NEVER go wrong with a panda. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 03:58:14 UTC">
      <body>Ty for the laughs.  Texting like teenage girl is always the way to go!
I'm definitely thinking smooth flow of qi but also because liver is often the culprit in our society, right?  Check out gmac foundations table 31.1 p 447</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:08:37 UTC">
      <body>I'm glad to make you laugh. A good laugh is good for you right now. :) I'm going to go bond with gmac for a minute before bed. I love that nickname for him. I've always suspected he's a hustler or a pimp. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:11:17 UTC">
      <body>EXACTLY! the gmac daddy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:11:44 UTC">
      <body>Have a good night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:11:44 UTC">
      <body>which illustrations?  Isn't it all tables and flow charts and stuff?  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:12:03 UTC">
      <body>Do you ever feel creepy while studying his illustrations??? I mean really! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:13:51 UTC">
      <body>Sometimes there are people who definitely aren't human. Like the channels book.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:13:52 UTC">
      <body>Ill have to flip thru that book again w a look out for creepiness.   
Oooooh.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:13:52 UTC">
      <body>Well I did it for myself too. And then shared.  Always learning.  Or trying to </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:14:42 UTC">
      <body>PS: I can't believe you went and looked up a chart for me. That is above and beyond at its best!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:15:52 UTC">
      <body>Don't do it before bed! You will have science fiction dreams! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:16:00 UTC">
      <body>Science fiction dreams?  That's never good.  
Ty for the koala </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:16:00 UTC">
      <body>Have a great tmrw</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:16:46 UTC">
      <body>That's something I admire about you! You're totally committed and there's no fluff. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:17:54 UTC">
      <body>If you think you can handle it see foundations 294 for creepiness!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:18:11 UTC">
      <body>Ill check it out - but not now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:18:27 UTC">
      <body>I need good sleep </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:18:58 UTC">
      <body>It's good that you know your limits! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:20:16 UTC">
      <body>That's a dangerous formula - two koalas and only one slice of cake </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:20:32 UTC">
      <body>Thanks for the chart. Super helpful! Sleep well. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:21:44 UTC">
      <body>Since you responded favorably to one koala I thought two might be tempting! And cake is tempting. But not to koalas. They prefer </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131424" time="2013-02-12 04:22:51 UTC">
      <body>Ooooh  I learned something else today.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130962" time="2013-02-12 04:23:48 UTC">
      <body>:) I hope you dream about really nice koalas.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
