<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120413.0003" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 02:32:20 UTC">
      <body>Did you get my voicemail?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 03:04:55 UTC">
      <body>Why are you ignoring me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 03:27:11 UTC">
      <body>Tim, please, you're scaring me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 05:28:41 UTC">
      <body>Not really ignoring, just been busy. Also pretty hurt. I'll call sometime soon.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 10:46:33 UTC">
      <body>What are you hurt about?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 11:03:39 UTC">
      <body>I know you're awake - Tim,  I'm trying to be a friend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 11:12:58 UTC">
      <body>You wouldn't let me get away with this</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:31:37 UTC">
      <body>(01/03) So many things Martha. Scott. That you're dating someone so soon after dumping me. It makes me feel sick. Little things like you deleting the only photo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:31:47 UTC">
      <body>(02/03)  of you and I and blocking me on gchat. And you HAVE gotten away with this since day one! This is exactly how you've treated me since you dumped me. I'm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:31:57 UTC">
      <body>(03/03)  not trying to be didactic or prove a point, just observing. I want to believe you so badly Mattie, but you don't feel like a friend. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:31:58 UTC">
      <body>Great text convo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:34:05 UTC">
      <body>Oof</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 11:36:16 UTC">
      <body>Don't I have the ability to date someone else and still be a friend? And I did do those things but not to hurt you. It hurt me to see a picture of you and I and I went invisible bc I was terribly busy! But that doesn't negate the fact that I'm reaching out now and saying the things I said last time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:42:06 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) Im sure there's an explanation for everything. It just hurts like fucking  hell. And until now you haven't been a friend. You're going to need to say th</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:42:16 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ose things many times before they mean anything. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 11:43:41 UTC">
      <body>Ok, well I'll do what I can but you have to forgive me for them for this friendship to work. One question: how did you know I was dating Scott?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 11:47:14 UTC">
      <body>Ok that should be easy. Because I know how you operate. You're already dating him? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 11:53:11 UTC">
      <body>"because i know how you operate." Forget it, Tim.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 12:05:05 UTC">
      <body>I'm deeply offended - though I totally understand your feelings and apologize that this knowledge makes you uncomfortable though I assure you I didn't do anything to demean you. In the end I can't justify your means for expressing yourself or those feelings. It only proves the fact that we shouldn't be communicating then. So please stop. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:06:00 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) You dump me and start dating someone you've been friends with for a while. Before it was "not a possibility " as you told me, but once it was, or incent</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:06:09 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) ive there was the slightest chance there would be, you dumped me. That's how it seems </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:07:27 UTC">
      <body>What? You asked me! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 12:09:46 UTC">
      <body>I broke up with you because of fundamental flaws in the relationship. Period. I did ask but now I'm asking for space bc I already feel deep shame for ending things honestly without you saying that I was dishonest. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:12:40 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) That's not fair at all. I'm sorry if I offended you, I'm not attacking your character Martha. And not suggesting you were dishonest. Lack of communicati</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:12:50 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) on is what leads me to conjecture. When you communicate with me I have no reason for those thoughts  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 12:14:31 UTC">
      <body>I communicated with you this week. I had the right to take time at the beginning. You can feel hurt but you can't say hurtful things to me. Either way, I want some space </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:30:35 UTC">
      <body>(01/05) Fuck Martha. I'm sorry that came off that way. Really. Can you please, for once, not ask for space. These whole fucking two months have been at your con</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:30:45 UTC">
      <body>(02/05) venience. I don't expect you to talk any more than you have, but please don't ask for more space. It makes things worse. It makes me think that you don'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:30:55 UTC">
      <body>(03/05) t actually want to TRY at a friendship because space is easier. Please stop being defensive and make yourself vulnerable in some way and I will do the s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:30:56 UTC">
      <body>(04/05) ame. Just be fucking honest with me because you care about me. I'm sick and tired and need you to be a friend. I know how you operate, and by that I mea</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 12:30:57 UTC">
      <body>(05/05) n I know you know how to do things right. Even if it's hard.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131839" time="2012-04-13 13:04:37 UTC">
      <body>That isn't what you meant.  I'm not going to fight with you. I'll be open.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 14:46:58 UTC">
      <body>(01/02) I don't know what I meant before but that is what i mean now. Just do what's right Mattie. Not what's right for me or right for you, just what's right. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="135117" time="2012-04-13 14:47:08 UTC">
      <body>(02/02) And please no more serious conversations via text message or at 6 am. Or on Friday the 13 th. That's not right. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
