<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150201.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-01 17:25:20 UTC" participant="149394">
      <body>Hey ##### I hope you are feeling better. If you'd like the St. John's wort tincture Id be happy for you to have it. It's noted for helping with ####### and ########### It may help you get through this uncertain time with your ###############. You can look up info on it. I don't know if there are any concerns about it interfering with #################################### What I have is a wild crafted vodka tincture my mother made with at johns wort that grows in her labyrinth. Let me know if you'd like to try it and I can leave it at ####### for you. I was also thinking you might try drinking a cup of bone broth every day. It helps with vitality and bone and joint health. I hope this isn't annoying meddling! I just don't like seeing you ##### and ############ Xo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-01 18:26:20 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>No, not at all meddling. I need a small support team I think to get back to a manageable existence. I would like to try both the St. John's wart and the bone broth. Thank you for being so helpful! It's good to know I have some support.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-01 18:31:28 UTC" participant="149394">
      <body>Good! I know there are a couple quarts of broth I made in #'s freezer already and a couple bags of bones I'm planning to make another batch with this week. I can also show you how to make it, it's easy. You're such a wonderful person and I know how much you mean to ###### and everyone, myself included. # and I are planning on trying out the flotation tanks too if you're interested in joining us. It's called halcyon floats if you want to get more info. Hang In there buddy! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-01 18:33:00 UTC" participant="149306">
      <body>Let me know how the tanks go. Thanks for all the love.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

