<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140722.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-07-22 20:30:39 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Hey. I haven't heard from you, but mike and I are going to go down the shore on Wednesday and Thursday (assuming my mom doesn't have work Wednesday). Are you able/can you take off those days?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-07-22 20:34:52 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I know! I'm sorry. I was actually going to text you later. Michael still needs to ask at work. His boss has been on vacation but she's back now. Let me text him. I should be able to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-07-22 20:36:08 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>So that's the 20th and 21st right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-07-22 20:38:07 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Yes! And I'm going to make sure that my mom is off that Wednesday. I want to do it on a day she's off so she won't be stranded.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-07-22 20:40:25 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. I asked him. Hopefully he'll get an answer soon. Also,  I feel bad. He had to put Jackie down this morning. She was in kidney failure.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-07-22 20:41:38 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>OH GOD! That's awful!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-07-22 20:44:14 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I know. It's sad.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-07-22 22:28:42 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>So I just asked my mom. She actually has an appointment with the social security department so we'll have to go Thursday-Friday. Is that okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-07-22 22:31:26 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. That's fine for me. Michael still needs to ask. I don't foresee it being a problem. I know he does have a lot going on in work though. He just actually needs to ask and put in for it. I'm trying to stay on top of him. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-07-22 22:34:09 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. No worries!!! The only stipulation is that on Friday we'd have to be back by 5 so I can pick up my mom at work. Haha.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-07-22 22:34:44 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah that's fine.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-07-22 22:35:11 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>When do you for sure need an answer by so that reservations can be made?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-07-22 22:36:58 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>I have no idea. I'd like to make them as soon as possible. Prices will only be going up, but I don't want to rush you, especially if Michael is in a bind.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-07-22 22:37:24 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok. I'm just gonna tell him by the end of this week he needs to know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-07-22 22:38:57 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay! If that doesn't work, then I will figure out another day we can go! Even if it's only for a day. We'll hijack a pool!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-07-22 22:39:26 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. Ok. I'll be in touch :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

