<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130327.0023" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 12:21:19 UTC">
      <body>Good morning sweet MaDonica! I hope your peer review search wasn't too aggravating </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 12:44:49 UTC">
      <body>Hey sweeters!! It wasn't too bad. I just have this thing I've had my whole life where I hate doing things that I feel compromise my integrity. I found something ok I think. (Don't even remember what it is now!!)  Ed jus scored some major points with me by</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 12:48:22 UTC">
      <body>Oops...I can't find the Rolly guide email</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 12:48:57 UTC">
      <body>It's in google drive shared with you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 12:56:34 UTC">
      <body>Did you find it or do you need help? I still haven't filled in Shaoyang because that's not till next week.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 13:03:34 UTC">
      <body>You know I'm computer illiterate lol! I usually just get an email with a link. Okay.....here goes, my virgin effort!  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 13:04:25 UTC">
      <body>Be brave my darling! Yes I do know you are computer illiterate. That's why I wrote back to you!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:28:08 UTC">
      <body>Sooooo, finally found it...we're doing yang ming? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:29:44 UTC">
      <body>Yes that is what he said I think! 98% sure. Yangming is my favorite. I hope it didn't take you that whole time. :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:35:18 UTC">
      <body>It did take most of that time....and yang ming being your favorite makes you such a weirdo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:46:48 UTC">
      <body>I am proud to be a wonderful weirdo!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:48:21 UTC">
      <body>Good luck with that!  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:49:17 UTC">
      <body>It's why you love me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:49:53 UTC">
      <body>Noooo, i love you despite it :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:49:59 UTC">
      <body>Yangming is the colon (ok, big daddy intestine for you) and the stomach. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:50:17 UTC">
      <body>No you love me for who I am exactly! At least I hope so. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:50:32 UTC">
      <body>I love that we get along despite my uterus. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:51:36 UTC">
      <body>Acupuncture=flesh and organs! Woohoo! Way to end my healing career! Lol! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:52:01 UTC">
      <body>You had to add the uterus!  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:54:15 UTC">
      <body>I love flesh but I don't think that's the point at all. Yangming is big appetite and hunger and excretion.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:54:38 UTC">
      <body>I save you from do many other references to uteri just because I love you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:57:04 UTC">
      <body>Our etheric bodies have no appetite or excretion.....so potato potahto right! Lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 14:57:49 UTC">
      <body>And thanks for looking out with the hey nani nani references. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 14:58:20 UTC">
      <body>I don't know what to tell you. :) I have one understanding and you have another. I hope you don't think I'm dumb or wrong. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:05:05 UTC">
      <body>Not at all.....you're certainly not dumb.... Just the acupuncture that's available isn't energy medicine from what i can see, it's physical therapy focus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:05:15 UTC">
      <body>ed on the physical frame and organs and muscles and all that....we all learn differently...it's just a matter of all that, not better or worse..... But e</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:05:16 UTC">
      <body>nergetic issues and patterns are carried lifetime to lifetime....soooooo, unless we're bringing organs and tendons and muscles in with us.....lol. But i </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:05:18 UTC">
      <body>never think you're silly or dumb.... I wish sometimes tho you could sit in on a class with me that's devoted to real energy healing so we could have that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:05:19 UTC">
      <body> discussion....maybe some day you'll go with me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:07:03 UTC">
      <body>I would love to go with you. Invite me. I will likely come. The way I want to practice is not tendinomuscular. Though I would like to help sore necks and backs and knees sometimes too. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:07:17 UTC">
      <body>That's why in learning from Laura. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:08:55 UTC">
      <body>I know that for sure! You know i know you and your struggles for five element treatment of the whole person.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:09:20 UTC">
      <body>I will likely never take the same path as you but we will still love and respect each other, I hope. What we do at school is nothing like what I learn from Laura. Then again there are similarities. I just did something really exciting. I got a bus ticket </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:09:27 UTC">
      <body>It was a $1 ticket!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:10:01 UTC">
      <body>Yay! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:10:42 UTC">
      <body>I am grateful for you but I don't have the background to know what you know and I probably don't have the brain power to do so in this lifetime! :) But that's ok. Maybe next time around.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:11:25 UTC">
      <body>I called Laura this morning with worries about my understanding of Ryan and she helped me. Maybe I will tell you a little big about it sometime. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:13:26 UTC">
      <body>You definitely have the brain power! But i just have put more tine in it in terms of years.  that's all. Plus, we have different ray structures.....you h</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:14:33 UTC">
      <body>ave a lot of six ray, i have lots of fifth and seventh. Soooooo we approach things differently....but still wanna help humanity, right? That new what's i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:14:34 UTC">
      <body>mportant. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:14:55 UTC">
      <body>Yes! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:15:14 UTC">
      <body>You still have to decide which ray is the cute ray body. Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:16:00 UTC">
      <body>Blasphemy! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:17:13 UTC">
      <body>Want to do a day trip to NYC on May 26? It's a Sunday. Long treatments start at 9am usually. Not alot of talking. Just sitting in treatments. You might not like it. Or you might. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:17:46 UTC">
      <body>#####################################################</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:18:54 UTC">
      <body>More blasphemy!  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:20:11 UTC">
      <body>I'll think about it and let you know.....i think i have an inherent bias against the extended treatments.....but I'll examine myself and see where that's</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:20:52 UTC">
      <body>:) I mean total respect to your tradition though. I like the ideas of rays within rays. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:21:18 UTC">
      <body> coming from...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:21:53 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know, I'm inviting you with trepidation. I think we should wait till we can go to NYC for a day on a Friday when she is talking not treating. I think that would be better for you. Lets wait then. It just feels like it will be a long time till we ca</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:22:33 UTC">
      <body>I think you need to use your mind and would like the talking workshop part better. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:23:37 UTC">
      <body>Cara might actually go on May 24 to the workshop. I want to go to buy have to miss two weeks of clinic for the IDs workshop in Maine this summer so I can't go to that too. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:24:10 UTC">
      <body>NYC is definitely better for you than Maine because you can slip in and slip out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:30:10 UTC">
      <body>Definitely a good idea. Could i ask her questions too? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:32:38 UTC">
      <body>Yes you could talk during the workshop. :) On long treatment days there is not a lot of time to talk. Just back to back treatments. I don't think that would be as satisfying for you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:35:21 UTC">
      <body>The workshop days are not droning lectures. More like whatever learning arises from the group. You have so many questions I'm not sure there would ever be time to really sink to the vote with you and clear everything up but you could try. Today Laura told</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:37:52 UTC">
      <body>If you did go to long tx days the first time anyone sits in a long tx they wear white and are in the role of the witness. The witness sits in the tx and watches whatever is of interest to them. You would watch well bc you are a natural observer. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:38:19 UTC">
      <body>But you want to know/understand more than watch. I think. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:42:27 UTC">
      <body>Plus.....i have my own issues of course . Okay...radio silence for a bit, back to my hearing! Ciao! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:43:35 UTC">
      <body>I love you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:45:16 UTC">
      <body>And i love you....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:47:08 UTC">
      <body>I know. I want you to know that I love you no matter what. I don't want our separate ways of understanding to come between us. I really look up to you. And I think that you are caring towards others. Which is important to me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:48:11 UTC">
      <body>Same with me...exactly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:48:42 UTC">
      <body>:* Sideways kisses. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:49:11 UTC">
      <body> :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="131435" time="2013-03-27 15:49:32 UTC">
      <body>See you in class..... Maybe!  :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="130962" time="2013-03-27 15:49:53 UTC">
      <body>You should be bad and stay home!!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
