<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110521.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130845" time="2011-05-21 17:57:46 UTC">
      <body>I see you... Look up!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130845" time="2011-05-28 18:44:54 UTC">
      <body>Heya- favor to ask. Any chance we could borrow tubes/rafts for monday? Have some but not enough. Wanting to take mom for a float down the brandywine...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130755" time="2011-05-28 18:46:00 UTC">
      <body>Yea!  For sure, I have tons.  When ya wanna get 'em?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130845" time="2011-05-28 18:48:09 UTC">
      <body>Heading out to downingtown now to visit victory. Later this eve maybe?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130755" time="2011-05-28 18:52:26 UTC">
      <body>Shurrrrrmaybe.  Gonna be in west phila, till I don't know when, but give a ring and we'll give it a go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130845" time="2011-05-28 18:55:19 UTC">
      <body>Ok, sounds good... I'm flexible. I'll give you a shout when we're back, we'll work something out. Thanks!! You are awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130755" time="2011-05-28 18:55:43 UTC">
      <body>No prob!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130755" time="2011-06-30 17:53:47 UTC">
      <body>Heya!  I'm back in town and my sorrows can only be drowned in beer and river water...any chance I can nab those tubes from ya sometime soonish?  And do you want to go (birthday toob on the 17th and possibly before!)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130845" time="2011-07-09 22:20:45 UTC">
      <body>Hey! You around your place? Just got home, but heading out again in a bit. Can do toob drop if you're available...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130755" time="2011-07-10 05:29:26 UTC">
      <body>Sorry!  Will be around tomorrow?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130845" time="2011-07-15 16:22:14 UTC">
      <body>Hey- I'm suddenly only a maybe for tomorrow- are you around today our tonight to receive toobz just in case?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130755" time="2011-07-15 18:32:00 UTC">
      <body>Not tomorrow, Sunday! Jeremy is around today to receive toobz tho...but hope you can come!  Lemme know so I have a count for the car!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130845" time="2011-07-15 21:14:34 UTC">
      <body>Sunday! Don't know how I got that mixed up. Ok, that may work better...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130755" time="2011-07-16 02:27:27 UTC">
      <body>Ok!  When can you let me know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130845" time="2011-07-16 21:37:54 UTC">
      <body>Ok... In for tomorrow! If you still have space for me... Don't think I can wrangle a car</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130755" time="2011-07-16 21:39:27 UTC">
      <body>Should be good!  See ya in the morn round 9!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130845" time="2011-07-17 12:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Hey! would it be be possible to swing by and grab me from/near my house in a car? Not sure I should attempt biking all those tubes. Can walk but it'll be a bit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130755" time="2011-07-17 12:57:17 UTC">
      <body>Shurrre.  It's just you right?  I'll letcha know when we head over.  Also, hadta get a carshare, $10 a person</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130845" time="2011-07-17 13:10:03 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good... Thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130755" time="2011-10-01 20:48:41 UTC">
      <body>Heya!  Got a request to see if you and yr cornhole game would like to come to an awesome hoedown tonight!  Ride provided for ya both!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130845" time="2011-10-01 21:04:31 UTC">
      <body>Oh, rats! I'm already planned up for the evening and my cornhole boards are loaned out! Have fun though!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130755" time="2011-10-01 21:09:43 UTC">
      <body>Thanks anyway!  And we need to hang soon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130755" time="2011-11-22 23:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Post thanksgiving feast! Friday at a location soon to be decided...celebrate year 2 of our tradition of eating a seitan loaf shaped like the object/animal of our choice.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130755" time="2012-05-22 17:34:07 UTC">
      <body>Heya! Our show in Knoxville is tonight at the birdhouse. If you know anyone who might like it, send em our way! Thx!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130845" time="2012-05-22 21:04:26 UTC">
      <body>Sent messages to the puppet-lovers and art heads in K-town... Hope you get a good crowd! How's it been so far? Break a leg tonight!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130755" time="2012-05-22 21:05:21 UTC">
      <body>Thx so much! It's been great so far!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
