<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150325.0038" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-25 22:15:19 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Has the cat caved in to her need for love? We"ve been laughing that she was probably smelling you while you slept. She is such a little creeper!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-25 22:27:30 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Last night she totally hopped the baby gate 15 times before I went to sleep so I'm sure she was night creeping. We played for about an hour last night and she let me pet her a bunch but runs when I stand up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-25 22:30:10 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>You just put the biggest smile on mc's face. That cat is such a piece of work. You are apparently just too damn tall :)
she actually loves jonah but runs every time he stands up too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-25 22:30:41 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I'm just gonna have to crawl around the house.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-25 22:32:57 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Lol. Mckenna says she's worth it. Donna says she's a spoiled brat and not worth it :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-25 22:34:05 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Hahahaha. Your neighbors are gonna wonder what the deal is if I'm crawling around the house!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-26 17:08:02 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>There is a gray kitten on you porch!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-26 17:11:30 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>There are 2 bowls on the porch under the couch. You can give it food and water. There is cat food in the bin with the dog food. We'll take it to AaCT PHILLY TOMOrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-26 17:12:48 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Will do! It's pretty cute. Just sleeping on the couch. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-26 17:27:09 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Our neighbor had taken it in. Guess he let it go. Argh. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-26 17:33:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>She will get adopted fast! Also Pyper was so chatty this morning. What a squeaker! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-26 17:35:14 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Was she telling you that the cat was out there? She gets really vocal about other cats</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-26 18:16:13 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I think she was telling to feed her immediately. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-26 18:17:54 UTC" participant="153685">
      <body>Yes. She does love her sources of foodI</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

