<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130619.0004" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 10:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Hello webfoot, you're back! I was just regretting falling off yesterday. We're having a harrowing roadtrip and using my phone to solve problems constantly. 4 hrs from Philly and just about no money for gas, tolls, or food and no sleep. I guess that's how it goes.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 11:15:31 UTC">
      <body>Just take the toll roads, it's like deliverance on the side roads out there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 11:16:29 UTC">
      <body>So where r u from you never said or if you don't want to that's understandable</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 11:48:43 UTC">
      <body>Oh no are you stuck on the side of the highway right now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 11:49:22 UTC">
      <body>I could send AAA</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 11:53:29 UTC">
      <body>It's ok, thank u stranger. We happened upon the bank that I needed to find to cash a check. I'm originally from upstate ny. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:03:06 UTC">
      <body>I'm from finger lake region sw of Syracuse</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:03:06 UTC">
      <body>Are you from real upstate or Yonkers upstate</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:03:06 UTC">
      <body>Which is actually down state</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:03:06 UTC">
      <body>To most of the state</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:07:24 UTC">
      <body>Broome County upstate, touching PA but no NYC culture. Fingerlakes is nice. I know what u mean about fake upstate tho. White plains? No way jose.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:09:03 UTC">
      <body>Yeah ppl from NYC don't know what the real upstate is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:09:52 UTC">
      <body>Do you know Chris Lawrence? He's from near there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:10:54 UTC">
      <body>I do kinda. Our moms know each other.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:11:55 UTC">
      <body>I know Chris' mom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:12:53 UTC">
      <body>I don't actually</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:16:28 UTC">
      <body>So are you driving back to Philly or somewhere else</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:19:40 UTC">
      <body>I'm just catching a greyhound to Binghamton and picking up my van to drive to Richmond to get ready for a show.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:21:19 UTC">
      <body>Art show, with giant bat bikes?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:33:07 UTC">
      <body>We're you in the truck show at the ice box last year</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:33:07 UTC">
      <body>Yes, but no. Some sculptures and costumes and sound and performers. I have to cut down these big carbon fiber things and figure out how to get em back together to get through a standard doorway. Sucks. I would've just turned it down, but if I figure it out, it opens up possibilities to show it elsewhere.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:33:07 UTC">
      <body>I'm hoping I can do it for as close to $0 as possible.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:35:01 UTC">
      <body>No. I know there the only place without a tiny door problem, other than Little Berlin, but a rental gallery is out of the question.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:35:29 UTC">
      <body>Found material is the only way to make large scale sculpture unless you are a rich kid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:36:01 UTC">
      <body>Big doors are a plus</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:36:25 UTC">
      <body>I think I know who I'm talking to now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:37:12 UTC">
      <body>Noooo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:37:18 UTC">
      <body>You probably do</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:39:02 UTC">
      <body>I don't know who you are</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:41:29 UTC">
      <body>Just ask Chris's mom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:41:29 UTC">
      <body>Just joking</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:42:15 UTC">
      <body>You probably don't know me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:42:15 UTC">
      <body>I don't think we've ever met</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 12:43:52 UTC">
      <body>I'll ask my mom to ask his mom</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 12:45:18 UTC">
      <body>So what are the carbon fiber things you are cutting up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 13:15:29 UTC">
      <body>They're these drapey triangular peaks that have speakers mounted in them.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:38:13 UTC">
      <body>That sounds cool.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:39:04 UTC">
      <body>Did you record sound pieces to play through for them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:39:09 UTC">
      <body>*through them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 13:41:00 UTC">
      <body>A friend of mine from Richmond did. We had a number of meeting in which I described what I wanted without a competent sound vocabulary.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:45:47 UTC">
      <body>I've recorded some sound stuff for installations and it was super fun. I got to scream a lot and play with chainsaws</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:46:13 UTC">
      <body>I like screaming the best</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 13:56:41 UTC">
      <body>So where did you go to grad school?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 13:57:55 UTC">
      <body>Vcu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:01:14 UTC">
      <body>I went to penn.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:01:42 UTC">
      <body>How was vcu's program</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:02:58 UTC">
      <body>Penn was ok but I definitely wouldn't have gone if the hadn't paid for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:02:58 UTC">
      <body>It's crazy how much that place charges</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:04:57 UTC">
      <body>I went to undergrad at mica and paid for that though. I'm still paying for that and will be for a long time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:06:16 UTC">
      <body>I also did a postbacc program at goldsmiths in london before penn. it was only a 1 year program</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 14:06:16 UTC">
      <body>That makes sense bc I don't really know anyone from Penn. I was in the sculpture program, which is great solely for nonfigurative sculpture, and unbelievably ignorant about anything else.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:07:19 UTC">
      <body>Did u know Nigel Roth at vcu's</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 14:17:41 UTC">
      <body>Not really. I've met him, but that's it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:20:09 UTC">
      <body>He's quite tall</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:33:05 UTC">
      <body>So do you live Virginia more than Philly?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 14:57:47 UTC">
      <body>I did, but I'm graduated now. Just this last show. I'm not really in Philly either. I'm working in Minneapolis occasionally, have this show and a residency at art farm Nebraska in Sept, and am going on trips and crashing with my family in between. In oct, I'll move to ny.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 14:59:49 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like a fun summer. What are your plans for ny? Do you mean NYC or upstate?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:01:49 UTC">
      <body>NYC. I don't really have any plans, just have to go somewhere. Philly's great, but I'm done dealing with the revenue dept.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:11:28 UTC">
      <body>NYC is whole other batch of problems/ opportunities I guess.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:11:28 UTC">
      <body>It was always way too expensive for me. Especially when I started doing large sculpture because so much space is needed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:11:28 UTC">
      <body>They randomly tried to sue me for $10k right before BPT was reformed, even though I worked with a Philly accountant the whole time I lived here. I won with a volunteer lawyer, but bombed a show in the process.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:11:28 UTC">
      <body>And now they're looking for me again even though I haven't lived, worked, or intersected with money here in 2 years. No thanks.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:16:11 UTC">
      <body>Huh that's crazy. I haven't had any problems like that here, knock on wood.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, they tried to sue a handful of random artists at once to see what came of it, then the tax was reformed.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Did you have a business in Philly then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>I'm pretty sure NYC has higher business taxes than Philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I don't know yet how I'll manage. I imagine there will be a gap of time in which almost nothing is possible. I'm trying to buy some dirt cheap landwith the first time buyers' program and build a barebones studio shack on it 2 hrs upstate. The mortgage would be half the price as a closet-sized studio. I'll just have a studio in the city if it miraculously appears from an LMCC application or something.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:25:53 UTC">
      <body>You're safe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:27:53 UTC">
      <body>Good to hear that I'm safe!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:28:18 UTC">
      <body>But I don't make any money to speak of off of art in Philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:28:51 UTC">
      <body>Not much of a market in Philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:38:15 UTC">
      <body>No, but I was paid on 1099 as an individual, which nearly everyone low-income is in Philly. It gets messy with BPT because only an experienced Philly accountant can fill out the forms bc they're so convoluted, plus it costs $75 a year just to pay, or $300 for a lifetime license. NYC reformed business taxfor 1099'd individuals long ago.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:38:15 UTC">
      <body>And business tax is definitely lower overall there even for big biz. Comcast only relocated bc Philly gave them an exemption to try to change that perception.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:38:15 UTC">
      <body>The things I make are too ephemeral to be purchased for the most part.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 15:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Huh, well lets hope that never happens again. Sounds like a nightmare</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:57:53 UTC">
      <body>Yup, but over now. I think I nearly have a good combo of collectible and ephemeral. I'll just see where it goes. I want toile a play next.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 15:57:53 UTC">
      <body>Oops, to make</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:03:16 UTC">
      <body>Ah my friend in Berlin did art direction and created sets for avant theater in NYC for a bit. She would fly back in the summer and build these cool inflatable sets with autonomous flying components that responded tho the audience and stage action</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 16:06:41 UTC">
      <body>Awesome. Berlin makes sense. Theater there is more likely to be invested in the stage magic. It's way more focused on the craft of acting here. I was inPoland over Christmas break to check out the theater. Pretty rad.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 16:07:12 UTC">
      <body>What's her name? I'd like to see.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:15:20 UTC">
      <body>Hannah Dougherty, but she's originally from Philly, we met at mica.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:16:42 UTC">
      <body>I want to go to Poland! I'm half polish and want to see Warsaw where my grandparents lived before WWII</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 16:26:23 UTC">
      <body>There are a lot of foreigners doing that in Warsaw especially. I think if you're foreign, they kind of assume you're researching Jewish heritage.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:27:47 UTC">
      <body>I guess that makes sense</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:28:58 UTC">
      <body>But my family was not Jewish but had Jewish friends which they helped hide so my family lost all property.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:29:53 UTC">
      <body>My great grandparents were killed and my grandparents and uncles were sent to a work camp</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:30:58 UTC">
      <body>I think my great grandparents were sent to buchenwald.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 16:32:06 UTC">
      <body>Wild. Both times I went to Europe, it was striking how current ww2 seems still. I guess it is here, but the evidence is invisible.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:32:06 UTC">
      <body>They were wealthy before the war but were dirt poor when they came to America because all there money and property was taken destroyed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:32:06 UTC">
      <body>*&amp;</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 16:33:22 UTC">
      <body>How did they manage the passage?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:41:14 UTC">
      <body>My grandparent parents and uncles were sent to a work camp making bomb shells and then after the Americans liberated the camp they came to the US as refugees because they had no home or money in Warsaw</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:41:47 UTC">
      <body>I think the army brought them over</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 16:41:53 UTC">
      <body>But my mom was born here after the war</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 17:47:57 UTC">
      <body>Do you know Matthew Maycock? He curated a show at Little Berlin about 3 yrs ago of polish and polish-American artists. He was living in Warsaw for awhile.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 18:51:53 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know him a little bit. Didn't he move to NYC</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 18:55:48 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I've ever talked with him about being polish but I knew he lived there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 18:56:55 UTC">
      <body>He always had good shirts</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:00:30 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure. I just knew he was there recently. I miss that guy, so amiable. He's been wearing Hawaiian shirts for like the last 7 or 8 years.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:00:30 UTC">
      <body>And studying fruit flies.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:01:12 UTC">
      <body>I hope I catch him there and talk about Poland.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:02:26 UTC">
      <body>That place is chock full of amazing homemade traditional polish food and beers diiiirt cheap.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:02:47 UTC">
      <body>So many 4 course meals with beers for two under $15</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:02:47 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I remember seeing him a lot at the berks warehouse years ago and much less recently in w Philly.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:11:17 UTC">
      <body>He also used to teach midnight math or something at PIFAS.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:11:17 UTC">
      <body>Almost to Scranton for my 2 hr layover</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:11:17 UTC">
      <body>I think he's a programmer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:11:17 UTC">
      <body>I'd like to talk to him about Poland too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:11:17 UTC">
      <body>What place is chock full of amazing homemade traditional polish food and beers diiiirt cheap ? Poland?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:13:12 UTC">
      <body>Tessa</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:21:37 UTC">
      <body>Yesss? Thank u autocorrect</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:31:23 UTC">
      <body>That sounds cheep.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>Did you ever go to the polish restaurant / bar on allegheny ave called new wave?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>In Philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>It has polish beer and food and the weirdest paintings of outer space meets Hokusai's wave meets digitalization.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>All the guys at the bar wear track suits and gold chains and are polish gangsters.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>The food is real good, it's made by one old woman and the kitchen closes at 8 pm sharp.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>Sometimes after the kitchen closes the dining area turns into a polish disco.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:42:32 UTC">
      <body>The room is mirrored and they play euro techno, it does not feel like you are in America at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:42:33 UTC">
      <body>Finding things was really hard and cryptic, but that made it better.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:44:04 UTC">
      <body>Whoooooooa no I had no idea. I must go next time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:44:35 UTC">
      <body>I'm afraid I'll get addicted.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:47:59 UTC">
      <body>It's not that easy to get to and the area isn't great so I don't go very often</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:48:57 UTC">
      <body>Sometimes you get the feeling you are not welcome by the guys in track suits</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:49:02 UTC">
      <body>The inaccessibility keeps it classic</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:49:57 UTC">
      <body>But that whole area On allegheny is a polish neighborhood</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:50:29 UTC">
      <body>Something about that must be cool though, like when one unfamiliar tough guy walks into a bar full of other tough guys.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:50:40 UTC">
      <body>East of the el</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:51:27 UTC">
      <body>I didn't know. I used to work in a flag factory near there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:51:27 UTC">
      <body>But I did not explore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:51:36 UTC">
      <body>I'm not so tough so I wouldn't know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 19:52:31 UTC">
      <body>Ah did you go to shows at adventure island</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:53:22 UTC">
      <body>No, I kind of missed that boat. Wish I did though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 19:54:11 UTC">
      <body>Maybe you have the force like that kid at the end of wet hot American summer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:02:36 UTC">
      <body>The savior</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:02:36 UTC">
      <body>New wave is close to adventure island</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:03:36 UTC">
      <body>You mean the kid at the talent show who makes the satellite crash?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:04:39 UTC">
      <body>What makes you think I have those sorts of powers?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:11:10 UTC">
      <body>Yes that kid. There could be a compensation for lack of toughness. I'm trying to be positive here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:16:26 UTC">
      <body>I wish I could make satellites fall to earth, I'll just have to settle for making sphinx's out of broken glass and golf balls.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:16:55 UTC">
      <body>Although its not a great defense</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:17:22 UTC">
      <body>What is your super power?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0142" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:18:31 UTC">
      <body>That sounds like it'll do. I keep thinking you're Howard because of the artwork, but I know him?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0143" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:18:31 UTC">
      <body>Preternatural understanding of late ripe motives</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0144" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:19:43 UTC">
      <body>What? ALTERIOR</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0145" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:19:43 UTC">
      <body>I don't understand my new phone at all.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0146" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:19:43 UTC">
      <body>Yours?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0147" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:19:43 UTC">
      <body>Mine's more of a curse</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0148" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:21:37 UTC">
      <body>I had a flip phone for 6 years and just got an iPhone , I nearly returned it before I left the store.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0149" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:22:37 UTC">
      <body>So you know everyone's motives ? Even mine?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0150" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:23:44 UTC">
      <body>No, your texts are not informationy enough.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0151" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:24:13 UTC">
      <body>They have sparse evidence of attitude</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0152" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:24:50 UTC">
      <body>So I'm safe... For now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0153" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:26:21 UTC">
      <body>No, forever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0154" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:26:50 UTC">
      <body>No Philly livin again</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0155" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:30:08 UTC">
      <body>I do have a bit of an attitude but it comes out more when I am not face to face with someone. I am pretty shy around people I don't know or self conscious anyway.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0156" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:39:56 UTC">
      <body>Usually you find out eventually that shy people are bubbling over with 'rude</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0157" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:39:56 UTC">
      <body>'TUDE</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0158" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:39:56 UTC">
      <body>At least in person, not when I'm texting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0159" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:47:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh no I'm just taking it out on texting partners!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0160" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:56:08 UTC">
      <body>Sorry bout that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0161" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 20:56:08 UTC">
      <body>I can't help myself, I'm a monster</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0162" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 20:58:04 UTC">
      <body>It's ok to victimize the faceless, like coral.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0163" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:07:09 UTC">
      <body>It hasn't been my best day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0164" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:08:49 UTC">
      <body>I suggest heading to new wave, or karaoke, just to watch since you're an introvert.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0165" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:08:59 UTC">
      <body>Watching karaoke is awesome</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0166" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:15:32 UTC">
      <body>It's good advice but I have to adjust some photos in photoshop tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0167" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:16:45 UTC">
      <body>No rest for the wicked I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0168" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:17:08 UTC">
      <body>Well ok. I have to keep riding in vehicles forever and ever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0169" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:18:04 UTC">
      <body>If I don't have a pulmonary embolism after all this, I'm invincible.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0170" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:18:04 UTC">
      <body>That sounds better to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0171" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:26:53 UTC">
      <body>Maybe that's your super power</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0172" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:27:47 UTC">
      <body>I don't clot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0173" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:28:12 UTC">
      <body>It's just hemophilia.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0174" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:31:09 UTC">
      <body>Well when put that way it doesn't sound so super</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0175" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:32:31 UTC">
      <body>It's a Blooper Dour</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0176" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:38:10 UTC">
      <body>I don't know what that is</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0177" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:38:59 UTC">
      <body>I made it up. I don't know either.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0178" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Rhymes with super power, but sounds like a downer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0179" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 21:41:08 UTC">
      <body>A comical sedative ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0180" participant="131837" time="2013-06-19 21:42:43 UTC">
      <body>Sure. Speaking of them, I found the seat with the most legroom, so I'll probably be falling asleep soon. Clot on.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0181" participant="130518" time="2013-06-19 22:12:10 UTC">
      <body>Sleep tight. Thanks for the interesting conversation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0182" participant="130518" time="2013-06-20 08:29:07 UTC">
      <body>I hope you got to your destination without experiencing any serious medical issues.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0183" participant="130518" time="2013-06-20 08:30:33 UTC">
      <body>We are all kinda superheroes without healthcare ...if we don't get sick that is.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
