<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130827.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-08-27 19:57:18 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Did such a good job watching the dog.. that's whyhe chewed up steph's hat</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-08-27 19:58:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>How long has the air been on 74? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-08-27 19:59:12 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I took it off him and put it on the sofa. I don't know where he got it from.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-08-27 20:02:06 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Last night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-08-27 20:02:50 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I forgot to change it back</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-08-27 20:02:56 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok well you left it on. Air is to be off or raised to 76-78 the second you wake. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-08-27 20:03:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And why does it look like a party took place?  No one is allowed over when we are away</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-08-27 20:04:02 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>No one was here except Eden. What do you mean a party? Everything lying around th house was there when we got there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-08-27 20:04:55 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Just bec beer and pizza... and the trash was taken out early.why is it in the porch?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-08-27 20:06:06 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Idk if it was you or marc but twinkies and smartoned are for my baking.  Someone ate those too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-08-27 20:08:18 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And you didn't tell us we were out of detergent. I needed to wash work clothes when I got home.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-08-27 20:10:56 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I didn't have beer. That was already there when I got there the firs night. Me and Eden didn't have pizza. Unless you're talking about the frozen pizza bread box. I also didn't eat twinkies or smarties. Eden asked for one and I said no cause they were for your baking. The detergent was basically out before I used it this morning. I used the last drops. Meant to tell you before I left for work but forgot.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-08-27 20:11:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>So then it was marc?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-08-27 20:11:49 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I also didn't take out trash</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-08-27 20:12:56 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Do you know if he had anyone over?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2013-08-27 20:14:06 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And I'm not coming down on just you. I'm irked right now. Dog chewed #### up and air was left on so it just all snowballed. I'm getting marc now tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-08-27 20:15:29 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>The beer and pizza probably was marc. I didn't notice a pizza box and just thought the beer was yours or steph's. I didn't see much of marc. When I got back from work sunday night he was on the step and then left to sleep at his bosses. Didn't see him all day yesterday until last night but he just went to bed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2013-08-27 20:16:43 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And yeah its annoying that the dog chews stuff up. You should leave it out of his reach</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2013-08-27 20:17:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>No we don't really keep beer.. and there is pizza in tin foil in the fridge. I bunch of tradh in our recycle bin like beer cans and a trash bag in the porch </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2013-08-27 20:18:09 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>The pizza in tin foil is mine from work. I brought it home last night but didn't bring a box with it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2013-08-27 20:19:10 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>The hat was on the banister. Someone human had toknock it down andhe only chews stuff when left alone.  I already told you if he isn't up your ### he is doing something wrong.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2013-08-27 20:19:22 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Those two slices were left over from work and I brought it home in the tin foil already</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2013-08-27 20:19:37 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He follows everyone. If you are not yelling at him to move then ge is doing something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2013-08-27 20:20:01 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok so just the beer is marc's. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2013-08-27 20:20:08 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>There's a lot of paper towels in the trash. That was me. I had to clean up his poop and he also spit up on the rug</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2013-08-27 20:20:20 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2013-08-27 20:20:28 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Well I'm assuming</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2013-08-27 20:22:15 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lot of paper towelsin this current trash? No I mean the huge recycle bin in the porch is filled. It was empty when we left and there is a white trash bag in the porch next to it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2013-08-27 20:22:41 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Kitchen recycle bin is empty</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2013-08-27 20:22:46 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Oh no I didn't touch that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2013-08-27 20:25:49 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I didn't empty that. It wad full. Unless Eden emptied it without me knowing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2013-08-27 20:30:44 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And since when are my friends not allowed over when you're not home?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2013-08-27 20:31:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I doubt it was eden. It was marc. He put the beer box in the trash bag and trash in the porch. I don't like that.  That can draw bugs... I'm over this texting, are you coming home tonight?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2013-08-27 20:33:18 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And its not that.. I'm annoyed that no one in this house wants to listen. Like I said I come home to what looks like the dog unwatched, trash out and beer cans. Looked careless. But if your friends are over that's fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2013-08-27 20:34:24 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Steph and i were annoyed with how it seemed but When you come home I want to talk to you. Told marc the same</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2013-08-27 20:40:44 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay. I did do everything I was told though. I watched the dog, fed him, and watched spike. I forgot to raise the air this morning and think I forgot to put spike's light back to white this morning (which you should check on if you didn't yet). But other than that I followed the rules. I wouldn't trash a house. I don't like leaving a place in a condition other than the one it was in before I got there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2013-08-27 20:41:13 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I do come home tonight. But I get done work at 11.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2013-08-27 20:42:02 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>So I should be there sound midnight.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2013-08-27 20:42:10 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>*around</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2013-08-27 20:48:03 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok honestly I'm not mad at you. Just with the air on I was hoping it wasn't on all Weekend like that.  Our bill last time was $300 (normal is $85-90)... you see the difference and the dog eating things.  But not mad at you... marc on the other hand is in trouble</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2013-08-27 20:50:23 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

