<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150330.0036" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-30 13:15:44 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>ahhhhhh you're going to paris next week!!! i'm SO PSYCHED for you and HOW COOL you get to hang with houtii omgahhhhd! may i give you something to bring to him? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-30 13:15:44 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>it's a candle. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-30 15:31:27 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>Of course!!!! He will be so happy to have gifts from you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-30 15:31:53 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I'll see you Sunday at brunch yeah??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-30 15:34:33 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>haha he had a letter mailed to me recently (having to do with his biometrics for french citizenship app) and when i sent him the letter in paris i threw in a few little gifts, some temp tatoos a book a king size kit kat, I don't think he's expecting any more birthday gifts but i'd like to give him this candle which you MUST burn while yr there. it's so classy!!!! yes i'll see you on sunday!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-30 15:43:44 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>He's gonna love it! Can't wait to see you this weekend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-30 15:44:31 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>totally </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-30 15:45:04 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>i feel like tessa should be my ambassador and fill you in on all my shit bc we won't have enough time or privacy to get through all of it haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-30 16:54:36 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>I'll ask her to fill me in! We have dinner tonight. Then when I see you and can get to the nitty grits.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-30 16:55:28 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>ugh perfect! there isn't anyone that i entrust more than tessa to represent me in this. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-30 16:55:28 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>i'm jelz of yr dinner</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-30 16:55:28 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>have the best dinner!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-30 16:57:36 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>ps when you go to france please put a brillo pad in houtan's breakfast smoothie. trust me it's for his own good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-30 22:15:28 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>is he all blocked up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-30 22:15:28 UTC" participant="153548">
      <body>he needs a clean out!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-30 22:17:36 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>haha no he drinks this smoothie every morning instead of eating a food breakfast. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-30 22:17:36 UTC" participant="153648">
      <body>and i'm on his case bc he's scrawnier than ever and needs to like eat a damn ploughman's platter every morning instead of freakin hot water with lemon and a smoothie i shit you not that is his breakfast. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

