<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20121103.0022" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>I loved what you wrote on Michela's wall</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. Me too lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 21:57:41 UTC">
      <body>Lmfao yeah maybe it was too mean but I really don't know anything about her except that she made out with everyone in grease</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 21:58:30 UTC">
      <body>You didn't get with her tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 22:21:52 UTC">
      <body>I miss you. Come back into my life omggggg</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 22:23:00 UTC">
      <body>YEAH CUZ SHE GROSS LMAO</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 22:24:00 UTC">
      <body>It's ok. It was something abt managing having social groups but I forgot what going to school was like so no worries. My grandmother died two weeks ago which sucks. But other than that things are gooood. How are things with you????</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 22:24:32 UTC">
      <body>Omg miss u toooo. How are things??? We still never talked about what was bothering you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 22:28:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh that's so sad :( yeah you guys have been out of school for like a week wtf. I'm generally really busy during the week and then on Friday and Saturday I do absolutely nothing lol. But everything is good, I'm starting to feel comfortable here like this is my home. How are your apps going~</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 22:31:39 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. And tech doesn't restart til Wednesday. So crazy. How's your workload? Are you meeting people you connect with? I'm so happy you're settling in so well. My apps are fine haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 22:37:40 UTC">
      <body>It's mostly reading which you can skim most of the time but it is a lot of work. It depends tho cuz if you take math/science classes most of the work is in class or in lab so it's actually less hw. People here are really great, and I am connecting with them. Even if you get tired of someone there are a bunch of other cool people to hang out with. Did you do EA or ED or are you doing just regular decision</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 22:39:46 UTC">
      <body>I did ea to Stanford (gulp) but that's a total toss up. There's a kid who really annoys me who's applying early to Emory </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 22:40:37 UTC">
      <body>Nice! OMG whooooo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 22:41:04 UTC">
      <body>But that's crazy. What's it like knowing you're a plane ride away</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 23:23:03 UTC">
      <body>What do you mean</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 23:23:27 UTC">
      <body>like being so far from home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 23:32:40 UTC">
      <body>Well it feels very close and very similar to home. I feel like I can leave New York and go anywhere and do anything and it will always just be there for me to come back to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 23:34:22 UTC">
      <body>yeah but college is a different world with totally different poeple and ways of life etc</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136164" time="2012-11-03 23:38:42 UTC">
      <body>That true, but you kinda naturally adapt very quickly without realizing it. It just feels like sleep away camp for a while until you're like "oh shit I live here" at which point it's totally normal and you're used to it. Plus everyone else is in the same position and eager to make friends and such</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="136203" time="2012-11-03 23:39:52 UTC">
      <body>that's so cute im excited</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
