<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120529.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-05-29 22:47:11 UTC">
      <body>How'd it go today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 03:56:37 UTC">
      <body>Hey do you have a minute to talk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:01:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah sure man no speaking tho lol. Also she said yes i'm sorry i forgot to respond!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:05:46 UTC">
      <body>Haha nice!!!! That's great. I'm so happy for you. Do you know anything about kristy liking me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:08:48 UTC">
      <body>Thanks man i'm glad it worked out. Now this is interesting. Today she mentioned she was in the friendzone with some guy and was going to drug and rape hi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:08:59 UTC">
      <body>m. I, of course, encouraged that plan of action. And she did wanna ask you to prom... What going on?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:11:03 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea. Nicole (the ghetto chick from the debate team whom I never speak to) started messaging me about how kristy is really upset and I'm being blind and insensitive. Meanwhile I had no idea anything was going on. What the fuck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:14:06 UTC">
      <body>Lmao leave it to nicole to be hardheaded as fuck. Did she detail anything? Did you message her back?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:16:22 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I just said I didn't know anything was happening and that I thought we were just friends cuz she treats everyone the same. No "details"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:21:46 UTC">
      <body>Excellent response! Leave it at that. Women are fucking retarded. She'll love you. She'll hate you. She'll get over it! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:23:09 UTC">
      <body>Haha thanks! I just don't want to deal with this. Especially now that this year is almost over. I don't give a fuck about anything anymore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:26:14 UTC">
      <body>Swag seriously. I mean i don't see it as a problem for you. Like, yay, a girl likes you, thats awesome! How's gabby?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm just afraid of the repercussions and/or awkwardness. Also kristy is going to Emory so...
Gabby is fine. We don't really get to hang out a lot but I will def make more time for that soon, once there's less schoolwork</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:33:30 UTC">
      <body>KRISTY IS GOING TO EMORY? Ok this could be a problem not for now tho, also nice get that. But seriously four weekends until graduation get on it! Also br</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:33:40 UTC">
      <body>o i deadass think you're gonna win ten thousand dollars for that story</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:37:54 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I really don't know anything, I will just continue to ignore this problem until it goes away. I don't really feel that gabby and I have a promising romantic future, so I don't really feel like I missed any opportunity or have to rush anything. Could be wrong tho. Also you really think so? I didnt think it was that great and it might be too disturbing for the judges of the contest!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:41:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah when i read it i was hooked and now that the deadline is like here i've been thinking about it. It had me captivated but it was a little disturbing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:41:26 UTC">
      <body>lol. But yeah anyway girls are retarded. This girl sandy hit me up today i'm not sure what she wants... Maybe she's pulling a joke. Maybe she's retarded.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:41:29 UTC">
      <body> Maybe she wants the d you can never tell.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:42:49 UTC">
      <body>Haha thanks! Girls are so stupid. Whats gonna happen with Michelle</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:44:25 UTC">
      <body>We'll have lunch talk about prom. I'm fine with going as dates or as friends. I have to judge at our next encounter. Alright man i'm hitting the sack, go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 04:44:35 UTC">
      <body>odnight!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 04:45:07 UTC">
      <body>Alright sounds good. That's what its like with me and G. I'm going to bed too. Good night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:26:58 UTC">
      <body>Yo will can i borrow your graphing calculator for two days?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:34:45 UTC">
      <body>Lol uh yeah sure I don't think I need it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:36:11 UTC">
      <body>Yeee perhaps i won't need it either. Also anything go down with kristy lmao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:43:23 UTC">
      <body>No I didn't see her today. Hopefully I can at least make it through this week without confrontation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:44:43 UTC">
      <body>Lmao i mean it doesn't have to be dramatic unless she drugs and rapes you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:45:19 UTC">
      <body>Which you encouraged her to do! Yeah I don't want drama, I'll be supah kool about it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:46:46 UTC">
      <body>Lmao i didn't know it was you getting raped not my fault! Soo what english hw we got?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:48:04 UTC">
      <body>Uhhh bloody chamber annotations. That's it I think</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:49:04 UTC">
      <body>Aight. Stranger annotations due friday! Gotta get on that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:49:57 UTC">
      <body>Omg really? I thought she said have the stranger on Friday, like just have the book with you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:54:46 UTC">
      <body>Hmm idk i'm not taking my chances. She is upset with me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="136164" time="2012-05-30 23:55:54 UTC">
      <body>Word. I'm finally kinda out of the line of fire. I probably won't annotate tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="136210" time="2012-05-30 23:57:11 UTC">
      <body>Lmao apparently you are constantly giving her the fu LOL</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="136164" time="2012-05-31 00:00:39 UTC">
      <body>Ugghhhh that didn't happen! Lmfao she is legit cray</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="136164" time="2012-05-31 19:55:10 UTC">
      <body>LOL YOU ARE SO FUNNY IN THIS YEARBOOK</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="136210" time="2012-05-31 20:01:19 UTC">
      <body>Lmao thanks man, what did i do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="136164" time="2012-05-31 20:01:48 UTC">
      <body>Your picture. Also most likely to rule the world. Also we are not in the debate team photo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="136210" time="2012-05-31 21:47:43 UTC">
      <body>I KNOW WHAT THE HELL LAST YEAR DEBATE HAD A PAGE, NOW WHAT IS THIS </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
