<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110908.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 14:15:48 UTC">
      <body>How are you, disappeared? I love the robin pecknold. Did you get the article I sent you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:33:47 UTC">
      <body>Disappeared. Pretty much. I like how that song feels so rambly and off the cuff. Makes it sound very genuine to me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:35:40 UTC">
      <body>All in all I'm doing alright. On a new medication that doesn't seem to be doing anything. So I'm just waiting. And then consulting with my docs about surgical</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 14:37:49 UTC">
      <body>And in Kansas for the indeterminable future?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:38:23 UTC">
      <body>options. Because I can't let my life derail like this every fall. Its nice to be with family, though I wish I had the concentration to start doing something </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:39:55 UTC">
      <body>productive. I started a book, piano, guitar, knitting, drawing. Just really hard to focus with an itchy brain.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:42:34 UTC">
      <body>Not sure how long I'll be in ks. Gonna start looking for some work here soon. Can't really go anywhere until I get some money saved up. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 14:43:52 UTC">
      <body>Are there any permanent fixes? Is that what youre seeing the surgeon for?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:44:26 UTC">
      <body>I am going to chicago this weekend to drop chuck off. that'll be good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:47:21 UTC">
      <body>There are some theoretical fixes. One involves removing a portion of the intestine (chuck had this done still waiting to see if it was successful)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:48:07 UTC">
      <body>The others involve finding ways to drain bile directly out of the body- usually through some sort of permanent plastic port.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:49:44 UTC">
      <body>But the success rate percentages are all over the place. Especially because chuck and I seem to be the only young adults who have this condition.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:51:32 UTC">
      <body>Absolutely everyone else is pediatric. And they all usually reach the point where they have to have a transplant by the time they're 15.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:52:12 UTC">
      <body>Gotta love being the anomaly. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 14:53:15 UTC">
      <body>Rough. Maybe you'll be the anomalous case thT leads to a new discovery. Little recompense though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:55:07 UTC">
      <body>No one seems interested in making discoveries for rare liver diseases. It's all about the flashier afflictions these days.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 14:55:39 UTC">
      <body>Fucking AIDS</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 14:59:43 UTC">
      <body>Right. Anyway. Read the article pretty interesting stuff. And I obviously agree with a lot of it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 15:00:36 UTC">
      <body>Where'd you find the new robin pecknold?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 15:03:08 UTC">
      <body>Just not sure what to do about it, you know? Get comfortable not knowing. Which I like that idea. But then where fo you fit in? Hm. Just rambling sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 15:03:23 UTC">
      <body>Pitchfork of course</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 15:24:08 UTC">
      <body>Not knowing ideas? That's sad. Maybe inevitable but I'm not comfortable with that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 15:28:08 UTC">
      <body>No no. I mean giving up the drive for knowing information in exchange for thinking ideas. Getting comfortable not knowing the answer often.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 15:39:25 UTC">
      <body>I prefer understanding I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 15:46:44 UTC">
      <body>When do you leave for foul fetid fuming foggy filthy philadelphia?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 15:52:11 UTC">
      <body>Wow. Don't have a date yet!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 15:53:59 UTC">
      <body>Sorry. I think that's a lyric from 1776.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 16:03:28 UTC">
      <body>Anyway. Thanks for asking about me. Its good to hear from people. I don't want to disappear entirely.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131839" time="2011-09-08 16:04:22 UTC">
      <body>Sure sure. And of course! I feel for you. Keep me updated.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="135094" time="2011-09-08 16:15:26 UTC">
      <body>Likewise. I'll especially want to  know how the adventure in the east unfolds.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
