<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150111.0014" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-11 00:46:56 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>They must be the cutests when they sleep. I actually had a budget review meeting today and had to do some work on it. Just finished now. Yourself? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-11 00:53:20 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I love babies, but if I had to watch them as much as you do, I may get annoyed. Lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-11 00:53:55 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>They are! And we're pretty happy when they sleep since we would get a little break. Oh man, Working on a Saturday. What a trooper you are! I just got home, tired. Might have to babysit again tomorrow for a bit. So that's pretty much my weekend hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-11 01:02:23 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I have such little energy right now. And i'm not even there every day hahah! I have to give it to my sisters and to all parents in general. I love babies too but it's exhausting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-11 01:07:45 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Of of course. Gotta give it to all parents. Lots of work. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-11 01:09:25 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body> Steve can I ask you something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-11 01:09:50 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>As always. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-11 01:12:17 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>So I met this guy at my friend's birthday party and we talked here and there. It was mostly joking around, you know, party conversation. He's since contacted me and we've been talking for a few days. I know he's interested but you know how I am right now. I'm just not sure about this stuff and I'm not completely sure what I should do...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-11 01:13:23 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I don't want to lead some one on. But I don't want to be rude or mean. Like he's seems like a nice person, and it's not personal. I'm just awkward about this stuff. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-11 01:13:38 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*he</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-11 01:14:07 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I think he would be a good friend but I'm not completely sure what to to next.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-11 01:14:47 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I don't want to just stop talking to the guy. That would be abrupt. He is nice to talk to. But I don't want it to be miscronstruedz</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-11 01:14:55 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*misconstrued.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-11 01:15:43 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>I would just keep talking with him and keep it low key. But if he ever asks to move forward or kinda just hang out alone, then just let him know then. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-11 01:15:53 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>He wants to hang out but wouldn't that be like a date?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-11 01:16:14 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Oh, well that's</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-11 01:16:26 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>What I was thinking. You definitely can, but I would clarify. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-11 01:23:12 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>He wanted to hang out today but I was babysitting. Then he asked me earlier if I wanted to grab food after I was done but I'm just so tired. And honestly, I want to afraid it coming across as a date.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-01-11 01:23:34 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>So I want to ask, do you think it's beat if I nip it in the bud?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-01-11 01:24:26 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>Like how would you want this to be handled if you were the guy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-01-11 01:25:45 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*avoid</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-01-11 01:25:56 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>*bettet</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-01-11 01:26:02 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>**better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-01-11 02:54:56 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>It's really dependent on the person. Some people don't want to just hang out if they don't have a shot. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-01-11 03:05:18 UTC" participant="153491">
      <body>I just dread potentially hurting people's feelings.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-01-11 03:17:58 UTC" participant="153543">
      <body>Sometimes you have too... </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

