<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150409.0011" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-04-09 00:31:16 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>So.., I got the practicum. Now do I take it and change programs at work? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-04-09 00:32:14 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Awesome!!! Would changing programs be awful?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-04-09 00:33:36 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Well I wouldn't have a 'home' I would be a tss in different schools within the philly school district but there isn't really a guarantee that my current position will be there coming the new school year because it seems as if they are fading my program. Like I really can't learn anymore where I'm at. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-04-09 00:33:42 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>But it's home haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-04-09 00:34:38 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Ohhhh well as much as it sucks I guess your best bet is to switch. Especially if it seems like they're trying to fade you out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-04-09 00:36:15 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>It's like I'm trying to talk myself into it even though I know I should do it. I figure if I make the move instead of them making it for me I will feel better about it. And it's the freaking university of penn!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-04-09 00:37:09 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Very true! Do it Laura!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-04-09 00:38:24 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body> Thanks!! Haha that's what I want. Someone to make the decision for me haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-04-09 00:40:14 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Hahaha I got you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-04-09 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>We need to find those sugar daddies </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-04-09 00:40:32 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>If only. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-04-09 00:40:59 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>We sure do lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-04-09 01:24:14 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>It's okay for me to have hung up on manny and not to talk to him for a day probably more because when I was trying to say how am I going to work and do this practicum and he responded with 'just roll with it' and then started talking about how many views a video had??? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-04-09 01:26:06 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Uhhh yes. I would have hung up. What the hell is that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-04-09 01:27:28 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Crystal I was seriously livid. Like pretend to have some respect for my life and problems. He was like 'are you really mad!?' Umm yes I'm really effing mad. I like to every little detail of his day and then something important like this gets that response? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-04-09 01:32:07 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah I'd be mad too. How could he just brush it off like that and act like he doesn't care. That's irritating. I feel like you 2 have known each other long enough to a genuine interest in what's going on in your lives, especially something like this</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-04-09 01:33:52 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-04-09 01:36:00 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body> I have no  what audio just sent to you... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-04-09 01:36:00 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>But you're right. I was left wondering does he even know what I do for a living. Like how can you just brush me off like I was completely boring you and you had no time for me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-04-09 01:38:21 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol it was just background noise from the TV and I think your dad said something if that makes you feel better </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-04-09 01:39:35 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>But yeah you have every right to be mad. He's stupid if he thinks your mad for some dumb reason. What he did was hurtful and you shouldn't let him slide. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-04-09 01:41:55 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Haha that's what I figured. He is watching the Phillies game... I was really hurt. Like complete strangers at least pretend to have some interest. And I'll be damned if he thinks I'm calling him. Like he is the one who owes me an apology </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-04-09 01:44:49 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Definitely! Well just know I'm happy for you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-04-09 02:22:03 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Aww thank you! I love you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-04-09 10:57:04 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I need to just let this go. But after I told him I was going to hang up, two days ago. He never even attempted to contact me. Not a text or call. If I know someone is mad at me. I try to make it right. I hate that he decided if I needed space or not </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-04-09 11:03:28 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Okay. I thought I was crazy! I haven't been ignoring he hasn't attempted shit! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-04-09 11:03:36 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Oh wow. That's crazy. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-04-09 11:04:41 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Ya think he would at least try. That's annoying.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-04-09 11:05:36 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Like I want him to attempt to invade my space. I probably more mad that he doesn't care that I'm mad. Real girlie shit </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-04-09 11:07:03 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah that makes me mad too and I'm not even part of this haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-04-09 11:08:14 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Haha you are by association. Like he is going to call when he needs something and expects me to want to talk to him and pretend like nothing is wrong. He will never approach the topic and if I bring it up in dramatic </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-04-09 11:11:11 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Well forget him.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-04-09 11:12:30 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I was honestly thinking that. All yesterday I kept saying to myself that I'm too pretty and smart for this. Haha. I mean it could look like something simple but this situation says much more than it seems </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-04-09 11:13:32 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Like it was a real life changing situation i was trying to make and that's what I got? No support nothing!?! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-04-09 11:18:49 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>I agree. He should have had some sort of reaction. Geeze. This is a major thing for you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-04-09 11:20:13 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I mean I'm literally stressing the eff out. It's no joke I have to make sure they give me a schedule that gives me insurance etc. and I would have liked just so acknowledgement that it was stressful and would be okay. Or just the fact that he could have listened </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-04-09 11:24:06 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah I agree. So we're either both crazy or both right. I'd go with the latter.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-04-09 11:26:56 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Oh we are both right. He could have ignored me. It's the principle of that fact that his response mid my sentence was 'oh wow look how many views this video got'.. You can't be serious </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-04-09 11:30:44 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Yeah that's just irksome. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-04-09 11:31:12 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I'm trying to let this shit just slide for my sanity. Not let it go but slide haha  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-04-09 11:32:42 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Haha never forget!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-04-09 11:55:56 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Ha! Never. Even if I tried. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2015-04-09 19:05:04 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>He called me twice while I was at work, call back? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-04-09 19:07:04 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Eh call back just to let him know you're alive. But not to chit chat if that's what he has in mind.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2015-04-09 19:07:30 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Yeh I'm sure I will be short with him. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2015-04-09 21:23:44 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Tell your dad I said happy birthday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2015-04-09 21:24:16 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body> Aww! I sure will. Thank you! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2015-04-09 21:33:05 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>What?! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2015-04-09 21:34:32 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Oh snappp lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2015-04-09 21:34:56 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>We must do it all!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2015-04-09 21:35:10 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Of course!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2015-04-09 21:35:24 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>So much is happening in philly </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2015-04-09 21:36:18 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>I love it! Lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2015-04-09 22:01:11 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Yes I'm excited </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2015-04-09 23:03:06 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>He said he was just being sarcastic but he knew something was wrong because he said he could hear it in my voice.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2015-04-09 23:03:35 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Pffffft</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2015-04-09 23:05:16 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Right like eff you dude. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2015-04-09 23:48:19 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>I'm pretty sure manny's friend is hitting on me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2015-04-09 23:49:01 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Uhhhhh awkward.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2015-04-09 23:49:20 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Haha so I was on Bluetooth and manny is in the car with his friend. Manny gets out of the car and I know this friend so he started asking me how life is and what I do for fun etc </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2015-04-09 23:51:29 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Hmm that's fine I think lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2015-04-09 23:53:36 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>Hey he shouldn't have left... I was just bullshiting. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2015-04-09 23:55:29 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>He was on the phone when I was talking to manny when I was telling him I was annoyed with him and he said 'wow he is so insensitive' umm thank you!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2015-04-09 23:55:44 UTC" participant="153424">
      <body>And makes me feel less crazy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2015-04-09 23:56:43 UTC" participant="153417">
      <body>Lol that's great</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

