<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120930.0010" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 19:25:39 UTC">
      <body>How r u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 19:41:13 UTC">
      <body>Good! I stay with Elaine and her lovely cats for 2 nights, they energized me! Now I feel much better! Elaine has a lot interesting collection and super good paintings! You'd love them! Let's visit her together some other day!! The conference is actually about social design, nothing about media/visual arts but interesting though. Azeem socialized a lot and seems got internship opportunity.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 19:44:49 UTC">
      <body>Sounds interesting.  I am glad you went and that you are feeling better.  And I would love to visit Elaine. Good for Azeem! Thats the goal, i guess.  My parents are gone and I am trying to do homework.    Would you like to chat tonight about our studio class? I have questions. Ideas. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 19:51:16 UTC">
      <body>I'd love to!  i'm worrying about assignments. But our train departs at 8:32pm so I won't get home until 9:30pm, is that too late? &gt;_&lt;</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 19:54:11 UTC">
      <body>No not at all! Thats great   If youd like to come over you are more than welcome but maybe we Skype or chat on the phone?  Also, Amtrak is very flexible. Sometimes they can put you on an earlier train.  But you will have to pay the difference if it is more.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 19:59:59 UTC">
      <body>Ok, I'll text you after conference closing, I think it's about 5 or 5.30, and i'll find somewhere accessible to internet so that we can skype, ok?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 20:02:07 UTC">
      <body>Ok can u also send me the audio file?   I just feel so unclear about where to go from here...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 20:04:50 UTC">
      <body>sure, but before that I need to get it out of my phone and trim it... :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 20:05:31 UTC">
      <body>Ok yeah duh .., I'm silly!   Sky, I'm going to go outside and paint.  I'll talk to u after 530</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 20:09:47 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I should have done it earlier &gt;_&lt; Talk to you later! Have a nice painting experience!! ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 21:55:30 UTC">
      <body>I'm done!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 21:56:06 UTC">
      <body>We can wait until you get home if you want... I don't want to tire u out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 21:56:57 UTC">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 21:57:25 UTC">
      <body>Whatever is better for you... But what exactly is due for next week</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 21:58:56 UTC">
      <body>may I have you apt number? I only know 20 Alton Pl &gt;&lt;</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 21:59:13 UTC">
      <body>Apt 5.  Do you want to come over?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 21:59:16 UTC">
      <body>Yay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130622" time="2012-09-30 22:01:05 UTC">
      <body>If there is an easier place for you to meet I can do that too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135381" time="2012-09-30 22:02:00 UTC">
      <body>I'm thinking :p</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135381" time="2012-10-01 04:05:30 UTC">
      <body>Sofie I'm saved! I got my iPhone revived! Actually it's never dead... I'm now downloading the records, you can skype me or facetime me anytime</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
