<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150223.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-02-23 02:46:24 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Ivanco this is so sweet! Thank you for writing me back! I def battle with being too rigid in the classroom...but I’m getting better. But I think I’m too rigid with the projects I assign... maybe I can try to “shift shit” up on this front... break from these rote beginner assignments. It is so hard because we are stuck in the computer... everyone wants to learn software. they don’t care about learning how to think. Ok just rambling. ANYWAY! Thank you for your response. I think of you often and hope all is well. I will be in Philly next Sunday and Monday, but it’s a really tight trip - I’m coming because Ingrid is having a baby (not this weekend, but in a few months)! Super exciting. YAY! Ok sending you so much love. love love love. from both me and nate!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-02-23 02:56:40 UTC" participant="152241">
      <body>You are soooo sweeet!!! I think of you often to Sophia Lauren!!! stand your ground... be transparent... and always give them your beautiful smile!!!! in their face!... try not to let the shitty attitude of a kid or two make you bitter... you are young, generous, caring and full of energy... tell the stinkers... they got to do it... they will... Ingrid=baby??? wow??? who is the father??? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-02-23 03:00:34 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-02-23 03:00:45 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Crazy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-02-23 03:01:05 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Wear your raincoat mister!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-02-23 03:04:41 UTC" participant="152241">
      <body>wonderful!!!! happy for her!!!!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

