<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130329.0046" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 03:26:38 UTC">
      <body>It's such a slow night. I'm bed ridden. Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 03:27:03 UTC">
      <body>that doesn't sound fun... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 03:28:31 UTC">
      <body>Well, it's been a good week. Something bad was bound to happen. Sickness is tolerable. What's new with you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 03:34:53 UTC">
      <body>i hope you feel better! :) i'm going out of town this weekend but i have to leave in like 2 hours so i'm frantically packing and getting ready... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 03:36:55 UTC">
      <body>Ill prepared is the way to go. Trips are always better when nothing's ready. I always leave all the essentials with my luck. Where are you headed off to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 04:02:21 UTC">
      <body>fraternity formal in charleston (which is, conveniently, my hometown). </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 04:05:18 UTC">
      <body>That's quite convenient. My plans are just strolling around the city with friends, granted I get some rest. What're you going to do after college? Stay n Atlanta? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 04:21:29 UTC">
      <body>what part of town do you live in? i'm really not sure about my post-college plans. i've got time to decide, though. luckily. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 04:29:35 UTC">
      <body>I'm in Columbus most of the week exceot Monday through Sunday, which I'm at a hotel for music work. In june, I'll be a full-time atlant...ian. is that hw you say it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 04:29:46 UTC">
      <body>ATLiens like the rappers say? I dont know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 04:30:32 UTC">
      <body>atlantian, i believe. definitely haven't lived here long enough to be an authority. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 04:31:44 UTC">
      <body>We'll go with that. Haha. When should we hang out? If you'd still like to, naturally. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136112" time="2013-03-29 04:52:05 UTC">
      <body>well, i'll be back on sunday night, so i guess sometime after that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 16:27:28 UTC">
      <body>Have fun on your trip back home :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 17:51:57 UTC">
      <body>I'd love to be there with you, truly. It looks wonderful! Hey, this is a weird question, but what station is npr in Atlanta?  If you know. I can't seem o find it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136191" time="2013-03-29 17:52:48 UTC">
      <body>Also, that photo would have been infinitely better if you were in it, with a background of the city. Just saying. ;)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
