<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120813.0006" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 03:33:37 UTC">
      <body>Hey how've you been!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 03:36:02 UTC">
      <body>Im good! I'm actually at bard now because it starts mad early for freshman. What're you up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 03:40:06 UTC">
      <body>Wow really? How is it?? I'm mad hype for college but still a little nervous. I haven't been up to much this summer, I've just been taking driving lessons and my road test is tomorrow ahhhh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 03:47:06 UTC">
      <body>Oh shit good luck! I need to learn to drive. That'll be useful when you're at Emory. Bard has been super chill but so far the kids are either really awkward or trying too hard to overcompensate, but I think that's just like any first few days at college freshman year ahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 03:53:29 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! Haha yeah that's probably it, I'm kinda worried about that too. There's a weird balance you have to get between being friendly and open and coming on too strong. I think things will shape up in that regard. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 04:05:09 UTC">
      <body>Yeah word I agree. My classes start tomorrow and i think that'll probably make things more relaxed </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 04:11:39 UTC">
      <body>Awesome what's your schedule like</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 04:15:49 UTC">
      <body>Everyone is taking a "language and thinking" course the first three weeks and then we choose real classes hahah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 04:30:19 UTC">
      <body>Cool! That subject is actually something that fascinates me. But it will be good to choose real classes too haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 04:45:10 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure. When does school start for you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 04:49:13 UTC">
      <body>Move in is on the 25th, classes start on the 29th</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 04:50:31 UTC">
      <body>Awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 04:51:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it's a little too soon though haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 04:53:37 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha believe me I know, it's so weird I'm at school already. I forgot how to make friends hahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 05:04:18 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it will be hard to kinda restart your life but it will be fun once you're used to it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136217" time="2012-08-13 05:09:29 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I'll let you know how it goes! I'm going to sleep because I have to wake up at 7 tomorrow. Sweet dreams!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136164" time="2012-08-13 05:16:21 UTC">
      <body>Good night!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
