<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120703.0013" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:21:03 UTC">
      <body>Me neither he's soooo weirddd</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:22:24 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I could go away with Jeff for a weekend </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:22:24 UTC">
      <body>And like the Jordan that hangs out with him is also so weird</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:23:17 UTC">
      <body>Yeah. It's hard to try to predict which Jordan will be prominent in any given situation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:24:32 UTC">
      <body>That's so true. But Jeff Jordan is like the Jordan that we used to dislike but more prominent </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:26:40 UTC">
      <body>I feel like we'd have to intervene in that situation. Or you me and Julia camp out in The next town</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:27:35 UTC">
      <body>Lmfao omg I didn't know you used to not like Jordan</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:28:48 UTC">
      <body>I've known him since I was a freshman. I didnt totally hate him or really know him that well but what i did know I did not like. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:28:48 UTC">
      <body>He always invited me to weird events on Facebook and his musical personality... Idk I just disliked him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:30:56 UTC">
      <body>Yeah! I was like stop. Rude. And while you're at it cut your hair. Cus it's bad. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:30:58 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know, that's exactly how it was with me. He was kinda annoying and condescending about artsy shit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:32:49 UTC">
      <body>Yeahhhh omg his hair. I went through my long hair phase in middle school so I was just like "ugh grow up"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:33:04 UTC">
      <body>It looked SO bad. Exactly. And it was also like he thought he was so cool and I was like no you're a loser. So there were some communication issues</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:39:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, and I think fundamentally the issues I still have with him now are rooted in my old animosity towards him. We have a lot in common but he has different values than me and it annoys me sometimes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="136203" time="2012-07-03 04:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I see that. But you guys are able to appreciate that and you like each other a lot despite it. When you guys are working really well together it's a beautiful thing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="136164" time="2012-07-03 04:42:39 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know. I love it. The problem is that it's hard to know when it will be good and when we will be at each others throats</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="136203" time="2012-07-04 01:14:40 UTC">
      <body>Jw when do you leave for Atlanta?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="136164" time="2012-07-04 01:18:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm not exactly sure. Move in day is August 25th but idk how soon before then I will actually be leaving NYC</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
