<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140903.0005" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-03 19:28:24 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I woke up today w seven new bites down my side just FYI- not sure how long it takes for them to die but I did put all my stuff on high heat and did everything I had to in my room. All my stuff is in trash bags </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-03 19:28:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And has been since the exterminator came </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-03 21:02:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ok Cindy's going to come Friday at ten. She said I shouldn't be getting bitten </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-03 21:52:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Friday is the earliest she can get there??  Beth thought she might be able to stop by today...... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-03 21:54:08 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>OK.  Gotcha.  From what I understand sooner is better then later.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-03 21:54:13 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Well I wouldn't have been there bc I work all day and I wanted to be there </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-03 21:54:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I mean she already sprayed n powdered twice not sure what diff is if she comes today or Friday ? Dunno</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-03 21:56:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Actually not sure what point is at all which is why I wanted to be there </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-03 21:57:48 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Hmm ok yeah . I mean some stuff I couldn't bag bc I have to Wear it  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-03 21:58:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Or sleep on/under it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-03 21:58:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I wanted to ask about carpet maybe and other roomies doing their rooms </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-03 21:59:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Bc I'm still confused how...she didn't see bugs or traces of bugs in my room either . Just bc she doesn't see them in theirs, doesn't mean they're not there ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-03 22:00:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm willing to even trash bag my furniture?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-03 22:01:20 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Eh ya I mean she can go in now if she wants but i won't be home all night </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-03 22:53:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm not sure but obviously something is in there.  I'm assuming its bed bugs.  She didn't see anything last time? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-09-03 22:53:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Have you talked to David? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-09-03 23:03:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It's def bedbugs. The bites I'm getting this time are perfectly in a row </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-09-03 23:03:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>First a row up my legs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-09-03 23:03:49 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Now a row up my sides </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-09-03 23:05:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼Hate to send a bit of side pube buuuut hahaha here ya go!! A bit of nudity doesn't  hurt anyone especially since this is the least sexy thing ever </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-09-03 23:05:11 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But I have these on Both sides </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-09-03 23:05:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>On both legs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-09-03 23:05:21 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And across my lower back </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-09-03 23:05:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It's def bedbugs no doubt </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-09-03 23:05:52 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Before I had random all over bites but now every night it's like a New row lol </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-09-03 23:10:56 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Shit.  I'm sorry.  I think part of the problem is we didn't jump on the problem early enough. Then when she came the first time she should have had you bag &amp; wash everything.  Since you have done all of that this time; I'm hoping one more treatment should kill off the remainder.   </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-09-03 23:15:12 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Did Cindy see any evidence of bed bugs last time she was there? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-09-03 23:18:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body> Nope she hasn't seen any at any point </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-09-03 23:18:58 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Which is why I don't see why her not seeing any in the roommates' rooms means anything </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-09-03 23:40:39 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Yeah. I'm just not sure but I know when David &amp; Phillip had them in their rooms they def noticed them.  I know some people aren't bothered by the bites but I'm guessing its a small minority of the population.  Have you been to bedbugs.org? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-09-03 23:48:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Please call/ text David when you get a chance.  I sent him a text earlier.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-09-04 00:24:59 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Haha ￼That is Exactly what my back looks like. Both lines up and down and also a row horizontally across above my butt </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-09-04 00:25:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K and I guess I'll sleep at my dads for awhile again </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-09-04 00:25:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>At least for my current bites to heal </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2014-09-04 01:39:12 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Ok.  David just sent me this in response to my question - - - No, but I was feeling bruise and itchy last night on my back and stomach. I'll check it out tonight and tomorrow if these bastard are still alive </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2014-09-04 01:39:31 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah I mean we def have them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2014-09-04 01:39:48 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>All my bites on side are from these past two days </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2014-09-04 01:40:21 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>￼Arm too :( :( </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2014-09-04 01:41:06 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It's pretty awful and I can't really go home bc my dad lives in burbs and I dog walk w a bike that I can't take on train and I open coffeeshop at 6am which is too early to get to from suburbs </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2014-09-04 01:41:18 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I need to sleep there tonight but I know I'll get a bunch of bites </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2014-09-04 01:41:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm going to figure out plan to stay at my dads for a bit and I'll let you know when I'm out of the house </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2014-09-04 01:42:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But basically if it doesn't get fixed I'll have to move out :( bc i really need a place in the city to stay for my jobs to work out </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2014-09-04 01:42:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And I broke up w my bf a few days ago and can't sleep there haha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2014-09-04 01:43:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I don't really have friends in the city to stay w bc all my best friends live in other cities so Eventually I'll have to find a place in city that I can sleep in while the problem gets fixed :( aka I'll have to move</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2014-09-04 01:43:50 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I can't live at my dads and make my jobs work out </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2014-09-04 01:44:07 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(Or I would just do that while this got sorted out)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2014-09-04 01:50:56 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>OK. I understand. Lets try to get Beth in there ASAP &amp; we will go from there.   Either way I HAVE to get this taken care of.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2014-09-04 01:50:56 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Is there anyway you could meet her tomorrow? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2014-09-04 01:52:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2014-09-04 01:52:12 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I could but she can't do tomorrow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2014-09-04 01:52:29 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm meeting her Friday ten am and then I'll call you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2014-09-04 02:29:02 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Cool. I'm thinking that this should be it. Lets keep our fingers crossed!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2014-09-04 03:21:50 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I asked David to call / text you.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2014-09-04 17:48:48 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Do you have David's number or see him often? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2014-09-04 17:56:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>No </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2014-09-04 17:56:57 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I looked at that website though and it looks like they could be hiding in my furniture etc </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2014-09-04 17:57:16 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And my furniture is prob ruined since id have to pack it up in bags for a year </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2014-09-04 17:57:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also that the carpet needs to be heat treated/shampoo </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2014-09-04 17:58:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>No where on that website does it say the perimeters of the room just need dusting and the fabric just needs to be packed up </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" time="2014-09-04 17:58:20 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>It says that you have to get Everything and that they'll hide and then come back out </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" time="2014-09-04 17:58:59 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also clearly I'm allergic to the bite etc </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2014-09-04 17:59:06 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Bc mine do look like large welts </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2014-09-04 17:59:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So maybe someone else will move in and be fine bc they won't Notice it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" time="2014-09-04 17:59:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But I feel like I'm going to continually be the canary in then coal mine so to speak </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" time="2014-09-04 17:59:59 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And then they'll run into another room while I'm gone, then a week after I move all my stuff back in, they'll bite me again </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" time="2014-09-04 18:00:41 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And that will have ad infinitum </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" time="2014-09-04 18:01:15 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>*happen </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" time="2014-09-04 18:01:36 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm not sure. But if you have questions you can call Beth.  Between Beth &amp; the website, I'd trust Beth.  
She has been with bedbugs successfully for years.  You might be more allergic then most but either way I Have to get rid of these.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" time="2014-09-04 18:02:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Not sure why talking to David would help </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" time="2014-09-04 18:02:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also not sure how meeting w exterminator for 3rd time would help </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" time="2014-09-04 18:03:44 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>It all started in David's room.  He was the one who first reported the issue back in April or May. Before you moved in We thought they were gone.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" time="2014-09-04 18:08:06 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>This problem hasn't been attacked correctly until the last week.  It wasn't being addressed at all for the first 3 or 4 weeks you lived there.  Then when Cindy came out initially she probably Should have had you bag &amp; wash everything.  In retrospect I have no idea why she didn't esp considering the fact that we just had them.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" time="2014-09-04 18:09:34 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I truly believe if it was Beth treating this instead of Cindy we wouldn't even be having the conversation because the bed bugs would be have been long gone.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" time="2014-09-04 18:36:12 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>:/ yeah that makes sense</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" time="2014-09-04 18:36:31 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>She told me we didn't even have them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" time="2014-09-04 18:36:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So all my roommates acted like I was paranoid </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" time="2014-09-04 18:37:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm not paranoid lol My whole body is covered in bites </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" time="2014-09-04 18:37:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I Really Really wish Beth was around!!  I'll call her in a little bit.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" time="2014-09-04 18:37:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Of course not.  I'm kind of shocked that anyone would think you are paranoid.  Everyone knew about the bed bugs.  I sent out many many text messages to everyone about this over the past few months.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" time="2014-09-04 18:41:59 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Well since they aren't getting bitten, they are in denial </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" time="2014-09-04 18:42:05 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I am fairly certain we can get rid of these lil fuckers with in a week. But if they aren't gone in a week - if you want to move, I totally understand.  Pls just give me a few more days to get rid of them.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" time="2014-09-04 18:42:08 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Clearly, bc they keep having people stay over too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" time="2014-09-04 18:42:33 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Which is awkward bc I'm like cleaning all my stuff in drier for third time and their bf gf whatever is like ooooh whatcha doin </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" time="2014-09-04 18:42:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Hahahahahahaha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" time="2014-09-04 18:43:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>'Oooh nothing I'm just really clean um..' </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" time="2014-09-04 18:43:11 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Geez.  Who is acting like that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" time="2014-09-04 18:43:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Nah not acting Mean </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" time="2014-09-04 18:43:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I just think that the house isn't convinced we have them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" time="2014-09-04 18:43:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Or thinks , as you seem to hope, that they are just in my room </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" time="2014-09-04 18:44:04 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But she didn't see any signs of them in my room either </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" time="2014-09-04 18:44:16 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'd really like to keep you as a roommate.  I have to get rid of the problem regardless of whether you stay or not.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" time="2014-09-04 18:45:27 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So I see no reason why they wouldn't very likely be all over the place </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" time="2014-09-04 18:45:54 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm willing to give it another week :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" time="2014-09-04 18:46:00 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I just don't know but I sent them all multiple texts about it like this -- Have you noticed any bed bugs or any bug bites? Ingrid thinks she may have them.  I'm waiting on a call back from the exterminator.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" time="2014-09-04 18:46:07 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I just highly doubt it'll  be solved </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" time="2014-09-04 18:46:18 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Right they know I Think I Might have them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" time="2014-09-04 18:46:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And they know th exterminator keeps coming and saying she doesn't see anything hahaha </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" time="2014-09-04 18:46:44 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>So they think I'm getting them some where else but I am NoT </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" time="2014-09-04 18:46:57 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>OK. Thank you.  I really appreciate it.  This is a solvable problem.  People get bed bugs &amp; get rid of them all the time. N</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" time="2014-09-04 18:47:01 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I have only been sleeping there and I go to bed and then wake up w many new bites every night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" time="2014-09-04 18:47:17 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah it's solvable but not if I'm only doing my room </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" time="2014-09-04 18:47:56 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I'm not trying to be a bitch I just truly don't understand how me once again drying everything will help. My stuff is Already in bags </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" time="2014-09-04 18:48:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The know things I don't have in bags are the clothes I dryed but need to wear for the week </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" time="2014-09-04 18:48:22 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But the bugs could be in my Furniture, my carpet </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" time="2014-09-04 18:48:32 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I'm not sure but I'll check with Beth.  The do tend to migrate from room to room &amp; house to house but not always.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" time="2014-09-04 18:48:35 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The Other roommates furniture and clothes </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" time="2014-09-04 18:48:41 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>The downstairs carpet and furniture </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" time="2014-09-04 18:48:52 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>(Bc I swear I slept there once and was bitten a ton there too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" time="2014-09-04 18:49:30 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>*only things </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" time="2014-09-04 18:49:54 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K I'll meet with her again tomorrow and redry the stuff I have out for me to wear </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" time="2014-09-04 18:50:03 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also my bed in in Center of room now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" time="2014-09-04 18:50:10 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And I lifted bed off floor w metal frame </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" time="2014-09-04 18:50:28 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I don't know that you do need to dry everything again.  Did Cindy tell you to do that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" time="2014-09-04 18:50:40 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And have been sleeping on the vinyl with only one blanket that I dry every night and Don't let touch floor </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" time="2014-09-04 18:50:40 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I think having the mattress off the floor helps.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" time="2014-09-04 18:50:53 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yes she said that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" time="2014-09-04 18:51:07 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>But according to everything I've read, what I'm doing isn't remotely enough </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" time="2014-09-04 18:51:14 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>And powdering won't be enough either </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" time="2014-09-04 18:51:32 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>You have to deal with All furniture and all carpets and everything At Once </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" time="2014-09-04 18:51:37 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>After I call Beth I'm going to have her call you.  What is the best time for you to talk today? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" time="2014-09-04 18:51:49 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>I can talk any time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" time="2014-09-04 18:52:26 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>The first time we had them was years ago when this girl went to AC to take the NJ bar exam &amp; brought them back.  We treated her room &amp; that was it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" time="2014-09-04 18:52:45 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Hmm </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" time="2014-09-04 18:52:48 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>We didn't have to treat the rest of the house because they didn't spread there. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" time="2014-09-04 18:52:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Ok yeah I dunno </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" time="2014-09-04 18:53:01 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Maybe you got lucky and killed them all in one go </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" time="2014-09-04 18:53:38 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Yeah I dunno I see what you're saying and Maybe me doing my room again Will kill them all but you can see why it's frustrating and feels futile to me </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" time="2014-09-04 18:53:53 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>From what Beth told me there are patterns but no set rules to bed bugs.  Sometimes they spread like wildfire but sometimes they don't. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" time="2014-09-04 18:54:23 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Bc it might or it might not and that's annoying when I'm the only one doing the effort </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" time="2014-09-04 18:54:51 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Like it seems more rational to bE Safe and have More people do it so that I know I'm not doing the effort Again for nothing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" time="2014-09-04 18:54:56 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>I totally understand. I mean as much as someone who isn't getting bitten every night can understand.  And I sincerely appreciate your patience up to this point. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" time="2014-09-04 18:55:19 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Also I see no reason why I'd do my stuff again when I have a carpet that they could have laid eggs in </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" time="2014-09-04 18:55:26 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Or just be living in </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" time="2014-09-04 18:55:34 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Maybe there are tons of them under my carpet who knows </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" time="2014-09-04 18:56:20 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>This idea that- oh well Ingrid will do all her clothes and sheets again and live out of trash bags for another two weeks Just To See </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" time="2014-09-04 18:57:00 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K I will meet w her tomorrow and put all my stuff in bags and prob stay at my dads somehow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" time="2014-09-04 18:57:04 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>All these questions are things that Beth will know the answer to.  Please have a list of questions when she calls &amp; she can explain the answers in detail.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" time="2014-09-04 18:57:25 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>K </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" time="2014-09-04 18:59:12 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Either was if they aren't gone in a week, I'll cancel your lease &amp; give you back your money so you can find a place that is free of bed bugs.  I can't ask you for anything else.  You have been more then patient through this ordeal.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" time="2014-09-04 19:08:37 UTC" participant="152735">
      <body>Thank you :) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" time="2014-09-04 19:09:52 UTC" participant="152759">
      <body>Thank you &amp; I am so sorry that you are dealing with it. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

