<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130603.0040" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 18:33:50 UTC">
      <body>Leesie. I'm sorry I never responded to these texts! Yes now I have everything I need to survive in my apartment which means I am bored as fuck. How are you? How is the beach?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:05:04 UTC">
      <body>Good! Parents finally peaceful. It's storming, so i'm reading to the lighthouse on the porch and waiting for lightning. Sister-brat is here. Content-elise.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 19:05:49 UTC">
      <body>I am sitting in my pink chair at corals table. This is my only furniture. It looks sad :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 19:06:11 UTC">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:07:04 UTC">
      <body>So you successfully beat off your mother's antiques?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 19:08:10 UTC">
      <body>Yep. I have one of my grandmas dressers but that's it. Lizzy is bringing a couch and a table. But she isn't moving in for two weeks &gt;.&lt;</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:12:46 UTC">
      <body>￼Two weeks! I should just come stay until then...
Beyond the houses of life's lottery winners, lies the ocean.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 19:14:48 UTC">
      <body>True that. Both of those things. I do start work next week so I only have a week to be this bored, luckily. Or maybe next week I will long for this week back. I've just never been one for exploring cities alone...  Also I hope I win life's lottery and have a beach house. Where are you guys?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:21:40 UTC">
      <body>Kiawah island, sc. A lovely, secluded bubble for the wealthy. The whole island's gated. Nevertheless, i love being here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:24:52 UTC">
      <body>Though things are improving--parents say they never used to see black families here. I've seen a few. It's rather sedate, golf, tennis, bike trails. Have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:24:54 UTC">
      <body> to go into charleston or neighboring public islands for any kind of night life or gathered young people. I've already read two books. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:27:16 UTC">
      <body>Aside--my potter says we can pit fire things this summer. That is, dig a hole, insert pots, and set aflame for twelve or so hours. Very excited... Are pe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135269" time="2013-06-03 19:27:16 UTC">
      <body>ople in hca? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135080" time="2013-06-03 19:37:43 UTC">
      <body>That sounds fun if overly privileged :P how is the weather? Any better for the beach than here? The fire pit thing sounds AWESOME! :D Anna is in hca but she works during the week and is studying for one last final she is taking Thursday when she isn't at work. I visited her yesterday and ill probably go tomorrow. Once she is done on Friday she will visit me :P but I have no Internet still so she can't study here. I love how my iPhone auto-capitalizes Internet haha :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-06-04 19:35:57 UTC">
      <body>Leeeeeeessssiiiieeeeeee</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
