<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130606.0025" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 17:57:58 UTC">
      <body>Hi! Two things. 1. How are you? How are classes? I miss you!

2. I bought all this raw chicken and I just wanted to cook a piece of it but its frozen and stuck together but can I thaw it just enough to take off a piece and refreeze the rest? Or do I have to cook it all now and hope I don't fuck it up? How do you do real life? And why do I not know how to deal with raw chicken??? :(</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="135271" time="2013-06-06 18:52:48 UTC">
      <body>You can try putting it in the fridge to thaw it enough to hack off a little to cook. If you're gonna cook it, you might have cook it all. But for next time you should cut the chicken up into meal servings then freeze. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 19:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Ugh okay. I was kind of overwhelmed the night I did grocery shopping and just threw it all in the freezer. Also it was frozen when I bought it...is it still possible to break apart when you buy it frozen? If not how should I buy it?
I think I'm gonna cook it like tomorrow and the next day and then refreeze some of what I cook. #reallifefail</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 19:06:10 UTC">
      <body>Also thanks! :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="135271" time="2013-06-06 19:09:52 UTC">
      <body>It's def cheaper to buy bulk frozen but it's easier and not that much more to buy it regular. We usually buy the prepackaged ones that you get boneless or however you want and then cut it up and freeze what we don't use. As for refreezing, idk for sure but you might get freezer burn type effects. But you might as well try something if alternative it throwing it away. But You might be able to buy it frozen, just look individual servings or smaller servings, idk if the do that for frozen meat. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135271" time="2013-06-06 19:10:57 UTC">
      <body>And you're welcome! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 19:12:32 UTC">
      <body>Is "regular" just refrigerated? The internet says I can refreeze it once its cooked so ill give it a shot...haha now I know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="135271" time="2013-06-06 19:22:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's what I meant. Haha good luck! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 19:25:13 UTC">
      <body>Thanks :) how are you? How is the class (the classes) you're taking? Is abroad still happening?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135271" time="2013-06-06 22:40:14 UTC">
      <body>I'm alright. Classes are fine, boring really. A lot of basic writing stuff. Yeah, study abroad is all set! How are you? How's the job? Apartment life?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="135080" time="2013-06-06 23:29:07 UTC">
      <body>Job starts Monday. Apartment life is lonely so far (Lizzy doesn't move in for a week and a half) and clearly I don't know how to cook :P I'm glad abroad is still happening! Sorry your classes are boring. I'm sad I didn't get to see you when I was home!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 02:05:52 UTC">
      <body>I wish I could have seen you too! Haha you'll get the hang of cooking though! Eventually </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 02:08:32 UTC">
      <body>Not my good friends. Hannah Michelle comes back at the end of June and Fairleigh in August. Anna is at Haverford so I have seen her a couple times. Mostly I clean/unpack and walk around here and watch movies </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 02:12:59 UTC">
      <body>Ah. Gotcha. That's unfortunate but at least people will around eventually. And watching movies and walking around isn't a bad way to pass the time </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 02:13:31 UTC">
      <body>Nope :) and next week I start work so that's good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 02:16:04 UTC">
      <body>Right. Are you excited?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 02:16:46 UTC">
      <body>Sort of. Haha I mean yeah but also nervous. At least it will be something to do and focus on</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 02:18:01 UTC">
      <body>That's true. I think it'll be great! Something new, meet new people, new friends. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 02:18:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 02:18:49 UTC">
      <body>The next chapter in my life or something g like that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 02:19:58 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I think that's what they call it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="135080" time="2013-06-07 16:40:46 UTC">
      <body>￼Chicken!!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="135271" time="2013-06-07 22:40:13 UTC">
      <body>Nicely done! </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
