<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150103.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-01-03 00:36:56 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Are you going tomorrow and if you are, what are you dressing as?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-01-03 01:16:10 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah.  We're going but I don't know what I'm wearing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-01-03 01:16:53 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Me neither. I don't know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-01-03 01:17:57 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I mean.  As you know. I don't have costumes or costume- like clothing readily available.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-01-03 01:21:13 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. Yeah, the only thing I'll be able to do is wear a dress....and glitter. Isn't that what Kesha is infamous for?
I am going to the mall though. I have to exchange a north face vest, so maybe I can find something there.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-01-03 01:23:26 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah.  I'll just be wearing a dress. I think we mentioned doing that and wearing a masquerade mask or something glittery. So if I make it to a store for one I'll let you know and pick you up one of you want.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-01-03 01:25:45 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oh cool. That sounds good! I'll look around in the mall too, although I'm sure I won't find a cheap one like at party city.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-01-03 18:53:56 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Hey. We were at the party store. I was quicker than I thought I would be and my dad was waiting for us so I couldn't stick around. I'm sorry! I tried to call you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-01-03 18:57:52 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>ahh!! That's okay! I'm sorry i didn't answer. I was getting ready to go to the mall. Did you buy a mask or a costume?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-01-03 18:59:18 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I bought a mask. It was thirty dollars though. I wasn't sure if you wanted to spend that much anyway.  The only reason I got it was because I can hang it up in my room after since its purple.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-01-03 19:10:40 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. Okay! Yeah, I probably wouldn't have spent $30 but thanks!!
I still don't know what to wear. Haha. I have a sequin dress and I can completely gitterize my face but...it's going to rainy all day.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-01-03 19:14:27 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I know. The weather sucks. I think gonna ask uyen if I can get ready there instead of traveling there in heels and a dress.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-01-03 19:15:59 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Ohhhhh. Can you let me know what she says? And if she says yes, can I third wheel with you and Michael?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-01-03 19:16:44 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yes. Of course.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-01-03 19:17:21 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body> thank you! Btw, what's Michael wearing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-01-03 19:18:10 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>His antler mask.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-01-03 19:18:44 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oh okay! Good to see its getting a lot of use.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2015-01-03 20:36:45 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>So uyen said we can get there early. We're thinking about getting there between 7-730.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-01-03 20:37:11 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay! Sounds good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-01-03 20:37:12 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>We thought it started at seven but uyen said she's not going to be ready until eight.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-01-03 21:57:22 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. Wow. I like the middle one.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-01-03 21:59:51 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Yeahhhh. Haha. If this isn't an occasion to wear one of these, I don't know what is! 
I think I'm stuck between the middle one and the all sequin one. It's very Kesha-esque.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-01-03 22:01:11 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yeah. I like that one but it depends if you want to go sleeveless or not.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-01-03 22:01:44 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Oh I'd wear a jacket!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-01-03 22:01:55 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>I picked the middle because of the sleeves but if you think you'll be fine,  the last one is more fitting.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-01-03 22:02:08 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Haha. Ok. Then definitely the purple.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-01-03 22:04:02 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Haha. Okay. I'll do that and just throw glitter into my face. I'm coming home from the mall now. I bought some glitter eyeliner from sephora. There were 5 small tubes for $16 so I figured what the heck.
Are we walking to uyens?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-01-03 22:05:11 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Yup.  Just throw on the glitter. Haha. I'd prefer not to walk in the rain. Perhaps the subway? And Cassy and Jimmy are coming with us.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-01-03 22:07:03 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay! Sounds good to me. What time should I meet you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-01-03 22:08:31 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Michael wants to leave close to seven.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-01-03 22:08:49 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-01-03 23:35:48 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Cassy and Jimmy are going to be at my house at 7.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-01-03 23:42:07 UTC" participant="152118">
      <body>Okay. I might be there a little earlier. I'm leaving in a couple of mins and my dad is dropping me off.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-01-03 23:42:18 UTC" participant="152115">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

