<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120215.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131019" time="2012-02-15 22:04:00 UTC">
      <body>Sorry to break the silence but this is too funny not to share. Just ran into Charlott and the smile on her face was bigger than anything I've ever seen </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131065" time="2012-02-15 22:04:48 UTC">
      <body>Haha oh Lordy... Fuckin Charlott... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131019" time="2012-02-15 22:06:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah dude....people like that scare me. Anywho hope your valentines day was good. TTY in a few days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131065" time="2012-02-15 22:09:04 UTC">
      <body>Hope you have a goodie too. Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 06:46:39 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I called you. It was an emergency but it's okay now and won't happen again sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 06:58:08 UTC">
      <body>Was in the shower, you all good?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 07:06:56 UTC">
      <body>Umm I almost got mugged so no not really. But I'm fine dwai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 07:08:48 UTC">
      <body>Well going to worry about it... What happened?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 07:08:51 UTC">
      <body>Idk I took the shorter way home I never take and cut across a parking lot and some guy grabbed my arm and told me to give him my money but then these two guys turned the corner and he ran away. Sorry I had no one else to call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 07:10:44 UTC">
      <body>It's fine. I was just really shaken up like anything could have happened nd he could have had a weapon and idk. I'll let you go dwai about it don't worry about it I'm sorry I called and jut worried you sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 07:10:56 UTC">
      <body>It's fine, shit I'm really sorry. I'm glad you're safe now tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 07:13:04 UTC">
      <body>You're all good Sara, no need to apologize. Glad you're safe but that sketch I'm sorry. I'll ttyl tho. Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 07:14:11 UTC">
      <body>Yes, actually, there is. I should have known better than to call you. I'll talk to you sunday. Bye.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 22:25:24 UTC">
      <body>Did you still wanna talk tonight or leave it for later!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 22:28:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah we can talk tonight, what times good.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 22:28:24 UTC">
      <body>You choose, pick a time when you'll be free after, doesn't matter how late.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 22:53:52 UTC">
      <body>How about ten?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 22:54:06 UTC">
      <body>Will you be free after that? Like we can talk as late as you want, just don't like have somewhere to go after you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 23:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure I understand, we can talk till whenever from then.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 23:15:57 UTC">
      <body>Okay, so you want ten? Cuz whenever is fine by me. But thanks Johnny (: I hope you're not mad at new</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131065" time="2012-02-16 23:32:16 UTC">
      <body>I'm not mad at you Sara, you're all good.  But yeah ten is good! Ttyt?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="131019" time="2012-02-16 23:32:27 UTC">
      <body>Okay, see you then!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 07:59:09 UTC">
      <body>I feel like every time we talk it's like a therapy session hah, but thank you for being patient, and trying things my way(: it means a lot to me Johnny. Don't wanna lose my best fwend. But have a nice smoke, enjoy your night, and I'll prlly talk to you to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 08:00:00 UTC">
      <body>For sure Sara, I got you. Things will get better. And you too! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 08:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Also sorry for being so crazy, you're very patient, I greatly appreciate it. Just wanted to say that. Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 08:10:40 UTC">
      <body>Understood, all is well. Ciao </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 20:53:43 UTC">
      <body>Ambient waves is def the most you mix ever, but I don't have the order of the songs :/ also idk if you got my email but yeah </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 23:15:12 UTC">
      <body>I can tell you the list another time. And I got your email. It was very eloquent and I agree and understand it all Sara. For being written at 3am props. You know how I feel you, I want to be friends. Sorry was hardcore napping </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 23:16:09 UTC">
      <body>Hah no worries, I figured you were (: and I'm really happy about our talk. I mean I know I was a little crazy, but I feel like we got to the root of the problem, and thank you for being understanding. I hope your nap was good (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 23:17:16 UTC">
      <body>But oh y god Johnny idk who else to tell and not sound like a bitch but I got a perfect score on my ling midterm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 23:17:20 UTC">
      <body>Hah nice dood! That's awesome. It 'twas good, I straight slept for like four hours hahahah. And I def think we got to the bottom up, happy as well for sure</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 23:19:51 UTC">
      <body>Ah that's never happened before :D and jelly dude, I could not sleep last night. And I'm very happy. Like I am honestly extremely happy being friends, I just hope you can be as open with me as you are with other friends, I mean it'll take time but you kno</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 23:21:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho def got you, time will help that. And well that's awesome tho! Okay to brag. And take a nap?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 23:24:08 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, won't be out of class until 5 and then will be too late. Just gonna drink some coffee. And yeah it definitely will, but we will be alright (: I'm happy you're willing to be friends with me at this point. You're pretty great(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="131065" time="2012-02-17 23:30:08 UTC">
      <body>Hah why thank you Sara, and I'm glad that we have been able to work to this point. Takes two ya kno. And I'm about to get an americano hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="131019" time="2012-02-17 23:30:13 UTC">
      <body>Yes it does, so just you know, thank you. Like I'm really grateful for you. Ahh nice, jelly. You should be able to teleport objects with some app :P anyway I got class, focus time. Might hit you up after! Enjoy your americano, ciao!(: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 02:08:13 UTC">
      <body>You should play me back in words, I have a good word I wanna use!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 02:09:36 UTC">
      <body>Hah I've been out of class for a while, but no worries. And yeah play me back (: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 02:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Okay! Ciao ciao Sara! Hope class goes well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 02:10:08 UTC">
      <body>And will do! Fuck just noticed that didn't send</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 02:12:07 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah I was just tellin you to play (: have a good night tonight!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 02:12:16 UTC">
      <body>Okie! I'm eating currently so ciao ciao tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 02:18:40 UTC">
      <body>You too! And working in a good word hah, bai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:04:35 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, what's up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:05:20 UTC">
      <body>Awake?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:05:20 UTC">
      <body>Can't sleep meh. Busy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:05:24 UTC">
      <body>Nope, just crawled in bed after some greys. Why can't you sleep?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:07:28 UTC">
      <body>Debos light, zachs snoring... Took a nap today, but went climbing. Idk shud be tired. How's grey?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:07:32 UTC">
      <body>ah, yes I should be tired but had too much caffeine...even tho that was like Ten hours ago. I'm sorry tho :/ and it was good, saving other shows for tmrw night. How was your night?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:09:36 UTC">
      <body>Mmm I got you. Yeah had an americano. But it was good, and so was my day. Get sad at night meh. But had an awesome convo with my English teacher, got tazed, climbed and watched skins. Yourself?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:10:53 UTC">
      <body>Ah why sad? And tazed...? And what was the convo about? But I went to a co op party, just hung out all day basically</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:11:44 UTC">
      <body>Idk, seeing zach sleep with Miranda and also your fb/ instagram pics hah not gonna lie. And like everything! She rules dood! From Kerouac to San Diego to like awesome Mexican food hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:13:37 UTC">
      <body>Okay but you got...tazed??? And ah Johnny, why my pics? And you'll find someone! But that's tight, glad you like her</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:13:52 UTC">
      <body>Oh but like tazed by a tazer stun gun thing. Not that cool really tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:13:52 UTC">
      <body>Mhm, yeah was super cool, fifteen minute convo turned into an hour hah. And cuz u party and I no party hah. And cuz Sarah has one and we wanted to try it. We as in John and nick and I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:14:01 UTC">
      <body>Yes...why? Like wyf!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:17:22 UTC">
      <body> Why does she have one? Did it hurt? (ps you guys are such guys) and Johnny, I party because that's all there is to do here. Like otherwise I'd be sitting home alone. You party too! And like have a dozen girls with you, always</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:17:32 UTC">
      <body>You'll find someone else</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:18:08 UTC">
      <body>I meant davita, and cuz her sister was mugged so she sometimes carries it and also has pepper spray. But surprisingly not that bad. And for sure, you don't gotta justify, all good. And yet I feel so alone...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:21:09 UTC">
      <body>Ah okay, and I still can't believe youdid that. Oh Johnny :/ why? Im always here for you though, I hope you know that. No matter what happens</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:22:24 UTC">
      <body>Hah I can't either, I feel accomplished. Always wanted to try it. And idk, I guess at times I do and don't. I have a good friend base tho. Just nights are the worst ya know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:22:24 UTC">
      <body>Do people sneeze in their sleep?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:24:18 UTC">
      <body>Hah well now you know. And yeah, are you okay with them tho? And yeah, I know. Difficult to think of not having anyone to sleep next to. Sleepibgs a lonely sport </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:24:37 UTC">
      <body>Uhh never heard of that? My roommates snoring tho yay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:26:40 UTC">
      <body>This is true, sleeping is and I have a tough time going to sleep with my mind running everywhere. And okay with my friends? Yeah for sho, def a good crew. And samezies dood! You ain't alone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:28:03 UTC">
      <body>That's good, glad you have people who make you happy around you. And yeah same, I don't think I've hone to slept before 3 or 4 in over a month. Wish i had a sleeping buddy, like a giant bear. Ughhh Alison :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:30:56 UTC">
      <body>Hahah a giant bear huh? Like a live one or a teddy? And weak sauce... Ah debo is goin to bed now woot! And for sure. How about your homies?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:31:17 UTC">
      <body>Haha preferably a teddy. And well, humans who like me are very rare, so a a bear will have to do for now! And they're great, def making more friends and getting to be better friends with others, I'm rarely ever alone which is good. Only Maddie and Doriane</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:33:04 UTC">
      <body>Why're they getting to you? And maybe time to move on? And hah well Teddy's are always good and humans like you! Don't lie</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:35:06 UTC">
      <body>Hah well my body. My personality, my mind, me, few like that. And idk like they complain about every little thing and make it a big deal, which is fine but like...not really. Not when I'm trying to be positive about life and all dori does o's complain abo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:38:05 UTC">
      <body>Nah, I talked to her too, it's all good. Kendall and I are close tho too. Hah well yes, that's inevitable. They are pretty great. But nah, no one here really likes me. Like for me, no one tries to get to know you like that. Idk it's whatever. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:38:12 UTC">
      <body>What a flat bottomed boat?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:38:39 UTC">
      <body>Pontoon nvm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Well done. You and seven words.... But that's good, glad Kendall is chill, and I must say she is also pretty too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0076" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:39:28 UTC">
      <body>But those who matter will get to know you, if they don't want to, fuck em</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0077" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:41:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, she's gorgeous! I love her. And dude, they're just so bouncy and great! And that's true, time and all. How about you though? Have you been talking to anyone? Indigo?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Mhm, good to have attractive friends hah. Yeah for sho, and truthfully yeah sorta, and you guessed it, which is funny. Thinking of asking her to coffee actually. Is it okay for me to be this open?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:44:26 UTC">
      <body>Yes yes of course! And you should do that(: exchange some unknown indie music and all that. Hah I always did know(: and really Johnny, don't be afraid of being open. And fuck yeah, attractive friends are the best</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:45:06 UTC">
      <body>Flat tire? Flattened hat?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Hah that's why I'm sticking with John! And also nick too! And no idea for that word? And that's the plan! But got her number via Facebook and such, gonna text her and ask her to coffee to exchange music at a cafe. Good idea?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0082" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:47:50 UTC">
      <body>It's okay, it was beret. Dunno the tire one. And yup, do it. Wow, this doesn't hurt as much as I thought. But maybe that's cu it's really Kate</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:47:53 UTC">
      <body>Late </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:48:00 UTC">
      <body>Beret? Wtf? Yeah idk, still seems kinda weird to me... Like I don't think I'm ready to hear about your boys hah. We shall stop now. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:48:14 UTC">
      <body>Eh scratch that, it still stings a little</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:51:21 UTC">
      <body>Hah I wasnt gonna tell you anything. And it's fine tho, being open helps a lot. I gotta get used ti it. Just thought you'd move on like physically, before you did emotionally. If that makes sense. Oh and make sure to pay for her. And if she gets a snack g</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:52:16 UTC">
      <body>Hahah okay will do! And yeah I'll tell you once I'm ready for you to be open and such. And idk, that's not me to move on physically I guess? I've like never hooked up really</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:54:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah no worries. Yeah, idk I guess maybe like wishful thinking on my part? Like didn't think emotionally you'd move on so soon, and like to her. But I'm glad she's pretty and smart and interesting. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 12:54:34 UTC">
      <body>Can I tell you something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 12:56:32 UTC">
      <body>I think so, go for it! Hah I dont even know if I like her though ya know. Just going out and putting myself out there ya know? See what happens.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:00:29 UTC">
      <body>Because like, I know you. And you kind of lied about her and such, idk I just, I know you. Hah honestly, sometimes I wish I was that girl. Like who could just let loose and not care, but I'm not. And now I'm sick :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0093" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:00:48 UTC">
      <body>Hah word up! I'm not that guy tho ya know? And I don't think youre that girl either. Keep it classy hah. But really? Whys that? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0094" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:02:56 UTC">
      <body>You're sick? And I wish that too, that could be comfortable with that and not care... But yeah, wud be weird. And mmmm I see. Hmph it's late as fuck!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0095" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:04:02 UTC">
      <body>Sore throat, stuffy runny nose meh. Yeah it's hard for me, I care too much, about everyone. I'd do anything for a lot of people and expend so much energy making others happy, or trying to, and few return the favor. But idk how to stop myself. And was that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0096" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:07:12 UTC">
      <body>No not really, just idk how to respond ya know? I love the sound of an inhale. But fuxk being sick, I'm sorry. And for sure i got you, you need to put energy into those who matter.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0097" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:08:00 UTC">
      <body>You love the sound of an inhale? And yeah, it's just difficult because I feel like everyone matters. And I would want people to act with me the way I do with them. Idk relationships between people are so hard to manage. It's like this web that you have to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0098" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:09:20 UTC">
      <body>Like taking a breath in. That sound is so relaxing and invigorating at the same time. #5amdeepthoughts. I think you're worth knowing! And friending! And even girlfriending hah. Be positive sara, you'll find someone great.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0099" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:12:14 UTC">
      <body>Hah there is no one I would rather talk to at 5 in the morning. And yeah, I mean I will, eventually. So will you. Just wish I had someone lined up like you :P eh not really actually. I'd rather start over. I wanna be a lil baby again, all brand new, no mi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0100" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:13:36 UTC">
      <body>Mmm being a baby would rule, our minds wouldn't be full of shit, but our diapers could be and it doesn't matter. So helpless and care free, nothing would matter hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0101" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:15:10 UTC">
      <body>Ahaha Johnny, you are so great. Indigo would be lucky to have you (: but really, just find someone who makes you happy, who takes you as you are, and stick with them. But don't ditch me along the way(: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0102" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 13:15:44 UTC">
      <body>Aww why thank you, and yeah hopefully that goes well, maybe make a friend ya know! And I will, and you do the same okay. And i won't Sara. But sleepy time! Ciao and goodnight </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0103" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 13:18:41 UTC">
      <body>I hope it goes well too! Let me me know how it does go! Night Johnny, sleep well(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0104" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 22:31:07 UTC">
      <body>Hey it was nice talking to you last night (: when's your coffee date with indigo? (do people ever shorten her name to indie?) ps you should not worry about me, like you can text me whenever and such. I never sleep early Soo yeah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0105" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 22:38:56 UTC">
      <body>Hah okay for sure, what time you goto bed last night? And no idea hah and still need to ask her. But was def nice talking too Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0106" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 22:42:51 UTC">
      <body>Like 545 ish, hah I have really bad troubles sleeping. And ah well I hope it all works out with her, I mean if anything you'll get an awesome friend out of it (: and yeah, that was nice. Can I ask you something real quick?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0107" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 22:43:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah go ahead and ask! But I'm sorry, sleeping pills maybe? And true that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0108" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 22:47:06 UTC">
      <body>Okay, like is it normal for it to sting when you talk about girls? Don't get me wrong, I want you to be happy, and I want to hear these things, but it's normal for it to hurt a little bit right? I'm rally happy for you tho!(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0109" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 22:53:52 UTC">
      <body>She's busy... Hmph... Yeah I think that's gonna happen ya know? But I'm not sure tho, you're call</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0110" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 22:55:37 UTC">
      <body>Aww really? She's busy today? It's a 3 day weekend! She's gotta have some time. Yeah, but like would you feel like that? Ps I'm actually like sad that she can't go, like sad for you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0111" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:00:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I guess she's home for the weekend, ffffffuuuuuu. Yeah I'd feel weird about it, thats why I don't ask hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0112" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:01:33 UTC">
      <body>Ah where's she from? Hah she'll be back Johnny, relax (: do you like her? And yeah like I wanna help you, so you should tell me things, it really doesn't hurt that bad and I want you to be happy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0113" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:08:48 UTC">
      <body>Idk where she's from, hah need to ask her that. She ain't texting back, meh. And idk if i do. The date would tell me that hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0114" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:11:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh, is she one of those girls who take forever to respond and shit? Is she you in boy form??:P and isn't she from Seattle? I'm a stalker lol. And well I hope she does go with you, coffee is like an easy no pressure thing</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0115" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:19:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah fuxk me, out myself out there and got shot down meh... And not really, she just isn't to this. But I thought she was</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0116" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:22:01 UTC">
      <body>What did she say? And it happens to everyone Johnny, you just have to keep trying. Or take a break and learn to make yourself happy and then people will come to you, it'll be alright. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0117" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:23:44 UTC">
      <body>She said that she's home and has to work so she can't... And I was like well maybe sometime later this week :) and nothing back grr. But word, thanks Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0118" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:25:45 UTC">
      <body>Hmm, that's kind of aggravating. Hopefully she responds though. You're an amazing man Johnny, anyone would be lucky to have you. But you deserve aomeone who'll make you happy and secure, and you'll find that person in time (: are you okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0119" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Ohp, she texted back that sounds good! What's that mean in girl? Yeah I'm good, and was fine before she texted me. I just went shopping heh. How're you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0120" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:36:29 UTC">
      <body>Haha good (: and that can mean both "I'm not gonna text you later" or "I'm gonna expect you to make the effort" or "sounds good." idk how you guys talk, or what your relationship is. Does he seem into you? Ah nice, what'd you get? Who you go with? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0121" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:37:21 UTC">
      <body>And I'm fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0122" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:40:48 UTC">
      <body>John and nick, got an awesome American flag scarf, and a button down and t shirt. And idk, like when she texted me the first time we talked for a bit, but I can't tell hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0123" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:44:36 UTC">
      <body>Ah nice, where you go? Oh so she texted you first? What did you talk about? It seems like she'd be into it. Just if she is, make sure you're ready for it. I mean, would you be ready to jump into another relation ship right now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0124" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:45:04 UTC">
      <body>Buffalo and urban. Well I gave her my number via fb and she texted me. But we've chatted some on fb about stuff. And no, but im just testing the waters ya kno.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0125" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:49:58 UTC">
      <body>Oh I'm going there later! Mardi gras party and nothin to wear. And if she texted you then she def isn't not into it. So just go for it! Do what makes you happy, and hopefully she's a person who treats you the way you should be, and engages you, and just i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0126" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:50:19 UTC">
      <body>Ps if you end up with her, can i finally meet her :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0127" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:53:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho well that'll be fun! And yeah maybe? Hah idl how that'd work tho. But yeah true that hopefully it works out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0128" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:54:27 UTC">
      <body>I hope so. Frat parties arent usually fun tho. Hah well its likely I'm gonna visit Seattle at some point. I'm not Gonna stay away from a city I like cuz you're there, and eventually we might be close enough to visit each other(Austin and his ex are hah, k</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0129" participant="131065" time="2012-02-18 23:57:52 UTC">
      <body>Okay. Well in time we shall see ya know. But yeah gotta love Seattle. But yeah, frat parties are sorta weak.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0130" participant="131019" time="2012-02-18 23:59:51 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, but i mean, we can do it, like we can be friends. I mean idk if this is healthy what were doing, but it doesn't feel wrong to me so idk. And hah im def mad I can't go to Seattle now, but it's whatever. But yea, the ratio, the music, all kinda shitty</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0131" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 00:06:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho, bros and fist pumping huh. You don't like that? Come on? Get fratty! But yeah in time we will see ya know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0132" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:09:21 UTC">
      <body>Hah nope, co ops are fun but frats meh. Whatever I'll give it a shot and go home if it doesn't work. And yeah, it'll be nice to see you in march though. I hope your spring break is fun, and hope you can make some time for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0133" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 00:12:48 UTC">
      <body>Yeah we will def have to meet up on the weekend! And yeah we don't got co ops here, lame tho. But can't wait till spring break ahhh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0134" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:14:47 UTC">
      <body>Okay good, glad you're not backing out. Ughh and summer. I love my classes and the people but I just want a break you know? From like the constant stress and pressure. Like every hour there's something else</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0135" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 00:14:56 UTC">
      <body>Like every hour? What do you mean? And I feel yah, want a break super bad, well have Monday off hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0136" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:19:17 UTC">
      <body>Idk it's like i fix one thing, and something else happens. Like there's a different fight to fight all the time, and that's life, and I just have to stop waiting for it to get better, I have to just be relieved that I can stay positive. And yeah Monday wi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0137" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 00:25:36 UTC">
      <body>I know, that wuda been real nice. Like uc had it off huh? But that's true, just gotta hang in there and focus on the positive while dealing with the negative</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0138" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:26:06 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, like just colleges don't have Friday I think. Hehe did you see the pillow pet I bought Alex?(: and yup, just sucks when like I'm the only one with that mentality, like everyone else's problems stress me out a lot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0139" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:29:15 UTC">
      <body>Ps you should just jump on tht karlyn chick, she wants yo dick</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0140" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 00:32:00 UTC">
      <body>Mhm i got you, hah gtfo about karlyn, I like don't even know her. But my phones about to die, so I'll ttyl! But yeah that pillow pet looked awesome hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0141" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 00:33:37 UTC">
      <body>Mmk bye!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0142" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 05:50:43 UTC">
      <body>Hey this is kind of a weird question, but do any of your friends try to like control what you do up there? I don't know how to deal with it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0143" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 05:52:00 UTC">
      <body>Not really, actually none of em. That's weird... Who's doing that?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0144" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 05:53:46 UTC">
      <body>Doriane...idk like she's been talking down to me a lot, and kind of telling me what to do. And it's making me feel really anxious and like I have eyeliner on and I can't cry ahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0145" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 05:54:08 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry, well tell her no. And tell her to fuxk off hah. That's stupid tho.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0146" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 05:57:49 UTC">
      <body>Hah I can't, like it involves something that she's gonna do and isn't letting me do. Whatever tho, idk I don't even want to go out :/ but I'll let you go sorry for texting you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0147" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 05:58:24 UTC">
      <body>Okay well I hope it works out, ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0148" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 05:58:24 UTC">
      <body>Okay? Hope your night turns out alright.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0149" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 05:59:18 UTC">
      <body>Hah yeah, have a good night. Hopefully you can sleep tonight! Feel free to hit me up if you can't</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0150" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 05:59:36 UTC">
      <body>(although I guess now you have indigo to talk to)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0151" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 06:00:55 UTC">
      <body>Hah sorry I meant that in a good way! Never mind. I'll just stop talking to you, I keep fuxking everything up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0152" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 06:02:40 UTC">
      <body>No you don't, ciao Sara. Hope you're all good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0153" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:11:25 UTC">
      <body>Thats a lot of beer hah, and you said you don't party</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0154" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:12:48 UTC">
      <body>Hah well drinking in a dorm. Six patch for each, but not killing it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0155" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:14:14 UTC">
      <body>Six pack for each person? Damn you guys! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0156" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:14:56 UTC">
      <body>Haha that's really not that much tho...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0157" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:16:13 UTC">
      <body>Hah tru dat. Well you have fun then! Get gnarly breh! Get shwasted. Or stupid faceded</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0158" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:17:04 UTC">
      <body>Hah wow okay if you say so, that song tho! Hahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0159" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:18:15 UTC">
      <body>Haha exactly! Get it in! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0160" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:18:23 UTC">
      <body>K yah that's just weird</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0161" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:23:28 UTC">
      <body>Hah that was sorta weird, and I'm not gona get it in Sara...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0162" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:25:07 UTC">
      <body>Sorry!! I'm tryin to be like your bro hahaha. Not working huh?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0163" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Haha you can be my bro, but I'm not gonna get it in hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0164" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:27:19 UTC">
      <body> Hah okay, I'll be like your girl bro(: it'll be awesome!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0165" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:27:44 UTC">
      <body>Hah okay that sounds like a plan to me. Down with that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0166" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:31:49 UTC">
      <body>Haha shweet(: hope you're having loads of fun!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0167" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:32:00 UTC">
      <body>Hah yeah, not loads but good times. How're you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0168" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 08:34:08 UTC">
      <body>Feel yah and I'm good, Chillin with the crew. But I'll ttyl! Ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0169" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:34:10 UTC">
      <body>Hah I'm good, getting fratty and what not! Just fun win the girls. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0170" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 08:35:30 UTC">
      <body>By eeeee it's dance time (: have fun and get gnarls</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0171" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 10:22:00 UTC">
      <body>Johnny I miss you because I always had someone to walk me home and I would never get almost mugged</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0172" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 10:37:52 UTC">
      <body>Im sorry, you won't get mugged and if you feel sketch you can always call me or another guy friend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0173" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 10:39:58 UTC">
      <body>Oh my gosh I'm sorry I'm embarrassed for texting you that. I hope your night was fun tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0174" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 10:41:59 UTC">
      <body>No I just am like, I totally would do that. I'm sorry for bothering you and hope I didn't wake you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0175" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 10:42:08 UTC">
      <body>Did you not realize? And you too Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0176" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 10:44:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah you're all good, still up. I'll ttyl tho, be safe! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0177" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 10:44:36 UTC">
      <body>Haha okay, thank you. And I found Ahbishek, he's got my back. Have a good one Johnny thank you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0178" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 10:46:05 UTC">
      <body>Hehe fo shua barrada :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0179" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 10:46:24 UTC">
      <body>For shua, later!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0180" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:37:52 UTC">
      <body>What was that shit we bought you when you were sick in Seattle?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0181" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:38:57 UTC">
      <body>Ohhh yes. Thank you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0182" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:39:12 UTC">
      <body>Mucinex!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0183" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:39:12 UTC">
      <body>Word, hah I Srsly woke up the instant before you sent that </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0184" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:40:26 UTC">
      <body>Haha oh good. Maddie woke me at 11:/ and I'm growing fond of our late night chats, it's kind of bad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0185" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Damn fuxk that noise and word, I feel like we shudnt do em. Sleep is important hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0186" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:42:06 UTC">
      <body>What noise? Well if you say so, no more chats</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0187" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:45:36 UTC">
      <body>Hah I just meant like fuxk that. And no I mean we can, but you gotta get better Sara. I like em too.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0188" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:46:01 UTC">
      <body>Hah yeah, she always does that so I'm used to it. Hah yeah, that I do, but talking to you is so much fun (: about girls and ahit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0189" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:47:44 UTC">
      <body>Hahah really? It's fun? Cus I suck at it? Hah. But weak sauce</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0190" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:51:03 UTC">
      <body>Hah no, cuz I wanna help you and want you to be happy and be okay (: idk I just want things to work out well with you, cuz for me they aren't. And yeah hopefully I get better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0191" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:52:00 UTC">
      <body>They aren't for you? And yeah hopefully, you shud t go out tonight heh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0192" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 21:54:04 UTC">
      <body>I want your love life/life life to work out cuz mine isn't. And ah fuck def not. Prlly gonna stay home and watch a movie, but no one to watch with meh :/ my friendies don't wuv meh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0193" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 21:56:16 UTC">
      <body>Heh you and your baby talk, I'm sure they do Sara. But that's a good call. And how/why isn't your life working out?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0194" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:00:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah you know me, and they do but not enough to watch a movie with me instead of going out. And eh it doesn't matter, my life is good, just boys are dumb:P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0195" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:04:48 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow, don't base your life off of boys Sara. Just cus one doesn't work out, there is always more fish in the sea... Cliche but for real.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0196" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:05:01 UTC">
      <body>Haha no that's what I'm saying, my life is good but boys are lame. And it's a bummer were not I'm the ocean then :P hehehe I'm si clever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0197" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:09:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh like love life is particular got chya. Do you wana ask me questions about boy translations? Srsly tho, miss marine sooooooooooo much!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0198" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:10:25 UTC">
      <body>Haha no I'm all good. I know exactly what they mean, they just don't make sense. And dude fuck yeah, my dad tells be about his walks on the beach and I just get so jelly! Want summer si bad! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0199" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:10:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh no I can't go to the beach wih you :/ this just made me sad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0200" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:13:20 UTC">
      <body>Ah word, walking onthe beach is the best! Fuck. And you'll have other friends Togo with! And we make more sense than girls!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0201" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:15:11 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, summer will be amazing. Hah I know I will, but you're more fun, cuz you "womp" And what not.  I hope we're chill enough to hang out tho eventually, like personally wouldn't be too weird for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0202" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:17:36 UTC">
      <body>Mhm for sure, and I think I'd be okay with it... But I can't really know until I see you in person ya know? Fuxk I wana womp</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0203" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:18:32 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, exactly. I don't think it's be too weird. Like we can still hang out with our mutual friends and all you know? And I wanna go to the beach do bad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0204" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, Andre and Stefan and Alex and such. And I know, just the mentality and mindset of the beach. Fuck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0205" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:22:37 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I'm really happy with where we are right now (: like so grateful for you and this right now, you have no idea. And yes, def miss that! But bleh don't wanna be sick</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0206" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:26:08 UTC">
      <body>Mmm yeah being sick sucks dood, is it cold there? And yeah I'm content too with this, Tis good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0207" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:28:12 UTC">
      <body>It's windy but sunny, so sort of. And yeah, I'm glad you're okay with this too, let me know if I overstep ever or if anything makes you uncomfortable though, I really hope we can maintain our friendship</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0208" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho, and I think we will be able to. And got chya, yeah the wind sucks. But I ttyl cool? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0209" participant="131019" time="2012-02-19 22:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Yup I'm gonna take a nap now(: and yeah we'll be fine Johnny, meep well be good and everything will be okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0210" participant="131065" time="2012-02-19 22:36:48 UTC">
      <body>For shua, ciao for now! Bai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0211" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:24:44 UTC">
      <body>Andre be giving me break up advice... What even. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0212" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:27:12 UTC">
      <body>Hah he's the best at relationships huh?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0213" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:28:54 UTC">
      <body>Well I mean he has good points but like, idk he's looking out for me. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0214" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:29:20 UTC">
      <body>Well that's good then, you skyping?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0215" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:29:20 UTC">
      <body>Nice, not MySpace? Weird</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0216" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:29:52 UTC">
      <body>Facebook. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0217" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:30:26 UTC">
      <body>Oh right no twitter actually.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0218" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:31:27 UTC">
      <body>Oh reallySTOP</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0219" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:31:28 UTC">
      <body>Cool, I'm into telegraphing these days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0220" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:31:28 UTC">
      <body>Okay will do hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0221" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:32:40 UTC">
      <body>What?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0222" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:33:36 UTC">
      <body>I'll stop. I'm eating right now tho. Can I ttyl?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0223" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:33:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh got it, totes missed em</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0224" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 02:33:36 UTC">
      <body>Bai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0225" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:33:55 UTC">
      <body>That was...a telegraph joke. Ttyl</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0226" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 02:34:41 UTC">
      <body>Byee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0227" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:11:32 UTC">
      <body>Sorry to be hot and cold but I don't think we should talk about Indigo anymore unless I specifically ask. It's hurting me a lot more than I thought it would and it's kind of hitting me Really Bad. I'm sorry about that. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0229" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:13:52 UTC">
      <body>Okay that's completely understandable. Truthfully I don't think anything will come of that btw the Sara. What're u up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0230" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:18:02 UTC">
      <body>Idk to me it feels like, you met her at the beginning of last quarter, put her aside to see how worth it I really was, and decided I wasn't and tried her again. Idk it just really hurts. And about to smoke with Ahbishek and watch pirates with Kendall. You</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0231" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:20:16 UTC">
      <body>Nice, which pirates? And you actually think I had that ulterior plan Sara? Why the fuck? I just met her early on and she seemed cool and now I'm pursuing to be friends or something more...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0232" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:21:44 UTC">
      <body>I'm saying what it feels like, I know you wouldn't do that, but like even the fact that you're already looking for another relationship. Idk it just really hurts, more than I thought. I was ignoring it, and it hurts that I'm not worth it. And idk which pi</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0233" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:21:53 UTC">
      <body>What're yiu doin?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0234" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:24:32 UTC">
      <body>Bout to chill with John and such, and okay we tried it and now we don't have to talk about it. And you aren't? I'm not really pursuing anything that intensely, just testin the waters...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0235" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:24:53 UTC">
      <body>Exactly, I'm not worth it to you, that hurts. And yeah I mean good luck and I want you to be happy. Like if yiu meet someone I'd appreciate you telling me but I'm gonna ease up on giving you advice cuz I'm just sabotaging myself</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0236" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:33:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds good, well I mean I've already explained everything to you Sara. So maybe we should talk less? Idk what to do that'll help us.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0237" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:36:35 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know yiu did but that doesn't make it suck any less. And yeah idk I'm ginna try and be friends, like we should still Skype once in a while, idk maybe I'm just sick and feeling lonely right now haha :P I hope you're okay tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0238" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:37:20 UTC">
      <body>I'm good and definitely feel lonely alot too, but I feel it's a passing phase. And okay, well we can still talk some and such ya know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0239" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:39:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, hah wish it would go away. Sad to say it only really does when I have something completely engaging going on around me. Yeah I don't wanna cut off all contact, like I enjoy our chats, no matter how late :P </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0240" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho I got you, would be weird to cut off all contact ya know. It's good to talk. And this is true! You ain't alone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0241" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:42:35 UTC">
      <body>Yes it def helps, makes me feel less lonely, which is kind of sad I guess. But dude, I'm going ti see Seth Meyers on Tuesday (: meh I guess I just miss talking to you yiu know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0242" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh nice, for free? Shud be good stuff.  An yeah well I think that's a given, it's not sad Sara. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0243" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:46:04 UTC">
      <body>Nah only like 17 tho. Super stoked! And okay, does talking make you feel less lonely? Or are you ambivalent? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0244" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:48:00 UTC">
      <body>No it def does, especially at night when it strikes hard ya know. And that'll be cool tho!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0245" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:48:39 UTC">
      <body>Alrighty, well I'm gonna watch my movie now, hah I'll probably talk to you tonight when I'm all sad again, if that's okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0246" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:50:08 UTC">
      <body>Yeah might be busy, but sounds good. Ciao ciao to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0247" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:50:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay well never mind.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0248" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:51:16 UTC">
      <body>I'm not bitter. I won't talk to you tonight Johnny don't worry. Have fun wih your drinking crew or whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0249" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:52:16 UTC">
      <body>Don't be bitter. I'm just not making any promises Sara...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0250" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:52:16 UTC">
      <body>This is you being bitter. Seriously dood, now you're crossing the line.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0251" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:52:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god Johnny... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0252" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:53:53 UTC">
      <body>I am not bitter that you won't talk to me tonight. I hope you have fun. I also hope you stop making assumptions about what I'm feeling based on texts. Bye</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0253" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:54:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm done with this convo. Ciao for now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0254" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 04:54:24 UTC">
      <body>Goodbye.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0255" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 04:58:45 UTC">
      <body>Sorry Johnny. No need to be rude. TTY whenever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0256" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 05:16:16 UTC">
      <body>Johnny im sorry okay? I wasn't bitter, I'm just lonely. You don't need to be rude ti me and I don't need to be rude to you. This is a work in progress. Okay? We're both doin our best. We can't fault each other for that. I'm sorry. Anyway hope that's enoug</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0257" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 06:43:18 UTC">
      <body>Ugh you are the single most aggravating person I know! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0258" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 06:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Okay, well you're bitter when you just say "bye" or when you say stuff like "I hope that's enough..." idk how best to explain. Yes I'm down to work on this together, but when it comes to you saying stuff like "your drinking crew or whatever" dot assume I'</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0259" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 06:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Why do you say this ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0260" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 06:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Did that long text just get to you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0261" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 06:50:53 UTC">
      <body>Yup it just did. And you make assumptions too Johnny. Like assuming I was trying to get you to agree to talk tonight or something. Idk, whatever. I was just trying to explain. Why does it matter if I say "hope that's enough." like how is that passive aggr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0262" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 06:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Sorry, I seriously sent that like an hour ago, just noticed it never went thru with that text. Because you're asking me if thats enough or do I require more of your effort. And I assumed that cuz you said you wud text me later...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0263" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 06:55:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, like if an apology is enough or if you need more to not be mad at me. And well you know I respond right away, so yeah. Yeah, I said I would prlly text you late at night when im all lonely. Whatever never mind. I'm not trying ti start something I'm s</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0264" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:00:16 UTC">
      <body>I don't like fighting you either. We shudnt since we are friends ya know. An apology is enough Sara and I accept that. Sorry I suck at responding was walking and didnt feel it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0265" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:09:25 UTC">
      <body>It's okay Johnny. We're all good, no more fighting (: what're you up to? Chillin with John still?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0266" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:10:56 UTC">
      <body>Yer and now with nick too, bout to watch some skins i think. And down with no more fighting ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0267" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:10:56 UTC">
      <body>:)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0268" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:11:43 UTC">
      <body>Nice, okay cool. British version? And alrighty I'll work on not being bitter/passive aggressive and well both work on not making assumptions. Sound good?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0269" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:11:46 UTC">
      <body>Ooh wish!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0270" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:13:04 UTC">
      <body>I'm down with that! Let's do it, I promise.  And fuck missed it hah. And uk is like so much fucking better than the American version, it's ridic!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0271" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:14:53 UTC">
      <body>Hah I've heard. Is it with watching? Should I give it a chance? We can do this (: idk I just feel so like positive about things when I talk to you for some reason, I can't put my finger on it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0272" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:15:12 UTC">
      <body>No it's not weird that you're open. Definitely important to be open and positive about these things. And do it! Pretty good stuff. Uk tho for sure.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0273" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:15:17 UTC">
      <body>Also, is it weird that im so open with you? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0274" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:17:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I do get the feeling, I know exactly and it's hard to explain. Yeah teens with drugs, love and drama and drinking and such, good stuff hah and yeah on Netflix </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0275" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:17:23 UTC">
      <body>Is it on Netflix? Is it just a bunch of teenagers fuckin basically? And okay good, I think it is too. Idk I feel stupid that I feel less lonely talking to you, but like when I'm alone at night, I mean you know the feeling right?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0276" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:20:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, it really is. Like I can't even describe it to myself. Like its just like this overwhelming feeling and it totally hits at night when I'm trying to sleep. (I still use angry bird, is tht bad?) han nice, sounds like a good time. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0277" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:25:52 UTC">
      <body>No I think that's alright, but I feel it's important to lose that dependence eventually you know? Did that come out mean? Am I wrong? Don't take this the wrong way Sara, please </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0278" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:26:50 UTC">
      <body>Is this about angry bird or about us talking late at night when we can't sleep?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0279" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:30:08 UTC">
      <body>Well a bit of both, do you know what I mean? Or is this coming out wrong? Like I enjoy talking to you Sara, and it's good for us, but the dependent factor ya know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0280" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:32:40 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah, about the talking late night thing I completely understand, like we need to learn not to, but I'm here until you don't need me. I mean honestly I don't need to talk to you at night at all, it's just relaxing and nice on occasion. I hope I don't d</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0281" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Hah well don't do that, he's a boss! And needs you! But yes I completely agree with all and that's what I meant. Sweet, glad we're on the same page :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0282" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:35:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's good (: like I really would love to not need you as a friend right now, but I'm not ready to give up everythjng I have of you yet, not gonna lie. And okay, glad im allowed ti keep lil angwy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0283" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:42:56 UTC">
      <body>Gotta love angwy hah. But I understand that, in time it'll get better. I like having you as a friend tho, sincerely.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0284" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:44:05 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I hope so. I also hope it's not awkward when we see each other. Like I mean I know it will be initially but I hope we can stick it out until its normal. And I do too Johnny. That was really nice of you to say tho, wow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0285" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 07:47:05 UTC">
      <body>Bye Johnny! Nice talking to ya</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0286" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 07:47:12 UTC">
      <body>Mhm and I know that'll happen too, and we will be able to get by that. But my phones about to die Sara so I'll ttyl! Ciao for now Sara </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0287" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>I'm sowy, there's nothing I can find! Games like over to tough to play.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0288" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>Okay coolio. How're you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0289" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 09:55:15 UTC">
      <body>Stop playing two letter words!): </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0290" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 09:56:28 UTC">
      <body>I'll just start a new one, no worries. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0291" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 09:57:35 UTC">
      <body>I'm meh. Wasn't tryin to start a convo btw </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0292" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 09:59:17 UTC">
      <body>Hah Idc, I'm busy Laying in bed. It's very engaging. What're u doin?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0293" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 09:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, we'll want to continue? Or busy?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0294" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:00:56 UTC">
      <body>Ah okay, still? I'll let you go tho you're busy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0295" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:01:36 UTC">
      <body>Oh got chya, and watching skins with nick and John. Nothin to exciting hah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0296" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:01:36 UTC">
      <body>Hah yeah, plans for the night huh. Not busy tho, just watching this.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0297" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:02:10 UTC">
      <body>How long have you guys been watching? And I'm jut saying, I can let you go no biggie</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0298" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>All is well sara. Plans tmrw? And I'm not sure hah a long time but with breaks in between</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0299" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:04:09 UTC">
      <body>Hah nice. I've been watching Friday night lights and being pmsy hah. And lots of hw and then Andre is coming around 8 from mammoth. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0300" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Oh damn really? Dropping off the heels huh? And lotsa hw and I think that's it. Maybe climbing, not sure.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0301" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:06:00 UTC">
      <body>Nah I got those Friday when he left for mammoth, hah needed em to go out. But he's gonna chill with me and maybe crash for the night. Climbing should be fun tho! Meh I have so much to do tmrw though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0302" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Same here, gonna suck so bad. But at least there's a short week ya know. But for sho I got you, nice to see him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0303" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:10:54 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, just all my stuff is for Tuesday and I'm sick and idk if I should go work with he kids but I can't skip :/ you figure out your spring break plans?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0304" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:12:16 UTC">
      <body>Uh not really, but same plans as before. And you should go chill with the kids if you can. And just work hard tmrw.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0305" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:13:51 UTC">
      <body>But chances are you be in san Diego like that Saturday? The 24th or whatever. (just a thought, buy tix ASAP cuz prices are rising) and yeah fo sho, gonna do my best. When's your essay due?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0306" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:16:32 UTC">
      <body>Essay for envir is due on Thursday and yeah good call! Gone look into it tmrw. And yeah I think around then but maybe Sunday or Monday not precisely sure.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0307" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:17:48 UTC">
      <body>But won't you have to be back by Monday? For class? Yeah like I checked mine out today and they're pretty pricey. But yeah let me know if you want me to look over that for you. How long ou think you'll be in Santa Clara?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0308" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:18:40 UTC">
      <body>Oh wait yeah I'll be back by then I think, why do you ask? And I think just a night, then flying out the next day.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0309" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:20:40 UTC">
      <body>Just trying to figure out if I'll get a chance to see you that Saturday that our breaks overlap. Ah okay, well that'll be a fun road trip yeah? You guys gonna stop in Portland or something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0310" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:20:48 UTC">
      <body>Nah I think we are trying to just Go as fast as we can down the coast. Thinking two days tho maybe. And yeah I think that'll work out. I'll prlly fly out Sunday ya know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0311" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:23:06 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, and is it cheaper than flying all the way down? Or just for funsies? Alrighty yeah thatd be nice. I'm honestly scared to see you in person</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0312" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:25:04 UTC">
      <body>Yeah it shud def be cheaper and also for fun and also I'll be able to chill with Travis as well! And same, it'll be odd ya know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0313" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:26:33 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, that'll be fun. Yeah, I don't think odd is the word. Honestly I think the first time I see you in person is just gonna be horrible. Don't judge if there are waterworks hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0314" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:27:12 UTC">
      <body>Hah okay I won't judge, so shud we not do it at the pannikin or what?  But yeah don't know how best to choose a word for it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0315" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:29:04 UTC">
      <body>Hah idk well figure it out as it comes closer. I mean you never know where well be in a month emotionally. I'm in a really bad place right now but I'll prlly snap out of it soon you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0316" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 10:33:34 UTC">
      <body>Yup well figure it out. Hopefully I'm Totally fine by then. Im really tired tho so enjoy your skins marathon! Good night Johnny, I hope well be ojay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0317" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:33:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, well I'd be totes down for the pannikin so hopefully that ends up working alright. But we shall see and such.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0318" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 10:35:44 UTC">
      <body>I hope sho too. Nighty night Sara, sleep well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0319" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Hah why? I got plenty of sleep</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0320" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:46:23 UTC">
      <body>Johnny you should sleep more, I worry about you. Just sayin</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0321" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:47:29 UTC">
      <body>Cuz, you were on tumblr...until 5 in the morning? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0322" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:48:00 UTC">
      <body>Hah I just got up, that's lotsa sleep...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0323" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:48:00 UTC">
      <body>Well we watched skins till late and then I had to have my phone charge, it's all good Sara. I got like eight hours!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0324" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:48:38 UTC">
      <body>Err okay, if you say so. I just worryyyyy cuz I'm me and you never used to do dis</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0325" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:50:26 UTC">
      <body>Okay (: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0326" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:52:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah alritey, essay time ffffuuuuu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0327" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:52:41 UTC">
      <body>You'll be fine. Go get some coffee and a bagel. That's what I'm doing. Actually, that's what I'll do once I get out of bed.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0328" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:54:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm gonna get a page down and then Go get food hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0329" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:54:30 UTC">
      <body>Good stuff. What happened to broc? Why does he need survey? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0330" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:56:19 UTC">
      <body>Ah okay, well I hope it goes well. Dude I think my medicine fcked with my liver again :/ </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0331" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:56:32 UTC">
      <body>He's always had a bad shoulder, like since sophomore year. So been a long time coming, he should be good tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0332" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 20:56:32 UTC">
      <body>How so? What medicine?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0333" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:56:35 UTC">
      <body>Okay no you go write your essay, ready go!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0334" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 20:56:53 UTC">
      <body>Eassasssaaaaayyy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0335" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:00:07 UTC">
      <body>Actually can I ask you something before this? You don't have to answer if it makes you uncomfortable me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0336" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:00:48 UTC">
      <body>Sure go ahead </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0337" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:01:19 UTC">
      <body>I'm probably making this about me and blah blah it probably isn't even bout me but what's with the song you posted on valentines day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0338" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:02:56 UTC">
      <body>Oh, it was off hypem, just a good song ya know? Not really for v days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0339" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:03:38 UTC">
      <body>Okie just checkin. Idk why I was thinking about it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0340" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:05:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay for sure, no big deal! Essay time baibai!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0341" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:05:04 UTC">
      <body>For sure thanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0342" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:05:53 UTC">
      <body>Good luck, hit me up if you need edits! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0343" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:47:44 UTC">
      <body>Shigeto comments on starslingers instagram pics hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0344" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:49:05 UTC">
      <body>I'm confused?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0345" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:49:52 UTC">
      <body>Shigeto the artist from your smoking friend comments on another good artists "starslinger" instagram photos.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0346" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:51:21 UTC">
      <body>Ohh hah nice :P gotcha. Btw there are 60 dollar tix from sfo to sd on southwest. You should check to see if they have em for San Jose</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0347" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 21:58:16 UTC">
      <body>Yup, same. I hope you figure it out. Meh break is so far:/ but got my coffee and bagel ha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0348" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 21:58:24 UTC">
      <body>Will do! Yeah need to get that squared away today.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0349" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 22:11:12 UTC">
      <body>Hah skipped the coffee but got a bagel and cream cheese</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0350" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:11:30 UTC">
      <body>O my god fuxk the tickets I needed for home just jumped sixty bucks fuxk me fuxk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0351" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:11:52 UTC">
      <body>Sorry idk who else to fuckity fuck at</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0352" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 22:13:20 UTC">
      <body>Ah fuck, that's some weak shit, you instagrammer you heh.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0353" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:16:54 UTC">
      <body>Oh my god I am so fucking mad and now I have to get up at like 4 on Saturday to get home :/ you better be in sd then you beez cuz I'm doing this to have coffee with your ass! And hell yeah I'm an jnstagrammer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0354" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 22:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay I'll do my best to leave Sunday and such. But fuxk, I'm really sorry. Meh I shud got mine yesterday too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0355" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 22:21:52 UTC">
      <body>Well yeah of course, I'm totally planning on that Too. And true that. But essay time! I'll ttyl dewd</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0356" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:22:42 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, you need to do your ahit today cuz you fly even earlier than me. And you should, cuz I was kind of counting on seeing you, ya know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0357" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:24:07 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool, I really hope it works out. Good luck tho!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0358" participant="131019" time="2012-02-20 22:58:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah so I'll def be in sd Saturday, I get in at like 8 am hah. But let me know when you figure out your stuff. Gl on it essay!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0359" participant="131065" time="2012-02-20 23:00:16 UTC">
      <body>Will do! Thanks bye</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0360" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 00:48:44 UTC">
      <body>Yo can you do me a favor at some point when you have free time? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0361" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 00:59:32 UTC">
      <body>Umm send me music, cuz you have most of mine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0362" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 00:59:44 UTC">
      <body>Sure what's up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0363" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:00:05 UTC">
      <body>Although, actually if we meet up over break can you just bring your comp and I can get music? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0364" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:01:16 UTC">
      <body>No like cant you do it computer to iPod/iPhone?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0365" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 01:01:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, it's hard to do computer to computer tho. Have a hard drive?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0366" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 01:01:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah we can Do that easy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0367" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:02:28 UTC">
      <body>Sweet. Yeah I was gonna ask you to Skype me and send some but didn't think that I'd see you in a month. Let me know if that's fo sho happening and if not you should Skype me my tunes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0368" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 01:06:08 UTC">
      <body>Okay for sho, yea imma buy tickets tonight and such and we will figure it out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0369" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:07:23 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good. Lemme know if you want me to help you fin cheap ones, cuz I got really good deals on mine (: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0370" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 01:08:16 UTC">
      <body>Nice! Sounds good, ciaociao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0371" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:08:46 UTC">
      <body>Byeee</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0372" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 01:09:33 UTC">
      <body>You always say bye twice it's funny.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0373" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 01:10:24 UTC">
      <body>Ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0374" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:03:12 UTC">
      <body>No Sara, I think it's important for us to talk less and therefore become less dependent. I just don't wana fight anymore.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0375" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:03:30 UTC">
      <body>Are you mad at me Johnny?:/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0376" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:05:57 UTC">
      <body>Okay, was just wondering if you got the message. And I want that too Johnny . I don't wanna fight either I'm just having a rough time so im sorry. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0377" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:11:44 UTC">
      <body>For sure, I understand that. Let's just do our best to stay positive and not fight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0378" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:12:05 UTC">
      <body>Yup, agreed. You down to talk like Thursday tho? Meh i wish I could be a good friend to you Johnny. Like I try so hard</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0379" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:13:52 UTC">
      <body>I know and you are Sara. But yes let's talk thursday!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0380" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:14:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool (: thanks Johnny. Still wanna send me your essay? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0381" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Email it and I can read it tonight. And I can read the full one whenever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0382" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:16:00 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, got two pages deep. How shud I send it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0383" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:16:00 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds like a plan!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0384" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:16:49 UTC">
      <body>Alrighty I'll text you when I'm done with it, and I'll talk to you for real Thursday. I'm here if you need me. Ciao Johnny (: I hope you're okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0385" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 04:20:16 UTC">
      <body>I hope you're okay too Sara and I've got your back you know that. Ciao for now and thanks for the editing!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0386" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 04:20:26 UTC">
      <body>Thanks Johnny, I know you're there for me. Means a lot. No problem for the editing I can do it whenever. Bye (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0387" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 07:28:36 UTC">
      <body>I hope you figure it out Johnny I'm really sorry, I feel like its my fault cuz you used it to come down here and didn't come :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0388" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 07:41:26 UTC">
      <body>Johnny are you okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0389" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 07:51:00 UTC">
      <body>Well you're not talkin to me but I hope you are, if you wanna talk tonight I'm here(:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0390" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 07:51:28 UTC">
      <body>Oh didn't know when you sent that, but I'm all good now. And you're good to no stress.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0391" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 07:53:05 UTC">
      <body>Okay, are you sure? I'm worried, Andre said you didn't sound good :-</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0392" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 07:55:44 UTC">
      <body>Oh no I'm all good, was just getting over my stress hah and still need to write as well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0393" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 07:58:16 UTC">
      <body>Okay, well I'm still here if you need me Johnny. Don't be afraid to talk to me or call me when you're stressed, I can help (: even if it's just watching like portlandia or skins or whatever. I know you have your friends for that but sometimes it helps to </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0394" participant="131065" time="2012-02-21 08:00:00 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure I understand that and is good to talk to someone that knows me well. But I'll ttyl you later! Gotta kill this essay! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0395" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 08:00:55 UTC">
      <body>Good luck Johnny, email it when you're done if you want. I hope you're all good, hit me up if you need I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0396" participant="131019" time="2012-02-21 08:00:56 UTC">
      <body>To</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0397" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 00:02:08 UTC">
      <body>Will doo!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0398" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 00:02:30 UTC">
      <body>Email me your full research paper to edit btw if you want before Thursday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0399" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 00:05:02 UTC">
      <body>Sweet text when you do, TTY Thursday ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0400" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 00:08:32 UTC">
      <body>For sure, have a good one! Ciao ciao </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0401" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 06:40:57 UTC">
      <body>Hah I was just about to tell you to play me back :P </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0402" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 06:45:20 UTC">
      <body>I got you haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0403" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 07:20:22 UTC">
      <body>Did u finish ur essay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0404" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 07:23:44 UTC">
      <body>Almost, I just need a conclusion. I think I have everything I need tho. Only added like a couple smaller paragraphs to what you read already tho.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0405" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 07:24:55 UTC">
      <body>Mmk well send it over and I'll read it when I get home. Did you add citations?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0406" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 07:25:52 UTC">
      <body>Yup I did, I took what you said into consideration and such and edited it and all. But okay, I'll send it when I can</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0407" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 07:28:00 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds like a plan! Ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0408" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 07:28:20 UTC">
      <body>Mmk sounds good. Good luck, I'll let you know when I finish it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0409" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:05:10 UTC">
      <body>Did you want me to read your essay today or tnrw? Cuz I haven't gotten it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0410" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:08:16 UTC">
      <body>I havnt had a chance to send it. Can send it at like 130? Will you still be up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0411" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:08:43 UTC">
      <body>No worries ill be up. You know me and my insomnia </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0412" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:09:33 UTC">
      <body>No</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0413" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:09:41 UTC">
      <body>Np* lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0414" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:10:24 UTC">
      <body>For sure, sorry I havnt had a chance to send it sooner.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0415" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:10:24 UTC">
      <body>Hah I was like what? Okay cool, send it inna bit</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0416" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:27:45 UTC">
      <body>Lemme know when u send it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0417" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:31:44 UTC">
      <body>Is docx okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0418" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:31:44 UTC">
      <body>I sent it </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0419" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:31:44 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good! Thanks again Sara. Hope you're doing well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0420" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:31:53 UTC">
      <body>Yeah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0421" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:32:47 UTC">
      <body>I'll text u when I'm done</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0422" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:50:02 UTC">
      <body>Sent it, enjoy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0423" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:50:56 UTC">
      <body>Thank you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0424" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:50:56 UTC">
      <body>Oh, yeah I haven't done a conclusion yet! Plan to tmrw.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0425" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:51:31 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay, hah well I started one for you then. Yay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0426" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Oh sweet! Thanks very much then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0427" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 09:53:37 UTC">
      <body>Np, talk to ya thurs</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0428" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>Ciao ciao. Talk to you then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0429" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 10:00:52 UTC">
      <body>Sure thing, night Johnny (;</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0430" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 10:00:59 UTC">
      <body>(; awk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0431" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 10:01:08 UTC">
      <body>(: fuxk me double awk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0432" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 10:01:36 UTC">
      <body>Hahahah you're all good. Sleep tight </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0433" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 10:02:24 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! You too. But on the real that was funny as hell</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0434" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>Hah it certainly was hahah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0435" participant="131019" time="2012-02-22 10:06:34 UTC">
      <body>Hah anywho, good night. I hope you get a stellar grade on that paper!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0436" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 10:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Thanks sho much! And goodnight again heh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0438" participant="131065" time="2012-02-22 10:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Heh I'll keep that in mind. Final goodnight! Ciao Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0439" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 07:21:43 UTC">
      <body>I'm bored play words (: k I'll TTY tmrw night bai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0440" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 07:23:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay! Baibai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0441" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 08:43:34 UTC">
      <body>Hai I go sleepy nao so don't play me back until morning cuz the sound wakes me. Talk to you tomorrow night! Night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0442" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 08:44:48 UTC">
      <body>Night! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0443" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 16:38:30 UTC">
      <body>Dude, this guy just told me its like a minimum of 250-300 bucks...wtf</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0444" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 18:45:05 UTC">
      <body>Hey I owe you 90 bucks :D mind if I just give it to you when we see each other? Dont wanna risk mailing it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0445" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 18:46:24 UTC">
      <body>What happened?!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0446" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 18:46:24 UTC">
      <body>And yeah next time I see you is good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0447" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 18:47:02 UTC">
      <body>I can go tto like some 3 hour class and the case is dismissed. I'm so happy (: and I can def talk tonight, if you want. Im not tired </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0448" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 18:48:32 UTC">
      <body>For sure, well that's awesome! I'll tty tonight. Ciao for now class time tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0449" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 18:49:16 UTC">
      <body>:D talk to you then! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0450" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 21:47:07 UTC">
      <body>Mind if we talk a little later like 11 or so? Or even 12 I mean whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0451" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 21:47:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's fine. We can even talk earlier than that if you wana</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0452" participant="131019" time="2012-02-23 21:49:33 UTC">
      <body>Yeah well play it by ear. Wanna plan for 11 and I'll let you know if I'll be home earlier or whatever?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0453" participant="131065" time="2012-02-23 21:54:08 UTC">
      <body>Sounds like a plan to me! Ttyt </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0454" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 04:34:34 UTC">
      <body>I might be just a tad later than 11, is that okay? If not 11 is fine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0455" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 05:41:13 UTC">
      <body>I'll text you when I head home</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0456" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 05:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that's cool, sounds like plan.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0457" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 05:43:28 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0458" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 06:58:03 UTC">
      <body>On my way now, be there in fifteen or so</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0459" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 07:00:16 UTC">
      <body>Okay coolio!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0460" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 07:10:28 UTC">
      <body>Skype yiu in five I gotta use the bathroom. And wish!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0461" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 07:11:34 UTC">
      <body>Oh no worries, just text when you leave or something (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0462" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 07:13:04 UTC">
      <body>Gonna finish this episode, so give me a little bit. Didn't think it's overlap my bad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0463" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 07:13:04 UTC">
      <body>Will doooo!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0464" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 07:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Leaving now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0465" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 07:17:30 UTC">
      <body>I'll be out in a minute!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0466" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 07:21:36 UTC">
      <body>Okay</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0467" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:18:27 UTC">
      <body>I literally have all vowels right now this is great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0468" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:18:56 UTC">
      <body>I have like none, damn it... I'm sorry tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0469" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:19:40 UTC">
      <body>Hah wanna swap? Bleh why does night time suck si much and all my friends are sleeping?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0470" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:21:04 UTC">
      <body>I just got two vowels, sorry </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0471" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:22:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah talked to her a bit but yeah. And ugh I wish I just lived in the units. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0472" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:25:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I feel that, I'm sorry :/ make friends in the units who stay up late?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0473" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:25:57 UTC">
      <body>Yeah idk no one really does on the weekend and it's Berkeley and everyone always has work to do. Anyway I'll let u go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0474" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:29:36 UTC">
      <body>Shit i got no good words to play. Okay for sure, I'll keep playing. Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0475" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:30:36 UTC">
      <body>Night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0476" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:48:27 UTC">
      <body>Quit beating me! I never win this game</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0477" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:50:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm sowy. Just don't sent me up for stuff yeah?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0478" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:51:03 UTC">
      <body>Hah well i just suck! Like usually I can make one or two words and they only fit one place</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0480" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Mmm igot you, don't be afraid to make up stuff. And I agree that, def good convo :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0481" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:53:14 UTC">
      <body>Hah I def try to. And yeah (: overall went well, I'm proud of us. Spring/summer is gonna be awesome and I feel like we're gonna be fine for the first time in a while</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0482" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:57:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I agree with that, hopefully it does go well. Can't wait for school to be over tho ah! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0483" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 09:58:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah fuck Dude you only have 3 weeks:/ I gots a month. But then after that another month and like I'm fuxking done with freshman year. When did that happen? And it will, I mean idk what can go wrong that hasn't already, like I'm just gonna be positive ya </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0484" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 09:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, we will deal with it as problems come up. But yeah that's legit dood, going by pretty fast. Enjoy it ya know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0485" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 10:01:06 UTC">
      <body>Yeah everything will be fine (: well be friends and things will be as normal as they can be. Ah I know, so fast like I can't even blink </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0486" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure, so def enjoy it all and such ya know. But yeah, hopefully things will be normal and good.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0487" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 10:03:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah you shud snag some. I'm feeling pretty tired myself. But yeah I agree with that, summer will be good and show us ya know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0488" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 10:03:53 UTC">
      <body>Yup, well I'm happy with it(: and I'm hoping that too. I feel like spring break will be a good diagnostic. And in a month I feel like things will be even better! I shud sleep huh?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0489" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 10:06:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah im not tired which is weirdcuz was up at 6, but I should sleep. And yeah I feel like everything will be okay, especially in bigger groups. Like there's no need fr awkwardness or blame, no point when we can just appreciate our friendship you know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0490" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 10:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho I got you. Well we will be good, and ah can't wait for summer. But yeah you shud sleep dood! Been up for twenty hours huh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0491" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 10:12:08 UTC">
      <body>Same, gonna be so great(: kickbacks, slumber parties, and beach going! Just don't wanna be lonely. And hah yeah I need sleep, blah or sleeping pills</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0492" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 10:18:31 UTC">
      <body>Which ones? Hah I wish! But yeah I'm gonna try and get some shut eye and hopefully dream of summer (: night Johnny! Enjoy your Friday and let me know how coffee goes!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0493" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 10:18:40 UTC">
      <body>Hah those sleeping pills never worked huh? But I'm about to head home. So I'll ttyl! Goodnight! But stoked for summer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0494" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 10:22:56 UTC">
      <body>Those natural ones. But yeah will do! Ciao and nighterz</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0495" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 21:31:02 UTC">
      <body>Sorry I gots no letters</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0496" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 21:34:56 UTC">
      <body>You played tho?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0497" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 21:36:14 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm just saying I have  shitty letters </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0498" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 21:37:04 UTC">
      <body>So many vowels, sorry bs word</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0499" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:05:03 UTC">
      <body>Hah mines bullshit too :P how was coffee??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0500" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:06:56 UTC">
      <body>Word, 'twas good, went smooth and such. Nothing too crazy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0501" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:15:13 UTC">
      <body>Oh good, not awkward? Like you guys had stuff to talk about and such</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0502" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:17:22 UTC">
      <body>Ah okay hah you didnt have to tell me that last part, but that's good. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0503" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:17:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, not awkward and yup good convo and such. Just got coffee and then I walked her back to her dorm.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0504" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:19:01 UTC">
      <body>Skipped my 2 o clock, finishing up hw with Maddie and chillin til linguistics. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0505" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:19:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool cool. Yeah, what're u up to?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0506" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:24:00 UTC">
      <body>Nice nice, and just jamming to music, waiting for ppl to get outta class. And sowy heh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0507" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:24:07 UTC">
      <body>You're killin me in words btw</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0508" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:25:22 UTC">
      <body>Hah nice, shud I let you go? And it's okay you're just really good at it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0509" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:32:32 UTC">
      <body>Nah you're good, how's maddie? And for sho, it's kind of a bullshit game tho ya kno</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0510" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:34:28 UTC">
      <body>Ps idk why but talking to you last night made me really happy, like really hopeful that we can stay close despite everything (: like I hope we're on the same page with this, let me know if we're not but I feel like by summer we can be like totally fine. I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0511" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:34:52 UTC">
      <body>And maddies alright, she's just sad a lot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0512" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:36:48 UTC">
      <body>No I totally agree, I think we're like doing super well and for sure by summer stuff will be good. Just don't wana goto fast and fuck things up. And why sad?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0513" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:40:42 UTC">
      <body>Yeah def not, I feel like we're both forgiving you know? Like we both bounce back quick ya know? Idk I'm excited to be friends with you(: just wanna focus on that. And idk she has issues that I help her with</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0514" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:43:12 UTC">
      <body>Mmm I got you, well that's good you help her? Fam stuff? And for sure I know what you're saying. And yeah! Down with beig friends :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0515" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:45:23 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, like I understand her well and it's good(: yay! Eep this is good, like I'm getting better at not needing you at like those 2 am nights and idk I feel like we're in a good place right now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0516" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:51:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I strongly agree. And the talk last night def solidified that for sure. But that's good you can help her</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0517" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:52:58 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, last night was really nice (: eee idk why I'm so happy with everything right now. Can't wait to see you and drink coffee and milk shakes and just be friends! Like I'm not tw sort of person who leaves things poorly, like if we can stay good friends i</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0518" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 22:56:00 UTC">
      <body>Hah word up, lotsa history between us and can't just throw that away. We've put alot of time into each other ya know? And fuck wana be in as</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0519" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 22:58:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah definitely, no point in throwing that away, when we can potentially be just as close but friends. Anyway I'm hopeful and happy and feel like it'll all be fine. But dude me too, ahh one month! But I gots class so I'll ttyl (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0520" participant="131019" time="2012-02-24 23:00:06 UTC">
      <body>And we can just focus on being friends, it's kind of effortless for me to be honest (: which is how it should be I feel lie</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0521" participant="131065" time="2012-02-24 23:00:16 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sho, def easy to maintain. But ciao ciao!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0522" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 03:59:01 UTC">
      <body>You are ahead of greys anatomy with music all the time hah, it's great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0523" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 04:01:04 UTC">
      <body>Hah you already know it! Imma boss</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0524" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 04:01:30 UTC">
      <body>Hah I'll vouch for you if anyone says otherwise. Have a good Friday night (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0525" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 04:03:12 UTC">
      <body>Hah okay thank you! And you too :) ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0526" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 04:04:23 UTC">
      <body>Shmanks!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0527" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 09:55:06 UTC">
      <body>Johnny are you up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0528" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I am, how're y</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0529" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 09:55:12 UTC">
      <body>Ou?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0530" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 09:56:29 UTC">
      <body>Is there any way you can please walk me home in like ten minutes I know this is really weird but of there is I would greatly appreciate it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0531" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 09:57:20 UTC">
      <body>No boys will? But yeah I will. Wang you to be safe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0532" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 09:57:20 UTC">
      <body>I can totally do it. Let's make it happen </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0533" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 09:57:58 UTC">
      <body>No, I'm having a really rough night. If you can't it's fine johnny don't worry about it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0534" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 09:58:57 UTC">
      <body>Thank you so much Johnny you are amazing. I'll call you in like five</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0535" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 09:59:28 UTC">
      <body>Okay coolio! Ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0536" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 10:15:30 UTC">
      <body>I'm home safe, thank you so much Johnny, I appreciate so much. Good night (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0537" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 10:16:32 UTC">
      <body>For shua I got you! Goodnight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0538" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 11:34:36 UTC">
      <body>Y u post music that makes me think is about me/yiu sent me? Why u no post dubstep or some shit like errone else</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0539" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 20:02:28 UTC">
      <body>So every time I take one step forward with you I talk like two back, and it's killing me. And yeah idk, you should call me later I'm sorry</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0540" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 20:40:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah you should call me when your phones back on I'd like to apologize (: kthxbai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0541" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 22:45:46 UTC">
      <body> What I texted u about was the song you posted. That's what I was apologizing for, sorry that you were busy tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0542" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 22:47:28 UTC">
      <body>No you're fine Sara. I just was listening to the song and was digging it and decided to post. I havnt Obtained much new music sho yeah, I've been listening to old playlists. You're fine, it's understandable and it was night time. You okay meow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0543" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 22:49:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah no it was like the caption that got to me cuz like I'm the person who assumes everything is about me. And Eh not really meow </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0544" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 22:49:36 UTC">
      <body>Ah the caption wasn't about you, someone said that last night and it was funny so yeah. Not about you, dot worry. And heh me too. But gotta work on my project! If you need anything just holler :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0545" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 22:53:43 UTC">
      <body>Oh, okay. You and your cool inside jokes. And okay, good luck! One thing tho: like the reason im afraid of losing you I think is hat you're family. Like I worry about you, I care about you, I get mad at you sometimes. Like you're my family. Idk if I'm tha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0546" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 22:56:00 UTC">
      <body>Ah, Sara. You're a part of my family too. We've been together so long and you know you're an important part of my life. I care about you Sara.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0547" participant="131065" time="2012-02-25 22:58:08 UTC">
      <body>I understand completely! Thanks tho too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0548" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 22:58:18 UTC">
      <body>I'm glad Johnny, that all means so much to me. Like I lose friends a lot and I just don't want to lose you too. So thank you </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0549" participant="131019" time="2012-02-25 22:59:41 UTC">
      <body>Thanks, you too! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0550" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:25:11 UTC">
      <body>Hah is it you watching breaking bad and workaholics on my Netflix?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0551" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Workaholics yes, but breaking bad no. Love my workaholics hah so lame and funny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0552" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:26:57 UTC">
      <body>Hah I wonder who's watching that. But nice (: you can use my Netflix tho whenever you want, no worries. And it was pretty funny, def weird humor to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0553" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:27:44 UTC">
      <body>Hah my kind of humor for sure, what have you been watching lately?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0554" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:29:00 UTC">
      <body>Yeah definitely. And uhh...Friday night lights...I'm so pathetic. But greys and the good lighting show still :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0555" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:32:00 UTC">
      <body>Hahah private practice if I recall correctly. But hah that football show? Seriously hahah.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0556" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:33:17 UTC">
      <body>Yup that's the one. And oh shush! I'm so lame! It's horrible hah. I'll start watchin skins so I can be up to par with your coolness Johnny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0557" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:36:16 UTC">
      <body>Hah seriously tho I think you'd like that show a lot. Super intense and fun to follow. Except season 1&amp;2 are only good. Not that into 3...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0558" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:37:13 UTC">
      <body>I'll look into it I promise! You can show me the ways when we're all friendly again(: but seriously Johnny it amazes me sometimes how much of a good person you are, like ah I am so lucky to have met you and so grateful! Hehe </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0559" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:40:32 UTC">
      <body>Sara, you're the same and I think we are to lucky people that ran into each other ya know and definitely make good friends </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0560" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 00:41:26 UTC">
      <body>Yes, I'm so happy with everything (: like were not gonna let our relationship get in the way of your friendship. Well be good. But ill let you do your project and such, I'll watch my lame ass show hah </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0561" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 00:46:56 UTC">
      <body>Yeah same, it will all work out. But yeah ttyl! Ciao for now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0562" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 03:32:29 UTC">
      <body>Pway wods </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0563" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:04:48 UTC">
      <body>Will do, sorry was climbing </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0564" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:05:50 UTC">
      <body>I figured(: hope it was fun! You're the best climber in the whole world!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0565" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:06:56 UTC">
      <body>Thanks, heh I'll play tho</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0566" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:10:57 UTC">
      <body>Hehe have a good Saturday night Johnny (: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0567" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:17:36 UTC">
      <body>You too</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0568" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:19:08 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0569" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:43:12 UTC">
      <body>Eggplant heh </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0570" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Just cuz hah idk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0571" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 06:45:20 UTC">
      <body>Nice</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0572" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:45:52 UTC">
      <body>Hah I know, I meant why</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0573" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:46:30 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0574" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 06:47:15 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0575" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 09:55:57 UTC">
      <body>Sorry for some reason I didn't see you played til just now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0576" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:31:39 UTC">
      <body>Ugh Johnny I literally have no vowels and haven't gotten any ): but I shud prlly sleep soon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0577" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:32:15 UTC">
      <body>Noo! You resigned! That's like me fake winnig</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0578" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:33:20 UTC">
      <body>I shud sleep soon too. And I'm sorry :/ I'll swap with you? Hah it's whatever tho haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0579" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:33:31 UTC">
      <body>Hah I'm down for a swap turn. And yeah I was exhausted and like I get home to my bed and like I'm not. It's awful</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0580" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:35:28 UTC">
      <body>Hah I know exactly how that goes right! Like I wana fall asleep at someone else's room but not once I'm home haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0581" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:36:39 UTC">
      <body>Yes!! Like I fell asleep earlier but my friends woke me to walk me home and now...not tired. Ps I love how many "haha"s yiu use :P</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0582" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:37:28 UTC">
      <body>Me too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0583" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:37:36 UTC">
      <body>I exchanged!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0584" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:37:36 UTC">
      <body>Hahah i know right hah. But yeah hah I know exactly the feeling hah haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0585" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:38:20 UTC">
      <body>Omg hah like hah that's si funny hah. But for real, like if you fall asleep somewhere else, they shud just let you sleep! Blah 4 am problems</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0586" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:39:44 UTC">
      <body>Roite, yeah I got you. So funny! But gonna head home and sleep! I'll ttyl! And goodnight sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0587" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:40:16 UTC">
      <body>Night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0588" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:41:25 UTC">
      <body>Why does that bother you? Sorry tho, good night Johnny, hope you had a chill night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0589" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Why you do that? Just say "night"</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0590" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, well idk, just seems your angry ya kno? And hope you did too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0591" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:43:16 UTC">
      <body>Well idk like put off I guess? Not angry tho, it's all good Johnny dont worry about anything. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0592" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:44:00 UTC">
      <body>I do worry about things Sara. I hope you're alright okay.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0593" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:44:59 UTC">
      <body>But why? I mean like I try to act like I'm alright when I talk to you so you don't worry bout me, I don't want you to :/ I want you to be happy and not bogged down by me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0594" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:46:08 UTC">
      <body>But I want you to be okay and wana help you Sara. I'm your good friend.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0595" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:47:22 UTC">
      <body>You are my closest super far away friend Johnny hah. But i mean I have problems, you know? There's always something, and I don't wanna drag you down with me. I want you to be happy, sincerely all I want is for you to be happy and just get everythjng you w</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0596" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:48:16 UTC">
      <body>I know you have problems and i do too, but you can tell me them and I know when you're not okay. I want you to be okay. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0597" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:50:19 UTC">
      <body>Okay, well we can talk to each other about them, just dunno if 4 am is particularly good for that? And I forget that you know me so well hah, always know when's something up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0598" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 11:50:24 UTC">
      <body>Hah especially over text :p bit more obvious sorta. But true that! I hope all is well, just know I'm here. Ciao and goodnight Sara!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0599" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 11:52:17 UTC">
      <body>I know, and I'm here for you too. I mean the reason I try not to talk to you about problems is you don't. But good night Johnny, sleep tight </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0600" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 22:54:16 UTC">
      <body>We will only have like one day, but did you still need a ride ti the airport? It's not a problem </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0601" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 23:00:09 UTC">
      <body>Yup, well we shall figure it out, just letting you know it's not a problem (: anywho I'll ttyl!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0602" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 23:00:16 UTC">
      <body>I'm not sure if I will, but maybe. Cuz the parents will be working</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0603" participant="131019" time="2012-02-26 23:00:31 UTC">
      <body>Have a good Sunday tho Johnny, I hope you ward off the blues!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0604" participant="131065" time="2012-02-26 23:02:24 UTC">
      <body>Thanks for sure! And you too Sara. Ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0605" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:08:13 UTC">
      <body>Is Elliot from Eau Claire?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0606" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:08:16 UTC">
      <body>Yup just like Justin Vernon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0607" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:08:58 UTC">
      <body>Hah yea he's cool. Maddies mom went to school there</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0608" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:16:48 UTC">
      <body>Oh nice! Where at?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0609" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:16:48 UTC">
      <body>Yeah hah it's pretty quiet there. But that's still cool and random</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0610" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:17:41 UTC">
      <body>Uh uw Eau Claire but hated it hah, dropped out after a semester</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0611" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:19:11 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, just thought id share :P </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0612" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:21:04 UTC">
      <body>For Shua, I gotta tell him</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0613" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:21:04 UTC">
      <body>Why not?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0614" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:21:56 UTC">
      <body>Yup yup! I wanted to win this game but I can't :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0615" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:24:50 UTC">
      <body>Cuz I have shitty letters and fail </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0616" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:33:52 UTC">
      <body>Weak, do your best!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0617" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:33:54 UTC">
      <body>I'm tryin real hard!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0618" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:36:00 UTC">
      <body>Hang in there!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0619" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:42:45 UTC">
      <body>We shud play hanging!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0620" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:46:40 UTC">
      <body>Hah I like playing words better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0621" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:50:38 UTC">
      <body>Hokayyy, lemme know if u change your mind! Btw sf is very Seattle esque weather right now, makes me sad</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0622" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Ah well isn't that usual? And work, gonna go biking. Ttyl!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0623" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 01:53:04 UTC">
      <body>Word*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0624" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 01:53:26 UTC">
      <body>Hah I guess! Have fun (: ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0625" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:31:48 UTC">
      <body>Hey this is weird and awkward but I'm really bored so wondering if you wanna Skype maybe? It's chill if you don't want to, idk if I'm overstepping, it where we are. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0626" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:33:21 UTC">
      <body>Oh okay well nvm then. Good luck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0627" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:34:56 UTC">
      <body>You're not overstepping but I'm watching a movie for English for a paper meh. No can do :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0628" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:34:56 UTC">
      <body>Thanks! Ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0629" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:35:19 UTC">
      <body>Right, well let me know if you finish or want me to edit or whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0630" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:35:55 UTC">
      <body>Can I ask you something?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0631" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:36:50 UTC">
      <body>How did you move on so fast?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0632" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:37:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool, thanks. You okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0633" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:37:04 UTC">
      <body>Yes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0634" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:37:04 UTC">
      <body> I don't move on so fast Sara. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0635" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:38:13 UTC">
      <body>I mean you already have another girl lined up, like you already have someone you like and have feelings for, and you already stopped loving me. Like what did you do? I wanna be like that :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0636" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:41:10 UTC">
      <body>But you already had a person, like idk I didn't have a person lined up for if we broke up. And like you already like her. I don't see how you're still getting over us, or what's hard about it for you. I just wish I could be like that and isn't get it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0637" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:41:18 UTC">
      <body>I don't get it *</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0638" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:41:20 UTC">
      <body>Well idk, I urged myself into it ya know. It doesn't suppress or get rid of old emotions tho. I'm still getting over us Sara. It's hard.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0639" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:45:36 UTC">
      <body>I did not have her setup Sara, she was cool and I Srsly didn't talk to her since I met her in the beginning of school. You know whenever we talked, I told you. I shouldn't have to explain myself...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0640" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:46:55 UTC">
      <body>No no no! That's not what I'm saying at all Johnny seriously! I'm saying, no matter who it is, how have you already moved on? Like is it just cuz it's working out btwn you and her? Cuz I try and get let down time after time and I just dunno. Like no one c</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0641" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:47:33 UTC">
      <body>Sorry, can see how that came off as like blaming. I'm just in shock I guess that you already have someone you like and already don't love me anymore I guess? Idj</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0642" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:49:52 UTC">
      <body>Well I've moved on because I've changed my habits and you know went on a date to see what it'd be like. Get my feet wet, and got lucky and it's working out sorta. People can follow me Sara. I just know we can't work as a relationship, as friends yea tho.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0643" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:51:25 UTC">
      <body>It hasn't even like been a month and like you have someone and like, do you realize how much that hurts? That you can replace me or whatever or find someone that fast and like I'm just stuck? I don't wanna be stuck but I put myself out there and fail over</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0644" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:52:00 UTC">
      <body>I'm sorry it hurts, idk what to say or do Sara. It's a process and I'm not done with moving on. To me this is part of like the transition, making new friends and stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0645" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:54:05 UTC">
      <body>Mmk, well idk what to say. This is why I wanted to Skype. We can just talk another time cuz I dont wanna say anything that'll hurt you or ruin what little we have</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0646" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 05:56:16 UTC">
      <body>Okay. Skyping would help? Call me a dick for moving on in a certain way, but this is how I gotta get over it in my own way Sara.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0647" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 05:59:03 UTC">
      <body>Johnny dont assume I think certain things of you. I think so highly of you! You're a great person and we used to be so close. Im just jealous is all. Idk if I'm more jealous of you for moving on or of her because she'll probably be the next person you lov</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0648" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:00:32 UTC">
      <body>What do you think would help best with you getting over it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0649" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:02:37 UTC">
      <body>Finding someone else to distract me and to be attracted to, I mean that's the only way. That's what
You're doing, that's the only thing that works. Just sick of bein shot down. Like I don't even wanna out myself out there anymore cuz it never works</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0650" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:03:33 UTC">
      <body>It's like there's no one who feels about me the way you do about her, or whatever. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0651" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:06:56 UTC">
      <body>Hmph, well have you out yourself out to guys that are assholes? I mean I got lucky ya know, she wants a second date. But you just gotta keep trying, it will pay off.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0652" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:08:36 UTC">
      <body>Nope, just...idk, I don't know what the problem is. No one wants me for me. They want me for my body or sex or whatever, no one like sits up at night and thinks about me, and wants me. All guys want is sex, no matter how nice or friendly or intelligent I </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0653" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:25:00 UTC">
      <body>Anyway my point is, we had the right love, it was just the wrong time and place. And you say you wanna be friends and I really really do, but when you have a new gf and she doesn't feel comfortable wih you hanging out with me, you'll stop you know? And I </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0654" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I feel that, well she's not even my gf Sara? We went on one date. You know I really wana stay friends with you and will work for that okay. And well you gotta find the right guys, which is tough in college.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0655" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:32:41 UTC">
      <body>I'm saying eventually whoever your gf will be, and it seems like it'll be her Johnny. But like, it'll be hard for you to do that, I'm just sayin like do you get that? Yes, that is hard jn college. It's just easy for you, cuz you're the right guy and indig</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0656" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:41:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay, I'll tell you if you should beat her up. But are you really looking for a serious relationship? But I completely get what you're saying with that though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0657" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:41:20 UTC">
      <body>No, I'm not personally, but even casual shit is just failing. And like I try so hard to be happy, like during the day I am. And then at night it's like it all goes to shit cuz I'm all alone. I just like, I wanna see you finally. Like I miss you, I miss my</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0658" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:45:58 UTC">
      <body>"yogi?" as in the bear??</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0659" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Hah I have no idea, but it worked! And I know I get lonely at night also so i feel yah and that is hard but things will get better in time Sara and just only use your energy with nice guys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0660" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 06:50:13 UTC">
      <body>I mean it's not about the loneliness. It's just about like how I'm not allowed to use you to feel less lonely, even if it is as a friend. Idk like I just wish we could forget being together and just be like, best friends. Idk like that's what I miss most </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0661" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 06:53:52 UTC">
      <body>Yes! Good call, let em come to you and it'll work itself out. But the friend will come easier with time and you will be less dependent and there will be a good balance ya know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0662" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:00:35 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, idk it's like we just need to be open I guess. I mean next time I'd appreciate if you told me you had feelings, or wanted something more from a girl cuz you made it seem like just friends si I was a bit taken aback I guess. And yeah I mean time will</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0663" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:04:32 UTC">
      <body>Hah it's okay, and understand that. You know I like talking to you as a friend Sara. And I don't know what is going to come of indigo, so don't make any assumptions.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0664" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:08:06 UTC">
      <body>Mmk I wont. But I mean like I feel I want to be friends more than you do? Do you get that too? For some reason like just talking to you at night about anything calms me down and I wish ti god I had someone else but like meh. Blahbity blah blah life </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0665" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:10:56 UTC">
      <body>I get that also. I think because like maddie and Dorianne have kinda been weird lately right? But same here, at night its the worst.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0666" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:12:55 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, idk like maybe cuz of that, but also like I feel like I've always relied on you more? And you don't really rely on anyone, which I admire but I'm not like that. And yeah well I'm not really friends with Doriane anymore...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0667" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:13:26 UTC">
      <body>Idk does it help you when we talk or yiu just do it for me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0668" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:17:20 UTC">
      <body>It helps a bit, but it helps me by helping you ya know. And yeah you have I suppose, but I got your back ya know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0669" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:19:27 UTC">
      <body>Okay, yeah I don't know like I feel lame being like this but I'm the same with Alex. But like she helps me in different ways. Im pretty independent as far as most people go, but I wish I could be better. Like I look up to you a lot, and respect you a lot,</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0670" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:20:18 UTC">
      <body>Oh you have a new wrist thingy!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0671" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:28:00 UTC">
      <body>That's Johns hands hah. But yeah youre a part of my life too Sara. And I do wana stay friends, just in time things will get better sorted and we will find boundaries ya know </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0672" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:31:30 UTC">
      <body>Oh, right hah. Well nvm. You finish your paper? Want edits? Okay cool, I just wanna like get past all of this. And in time hopefully I won't feel the urge to text you at night. This is just shitty cuz like I should stop talking to you but in two hours I'l</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0673" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:34:24 UTC">
      <body>Well you shud turn that into something else. Like write or go on tumblr maybe? And I'm good on my paper, not very tough.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0674" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:37:11 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm on tumblr. And I've been writing actually. It's like, I'm the sort of person who needs to talk about my feelings for them to go away and you're the only person who understands me well and knows what I'm going through, cuz you know me so well. Tou</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0675" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:42:56 UTC">
      <body>You're one of my best friends too, but yeah that's changed some what ya know. But yeah that's good, tumblr and writing are good. I draw! But yeah I think you know me best to tell you the truth.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0676" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:45:21 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I mean of course, it's impossible for it not to change I feel especially for you. I just want us to stay this way you know? Like(apart from your next girly) I wanna be that person for you and like help you through stuff and I want youto feel comforta</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0677" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:49:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah last time we skyped was def good. Wang that to sara. It's just we need some sense of distance... Time will really tell ya know.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0678" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 07:52:03 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I mean personally I feel the distance. It's like, just tell me what you need.  You want to take some more non talking days and Skype later this week again or something? I'll do anything, you know that (: just don't wanna fuck this up. Like I said, I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0679" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 07:57:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah for sure I got you, it's like I don't mind texting you and such but just like idk need some distance and stuff. I care for you Sara, but still feel an unhealthy dependence on me I guess</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0680" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:00:00 UTC">
      <body>Well let me know what you need from me. And I feel it too, I mean I wouldn't say it like that..cuz that's kind of mean :P but it's like, I could not talk to you, but I feel better when I do. It's just difficult for me to self-soothe, idk. But also like I </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0681" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:00:00 UTC">
      <body>That was harsh I'm sorry, didn't know how best to say it. Yeah I think the friends thing is the biggest. What's up with maddie? And why'd dori fall off ?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0682" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:04:16 UTC">
      <body>Like what'd the do most recently and such? And yeah that would def help, why don't you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0683" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:04:23 UTC">
      <body>No worries, didn't take it personally. And yeah, like honestly I feel if I could hang out with friends until super late, wouldn't think about the loneliness as much. And maddies all good, but Doriane was...idk she's not a very good friend, over it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0684" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:07:32 UTC">
      <body>I can't, like all my friends have early classes, homework, like it's always high stress over here and it's just hard to hang out until late you know? And she tried to keep me away from our guy friends and such and idk, not very supportive, whatever. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0685" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:10:40 UTC">
      <body>That's pretty wack, not cool of her. And I feel that, but weak not everyone is down to post late. Maddie still cool tho?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0686" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:13:01 UTC">
      <body>Yeah Maddie and I are good, but yeah it's pretty lame. Like always been jelly of you cuz that. And well, Doriane will be Doriane but I'm over it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0687" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:14:56 UTC">
      <body>Yeah idk she's always been off and on huh. And jelly of what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0688" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:16:25 UTC">
      <body>That you have friends you can always chill with like super late? Like I never sleep until like 3 or 4 but always gotta be home at like 12. And yeh she has, whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0689" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:21:20 UTC">
      <body>Mmm I got you, yeah the dorm situation sucks :/ I'm sorry. So you think that your friendship is like done with her?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0690" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:23:54 UTC">
      <body>Yeah like especially ciz mine is far. Can't wait for next year, you find an apartment? And like if she wants to be like acquaintances and be friendly thats fine. But not friends. Like you and I are 800 miles away and broken up and just weird and you're mo</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0691" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:25:36 UTC">
      <body>Yeah shes pretty wack, but acquaintances are chill for sure. And havnt looked recently actually</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0692" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:28:30 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, itll be okay. Ah why not? Ah Johnny can I just say, im so happy I appreciated you when I had you. Like I met you for a reason. Like so much could have happened and might not have net you, i am so grateful (: </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0693" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:29:52 UTC">
      <body>Yes it is special what we have, and we were meant to meet Sara. And just havnt hah idk, but really we should</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0694" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:32:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I'm looking too. And yeah, I mean you're family now. Talking to my mom about it, about you and us. I hope you don't think my parents dislike you tho, they still love you (:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0695" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 08:34:08 UTC">
      <body>Ah well that's good to know, makes me happy :) but thinking imma head out. I'll ttyl Sara! Good night and sleep well!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0696" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 08:40:19 UTC">
      <body>Haha have fun! Don't party too hard on Sunday! And really tho, they love you so much hah my ma invited you to her new show (: they love you a lot. Have fun tho, hope you sleep well tonight! I'll be here if ya can't. Night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0697" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 19:17:38 UTC">
      <body>Sorry that I...cried last night. I'm super embarrassed. I'm glad you told me you smoked tho, you don't need ti be scared to tell me things. Anywho just, I'm really embarrassed at that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0698" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 19:20:32 UTC">
      <body>Sara your cant help stuff like that, it's okay. Like you were crying at turtles, it was just your body being weird. It's okay :)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0699" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 19:23:16 UTC">
      <body>Idk it's like I try so hard to hide from you that I'm not okay, and it just sucks when you can tell and just. Yeah whatever</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0700" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 19:37:36 UTC">
      <body>Well you shudnt hide it, and tell me and I can try and help work thru it ya know?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0701" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 19:52:17 UTC">
      <body>But it sucks when you're all happy all the time, and like you don't have time for me Johnny, you have shit to do and I'm not who I was to you anymore, that's just how it is. And now you have Indigo, and you say you don't want anything, but that's what you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0702" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 19:54:40 UTC">
      <body>Okay. I can't tell you what's in store for me in the future. I tell you countless times I want to be friends and such and that's hard to define when we physically can't see each other. There was no physical closure or transition in that sense and I think </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0703" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 19:57:02 UTC">
      <body>Yea I know, that's why this is so hard, and I wanna be friends too I tell you that all the time. But I can't stop looking back and trying to figure out what happened and what I did wrong, you know? I mean except for what we already talked about. Like I fe</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0704" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 19:58:56 UTC">
      <body>It's not all your fault Sara, I did things wrong and also there were things beyond our control. Why would I blame all of this on you. We need to love forward from here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0705" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 19:58:56 UTC">
      <body>Move****</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0706" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 20:08:51 UTC">
      <body>Okay, I just wanna know I guess that a loved you enough and was good to you, and it was just the wrong time and place. And that we do, thank yiu Johnny, you're a really good friend. I know I'm difficult but it means a lot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0707" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 20:11:44 UTC">
      <body>I truly think that's what the problem was, like we worked sho hard. And we both cud have done things better, but external forces really put wear and tear on us ya know? And of course Sara.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0708" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 20:12:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay, I think that what I needed to know, cuz we both loved so hard but sometimes love just isn't enough. Got class now tho so I'll ttyl, and thanks for talking to me. Yiu really are an amazing friend, it means a lot</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0709" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 20:13:52 UTC">
      <body>You mean alot to me too Sara. Hope your day goes well! Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0710" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 20:14:25 UTC">
      <body>You too Johnny (: I hope you're happy</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0711" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 21:50:20 UTC">
      <body>If I had a thing going on like you do, like how would you feel, honestly? Cuz when I think of you and her I just feel sick. And idk if that's normal. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0712" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 21:54:08 UTC">
      <body>Uh I'd feel weird, but i guess it's expected ya know. Like would take some time but is get used to eventually. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0713" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 21:56:23 UTC">
      <body>Alright, idk like I have to actively not think about it cuz when I do it just knocks the wind out of me. Like I don't think you were ever infatuated with me the way you are her, like it seems like you're just in awe of what she is, which is perfect. And I</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0714" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 21:58:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm in awe of her? I was never infatuated with you? This is all not true Sara.... Youre making this something it's not</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0715" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 22:00:40 UTC">
      <body>No like it seems like you just like admire her in a way you never did me? Idk, I'm bein crazy huh? I'm just having sad days which sucks cuz thought they were over hah. Anyway, was just wondering how yiu would feel in my situation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0716" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 22:02:40 UTC">
      <body>I'd feel weird initially, and then grow to accept it. It's a weird thought at first, but understandable. I obviously admired you greatly Sara. Don't put yourself down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0717" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 22:06:44 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I'm just waiting for the acceptance part hah. Alright, well I'm gonna go to class now. Idk I just want someone, you know?  I'm really happy for you though (: just I wanna be happy too </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0718" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 22:10:52 UTC">
      <body>Thanks Johnny, that means a lot. Hah that made me really upset actually when you wanted me to be alone forever or whatever. You deserve someone amazing too(: an thanks for beig there for me ad bein a good friend</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0719" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 22:11:12 UTC">
      <body>I want you to be happy and want you have someone else Sara. I revoke that old awkward comment on saying i don't want you to have someone. You deserve someone great Sara. Ciao for now </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0721" participant="131065" time="2012-02-27 22:15:28 UTC">
      <body>Anytime and you the same Sara. Ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0722" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 22:44:55 UTC">
      <body>Ughhh sorry to hit you up again I swear it's the fuxking last time, but I'm blanking: what was that graffiti/tattoo artist yiu like who worked at a tat shop in sf, one of the workers at tried and true had a tat by him? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0724" participant="131019" time="2012-02-27 22:46:07 UTC">
      <body>Perfect</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0725" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 06:49:47 UTC">
      <body>Mmk I sent it, there a few sentences I am confused by. You can Skype me and we can figure em out or whatever. Sorry if I come off mean, I'm really sick and feel like shit and yeahhh yayyyy </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0726" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 06:51:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay cool, I'll prlly just be able to figure em out on my own and such. Thanks a lot!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0727" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 06:54:02 UTC">
      <body>Alrighty then, your call. I'm here if you get so massively bored that you feel like skyping your ex :P and it's fine, I mean I'm not like hunched over the toilet vomiting or anything, yeah no it's fine </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0728" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 06:57:15 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I don't think so. Last time I was sick for 3 weeks  :/ but yeah whatevs, have fun doin, stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0729" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 06:58:08 UTC">
      <body>Okay coolio! Hope you feel better Sara. But thanks for that and I'll keep it in mind </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0730" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:04:32 UTC">
      <body>Well why not get some rest and chill out and such?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0731" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:06:19 UTC">
      <body>Because I have to make a poster for tomorrow and I had to edit your paper. And I just wanna watch a movie with someone but I have no one so I'm just gonna do work yay my life</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0732" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:10:56 UTC">
      <body>Mmm well work is good to finish, but why not kick back and enjoy a chick flick and hit the hay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0733" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:11:37 UTC">
      <body>Wish</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0734" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:12:30 UTC">
      <body>Because I gotta finish work. And I'm tired of watching stuff alone. I'm really sad right now so I should stop texting you. And hah I forgot to wish. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0735" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:13:04 UTC">
      <body>Got it!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0736" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:15:12 UTC">
      <body>Ah hate when that happens. But feel better and I hope work goes well and sleep well okay. Ciao ciao Sara</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0737" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:16:04 UTC">
      <body>Thanks, bye</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0738" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:18:02 UTC">
      <body>Let me know if you ever wanna Skype or talk, btw, cuz I'm gonna try and stop asking you cuz nothing ever comes of it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0739" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:27:45 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I know, everyone says that. It's so profound. I just want someone who will just sit and not be okay with me. Everyone is always fine. It's like I'm the only one who's fucked up sometimes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0740" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:28:00 UTC">
      <body>Okay for sure, in time things will get better Sara. I hope you feel better.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0741" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:30:08 UTC">
      <body>You're not alone sara. It's a tough time, idk what to say. I think you gotta do this on your own inna way.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0742" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:31:48 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, you're fine! Everyone's fine! And of course I have to do this alone, its not like I have someone. My someone left. And I'm on my own and like yeah I'm glad we're friends but you never wanna talk to me so like whatever. Maybe I'm just kidding myself </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0743" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:34:12 UTC">
      <body>Yeah sorry, I don't wanna fight with you. I just like, don't think you want this. But you won't tell me what you want so I just don't know anymore</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0744" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:40:48 UTC">
      <body>I talk to you every day Sara... Idk what to tell you. I wana be your friend.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0745" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:43:01 UTC">
      <body>Alright well I dont wanna fight. And clearly I just still am confused. And you never initiate talking, so idk what to say. I'm just not gonna initiate it anymore. Like I'll be here if you need me and you know, you wont unless it's for editing. But yeah id</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0746" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:47:12 UTC">
      <body>Okay, not going to fight with you. I'll ttyl Sara. Ciao for now.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0747" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 07:48:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm not fighting! That's the point! I'm saying that I just try really hard with you and like don't really get anything. I mean the last 3 times I asked you to Skype you declined. My point is, like balls in your court. I'm not mad at you, and not trying to</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0748" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 07:49:20 UTC">
      <body>Okay good night. I'm gonna start fighting, and gimme a chance maybe to intiate ya know. Ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0749" participant="131065" time="2012-02-28 10:05:52 UTC">
      <body>Sleepy time, no more words for me. Ciao and goodnight. I hope you sleep well. I wished you'd get better btw. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0750" participant="131019" time="2012-02-28 10:07:04 UTC">
      <body>Ah Johnny :/ good night, sweet dreams </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0751" participant="131019" time="2012-02-29 05:57:07 UTC">
      <body>Hey so I want to tell you some things as a friend that you probably won't want to hear(nothing rude or anything), so you should let me know if you want to hear them, and if you do I urge you to come into it with an open mind, just take them as they are an</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0752" participant="131065" time="2012-02-29 06:02:40 UTC">
      <body>Okay, how do you want to deliver these things to me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0753" participant="131019" time="2012-02-29 06:03:15 UTC">
      <body>Kinda long so Skype, but I mean really it doesn't have to be today. Like you really should be open when you hear them. Honestly you can wait til spring break. I just think someone should tell you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0754" participant="131065" time="2012-02-29 06:09:04 UTC">
      <body>Okay, well I think we should do it maybe tmrw? Like around 9/10? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0755" participant="131019" time="2012-02-29 06:11:19 UTC">
      <body>Yup that is fine. Idk if I'll be able to then, might have to be a little later, but yeah tmrw is fine (: it's really nothing bad, it's just like things I don't think your friends or your parents have ever or will ever say, and i mean you're family so I'm </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0756" participant="131065" time="2012-02-29 06:17:36 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds like a plan, I'll tty then and we can figure it out. Hope you're well too, ciao for now</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0757" participant="131019" time="2012-02-29 06:18:24 UTC">
      <body>Sounds good, I shall talk to you tomorrow. Good night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0758" participant="131065" time="2012-02-29 06:21:52 UTC">
      <body>Night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0759" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 01:25:46 UTC">
      <body>I think I can talk whenever tonight, but 1030/11 is prlly better. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0760" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 01:29:09 UTC">
      <body>Sweet deal</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0761" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 01:29:36 UTC">
      <body>Let's shoot for that! Sounds good</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0762" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:07:34 UTC">
      <body>730 dinner?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0763" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:08:00 UTC">
      <body>Wrong person...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0764" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:08:51 UTC">
      <body>My bad, wouldn't have even noticed tho thanks or sayin something</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0765" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:10:08 UTC">
      <body>For sure. I keep having six vowels and one consonant... Ffffuuuuu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0766" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:11:03 UTC">
      <body>I keep having 7 consonants. So I swapped. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0767" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:12:16 UTC">
      <body>So weak... </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0768" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:15:16 UTC">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0769" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:15:59 UTC">
      <body>￼Come on....</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0770" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:16:32 UTC">
      <body>I gave up smoking cigs for kent</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0771" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:16:32 UTC">
      <body>Lent*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0772" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:16:32 UTC">
      <body>￼Roite...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0774" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 02:22:56 UTC">
      <body>I'm too sick to drink... Feel like shit. But I'll ttyl! Hw time ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0775" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 02:23:43 UTC">
      <body>Damn Johnny :/ I'm so sorry. Let me know if you wanna talk earlier so you can sleep early</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0776" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 05:48:32 UTC">
      <body>Hey I'm gonna smoke a cig real quick, lemme know when you're down for Skype</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0777" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 05:49:11 UTC">
      <body>Hokayyy give me 5</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0778" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 05:49:52 UTC">
      <body>Right when you done lez do it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0779" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 05:49:52 UTC">
      <body>Word up.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0780" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 20:29:46 UTC">
      <body>Yo sorry for the petty comment. I know it's not fair of me but the fact that she's all posting music on your wall is really getting to me, so I decided to criticize it. In my defense it's not a very good song...but still I'm just petty and yeah. Enjoy you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0781" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 20:43:44 UTC">
      <body>Okay well sounds good, I shall ttyl. Just it's not necessary for you to say anything. Like its not nice, and I don't need criticism regarding anyone's music taste... Ciao</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0782" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 20:46:17 UTC">
      <body>Also, sorry for the spam, just gotta get the last thoughts out before I actually try not to talk to you. I hope you took what I said seriously last night even though I am your ex and you can't really disconnect that from me. I wasn't saying you shouldn't </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0783" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 20:47:33 UTC">
      <body>And yeah I know, that's why I apologized. You also said actually a lot of mean things last night that I just let you get by with. So if you wanna be bitter that's fine, but don't say douchey shit to me if you can't take it. And that winky was supposed to </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0784" participant="131065" time="2012-03-01 20:54:24 UTC">
      <body>I accept your apology and everything, and okay. We both have trouble disconnecting things to have a friendly relationship ya know. These things will get better with time and im seriously taking into consideration what you told me. We shall be in some cont</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0785" participant="131019" time="2012-03-01 20:55:39 UTC">
      <body>Yes we do, but we will learn eventually. And that's good, I'm glad you are. I hope yours does too, bye Johnny</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0786" participant="131019" time="2012-03-02 18:32:09 UTC">
      <body>Something really bothered me that you said the other night. Do you want a really
Long email or a quick Skype sesh? I really need to get it off my chest</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0787" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 18:40:00 UTC">
      <body>Skype right now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0788" participant="131019" time="2012-03-02 18:41:39 UTC">
      <body>10 mins?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0789" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 18:42:08 UTC">
      <body>Ok</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0790" participant="131019" time="2012-03-02 18:49:39 UTC">
      <body>Okay text me when you're done hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0791" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 18:50:40 UTC">
      <body>I gotta poop sorry hah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0792" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 18:50:40 UTC">
      <body>Will dew!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0793" participant="131019" time="2012-03-02 18:59:45 UTC">
      <body>Rah hurry up you big pooper</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0794" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 19:01:20 UTC">
      <body>Skype u in five!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0795" participant="131065" time="2012-03-02 19:01:20 UTC">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0796" participant="131019" time="2012-03-03 06:32:45 UTC">
      <body>￼Suck it. Enjoy your weekend! Do the art walk! Ciao ciao ciao ciao</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
