<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130703.0000" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:12:38 UTC">
      <body>Thinking about it we probably want to steal Tim's truck to move my bigger stuff not johns wimp ass truck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:14:12 UTC">
      <body>Tim traded in his big white truck and now has a whimp ass Ranger.  Same size as John's and mine.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:14:25 UTC">
      <body>Damn him!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:14:38 UTC">
      <body>Gas will be going up because of the shit going on in Egypt.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:15:12 UTC">
      <body>So does a queen fit in the back of a wimp ass truck</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:15:12 UTC">
      <body>yes we stand it up on end and tie it down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:17:36 UTC">
      <body>K. I just need to convince people to come because I have couch one shelf thing mom said she wanted instead of me throwing away, my mini fridge and my bed. I think the shelf thing might fit in KarL but the rest needs truck love. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:18:03 UTC">
      <body>I've been trying to get John up here with the promise of pizza and wine but he doesn't care cuz he's on lock down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:18:44 UTC">
      <body>yeah he is the only $60k a year lock down guy I know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:20:04 UTC">
      <body>Right? And I have all the ingredients for the pizza and I have wine all he has to do is show up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:21:10 UTC">
      <body>he is a pussy what can I say,  his name is johnny girl</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:23:29 UTC">
      <body>I forget that sometimes I admit. Maybe ill convince him for this Saturday</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:25:33 UTC">
      <body>good luck, sometimes he complains about gas to go to woody</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:27:05 UTC">
      <body>I just texted him. I have 5 pizza crusts he could eat til he bursts! And 4.5 bottles of wine right now. If Amanda doesn't come over I should still have 3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:28:00 UTC">
      <body>might need to throw in some azullitas</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="134904" time="2013-07-03 15:28:00 UTC">
      <body>what sucks is your american eagle credit card bill came in and it says pay up bitch!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:28:48 UTC">
      <body>Yup I can throw down some azulitas. Just saying I'm kind of a fun person even if gas sucks</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="134866" time="2013-07-03 15:38:30 UTC">
      <body>I did yesterday :p take that AE bill</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
