<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140805.0020" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-05 22:50:59 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>OMG!!! Meant to text you to say me and Joanna were in the bathroom today. I was done and washing my hands. She was busy in the stall.......FARTING!!!!! T</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-05 22:51:01 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>WO BIG ONES!!!!!!! I ran out!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-05 23:26:27 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lmbo!!! That made my day</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-06 18:04:02 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>.  They leave at 1:00 and lunch is done at 2:00/ 2:10!!!!! Pigliacelli and I get pissed!!! Janice and Kelly don't say ANYTHING.  I love CCP.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-06 19:01:57 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>On top of that he is scheduled for every other sat. He was off last sat and off not this sat but the following one.  Why is it that yesterday he puts himself as off this sat too. That's 3 sats in a row so im covering his shift again. And then today he schedules off the 18th &amp; 19th. Mon &amp; tues which means I have to close mon instead of leaving at 5 id leave at 730. And tues instead of working 10-730 it would be 7:30-730. F that. He couldn't do my shift in an urgent time im not doing his just bec he makes his own rules.  Idk what the company is going to do but I am not covering for him. Everyone can just be locked out until I arrive lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-06 19:03:00 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And after my aunt passed my cousin passed. He took off that extra thurs before his vacation knowing I now had another funeral to attend. I had 4 family deaths in 7 days and that was the selfish stunt he pulled. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-06 19:06:20 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>LMBO @ everyone can be locked out til u arrive!!!!!! WHAT IS THAT MANS PROBLEM?!  ..... he's taking you fir granted. Does he have that much PTO time???? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-06 19:06:22 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Dang!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-06 19:07:21 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Stick it to him, Michelle!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-06 21:42:54 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He has been taking me for granted since day. Weve had meeting with the higher ups and everything but he is a complete kiss ### so they like him. Except im a better worker so they have to like me too... I send you those texts on break, get back to my desk to see an email from him that he is now off tomorrow!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-08-06 21:43:58 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And next friday which means now he is cutting into my other job bec I deliver on fridays abd have to be there by 4. We do get a good amount of pto but I don't understand how he still has so much left!  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-08-06 21:44:26 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>What???!!!! Who can you complain to?/?.... is he about to quit??? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-08-06 21:44:47 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But like I said ill be requesting a review abd demanding a raise for filling a managerial position</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-08-06 21:45:37 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Nope I won't complain.  Ill denied a raise or they will lose their best employee.  And the director abd both drs will vouche for me that the office will fall apart without me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-08-06 21:45:46 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ill demand**</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-08-06 21:58:39 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And during my review all the crap he pulls taking advantage will come out.  When he requested off fri sat mon he went to miami. The director did not know that he was off because all he had to do was have the days approved by the HR department... so when he took off thurs too unexpectedly he lied and said he had a dr appt. I told the director that no he just didn't feel like coming in. So the director wasn't happy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-08-06 22:00:21 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Wow!!!!! He's a total ###!!!!! When will you find out about your test results?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-08-06 22:01:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Oh!!! Got the letter yesterday!  Passed!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-08-06 22:01:28 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Means another waiting list but that's better than not being on the list at all lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-08-06 22:03:17 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>True.</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

