<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130607.0060" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-06-07 18:16:00 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol yea I got a write and noticed at but I'm still working. I can tell you what happened when I see you</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-06-07 18:16:11 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>A write up*</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-06-07 18:17:11 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay good. I thought so but I saw a negative facebook status of yours from yesterday and was like... Oh god</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-06-07 18:38:40 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea bec both managers were in the meeting with me and the director.  I was ganged up on. When I told the director things the damon did he denied it. When bj asked sab if it was true she denied it as well even tho she witnessed it happen.  Bj said he trusts their word over mine</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-06-07 18:39:46 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>So I'm hurt that sab lied against me. Damon I expect that, he is a pathological liar... but I'm more stressed over now having a reputation with the director as a liar.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-06-07 18:42:16 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Are you serious?? I can't believe I just read that. I really thought shed have you're back after what you said</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-06-07 18:45:30 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I know same... I feel so backstabbed. But both drs found out what happened and they were so outraged that both called bj defending me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-06-07 18:51:09 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Oh okay so you had the doctors on your side?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-06-07 18:56:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea. Dr jim (who hates everyone btw) heard what happened and was so mad that he called bj just to tell him how grea t I am</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-06-07 18:57:15 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay that's good to hear</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-06-07 18:57:16 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Told bj that he just wanted to put it out there that I'm the best either and whenever I run the office everything goes smoothly but when damon is in change there are issues</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-06-07 18:57:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea I know</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-06-07 18:58:27 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Good haha</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

