<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130615.0025" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 06:02:36 UTC">
      <body>HAHAHAHAHA YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW BADLY THAT MADE ME LAUGH... Twice. Saw it last night, forgot, saw it again still made me laugh super hard. Guess who came into my restaurant tonight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 07:45:41 UTC">
      <body>Who?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:17:46 UTC">
      <body>Cho daddy and Susan and some homies. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 08:18:36 UTC">
      <body>O them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:19:34 UTC">
      <body>Hahahahah the most awkward thing happened (of course)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 08:21:12 UTC">
      <body>What..?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:07 UTC">
      <body>They were like guess what?!? I'm like what they are like we are grandparents!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:18 UTC">
      <body>And your dad goes, it's not Kyle </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:29 UTC">
      <body>And I'm like ha...haha yeah</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:38 UTC">
      <body>And Susan goes don't worry it's not Kyle!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:46 UTC">
      <body>And I'm like HAHA YEAH </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:27:54 UTC">
      <body>And she goes it's my oldest son</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:28:10 UTC">
      <body>And I'm like oh that's great congradulations!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 08:28:19 UTC">
      <body>Yeah they were my table by the way</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 13:05:26 UTC">
      <body>Wow, they are so subtle huh. Hope they weren't too much of a handful</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 17:30:52 UTC">
      <body>Hahaha no they were totally fine. Just awkward. Have you noticed how Susan will say exactly everything your dad says like 1 minute right after him? Haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 17:43:28 UTC">
      <body>Susan doesn't do much or see anyone but him, so that's not surprising. She's a bit of a shell I think.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 18:01:03 UTC">
      <body>Haha that's a really good description for her. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 18:01:15 UTC">
      <body>How are ye?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 18:30:58 UTC">
      <body>I'm good. Mark took me to a ridiculous crossfit work out this morning so I feel great. Now drinkin a beer with him hanging. How are you doing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 18:39:55 UTC">
      <body>Oh god..... Please don't turn into one of those crossfit junkies. Please please please. What you actually are having a Saturday!!?! Haha that's awesome though, sounds like you are living the life! I just got moes and Vic's with slime and five. Made 320 last night and have a new way better job so I feel pretty great too. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 20:05:26 UTC">
      <body>Haha crossfit is great! But there are definitely some people that are a little way too into it. Im btw projects at work, so I'm pretty free after normal hours. 320?! That's pretty sweet dude, grats. Good to hear things are going great!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 20:13:00 UTC">
      <body>Haha I know! I love the work out style, that's exactly what I do. But there are these groups that wear matching shirts and go out to eat together at my restaurant or whatever and its like 20 of them in their "CROSSFIT BROOMFIELD STUDIO 5" shirts like we are sooooo much better than you because we do CROSSFIT. Haha. Hell yeah! That's awesome, perfect timing for summertiiime. Yeah it was a killer night. I'll start brassiere ten ten Tuesday and then that will be a normal night haha. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 20:39:19 UTC">
      <body>They definitely cone off that way. But they're cool as hell after the workout when they fucking embarrass you but are super supportive. Competitive but cool. Wow, you'll be making more money than me!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="134847" time="2013-06-15 20:50:07 UTC">
      <body>Haha yeah I can believe that. :) sounds like you're making new friends!!! Haha noooo, how much do you make a month?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="134862" time="2013-06-15 20:53:08 UTC">
      <body>Not really, was my first go ha. Still scared of x fit haha. Plus I don't like some of their stuff. Wow! Get personal! I take home 3300$ a month</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="134847" time="2013-06-16 06:08:36 UTC">
      <body>Haha what didn't you like? Sooorrryyyy was just curious!!! Hmmmm well I guess I kinda will be haha now I feel like a dick... But I am gonna be working hard. Fine dining is a whole new ball game. I'm so stoked to work with people who actually give a shit. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="134862" time="2013-06-16 06:12:48 UTC">
      <body>I didn't like the using your momentum to get more reps. Seems like cheating.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="134847" time="2013-06-16 16:55:19 UTC">
      <body>Totally is cheating. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="134847" time="2013-06-16 16:56:29 UTC">
      <body>I've never done xfit, I've just heard about it from Shelby. I do my own circuit training and I'm super duper strong. ;P happy Father's Day to your daddy and Susan's son!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="134862" time="2013-06-16 23:46:00 UTC">
      <body>They have a different goal I think, they really work against the clock so you go for speed. They do none cheating work outs too. Thanks, Ill pass that one! He just finished kicking my ass on a 35mi mountain bike ride.@</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:38:12 UTC">
      <body>You think I can get those lights before Thursday?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 19:40:39 UTC">
      <body>Wait sorry forgot to respond properly to the 35 mi ride 0_o wow. I love biking though. And yes of course!!!! I just quit my job so I'll have lots of time while I'm starting training. :) maybe later tonight or tomorrow evening we can meet up?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:42:52 UTC">
      <body>After that ride I do not. Haha. I'm gonna be busy tomorrow night, so tonight would be best if that's cool</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 19:51:20 UTC">
      <body>Yeah sounds good let me know when yous home!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:52:10 UTC">
      <body>I moved to broomfield so maybe when I get done at work would be more convenient</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 19:53:26 UTC">
      <body>What!!! When did that happen? Yeah! My casa es on 19th and canyon!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:54:15 UTC">
      <body>End of may I moved. Ok cool. I'll call you when I'm in the area</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 19:55:24 UTC">
      <body>How come? You live alone then? Okay! Any idea around what time?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:56:42 UTC">
      <body>Sam wanted to live in boulder, I didn't want to live with Sam haha. No, I live with kev and Mitch. Kevs parents flipped the house, its way too nice. Uh, 530 ish.@</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 19:59:35 UTC">
      <body>Actually 6</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 20:07:31 UTC">
      <body>Wow that's awesome! That sounds like your ideal situation. Okay sounds good!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 20:08:32 UTC">
      <body>It'll work out I think. Living with kev could get interesting. I'll call you later then.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 20:10:08 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah..., what are you worried about most? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 20:27:54 UTC">
      <body>Despising him haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 21:16:15 UTC">
      <body>Haha oh yeah. That could happen. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 21:44:21 UTC">
      <body>It will happen to some extent. Always does for me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 21:45:07 UTC">
      <body>Yeah that sucks. I don't feel even a hint of that with Casey. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 21:47:33 UTC">
      <body>You have to.have your own stuff going on. Can't hang out every day, it just is too much. For me at least. Especially with friends.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 21:50:38 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I agree. We are so busy we hardly see each other haha like I want to hang out with her more hahaha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 21:52:48 UTC">
      <body>That's the best situation to be in. Unless you don't have much going on, like Sam and I. Never saw her, still she drove me crazu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 21:54:29 UTC">
      <body>Hahah that was rough. I'm so happy I'm staying here in the fall. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 21:55:23 UTC">
      <body>That's awesome. I'm sure it'll be a great time</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 23:13:24 UTC">
      <body>I'm going to dinner with Casey and her dad... If I'm not home by six I'll just bring the lights to you later? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="134862" time="2013-06-17 23:15:22 UTC">
      <body>I've got a lot of work to do, so ill still be in boulder</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="134847" time="2013-06-17 23:35:26 UTC">
      <body>Okay sounds good </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="134862" time="2013-06-18 01:16:34 UTC">
      <body>I'm finished at work. Think you'll be available soon?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="134847" time="2013-06-18 01:23:46 UTC">
      <body>Yeah headed home soon...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="134847" time="2013-06-18 01:39:28 UTC">
      <body>Sorry we will be there in like 15 is that okay?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="134862" time="2013-06-18 01:42:44 UTC">
      <body>Yea that's fine, i just got there. On the north side of canyon</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="134847" time="2013-06-18 01:47:59 UTC">
      <body>Not 4, 5 haha</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="134862" time="2013-06-18 01:48:40 UTC">
      <body>Ok. I'll hang out in front</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="134847" time="2013-06-18 01:49:06 UTC">
      <body>Okay :)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
