<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130923.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-09-23 22:46:34 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Holy shit! Students are back!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-09-23 22:50:22 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>I know, they're EVERYWHERE!  I just left my fitness assessment. Basically I have nowhere to go but up as long as I can work out without falling over, which is still in question. :/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-09-23 23:03:41 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Ha! It will be good to get a plan of attack. What's that saying? "A journey of a 100 miles always begins with the first step." By now ur well past step 1.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-09-23 23:04:09 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Yay!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-09-23 23:18:29 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>I know, I just don't know where to start. I knew I was in bad shape but seeing exactly how bad is hugely discouraging. I'm so embarrassed</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-09-24 01:14:55 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>I can understand how u feel but don't beat yourself up. Maybe you aren't in the shape u want to be in right now but u r making a change and that takes time. You have nothing to feel embarrassed about. You should be proud of yourself for taking this step... Not to mention the hundreds of other things you should be proud of too!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-09-24 02:09:35 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>I'm trying to be positive. Not easy for me though, you know that's not really my area ;)   I still need to schedule an orientation session so I know how to use the equipment, then maybe we can compare schedules and come up with some joint workout times?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-09-24 02:37:21 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>That sounds great! I still have to schedule my orientation too. I'm hoping to do it this week. I'll let u know when I go. I'll try to help you out with the positive thinking. Sometimes it takes another person to remind u of how awesome u are!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-09-24 15:40:07 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Please do let me know when yours is... Maybe we can even do it together?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-09-24 16:50:56 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>I scheduled my part 2 of the assessment for Thurs at 8:30 AM. I ran into ######## and she said they like to do this part individually but we could do the walk through together.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-09-24 16:51:47 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>I also registered for swim classes in Nov.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-09-24 17:49:24 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Hmm... Are you comfortable doing the walk through together? I can definitely schedule a separate one</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-09-24 17:53:42 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Sure. That isn't a problem at all. I just didn't realize the walk through was separate from whatever the 2nd part of the assessment is. I guess on Thurs ######## will go through whatever plan she devised for me and then we can schedule the walk through.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2013-09-24 18:06:05 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>Ok, cool.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2013-09-24 18:30:52 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Awesome! So do u know when u go in for your Part 2?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2013-09-24 18:40:35 UTC" participant="152374">
      <body>I don't have part 2, I only did the assessment that was included in my membership package</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2013-09-24 18:44:28 UTC" participant="153472">
      <body>Ah... Ok. Now this is making sense. Well, I'll let you know how my part 2 goes and then we can schedule the walk through. Prob sometime early next week will work for me, if it works for u...</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

