<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20120523.0001" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="131063" time="2012-05-23 01:42:40 UTC">
      <body>Ryan decided just now that he wants to sublet, better late than never I guess.... I'll have him meet Emily later this week if she's down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131019" time="2012-05-23 22:39:36 UTC">
      <body>I think Emily is fine with that by the way, just talk to Ryan and figure out if he has furniture. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 00:51:30 UTC">
      <body>I already talked to Emily and Rebecca yesterday so that's chill. Ryan's just pissing me off, he's "looking at other places to and will let me know soon".</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 00:51:32 UTC">
      <body>He said it's about the rent though, so he's gonna talk to his parents about it when he gets home Friday and he'll know by then</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 00:52:55 UTC">
      <body>Okay fuck him tell him he has until the 31st to decide yes or no im so sick of this bullshit he is paying half price here </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 00:55:49 UTC">
      <body>I told him earlier today that he has until memorial today or he's out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 00:56:21 UTC">
      <body>It's a bummer were desperate :P but seriously come on like he's just being obnoxious</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 18:47:32 UTC">
      <body>He'll definitely be staying from June 4-Aug 10 for $600/month</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 18:48:53 UTC">
      <body>Okay, how does that work for August then?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 18:49:04 UTC">
      <body>And what's the deal with furniture?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 18:50:57 UTC">
      <body>He'll just pay a little over 2 month's rent since that's how long he'll be staying and he's gonna get some bedroom furniture for himself that he may end </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 18:51:06 UTC">
      <body>up leaving in august</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 18:52:18 UTC">
      <body>Mmk well that's tight yay! Also we all need to get bank of America so that we can transfer money to Emily over the summer</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 18:53:40 UTC">
      <body>K I'll get on that, thanks for telling me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 18:54:45 UTC">
      <body>Unless you can online transfer to wells in which case you would have to transfer the full summers amount of your rent to Rebecca like now for her to take out and give to Emily. But idk</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="131063" time="2012-05-24 18:56:55 UTC">
      <body>Nvm, wells fargo can transfer money directly to b of a accounts, I just checked. But I'll have the cash ready on time!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="131019" time="2012-05-24 18:57:46 UTC">
      <body>Oh sick! Life just got way easy</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
