<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20150321.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2015-03-21 20:53:28 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2015-03-21 20:53:32 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>on amtrak</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2015-03-21 20:53:34 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>getting v excited</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2015-03-21 20:53:45 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>in great mood despite solar flares (did mom send you the article). how are u?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2015-03-21 20:55:09 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Good good good full of happiness and ideas bc you are coming!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2015-03-21 20:57:03 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body/>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2015-03-21 21:31:10 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2015-03-21 21:31:43 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2015-03-21 21:37:10 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Spacing closet </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2015-03-21 21:37:26 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Spackling </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2015-03-21 21:47:53 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Gorgeous!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2015-03-21 22:57:10 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>18j?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2015-03-21 22:57:16 UTC" participant="152212">
      <body>Or 8j?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2015-03-22 13:14:46 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>￼￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2015-03-22 14:03:30 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>￼</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2015-03-22 17:19:51 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I threw my back out just before leaving by literally shifting in my seat while sitting down</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2015-03-22 17:21:13 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Hey, funny story.  About a week ago my rib, almost completely healed, starting hurting a LOT again.  Felt it "clicking."  Went to a doc, and he said it's a break and the two sides are rubbing past each other.  Neat, I broke it twice in the same place!  Not even sure how I did it!

But the good news is that he recommended continuing to do EVERYTHING, including kiteboarding (albeit with rigging some foam around the problem).  He says the bone rubbing actually encourages healing (maybe chemical signal?) and keeping moving through full range of motion, despite pain, is a good thing.  I choose to believe all that.

Doc thought I was stupid to request an x-ray, which he said told him nothing.  He said when people report clicking, it's definitely a break.  Sure enough, he couldn't explain anything on the xray.  He said, "Well, it could have broken in the same place or somewhere else."</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2015-03-22 17:23:21 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Do not go gentle into that good night.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2015-03-22 17:27:19 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>So I did it…and solo’d again in a power plane for the first time in about 40 (FORTY) years.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2015-03-22 17:27:57 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Got a horrible upper back wrenching, seeing doc Monday, haven't gotten much sleep because I yell in pain all night!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2015-03-22 17:32:56 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Thank you!
I will set this in motion.  THis is just too pathetic.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2015-03-22 17:33:41 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Worst day/night yet.  Lots of spasms, crawling. Taking every drug.  Anti-spasm drugs are totally useless!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2015-03-22 17:34:52 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Back:  gave up on bed after midnight last night because it was too painful and went down to Studio and slept on the chair.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2015-03-22 17:35:38 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>GREAT idea re: blood test.  I'm asking my doc right now.  I have years of baseline to compare it with. What dosage of nsaids do you take per day?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2015-03-22 17:36:18 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>So I convinced my doc to order an MRI (which I think I'll pay for).   He says there's nothing he'd see in there besides a fracture or a tumor that'd be useful info (thanks for putting that idea in my head!) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2015-03-22 17:37:20 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Getting app't with endocrinologist.  Will be fun to compare drugs.  FATS!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2015-03-22 17:38:59 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Hey, the guy came and set up the bed.  Good, because last night was painful.  It's neat! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2015-03-22 17:40:11 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Back was good till I sneezed suddenly and didn't have time  to brace properly.  Now I am having spasms again in middle of night; therefore lost a week or more of healing.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2015-03-22 17:40:41 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Owen heard me screaming tonight and came upstairs.  I could not get into my bed or move...but he couldn't help. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2015-03-22 17:41:40 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Hey, I'm standing more.   I told Owen it was a victory to use the crutch to make it across 3' with no supports to the bed and he said, "small steps, Dad, but steps."  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2015-03-22 17:42:32 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>It's about same as 3 weeks ago I think.  I get an X-ray tomorrow.  Doc is predicting there's another compression fracture.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2015-03-22 17:43:20 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Today pretty good day.  I'm taking ibuprofen again and timing it carefully to get some inflammation reduction yet keep dose to 1/2 Max or less.   It actually is the best drug out of like 10 I have around!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2015-03-22 17:44:20 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I think I've isolated and calibrated the most important drug and dosage that helps: good 'ole ibuprofen.  It appears to reduce inflammation enough to stop the spasms IF I take 1000mg in 24 hours.   If I do 800mg, no cigar.  All the other pain killers and anti-spasm muscle relaxers do NOTHING compared to it.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2015-03-22 17:45:51 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>So I'm hoping the cancer doc is right that there's &lt;1% chance I have Myeloma. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2015-03-22 17:55:34 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Subject: RE: FM/Grierson/MyVM/Update:Moving better-saw the hematologist and neprhologist</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2015-03-22 17:56:33 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Biopsy is tomorrow at 1pm</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2015-03-22 17:57:20 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Ddoc told Julie there wasn't enough fluid, so analysis will be harder, have to be done with the bone sample they also took.  said it was unusual, but couldn't tell us if it meant anything to it have enough fluid or didn't want to. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2015-03-22 17:58:40 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I actually broke another rib. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2015-03-22 17:59:41 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Just wanna suggest that a friend comes with you for test results. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2015-03-22 18:01:31 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I go in tomorrow for a bunch of x rays, a "bone survey." </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2015-03-22 18:02:56 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Hey, new trial, hot off the presses, now being tried in humans:
http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2014/09/spread-of-multiple-myeloma-halted-in-mice/
If it hasn't spread to ALL my bones, this'd be the ticket for me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2015-03-22 18:04:26 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Sounds perfect!  You move fast!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2015-03-22 18:05:40 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I go in an hour early tomorrow for a "teach" about side effects of valcade. That sounds alarming.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2015-03-22 18:06:41 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>I'll ask Chatta what I can do about lessening bone fragility during this RVD course. (An exoskeleton?)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2015-03-22 18:07:11 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>We told the kids, unexpectedly good session</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" time="2015-03-22 18:09:37 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Bone marrow transplant is definitely required…that'll come after 6 cycles of this prelim chemo of 3 weeks each, or I guess 4.5 months, unless I'm getting it wrong.  Then it's the BIG TIME chemo.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" time="2015-03-22 18:10:38 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>It has suddenly occurred to me that the only reason I got the bone marrow biopsy was because I was worried about my kidneys from ibuprofen and you mentioned you get tested.  I immediately asked for some kidney and blood tests to be done, and they were outliers, and that's when they sent me to the hematologist.   (Although I let that be delayed for more than a week).  They wouldn't have otherwise! So you have already helped big time.   And we have learned yet again that we have to do it all ourselves.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" time="2015-03-22 18:12:21 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Below is an amazing white paper from Eli who looks like he had a free period today.  It's amazing because several of his questions are EXACTLY the ones I am in the process of formulating.  And I needed the dollar number today.   Can you believe it?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" time="2015-03-22 18:16:11 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>The  revlamid starts tomorrow.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" time="2015-03-22 18:17:42 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>RE: Three thoughts</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" time="2015-03-22 18:18:35 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>1) I know that you have your friend on SAAS board. But if he cannot get you to see a high up specialist  soon, I am thinking of other people who are in powerful positions, or might know someone in a powerful position who can make calls. 
governor
past board of Active Voice
past board of Cisco
Flip?
Bob D?
Who else?
And /or can Dr Chatta speed it up?
2) Also, I was thinking about you getting lined up for a potential clinical study, and this occurred to me: if your case is unique, then there are doctors out there who might actually be looking for YOU for a clinical study. So it is in THEIR interest to see you. 
And what if Dr Chatta said, “I might have a candidate for one of your clinical trials.”?? 
3) Would a back brace help while you are feeling fragile?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" time="2015-03-22 18:23:15 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>OK I know this is overwhelming but we need to be knowledgeable about all options:
http://www.myelomabeacon.com/opinion/2011/03/28/kadian-morphine-a-little-known-pain-drug/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" time="2015-03-22 18:23:48 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>In ambulance in way to ER virginia mason.  Not sure what this'll accomplish but Chatta really advised it. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" time="2015-03-22 18:24:39 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>It would be best to have the HLA typing done through SCCA. They have special procedures and an expanded testing panel.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" time="2015-03-22 18:25:59 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Dr. Becker and Bard - 

I am zipping this out as the referring doc for Bard and by way of doing some coordination of care.  Bard has an appt tomorrow with Dr. Becker (check-in 10:30). Bard is presently hospitalized at Virginia Mason for control of back pain due to a T-12 Compression Fracture.  He is pretty uncomfortable and will not be about to travel to SCCA to his appointment.

I would however, very much like for Bard to have an initial conversation with Dr. Becker.  

Pam - would you be amenable to a phone conversation with Bard in lieu of a face to face visit? If you are in the neighborhood you could swing by and see him at VM but I bet you are pretty busy - so how about a phone call tomorrow?  If that works please give Bard a time and a number to call.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" time="2015-03-22 18:27:29 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>My notes with our call to dr Becker.  </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" time="2015-03-22 18:31:12 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Fwd: A few quick questions as I begin cycle 2 Tomorrow</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" time="2015-03-22 18:33:37 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Yes, we gotta do the research and we have some immediate ones will write later about and yes you can help!
Love your optimism and you!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" time="2015-03-22 18:35:14 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Re: Some good blood tests, I think (and log in for VM)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" time="2015-03-22 18:40:12 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Re: WINIFRED NYC-SEATTLE 25 DEC 2014 Yay can't wait!! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" time="2015-03-22 18:45:30 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Non-Secretory Myeloma: A Clinician’s Guide | Cancer Network 
http://www.cancernetwork.com/hematologic-malignancies/non-secretory-myeloma-clinician%E2%80%99s-guide/page/0/1</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" time="2015-03-22 18:48:18 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>John Conner talk notes</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" time="2015-03-22 18:52:44 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Fwd: Daily Drug Developments from BioPharm Insight I think Greg is telling me to subscribe to this.   Seems way too business-focused.  But there appear to be some new MM trials reported, which I can't access unless I'm a subscriber.   Maybe you could sign up and filter?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" time="2015-03-22 18:55:04 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>http://www.myelomabeacon.com/news/2014/05/19/elotuzumab-breakthrough-therapy-designation-multiple-myeloma/</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" time="2015-03-22 18:56:26 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Becker said it's NOT non secretory, instead light chain, with possible amyloidosis affecting other organs like heart. She will find out. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" time="2015-03-22 18:59:00 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>"Again promising new antibodies specifically targeting myeloma cells are being developed and would become available within the next year or two:
Elotuzumab
Daratumumab”</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" time="2015-03-22 19:00:13 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>barbara's a mom of a couple kids at SAAS and was on the board.  She was the in-house attorney we hired at Active Voice.  Having a recent patient perspective about autologous at SCCA is THE GREATEST.   WIll try to talk to her husband Tim this week.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" time="2015-03-22 19:03:50 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>http://themmrf.org Guy who's rethinking always doing the autologous right off, Here's the abstract from his paper.
http://asheducationbook.hematologylibrary.org/content/2014/1/255.abstract Richardson
 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0075" time="2015-03-22 19:05:15 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>re: to Katy Giusti Small donation to your new fundraising initiative</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0078" time="2015-03-22 19:14:24 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>back on the bigger pain killers.   THought I might have to go to hosp again:  THe lower back thing, full on bad spasms again.   THis started Saturday,  andhasn't peaked yet.  Afraid to get into bed, because I know what happens when I wake up: bad spasms with yelling, etc.   Sure hope this gets better before you come!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0079" time="2015-03-22 19:15:47 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>My procedure in finding this was to google IMAGES of flow charts relating to multiple myeloma.

Then I went to the page that the image came from.  Here is the page that the flow chart I sent you came from: (May, 2010)

http://www.nature.com/nrclinonc/journal/v7/n5/fig_tab/nrclinonc.2010.31_F2.html</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0080" time="2015-03-22 19:17:58 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Date: December 23, 2014 at 4:17:21 PM PST
Subject: Happy Holidays!
Hi Everybody!
2014 can be summarized for us as:
“Good Times, Bad Times”</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0081" time="2015-03-22 19:24:23 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>EMERGENCY NUMBERS</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0083" time="2015-03-22 19:27:32 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Allogenic is currently the only way for me to survive past 5 years with odds of better than 35% according to the below. 
However, the phase 1 immunotherapy trials are trying to do the same thing. 
Timing is right! - See more at: http://www.cancerresearch.org/cancer-immunotherapy/impacting-all-cancers/multiple-myeloma#.dpuf</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0084" time="2015-03-22 19:28:27 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>MY GOALS FOR MY CANCER TREATMENT:
•Buy me 5 years of remission in order to get to phase 3 of new immunotherapy trials
•At least 4 of which are normal quality of life (i.e., transplant can cause maybe &gt;1 year of reduced quality or permanent)*
•Instead,  consider maintenance therapies to get to 5 years if there is a high probability that they will maintain the remission**
•Still harvest for autologous when M-protein down to best low plateau on current RVD or other cycle
•Still do bone marrow donor set up 
 
* physical AND mental. 
**  Assuming there's a fallback to another transplant if relapse</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0085" time="2015-03-22 19:29:40 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>RVD maintenance vs Stem Cell Transplant Trial for people &lt;= 65 years old https://clinicaltrials.gov/ct2/show/NCT01208662</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0086" time="2015-03-22 19:30:42 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Notes to go along with Goal statement:</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0087" time="2015-03-22 19:31:07 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Kathy more in depth answers to questions on Transplant vs no</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0088" time="2015-03-22 19:32:30 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>Personal face on the goals</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0089" time="2015-03-22 19:33:53 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>beta 2 microglobulin Another encouraging downtrend from Dr Chatta results</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0090" time="2015-03-22 19:34:55 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>beta 2 micro as a tumor marker test http://labtestsonline.org/understanding/analytes/beta-microglob/tab/test/
 </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0091" time="2015-03-22 19:35:58 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>RE: a thought re: making a patient profile for other doctors ; questions</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0092" time="2015-03-22 19:37:26 UTC" participant="152311">
      <body>RE: VERY ROUGH draft/thoughts for letter to Dr Becker You were busy on the plane!</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

