<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20110812.0002" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:15:06 UTC">
      <body>Hey martha. Been thinkin. Its hard for me to treat this whole thing as a secret because i dont want Katie to think i chose a side or that i betrayed her trust in any way when she does find out. So i beg you to tell her soon. Its only as big of a deal as you guys make it. :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:26:05 UTC">
      <body>I can offer my assurance that I'm doing my best to be respectful to you and yours and me.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:26:44 UTC">
      <body>Thank you. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:32:12 UTC">
      <body>This is a text from Sofie that I just got: Hey martha. Been thinkin. Its hard for me to treat this whole thing as a secret because i dont want Katie to think i chose a side or that i betrayed her trust in any way when she does find out. So i beg you to tell her soon. Its only as big of a deal as you guys make it. :-)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:32:38 UTC">
      <body>Sorry! Meant for you know who.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:33:44 UTC">
      <body>I figured. :-) are you giving it to him to talk bad of me?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:34:34 UTC">
      <body>No no no no. Giving it to him bc its his responsibility as much as mine to handle the situation</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:35:07 UTC">
      <body>I can't carry the burden alone. And it's all his fault anyway. ;)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:35:36 UTC">
      <body>Thats what i hoped. :-) i didnt mean to be dramatic i just want the best for everyone</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:36:02 UTC">
      <body>Haha exactly.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:36:55 UTC">
      <body>I completely agree and understand. Im very aware of all the complicated feelings involved.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:38:36 UTC">
      <body>Let me know if you know need anything. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:39:35 UTC">
      <body>I will. Thanks for everything sof. And sorry again for the text confusion. I respect your opinion greatly.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="135112" time="2011-08-12 19:40:44 UTC">
      <body>Not a problem. I know you do. Just needed to make sure. You know how this world can trick you.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="131839" time="2011-08-12 19:41:48 UTC">
      <body>Too well! &lt;3</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
