<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130612.0002" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 10:16:06 UTC">
      <body>Hey ya</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 10:16:54 UTC">
      <body>What's the story with u r username?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 10:24:01 UTC">
      <body>How are things today?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 11:45:38 UTC">
      <body>Haha so I'm pretty bad at picking creative usernames, and for some reason that line from the chorus of 'That's Not My Name' came to mind.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 11:49:01 UTC">
      <body>But I'm pretty good. Ran some errands and now off to see some friends. How about you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 11:57:26 UTC">
      <body>I'm at the coffee shop because there is no food at my house.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 11:57:26 UTC">
      <body>What errands did you take on today</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 12:21:40 UTC">
      <body>Just rode my bike home to do some work stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 13:15:41 UTC">
      <body>Oh I hate it when that happens. My mom stopped cooking when I went to college, so real food is often scarce when I'm home. I had to pick up stuff for myfriend's wedding on Saturday. What work do you do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 13:17:54 UTC">
      <body>All kinds of work some construction, art, linguistics, but the art is my favorite but doesn't pay to well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 13:19:26 UTC">
      <body>Do you like going to weddings</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:07:32 UTC">
      <body>Do you live with your mom? Do you cook now or does your mom cook?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:08:38 UTC">
      <body>I like to cook a lot but I don't have the time to do it as much as I like and in the summer when it's hot it's not as much fun to be in the kitchen</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 14:43:43 UTC">
      <body>Mm gotcha. Yea weddings are fun if people I know are going. I love cooking actually...I end up baking more when I have lots of time though. Well I just graduated from college and am home for part of the summer before grad school.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:45:52 UTC">
      <body>I never liked weddings that much until all my friends started getting married. Now I do like them most of the time.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:46:58 UTC">
      <body>It's cool that you like to bake, it can be difficult. I like to bake buttermilk biscuits but can't bake much more than that.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:47:32 UTC">
      <body>The biscuits are good though.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 14:47:53 UTC">
      <body>What r u going to grad school for?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 14:47:53 UTC">
      <body>Well yea..as a kid one is kinda just dragged along</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 15:15:35 UTC">
      <body>Biscuits are always a win. I'm going to get a master's in social work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 15:16:41 UTC">
      <body>Where are you from?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:17:06 UTC">
      <body>That's great</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:17:54 UTC">
      <body>Originally I'm from upstate ny. You?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:18:47 UTC">
      <body>I hear penn and smith have good social work programs for the east coast anyway</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 15:32:22 UTC">
      <body>Northern virginia. Yea I got into Penn and was considering it. I liked certain things about it for sure, but I ended up choosing Boston College. What kind of art do you do?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:35:25 UTC">
      <body>I make all kinds of art. Painting sculpture sound ... I am casting things from pet hair at the moment for part of an installation in a couple of weeks.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:46:05 UTC">
      <body>What kind stuff do you do in your spare time? Got any plans for this summer before you get loaded down with studies</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 15:55:01 UTC">
      <body>Oh wow, that is fascinating! In college I was in a chorus, but I probly won't do any formal singing from here on out. Yea I'm going to Brazil and argentina with family before my sister studies abroad and to Bermuda to see family. Are you taking any vacation?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:58:22 UTC">
      <body>I am taking a trip in July to Minneapolis to get a root canal so it's probably not going to be quite as exciting or fun as brazil and Argentina</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 15:59:34 UTC">
      <body>My friend was just in Argentina for a week with is family, dove hunting , of all things</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 15:59:55 UTC">
      <body>Ooh heck! Not fun. I actually just got my wisdom teeth taken out. Not quite the same, but still in the catgory of unpleasant.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 16:01:24 UTC">
      <body>No kidding! Never knew that was the thing to do in Argentina...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:41:40 UTC">
      <body>Ugg I got all 4 wisdom teeth out when 1 was impacted and it was an extreme experience</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:42:24 UTC">
      <body>Yeah I didn't know that about Argentina either</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:43:08 UTC">
      <body>What are your plans for brazil?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:43:34 UTC">
      <body>That sounds exciting</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 17:44:28 UTC">
      <body>Haha yea. I'm actually still taking pain killers because every once in a while the jaw still gets pretty sore. Amazon village, Rio, and Iguazu!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 17:44:28 UTC">
      <body>Can't wait</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 17:45:05 UTC">
      <body>Question: do you have any preferred convo partners in this study?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:45:17 UTC">
      <body>And why don't you think you'll sing anymore? Are you just over it? Or is it a time issue</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 17:45:17 UTC">
      <body>And if yes, do you ever get to talk to them?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:46:09 UTC">
      <body>Yes I do and I get to talk to them on occasion</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:47:28 UTC">
      <body>Just have your call partner set up their available time at a weird time like starting at 10:22 and you do the same.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:49:18 UTC">
      <body>The trick I think is to have a day off with no text time scheduled before the days you call up on so you are not still in the 24 hour conversation at thetime you and your friend signed up for.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 17:50:26 UTC">
      <body>Otherwise you will be stuck texting boring randos like me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 18:29:58 UTC">
      <body>I love singing, but there wont really be time for it with school, etc.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0046" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 18:30:24 UTC">
      <body>Ahhhhh you've really thought this out! That makes sense.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0047" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 18:30:56 UTC">
      <body>I need to work on the coordination of schedules better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0048" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 18:34:52 UTC">
      <body>Yeah the coordination doesn't work all the time but will probably work most of the time if you follow those rules.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0049" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 18:43:06 UTC">
      <body>So what kinda stuff do you like to sing? Gospel, punk, grindcore, rap, jazz, Gregorian chant, oratorio sung through vocoders or all of the above mashed up into one short bluegrass song?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0050" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 19:35:51 UTC">
      <body>Haha that would be intense. What do I LIKE to sing. Hmm, I mean, I guess to whatever you can harmonize easily enough to or just has good vocals in general. What do you listen to mostly?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0051" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 19:38:34 UTC">
      <body>Mostly, rock I guess probably 70s early metal stuff. But like most people I like a wide range of stuff.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0052" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 19:39:46 UTC">
      <body>How about you what do you listen to mostly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0053" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 19:42:41 UTC">
      <body>Electronic music mostly. And I like instrumental stuff and some more folksy stuff</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0054" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 19:46:53 UTC">
      <body>Do you ever watch arrested development? Have you seen the new season</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0055" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 19:57:47 UTC">
      <body>I saw through episode 7 but never got around to finishing the episode. I've seen random episodes from other seasons but not all the way through. Dis yousee all of season 4? What did you think?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0056" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:00:34 UTC">
      <body>I haven't seem the new season, that's what I wanted to ask you about because I've heard mixed reviews.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0057" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:00:34 UTC">
      <body>I was wondering if it was worth watching</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0058" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:03:25 UTC">
      <body>Ah. Well, the people who I watched it with (and i) thought that it was quite different from earlier seasons. It had a wackiness that is kinda hard yo describe. I had a harder time keeping up with what it was trying to do kinda</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0059" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:12:13 UTC">
      <body>But I also didn't finish the season, so I'm not sure how it tied together at the end...</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0060" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:12:13 UTC">
      <body>I like wacky, maybe I'll check it out.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0061" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:14:23 UTC">
      <body>In general I do too. There were definitely some really funny parts.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0062" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:17:58 UTC">
      <body>Do you know if it still has the same writers in season 4 do you? The writing was real smart and played the long game with a lot of jokes, it would be a shame if they tried to duplicate that with new writers.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0063" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:19:48 UTC">
      <body>I have no idea....I didn't hear anything of the sort, so my guess is that they are the same.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0064" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:21:22 UTC">
      <body>That's good to hear.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0065" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:21:22 UTC">
      <body>So what made you want to get into social work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0066" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:27:14 UTC">
      <body>Desire to do good in the world and use my Spanish skills for service; appreciation for its interdisciplinary nature, variety, and its stated values; and</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0067" participant="131451" time="2013-06-12 20:28:15 UTC">
      <body>its coherence with my faith</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0068" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:35:24 UTC">
      <body>Those are really good reasons!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0069" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:37:42 UTC">
      <body>It's nice to hear that people are still genuinely trying to do good out there, everything in the media seems to suggest the opposite.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0070" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:38:58 UTC">
      <body>It's nice to hear that you are so sure of what you want to do and it is helping people</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0071" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:41:59 UTC">
      <body>I don't think I could deal with the emotional wear and tear of a profession like that</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0072" participant="130518" time="2013-06-12 20:42:19 UTC">
      <body>You must be a very strong person</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0073" participant="131451" time="2013-06-13 01:11:23 UTC">
      <body>Well thanks, that is nice of you to say. I believe in the worthiness of the profession, although the world doesn't really value it. I will admit that myheart and my head tell me different things when it comes to whether I'm making a good decision. Nevertheless, like you said, I am sure that I want to help people.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0074" participant="130518" time="2013-06-13 08:32:39 UTC">
      <body>Well it's good that you are guided by your heart. Your head will most likely follow. ;)</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
