<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20130516.0019" medium="SMS" donated="false">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 13:09:41 UTC">
      <body>Hey how's it going?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 13:10:30 UTC">
      <body>Not too bad. How are things going with you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 13:12:46 UTC">
      <body>Alright, looking forward to some time off this weekend.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 13:50:18 UTC">
      <body>Do you work weekends?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 13:53:25 UTC">
      <body>Sorry, I was in the middle of responding to your last text and got sidetracked. I do not work weekends, but I will often do a lot of personal work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 13:53:52 UTC">
      <body>How bout you?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 13:55:52 UTC">
      <body>I usually have Saturday off but I'll wrk Sunday nights. Have two jobs. Personal work like projects/writing? Or more like errands</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 14:36:14 UTC">
      <body>Projects/writing kind of stuff. Are both your jobs FT, PT or a combo?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 14:38:04 UTC">
      <body>Full-time at a bar and PT elsewhere. It's a good combo but it can wear me out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 14:38:25 UTC">
      <body>Do you write fiction or what?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 14:42:23 UTC">
      <body>No, mostly music criticism/interviews, but I've tapered off from that a bit as I focus on working on music and video work.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 14:43:13 UTC">
      <body>Re: multiple jobs; I used to work 3 PT jobs and it got to be waaayy too much.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 14:44:14 UTC">
      <body>That's really cool - I wrote a lot of reviews for a site a few years ago. Any genre in particular?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 14:44:40 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, it definitely teaches you how to juggle priorities though</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 14:53:00 UTC">
      <body>Totally. No specific genre, mostly edge toward the weirder side of things. Have you also given up on journalistic writing?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 14:53:49 UTC">
      <body>Just to warn, 3-4 I will not be able to respond.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 14:55:04 UTC">
      <body>No that's fine / I'll be going in to bartend tonight so I'll be texting intermittently</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 15:55:57 UTC">
      <body>I pretty much stopped writing after graduating college - I've done a bit of travel writing but only for myself. What are a few bands you wrote criticismon recently?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 16:21:53 UTC">
      <body>The last album review I wrote was for a band called Lake, and although I really enjoy them, they're not very indicative of what I usually listen to.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 16:22:52 UTC">
      <body>But the last few bands I've interviewed were Man Man, O'Death and XBXRX, all more along my tast lines.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 16:25:44 UTC">
      <body>Cool, I saw Man Man a few halloweens ago at the starlight</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" participant="130529" time="2013-05-16 16:49:24 UTC">
      <body>Ah nice. Yeah, I think one of my friends went to that show. They put on a pretty great performance. What other music are you into?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" participant="130562" time="2013-05-16 17:38:27 UTC">
      <body>I'm into hardcore punk, hip-hop and I can get down with some instrumental stuff like Do Make Say Think</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 10:41:52 UTC">
      <body>Sorry for the lag or if this wakes you up after a late night. Also a big hip hop fan, mostly 90s and 90s influenced. Do you commonly go to shows, etc?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 11:25:22 UTC">
      <body>No sweat dude - didnt wake me up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 11:26:41 UTC">
      <body>Yeah, I try to go to shows when I'm not working, which recently isn't so often unfortunately</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 11:31:58 UTC">
      <body>I hear that. I used to really enjoy going to shows, but as I get older, I'm finding I am less and less motivated to do so.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 11:35:38 UTC">
      <body>I prefer making it out to house shows over legit venues these days</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 11:36:04 UTC">
      <body>Do you have a favorite place to see shows in philly?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 11:38:52 UTC">
      <body>Interesting. I haven't been around the house show scene for a hot min. What are the active houses these days? I enjoy JB's a lot, sometimes KFN.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 11:45:55 UTC">
      <body>Haven't been to many in the past 6 months, but wolf cycles over on lancaster ave has had shows upstairs, sriracha castle in north philly, golden tea house in w philly</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 11:59:00 UTC">
      <body>Interesting. It's good to know that people are still keeping it afloat. I was much more active with house shows, etc., around 2005-2009.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 11:59:29 UTC">
      <body>Since then, tho, I haven't really been to any.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 12:01:26 UTC">
      <body>Oh yeah, it's definitely still afloat. Have you been to any shows upstairs at KFN?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 12:03:46 UTC">
      <body>I saw a listing for that at some point, but was confused; the only place I know that's upstairs there is the Green Room, but it'd be a pretty intimate show up there. Is that where people play?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" participant="130562" time="2013-05-17 12:05:21 UTC">
      <body>The last three shows that I've been to at KFN have been upstairs. It definitely just feels like someone's house</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" participant="130529" time="2013-05-17 12:06:34 UTC">
      <body>Ok, yeah, there's like a small hallway with a few rooms, right?</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>
