<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20131104.0016" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2013-11-04 18:53:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey peco coming friday noon to 4... will you be home at noon?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2013-11-04 18:53:09 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I get done work at 3</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2013-11-04 19:15:27 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Also can you do french sunday mornings instead? 10:00?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2013-11-04 20:01:25 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>I have work at 2 and have to leave around 1:15</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2013-11-04 20:01:33 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And yeah mornings are better</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2013-11-04 21:24:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Ok Steph will have to reschedule it then.  No worries</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2013-11-04 21:26:12 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And ok cool I was worried that you would prefer evenings.... but yea he thinks he Is slick trying to tell me he has another teacher training him so he don't need you all bec he don't want to do sunday night studying </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2013-11-04 21:27:23 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Dawn me and Steph were like yea right to the having someone else teaching him. We know he Is lying but this Is my convo with him (2 screenshots....)</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2013-11-04 22:04:34 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Okay that sucks. Im used to tutoring people who like French. It's hard when you feel like you're forcing it on someone. He didn't even choose it over other languages. He had to do it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2013-11-04 22:04:59 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>And yeah morning is much better. I had to leave Edens to do it and I'd rather not do that at night.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2013-11-04 22:07:33 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Right... but I'm going to work on it all week with him. I don't mind forcing It on him lol. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2013-11-04 22:08:24 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But hopefully repetition with help him and he will get better... he isn't that bright but he isn't an idiot.  Just lazy and unmOtivated</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2013-11-04 22:13:47 UTC" participant="152116">
      <body>Yeah I can tell</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

