<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140822.0034" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-08-22 00:26:14 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Hey.. so do you remember that ####### ####### i was telling you about? And how ive been covering his days for him </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-08-22 00:58:18 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Yeah. What happened?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-08-22 00:58:31 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Did you get his position?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-08-22 00:58:44 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Or did he quit like I figured he would?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-08-22 00:58:45 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He got fired!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-08-22 00:59:35 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>:-) :-) :-) :-) :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-08-22 01:00:33 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>So what happens now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-08-22 01:00:59 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Not yet but other manager is still on maternity leave.  And with ##### off practically this whole month ive been running the whole office.  So now im in charge til sab comes back in sept and getting a review then as well</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-08-22 01:01:48 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>:-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-08-22 01:02:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Both the doctors have been telling the director of operations that I deserve to be in charge.  Apparently they have been telling him this for several weeks now. And ##### was taking off a bunch of days so ive been running everything</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-08-22 01:03:06 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Remember I was coming in early and leaving late to close bec he was off? Even then he was beating me there to clock in at 730 and leave then go back to clock out like 830 at night</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-08-22 01:08:47 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>On the 7th steph and I caught him going in at 7:39 pm to clock out. He said he "forgot something"... you would think that after us seeing him, he would have laid low a bit. In actuality he has been doing this for the past year but just spaced out</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-08-22 01:51:38 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>OMG! !! That man had balls.....!!!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-08-22 01:54:16 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Omg I know! Now it ##### bec when sab left she trained him how to do her job fit about a month. Now im during her job worth zero training so im teaching myself as I go. But its only making me look better lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-08-22 01:56:09 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>The part that killed me most was that he was mad at sab for taking maternity leave bec he didn't want to work open to close every day. So me being kind I step up and help out dividing the work days and he does to me exactly what he didn't want. Working alone open to close!  Like you should have been grateful of my help bec I didn't have to cover sabs shifts. Instead he took advantage</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-08-22 01:57:19 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>That's good! Doing your 'own on the job training'! Ha!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0016" time="2014-08-22 01:57:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yup and still doing a better job than him lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0017" time="2014-08-22 01:58:04 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Why didn't he just quit? </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0018" time="2014-08-22 01:59:38 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He thought he wouldn't get caught.  He didn't want to lose his job, he had nothing backed up. He has a daughter starting college in sept and a step son. So he is SOL</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0019" time="2014-08-22 02:00:55 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He wasn't even job searching.  He would need a 40 hr job starting at $17 an hour to equal what he made here with the OT we get</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0020" time="2014-08-22 02:01:35 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Oh DAYUUUM! yeah he effed it all up. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0021" time="2014-08-22 02:01:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>And he definitely isn't qualified enough to make anything over $10/hr let alone $17 to start</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0022" time="2014-08-22 02:02:23 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body> LMBO!!!!!!!!!!! :-) :-) :-) :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0023" time="2014-08-22 02:02:43 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Hey let me know if you're hiring! :-) :-) :-) :-) </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0024" time="2014-08-22 02:03:18 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yup.. we are all in shock still. Then the ####### goes in the workplace 830-845 last night. He got caught. They are debating on charging him with breaking and entering too now. He just keeps messing up</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0025" time="2014-08-22 02:04:02 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Lol I can get you an application.  We keep them in the cabinet next to me</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0026" time="2014-08-22 02:04:20 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>YUP!!!!!! they should do it! Did he take anything?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0027" time="2014-08-22 02:05:21 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>But with him gone ill be doing open to close for the next two weeks. Hello big checks!!! Just in time too. Ill be in Virginia beach for labor day weekend. Now I have some extra money for it lol</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-08-22 02:06:16 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Go girl!! Ch-ching!! $$$$$$</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-08-22 02:07:00 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>No but he trashed all the stuff I needed to take over his job, notes and important documents so I would have to do it all from complete scratch rather than deciphering his work</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0030" time="2014-08-22 02:07:55 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I recovered everything from the cintas bin. He trashed patients' paperwork and stuff from their attorneys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0031" time="2014-08-22 02:08:00 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>What an ###!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0032" time="2014-08-22 02:08:28 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>They need to charge his ###!!!!!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0033" time="2014-08-22 02:08:44 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>But I blame the company for letting him go that long.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0034" time="2014-08-22 02:09:26 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>First we knew he was there bec only I am allowed to open now.  No one else knows the code to get in (he had a copy of the keys). After he left, he forgot to reset the alarm. So I didn't have to disable it. That's strike 1.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0035" time="2014-08-22 02:11:31 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Uh oh! </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0036" time="2014-08-22 02:11:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I turn everything on, sit at my computer and, thanks to CCP, I use the number pad on the keyboard ALOT. I go to type abd my mouse cursor starts moving around the screen... when I tell you he was the only one who would turn the numlock button off, he was literally the only one! ! Only 3 front desk ppl and we all hated it</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0037" time="2014-08-22 02:12:26 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>He would sit at our computer for ten seconds and still turn off the green light like it was some self destruct button! So my numlock was off. Strike 2. </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0038" time="2014-08-22 02:14:53 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Now im looking around for other things. The binder he gave me upon leaving with all his notes and documents is missing. There were about 4 post its on the back computer for tasks he was doing.  All crumbled up in the trash. Then as ll the important documents missing and in the cintas.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0039" time="2014-08-22 02:15:42 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Also he deleted his resume off the computer.  But never deleted it out of the recycle bin so it was in there abd time stamped on when he was there.  So dumb!</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0040" time="2014-08-22 02:18:53 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>LOL LOL LOL!!!!!  Is the entrance code changed now?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0041" time="2014-08-22 02:22:52 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>Yea the keys are in a lock box so only I know the code and one other girl who would open and close if I can't make it in. But they also changed the locks now since he had his own keys</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0042" time="2014-08-22 02:24:31 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>They can even sue him for compensation of those days he was "out" through out the year. I have documentation for about half of them</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0043" time="2014-08-22 02:24:41 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>Lord Lord. I still press charges. Okay good night I'll catch up with you soon we need to make plans to go out soon.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0044" time="2014-08-22 02:25:22 UTC" participant="154899">
      <body>They'll probably do it. Let me know your schedule later on OK?</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0045" time="2014-08-22 02:25:46 UTC" participant="153244">
      <body>I would too... but good night and will do</body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

