<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<conversation id="SMS_ENG_20140907.0004" medium="SMS" donated="true">
  <messages>
    <message id="m0000" time="2014-09-07 18:56:23 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Hey Hunter. I hope you're well? Michigan is really awesome. You should try to come to Ox-Bow in the future sometime. I wanted to ask your advise about sh</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0001" time="2014-09-07 18:56:33 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>ipping our the prints to everyone from my kickstarter. So I have about 200 boxes and smaller items to ship to all over the world. Do I have to take them </body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0002" time="2014-09-07 18:56:35 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>all down to the post office and ship them individually. I have never used FedEx or UPS. Would it he easier or less expensive to use them. And how do I go</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0003" time="2014-09-07 18:56:37 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body> about do that. Thanks. I hope you're well.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0004" time="2014-09-07 20:51:02 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>You're going to have to check prices for international shipping. DHL may be cheaper than fed ex . I primarily use fed ex. If you get your pieces weighed and measured, you can print labels and have FedEx pick them up or u can drop them off . Since they are light, usps may be cheaper but fed ex is usually the cheapest for big and heavy.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0005" time="2014-09-07 20:51:34 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>By the way, congrats on the successful fund raiser</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0006" time="2014-09-07 20:52:42 UTC" participant="153547">
      <body>I got into Vermont studio again but only got a partial scholarship so I'm not going</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0007" time="2014-09-07 22:52:51 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Oh. That sucks. The last 2 times I went there I got in on the fellowship the offer for cancer survivors. Yeah as always shit in the art world I'd frustra</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0008" time="2014-09-07 22:53:06 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>ting. You could always start a kickstarter:) But even with the partial grant, the VSC is just way too fucking expensive. Ox-Bow is totally wroth it thoug</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0009" time="2014-09-07 22:53:07 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>h, I think. The fall program is  250 a week. That's because there's no visiting artist durning the fall residency. It's so beautiful here.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0010" time="2014-09-07 23:04:53 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Yeah, so that Kickstarter thing.  Someone suggested that I try posting some stuff on reddit, and all of a sudden I saw that my views on flickr where incr</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0011" time="2014-09-07 23:05:03 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>easing by the thousands. I couldn't directly make a post advertising my kickstarter, except on one or two reddit pages that no body seemed to look at, bu</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0012" time="2014-09-07 23:05:04 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>t I tried to indicate that it was going in some of my posts. Anyway, then a few people blogged about it and wrote articles, and the rest is history. This</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0013" time="2014-09-07 23:05:05 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body> guy in England who produces books and movies contacted me about making a book. And some other dude is friends with Joe Rogan and he's going to see if he</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0014" time="2014-09-07 23:05:07 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body> wants to do a podcast with me - which I don't know if that'd even be a good thing, honestly. Another guy is building a website for me. I guess we'll wai</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0015" time="2014-09-07 23:05:08 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>t to see if any of this actually comes to fruition.</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0028" time="2014-09-07 23:07:27 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body>Anyway, the shipping stuff still seems pretty complicated to me, so I guess I'll try talking with you more about it a little later, when it actually come</body>
    </message>
    <message id="m0029" time="2014-09-07 23:08:33 UTC" participant="149373">
      <body> time that I have to start that process. Thanks Hunter. I'll talk with you soon. </body>
    </message>
  </messages>
</conversation>

